
26,July,2003


    
        
    
    


24,July,2003


    
       We are going to be offering offline advertising soon. This is something that my business offered in the past with much success for both you the advertiser and for us the publisher. Stay tuned for details... 
    
    


24,July,2003


    
       A new issue of Opportunity Assistance Online was mailed today.  
    
    


23,July,2003


    
       I just made a slight change so I need to make another post so that the settings for current posts is correct.... 
    
    


23,July,2003


    
       I'd like to welcome you to the Opportunity Assistance Blog. My name is Keith P. Stieneke and I am working to bring you as much information about working from home whether it be actual employment, subcontracting, network marketing or something entirely different. My main website Opportunity Assistance at http://www.opportunityassistance.com is full of helpful ideas and opportunities. I've finally got this going to where it will publish correctly. It took a while but perserverance always pays off in some form. Take care. 
    
    


23,July,2003


    
       Well, here I am trying this again.... If this doesn't work I don't know what I'm doing wrong... 
    
    


02,August,2003


    
       I just made some minor changes to the content of our software and ebook promotion page. To see what we have to offer go to  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/software.html  
    
    


28,July,2003


    
       I am making some subtle changes to the weblog's header.... Please bear with me 
    
    


28,July,2003


    
       I'd like to invite as many of you as possible to become members of this  BLOG  and post here as often as possible. To do so and be able to post you must first become a member of  BLOGGER.com . To do so just go to  urlLink http://www.blogger.com  and sign up with blogger. Then email me at  urlLink webmaster@opportunityassistance.com?subject=I_want_to_BLOG_OA . and I will send you an invitation. All you have to do is follow the instructions in the email I send back to you and accept the invitation. Then you're set up and ready to post to my page as frequently as you would like.... 
    
    


22,August,2003


    
       Most marketers fail because they don't have experience. Find out what the 10 Most Common Internet Marketing Mistakes are so that you can avoid them. Simply download the free ebook at  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/mistakes.zip  
    
    


22,August,2003


    
       Please check out  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/newsletterarchives/  for the two latest issues of our newsletter Opportunity Assistance Online. Thank you.. 
    
    


10,October,2003


    
        Hello. It's been a while since I've done a posting here.  I haven't really done much with this or any of my blogs as I am having trouble finding members for them. If you do happen to come across this and want to post here, send me an email to webmaster@opportunityassistance.com and I will send you a reply on how to post here.   In the meantime you may want to post to my guestbook at  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/guestbook.html . To do so simply go to  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/addguest.html  You can post your name, your email address and your web page link to this site along with a short message.  Also the latest issue of Opportunity Assistance Online has been added to our newsletter archives. It can be viewed at  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/newsletterarchives/oao102.html .  On another note if any of you are writers and you would like to post an article to our website you can find out how to do so by going to  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/articlesubmission.html . You can also view the current article summary page by going to  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/article_manager02/article_summary.html    And coming soon we will also have our own website forum...    
    
    


01,December,2003


    
       In an effort to try to boost subscription rates to my ezine Opportunity Assistance Online I am now posting each issue to my weblog as well as to the ezine archives. To see the most recent issue look below this post.  To subscribe to receive news of the latest postings to the archives go to  urlLink http://www.opportunityassistance.com/oaonline.html   Thanks Keith..... 
    
    


01,December,2003


    
       	 Opportunity Assistance Online       Editor & Publisher: Keith P. Stieneke       http://www.opportunityassistance.com    mailto:webmaster@opportunityassistance.com  =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=. Issue: 108 Subscribers: 101 November 28, 2003 =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.  Opportunity Assistance Online is now distributed to over 100 subscribers!  -----------------------  In This Issue ----------------------  

08,December,2003


    
                Opportunity Assistance Online      Editor & Publisher: Keith P. Stieneke      http://www.opportunityassistance.com    mailto:webmaster@opportunityassistance.com  =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=. Issue: 109       Subscribers: 102          December 8, 2003 =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.  Opportunity Assistance Online is now distributed to over 101 subscribers!  -----------------------  In This Issue  ---------------------- 

06,January,2004


    
                                Opportunity Assistance Online                    Editor & Publisher: Keith P. Stieneke                 http://www.opportunityassistance.com            mailto:webmaster@opportunityassistance.com  =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=. Issue: 112       Subscribers: 116            Jan 6, 2004 =.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.=.  Opportunity Assistance Online is now distributed to over 115 subscribers!  -----------------------  In This Issue ---------------------- 

07,August,2004


    
          Changes for Opportunity Assistance and OpportunityAssistance.com  


10,August,2004


    
         Magically Persuade Even Hard-headed People!   Michael Lee just made me an offer to joint venture with him and promote his new ebook. Below is an ad describing the ebook and the link to find out even more and order it.  ===================================================  How to Magically Persuade Even the Most Hard-headed People!  Persuade them to do what you want them to do and get what you want the fast and easy way! You're gonna love the amazing secrets of persuasion, seduction, and influence unleashed in this awesome e-book that is guaranteed to change your life. Go now to:   urlLink  http://hop.clickbank.net/?opptyassis/mikecpa    ===================================================  Thanks you for reading this and make sure to check this "Blog" everyday to catch new posts.      
    
    


09,August,2004


    
          Are you involved with Clickbank?     


08,August,2004


    
         New Archive Postings of Opportunity Assistance Online       Two of the latest issues of our newsletter Opportunity Assistance Online were just posted to our newsletter archives on August, 7, 2004. To access them click on the following links. For   urlLink  Issue #124 click here   . For   urlLink  Issue #125 click here   . Please visit them and show patronage to our advertisers. Thank you.    
    
    



