
30,September,2003


						
						   SIEMENS Lighting Brochure  urlLink   

						


29,September,2003


						
						   SIEMENS lighting control offerings...  urlLink Siemens Energy & Automation --  

						


29,September,2003


						
						   GE lighting control selection PDF For Atria... old estimates are $5k per panel installed options.. add DigExp block into oversized lighting panel for DOs.  urlLink   

						


29,September,2003


						
						   More stuff on cells... the Mike Motorlola i1000+ specifically...   urlLink Motorola iDEN Test Mode and Other Secrets  

						


25,September,2003


						
						   Cell Phone hacks etc...    urlLink CellPhoneHacks.com Cell phone Mod Ringtone Logo Mobile Cellular Hackers - View Forum - Motorola Cell Phones  

						


25,September,2003


						
						   Latest Dilbert...  urlLink Dilbert Comic on automationtechies.com  

						


15,September,2003


						
						    urlLink Dilbert Comic on automationtechies.com  

						


08,September,2003


						
						   Microsofts OS Software Lifecycle Dates:  urlLink Windows Desktop Product Life Cycle Support and Availability Policies for Businesses  

						


05,September,2003


						
						   Siemens SBT home page: http://www.sbt.siemens.com/ 

						


13,October,2003


						
						   Scopic Media Web Page (Home of the Gnome):   urlLink ScopicMedia.ca   

						


07,December,2003


						
						   More than you ever wanted to know about trees (of the Druidish type).   urlLink Ogham Tree table and ranks  

						


07,December,2003


						
						   Happy Yule! Winter Solstice is comming!   urlLink The Druid Grove - The Order of Bards, Ovates and Druids - OBOD  

						


13,January,2004


						
						   Audio Blog... Tried, works great, but I don't think I would use it' but thats just me. Not worth the cost to me.   urlLink audblog : sounding out  

						


10,January,2004


						
						    urlLink    urlLink audio post  powered by  urlLink audblog  

						


06,January,2004


						
						   Season's changed, so have the colours. Must make man effort to Blog more frequently. Keep losing stuff. Little bits of paper, PDA notes, laptop notes, so many places to look. It's time get myself a little more organized...   urlLink   

						


06,January,2004


						
						   Just info. for me... new fone service?...  urlLink Petro Canada - Webstore Home  

						


03,January,2004


						
						   A liitle on the bizzare side... but worth the look.   urlLink AcidPope - Not just a picture post but a tribute to the beauty of God's work   

						


19,February,2004


						
						   Monty Python T-Shirts too...  urlLink T-ShirtKing.com: Monty Python  

						


19,February,2004


						
						   Monty Python dolls! Action figures for everything...  urlLink Monty Python and the Holy Grail Figures  

						


17,March,2004


						
						   K-Lite.. hacked Kazaa, look for the red text for the download link.. you need to have Kazaa.exe, and Magnet.exe for it all to work, it takes a bit of work to get it going...   urlLink Kazaa Download Place  

						


13,March,2004


						
						   Zone Alarm free firewall... download just "Zone Alarm" not the Plus or Pro they cost money...   urlLink Zone Labs: Download & Buy  

						


13,March,2004


						
						   Here's the Symantic Norton Antivirus 2004 download page... just click on "Free 15 Day Trial" and follow the instructions..   urlLink Welcome to Symantec Store  

						


13,March,2004


						
						   Balaslm Lake map... Lakeshore Central Campground Thje good one (502) is not availabble until Aug. 15th., but 47 is avialable the week we want it. ??? what to do.. change vacation dates or take #47??   urlLink Ontario Parks Online Reservation System  

						


12,March,2004


						
						   Great episode of the BOFH...  urlLink The Register  

						


15,April,2004


						
						   The train's coming...  urlLink Exider  

						


19,July,2004


						
						   My info on the "Smart Car" was a little off... It's actually made my MCC (Micro Compact Car),a subsidiary of Daimler-Chrysler, and "Swatch" is the version of the car pictured. Details at the link below...  urlLink Smartstore: Smart Info  

						


15,July,2004


						
						    urlLink    When are we getting these? Italy's got them now...with the price of gas they should be here soon. "Smart Car" by Swatch, yes the watch maker...gotta have factories that build small things to be able to make these.&nbsp; urlLink    

						


15,July,2004


						
						    urlLink    Who is this woman, and why did she alow this picture to be taken?!&nbsp; urlLink    

						


15,July,2004


						
						    urlLink    Finally got it to work...IE wuz to blame... suprise, suprise!&nbsp; urlLink    

						


15,July,2004


						
						   Add pics to blog. Haven't got it to work yet though...what's a "loopback" problem?  urlLink Hello  

						


15,July,2004


						
						   FREE VoIP!!! Gotta Getta StanaPhone...  urlLink StanaPhone  

						


15,July,2004


						
						   Here's an strange and sometimes frightening site. The pigeon Mafia I know to be true... but the Yeti Journal must be fiction because I saw Osama just the other day at the mall.  urlLink index   

						


02,August,2004


						
						    

						



06,August,2004


	 
      More pictures from camping courtesy of Jason Douglas at...  urlLink GnomeServer 
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    "it's my clothesline!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    waiting for lunch...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    "Art with food" -peanut butter, straberry jam, on paper towell - 2004.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the monsoon...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    One of the pictures I was not supposed to put on this site...ah well...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    tiny door under Coboconk house...Hobbits?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    battle for the best cookies...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the incredible shredding machine...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    on the way down from Lookout Point.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    8am, sleeping in...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    view North along the beach.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    to go in or not to go in...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    clearing en-route to Lookout Point.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Not a Wolverine...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    dodging the poison ivy...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    clearing on the way to Lookout Point.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Really not happy at being photographed all the time!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    View South from the dog beach.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    contemplating turtles...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the gurlz, boy watching.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    look at the size of that skeeter!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hair & hair products were a reccuring theme...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Lookout Point.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Phew! 2.7 km uphill! &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the other side of the table...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    ? I don't know why...moving subjects.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    around the fire pit...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rejoice! The clouds are breaking up!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    squirrel type critter...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    critter...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the rain...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Not much to do in Coboconk, might as weel jump off the bridge...  urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink   some-a-ones gonna be in pain if she doesn't wake up soon...   urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Extreeme Put-Put...  urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    the very difficult "jump the fire wood" shot...  urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    hike tab&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    soaking up the sun...  urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    holding the cards close...to many cheaters around this table...  urlLink    
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    around the fire pit...  urlLink    
     

    



