

16,June,2004



       
      HOW TO USE KEYWORD SUCCESSFULLY FOR SEARCH ENGINES  By emmanuelsar   When it comes to submitting your website to Search Engines, Keyword building is the backbone of your online advertising campaign - These words that will lead the millions of online searchers to you. However, there is more to building keyword lists than just coming up with a few words that describe your product or service offering.  The market presently indicates that generic terms such as  "investment" and "insurance" are highly valued and that  more obscure, but targeted keywords are valued much  less (e.g.: "Atlanta Georgia car insurance"). However,  contrary to what the market is determining, searchers are  becoming savvier and are using more specific keyword  combinations to find what they're looking for. Results  show that 45% of searchers use a combination of  keywords (key phrases), 28% use one keyword, 18%  search by a predefined option (such as browsing through  a directory category) and 9% search by typing in  a question (NPD).  You therefore have two choices when it comes to creating  a keyword list. The first is listing generic keywords in order  to generate the most traffic possible to your site, resulting in  high click-through ratios, but low conversion rates.  The other option is listing targeted keywords that will drive  targeted traffic to your site, resulting in traditionally lower  click-through rates, but higher conversion ratios ratios (e.g.: "Atlanta Georgia car insurance").  For example, if you are selling insurance services in Atlanta, Georgia and are only capable of delivering your services there, then you may not want to list the generic keyword phrase "car insurance". You would receive a high volume of click-throughs, but from geographic places you would not logistically be able to supply. This is a waste of your advertising money. +The number of keywords that you list on a search engine is also crucial to your online success.  Each additional keyword and keyword phrase you suggest will increase your site's chances of being found. Think of it as, not only placing as many hooks as possible in the lake,but also making sure they are of the right type to attract the clients you want.  ==

15,June,2004



       
       urlLink MSN Family/Raising Kids 
     

    


14,June,2004



       
      Regulation E protects consumers when they are hit by electronic financial fraud  • What's covered  • Consumer liability  • What consumers should do  • What banks are required to do  • For more information        Consumers have well-defined rights with respect to fraudulent electronic transfers, and should generally be able to obtain refunds with little hassle. The rights are spelled out in what's known as "Reg-E," or the Federal Reserve Board's Regulation E. The Fed was authorized to draw up the regulation by the Electronic Funds Transfer Act of 1979. The regulation covers all manner of transfers into and out of bank accounts outside of paper checks, including the use of debit cards. It does not cover credit card transactions.      What's covered Any transfer initiated through an "electronic terminal, telephone, computer, or magnetic tape for the purpose of ordering, instructing, or authorizing a financial institution to debit or credit an account." These include point-of-sale transfers, automated teller machine transfers, direct deposits or withdrawals of funds, transfers initiated by telephone, and transfers resulting from debit card transactions, whether or not initiated through an electronic terminal.   Consumer liability When a debit card or other "acccess device" is lost, such as an online banking password, consumer liability is capped at $50 for those who notify banks within two business days. Consumers who notify the bank within 60 days have their liability capped at $500. After 60 days, if the consumer doesn't inform the bank, any charges which occur become the consumers' responsibility. If no access device is lost, and fraudulent charges mysteriously appear on a consumer's account, the liability clock begins when the bank notifies its customer of the activity, usually through regular monthly statements.       What consumers should do The quicker the bank is notified, the better. Reg-E says consumers can notify banks in person, by telephone, or in writing -- the notice is considered given, even if bank employees don't acknowledge receipt of it. A certified letter is probably the best bet; that way you have a copy in case the bank challenges you on the issue of timely notification.      What banks are required to do Banks must investigate disputed charges within 10 days, and report results to the consumer within three days. Errors must be fixed within one day. If the investigation cannot be completed within 10 days, banks must issue a provisional credit to the consumer for the disputed amount, less $50.      When a debit card or other "acccess device" is lost, such as an online banking password, consumer liability is capped at $50 for those who notify banks within two business days. Consumers who notify the bank within 60 days have their liability capped at $500. After 60 days, if the consumer doesn't inform the bank, any charges which occur become the consumers' responsibility. If no access device is lost, and fraudulent charges mysteriously appear on a consumer's account, the liability clock begins when the bank notifies its customer of the activity, usually through regular monthly statements.       
     

    


14,June,2004



       
      RMS can help you with all of your Executone voice mail needs.  Sales  and repair.
     

    



