
18,August,2004


    
       We will have a 20 player game at my house this Friday night @ 8:00pm.  We may have a new player from Poker Meetup.  Let me know by email  urlLink jia@akaak.com  before Friday how many you will bring so we can make sure we have enough tables. So far we are estimating approx 20 but can break out a 3rd table if we get more.  
    
    


07,August,2004


    
       We did not have our normal Friday night game due to Charlie but the next day I headed on over to Derby and joined the 170 player tournament.  I finished 4th and here the notes I emailed Jeff W. 

07,August,2004


    
       Some of our league members are playing the biggest NL Hold'em in Tampa Bay today - the 12:00pm 200 player No Limit Hold'em tournament at Derby Lanes in St. Pete. ( urlLink http://www.derbylane.com  727-812-3339.  Everyweek this tournament sells out at the open because they allow you to pre-register Friday starting at noon.  Most players purchase their seat the day before.  If you show up Saturday without a seat ticket, make sure you be at the Plaza door at 11:00am and get in line before they open the door at 11:30am.  As soon as you get in, run straight to the escalator, not the elevator on the right (much slower), and take a right and then a left to the next escalator.  Then go thru the glass doors and go to the left and get in line in front of the counter in front of the poker room.  Since 3 weeks ago, this tournament has sold out every Saturday.  The 1st place prize is $2,000.  I know a player who finished 4th a few weeks ago and it paid $650.  I finished 12th once and it paid $137.  
    
    


07,August,2004


    
       We had a good game Friday night at Dale's. A total of 19 players showed up. Gene, a new player, won the top prize of $100. Bad beat #1 : Jeff C.'s pocket queens vs. John's pocket aces - All In Action - Jeff gets a queen on the flop to take out John. Bad beat #2 : Casey had AK and the flop gave him trip kings... Casey then goes all in and was called by Bobbie who had a pocket pair... Bobbie hits trips and takes Casey out with a full house.  
    
    



