


31,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    in memoriam...
     
    


30,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    closeup of a bee in one of the rhododendrons
     
    


30,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    a bee in one of the rhododendrons
     
    


30,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Me relaxing quarter of the way down Mount Monadnock. My feet anyway.
     
    


29,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Taken half way up Mount Monadnock in New Hampshire (The dots are people on the summit)
     
    


29,May,2004


	 
       urlLink     Studying for finals is FUN! 
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    lush trees against a blue sky
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Picture of a drawing of mine
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    just another crack in the bark
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    spring cleaning and such
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Pile of legs at the Boston music trip. Great fun...
     
    


28,May,2004


	 
      Here is a list of some of my favorite photos so far on this website in no particular order:   rest.   Me relaxing on Mount Monadnock   Closeup of a bee   In memoriam...   Cool picture of me in Bermuda    (Last Update: July 03, 2004)  -Tristan
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
      This is a photoblog (sometimes called a 'photolog'). A photoblog is an easy way to share pictures, with comments and such, on the internet. Most of the pictures on this blog are ones that I have taken or made, though some aren't. For camera I use a less-than-great Kodak CX4230 (2 megapixels). I'm hoping to get a much better camera as soon as possible.  Some hints/tips for my photoblog: - You can click photos for larger versions - Click the 'Comments' link at the end of each post to view and/or post comments. Feel free to post... - As the blog gets bigger, older posts are be archived. You can access them by click on a link in the archives. The blog is archived once a week.  Guide to categories: (effected) - Means that the photo has been drastically changed from it's original by means of effects in Adobe Photoshop. Though I do make changes to lighting and color, they are only to make the original photo look better, not to make it look different. (not by me) - Pretty obvious. For photos not by me.  If I have posted a picture that has you in it and you object to this, simply email me at  TristanG@Gmail.com  and I will remove or edit the picture.  Also, I am accepting donations. ANY donation that you make would be greatly appreciated. 5 cents, 50 cents, 1 dollar, more? It all is appreciated. Donations go toward a much better digital camera, so donations help toward making this website's content even better! If you enjoy this website, please consider making a donation! Just click this button:        "

29,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here's what it USED to look like...Big improvement from this to below.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Got my braces off!
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Saw Fahrenheit 9/11 on Sunday. Depressing, yes, but good.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
      Below are a bunch of photos from my family's trip to Bermuda. We went from the 19th to the 25th of June. The pictures are in reverse chronological order, so scroll down to the picture from the airport to start from the beginning. Since I didn't want to overwelm you all with pictures, I only chose a few. In total we got about 75 pictures from the trip. Enjoy!  -Tristan
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (fifth day) During our stay there, a big yacht race finished in Bermuda. These are a bunch of the yachts, but not nearly all of them.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (fifth day) This is a cool picture of me. I can't remember which beach this was.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (fifth day) Since only residents are allowed to have cars, we did a lot of bus (and ferry) riding. This is what all of the bus stops look like.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (third day) Another postcard worthy picture from Warwick Long Bay
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (third day) Taken near Warwick Long Bay. This could be a post card...
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (second day) another picture from the porch. This picture shows the color of the water well. It really was that blue.
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (second day) this was taken from the porch of a house inside the large fort in Bermuda
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (second day) small harbor in the bay of Bermuda. This picture doesn't do the color of the water justice
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (second day) since Bermuda is a British colony, people drive on the left side of the road
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (first day) Bermuda International Airport (where we arrived)
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (effected) Timely Watermelon
     
    


15,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here is my full (first and last) name, first in Hebrew, then in Japanese. Someone did this for me in return for a Gmail invitation :)
     
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Saw it last night. Pretty good.
     
    


11,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm not sure if this is a butterfly or a moth. If it's a moth, it's a pretty nice-lookin' moth
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    yellow-purple flowers
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
       urlLink     the moth  (no intentional connection to the aimee mann song)
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    We got it out though (and no, we didn't kill it)
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    As my dad and I were picking strawberries, this sneaky chipmunk tried to get into the small patch, but rightfully got stuck in the netting.
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    No more, so stop asking me! Hehe
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    simply a peony
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yeah! I got 2 more invitations! Actually, I got three, but gave one to my brother. Yeah, I'm such a loving little brother.
     
    


07,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Matt on the bus home from our end of the year trip.
     
    


07,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Sam G. on the bus home from our end of the year trip. Sunburned, but happy.
     
    


07,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    taken at my grandparents' in upstate New York (farm/cow country, obviously)
     
    


02,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    well, it wasn't exactly a thunderstorm with possible hail, but whatever
     
    


01,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This was so easy to make and turned out pretty cool. It kinda looks like it could be one of those  ambigram things . It's not though. I love the 'S'. 
     
    


01,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    (not by me) what can I say?
     
    


27,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I don't know if any of you are wondering about the lack of updates lately, but I've come with an explanation anyway. This week I'm taking a photography class, using good ol' black and white film in a good ol' Canon SLR. The class teaches camera functions, composition, and developing of film. It's been great. I've enjoyed using the film camera and can't wait to print my two rolls of film. I've already developed the film and made negatives, but am going to print them tomorrow. Maybe once school starts I'll scan a couple of them if they turn out well (I don't have a scanner of my own). Once I finish this class, I hope to start up on digital again. Though, I don't know if I'll be able to bare using this Kodak point and shoot again...it seemed a big pain taking these pictures. Maybe this will be what gets me to buy a new digital camera. Who knows, maybe I'll buy a film SLR and a scanner...who knows....
     
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    NO. 71
     
    


18,July,2004


	 
      I probably should have posted this a few days ago, but I'm going to be at my  urlLink grandparents' house  for about a week. There won't be any new photos posted until I get back, so hang tight! &nbsp; -Tristan 
     
    


14,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    playful
     
    


12,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    News! News! News!
     
    


11,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    to fly...
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    beautiful cliche
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    semi-shadowed beauty
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ( photo friday ) suspended
     
    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    yellow is soft
     
    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    lily
     
    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    sphered!
     
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    (effected) no title yet
     
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    one toad.
     
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    through a screen
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    rest.
     
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    water on the lotus leaf
     
    


07,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    flowering wild
     
    


06,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    budding
     
    


04,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    yellowout!
     
    


03,August,2004


	 
      I've posted two photos today (not quite a la  Your Waitress Photos ...). They are linked in a way, one, a photos up the stalk to the flower (not blooming at the moment) of a lotus. It shows it being supported by a small, twisty-tied  tube. The second, a small vine of some sort growing up, twisting and bending, without any support at all. Right into mid air...      urlLink    simple support      urlLink    climb 
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Well, I'm back at it! To make up a bit for all the days I missed, I decided to post  three  pictures today. I hope you enjoy them.   A note about the photography class :  I thoroughly enjoy it. I was pleased with most of the prints I made and I learned a lot. I was correct in predicting that going back to the Kodak point-and-shoot camera would be painful. There were pictures I really wanted to take, but just couldn't because of limitations of the camera. I hope that soon I'll have a digital camera with which I can take all the pictures that I would like to.  [Shameful begging starts now] If you would like to help me get a camera with which I can take pictures with real creativity, a donation would be  wonderful . From one dollar to  five hundred, they all would be greatly accepted. If you would like to donate, click the donate button on the right column below the copyright text. [/Shameful begging]  Anyway, it's changed my view of photography. I enjoyed doing black and white and I think I might start doing more black and white or de-saturated photos. We'll see. I hope you enjoy these three pictures.  -Tristan 
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    [the garden hadn't had rain for years, yet] plants still grew
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    raise your corn up to the sky
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    pots by two
     
    



