
16,April,2004


						
						   What is a rivalry? In my mind, it's two teams that have a history together. It's two teams who don't like each other, and it shows when they play. You know a great rivalry, because the atmosphere at every game the teams play is off the charts. It helps to have fans of each team act as if the other team and their fans are evil, despicable human beings.  With that in mind, how could any sane person not think the Yankees and Red Sox have the best thing going in pro sports today? Granted, Yankees-Red Sox (or any other pro sports rivalry) doesn't hold a candle to established and legendary college rivalries (Ohio State-Michigan and Army-Navy in football, Duke-UNC in basketball, among others). But when you look at the top rivalries in pro sports today, there isn't one anywhere that can match the history, hatred, competitive nature, and star power of Yankees v. Red Sox.   This one has gotten so intense that FOX thought it made sense to sacrifice a Saturday afternoon telecast later in the season so it could have the first meeting of the season between the two teams, which is taking place as I type. And it'll pull a number. It won't be a number comparable to Game 7 of the ALCS, but it will be better than anything a Saturday afternoon game could bring.  I'm not saying it's a great rivalry because FOX thinks it is. Just look at the history. All the Hall of Famers who have played in this rivalry. All the great moments (Bucky Dent and Aaron Boone come to mind immediately). All the intensity (think Pedro Martinez and Don Zimmer). The atmosphere, whether the games are played at Fenway Park or Yankee Stadium. And, by the way, the two teams played a staggering 26 times last season, and they couldn't have been any closer without being clones of one another.  Other great sports rivalries? Okay, I'll make some short lists:  BASEBALL: Dodgers-Giants Cubs-Cardinals  FOOTBALL: Packers-Vikings Packers-Bears Raiders-Chiefs Raiders-Broncos Cowboys-Redskins  HOCKEY: Bruins-Canadiens Flames-Oilers Blackhawks-Red Wings Islanders-Rangers  BASKETBALL: Lakers-Kings Knicks-Pacers  COLLEGE SPORTS: Michigan-Ohio State football Army-Navy football Miami-Florida State football Notre Dame-Michigan football Minnesota-Wisconsin football Duke-North Carolina basketball Kansas-Missouri basketball Boston College-Boston University hockey Minnesota-Wisconsin hockey Michigan-Michigan State in just about everything 

						


15,April,2004


						
						   Apologies to my friend Mike "ScoobyDoo" Linehan for stealing one of his catchphrases for the title of this post, but it's appropriate.  Minnesota Governor Tim Pawlenty, who I'm absolutely not a fan of, just accepted the resignation of Public Safety Commissioner Rich Stanek. Why? Because Stanek told racist jokes 12 years ago.  Nice planet.  Stanek admitted in a 1992 deposition that he used the "N word" on several occasions, and that he told racist jokes. At the time, he was a Minneapolis police officer. The word got out because of his involvement in a traffic accident in 1989.   According to  urlLink the St. Paul Pioneer Press , the testimony came "in a deposition where I (Stanek) was being truthful and honest, not in a public setting. I did not use it to describe Mr. Freeman and never used it to describe another individual and I understand that, all that aside, that it is still inexcusable."  Stanek was also quoted by the Pioneer Press as saying, "I think it's a big deal…. Yes, I do. I didn't necessarily see it that way back then, but then again, as I said, look at who I am then and how I've grown over the years… I've been promoted through the police department four times. I've been an elected officer five times. I have had different positions and life experiences. I am the father of two beautiful children. I'm celebrating my 20th anniversary in a month or so."  Amazingly, none of this was thought of as a big deal until Stanek, who was appointed to   five terms   in the Minnesota House, won himself a job as part of Governor Pawlenty's cabinet. In another shocking development, it's a Democrat, Rep. Keith Ellison of Minneapolis, who spearheaded the charge to boot Stanek from his position.  Nice planet.  So now a perfectly qualified and acceptable candidate for a major position in the governor's cabinet is forced to resign over comments and dumb jokes made more than a decade ago? How does this happen  without  a fight? How does this happen with no resistance? How does this state allow this to happen?  What a sickening move by the DFL Party. More political games...just what we need. There is no pattern of recent behavior that would indicate that Stanek hasn't changed, that he hasn't grown up a bit, that he isn't qualified for the job he was hired to do. Instead, the DFL decided to dig up decade-plus-old crap to play a political game with the Republican governor.   Maybe Pawlenty should hire a Democrat next time. I'm sure s/he would be approved in a heartbeat.  What's truly sad is that this probably doesn't hold a candle to what we'll hear from the presidential campaign before the summer ends. Ugh.  Nice planet. 

						


15,April,2004


						
						   Thank you, Junior Lessard (for that matter, add Beau Geisler, Jay Hardwick, and Jesse Unklesbay to this list), for the wonderful play and leadership you provided UMD this winter. Thank you for all the work you did to help resurrect what was basically a dead program. Thank you for the entertainment you provided us over this past wonderful season. Thank you for the class you showed in everything you did in Duluth.  Finally, Junior, I thank you for making my life as an NHL hockey fan even more difficult than it was already about to become.  As I grew to appreciate the NHL during the 1990s, I grew to despise a few franchises. The Detroit Red Wings always win, and always spend a lot of money to do it. Adding to it, they had one of my least favorite players of all-time, Sergei Fedorov, playing for them all those years. The Dallas Stars, led by owner Norm Green, packed up and left Minnesota back in the 1990s. I vowed to never forgive them, as long as Green owned the team. The New Jersey Devils, with their trapping style of hockey and nonexistent-until-the-playoffs fan base, were an easy target.  I'm okay with the Devils now, thanks to the respect I've grown to have for their management and coaching staff. It's hard to sustain success in pro sports, especially on a very strict budget. While other teams spend like the money's going out of style, New Jersey continues to do it the right way. Add to that plenty of local and regional talent (highlighted by former Cloquet High School star Jamie Langenbrunner, former Gopher Paul Martin, and newly signed former North Dakota center Zach Parise), and it's become hard to root against the Devils.  Dallas was another story for a long time. Take the greed of Green, and combine it with some unflattering comments Mike Modonna about Minnesota, and there was very little to like about the Stars. That said, their Stanley Cup win came with some local help, as Langenbrunner and former UMD stars Brett Hull and Derek Plante all played on that Dallas team. Last year, Dallas drafted former Greenway High School superstar and current Gopher Gino Guyer, a great kid who I am convinced will make a splash in the NHL. He has the skill, toughness, and work ethic to make it happen.   Today, the Stars signed Lessard to a one-year deal. No one knows if the deal will even lead to an NHL cup of coffee for Junior, but we all hope it does. One thing is certain: It's becoming hard for me to root against the Stars. Especially when you consider that Norm Green sold the team.  Someone tell the Red Wings to stay the hell away from players I like. 

						


14,April,2004


						
						   Attendance is down. Ratings are down. Interest appears to be down.   Ladies and gentlemen, it's time for the 2004 NBA Playoffs!  There was a time when those words invoked great enthusiasm among sports fans all over the place. Now, no one even seems to notice.  Yes, the league was blessed this year with great performances from rookies Carmelo Anthony and LeBron James (James, by the way, should be Rookie of the Year, but won't be because Anthony's Nuggets made the playoffs). Yes, Anthony will be able to showcase his game in the postseason--well, at least for five or six games before Denver bows out to Minnesota. But the league still has a problem.  What is the problem? Too many off-the-court problems (namely Kobe and Jayson Williams, who is still identified as an NBA player even though he retired some time ago). Too much individualism on the court. Too much focus on "hard-nosed defense". Not nearly enough fundamentals. Not enough marketing of the game's two best players (Kevin Garnett, Tim Duncan). Horribly inconsistent officiating (to the point where I heard a national talk-show host ask an interview guest "Who does David Stern want in the NBA Finals?", and he didn't sound like he was joking).  It's reached the point where we are stuck giving credit to teams that are capable of selling out first-round playoff games, because many of them will have empty seats. It's getting to the point where the NHL should be capable of outdrawing the NBA in terms of television ratings for playoff games. The NHL already does a better job of filling its arenas than the NBA does in the playoffs.  The NBA needs a good playoff year. That means fun, competitive basketball, and no officiating controversies or conspiracy theories. It means more of Tim Duncan and Kevin Garnett, and less of Kobe Bryant (tainted image) and guys like Shaquille O'Neal, Dirk Nowitzki, Chris Webber, and Jason Kidd (all vastly overrated). It means more of Flip Saunders and less of Larry Brown.  What will happen? The Spurs and Timberwolves will clash for the Western Conference crown, while the Pacers meet the Pistons for the right to represent the Eastern Conference in the NBA Finals. Despite Kevin Garnett's best effort, the Spurs' experience (and that Tim Duncan guy) are too much for Minnesota to handle in a seven-game series, while the Pacers' ability to actually score points will spell the end of the Pistons' season. If only they had drafted Carmelo Anthony. If Detroit wanted a benchwarmer so badly, I'm sure they could have gotten Bill Curley on the cheap. 

						


14,April,2004


						
						   As if accusations of Mike Ribeiro faking an injury to get the clock stopped at the end of Game 3 weren't enough, Canadien forward (and major trade deadline acquisition) Alexei Kovalev took it to another level Tuesday night.   During the second overtime, Kovalev appeared to feign a hand injury after a slash from Travis Green of the Boston Bruins. The slash was a slash, but the impact wasn't enough to cause harm to Kovalev. Instead of playing the puck out of danger, Kovalev went into WWE mode and acted like his hand was going to fall off. In doing so, he ran into teammate Sheldon Souray, and the puck came free to Bruin Glen Murray. Murray went in unmolested for the game-winning goal, and Boston took a 3-1 series lead.  Kovalev has a history of acting up. He apparently thinks it's better to act up and cost your team a game it needs to win than to fight through (probably minimal) pain and help your team win a game it needs to win. This attitude may work with the Pittsburgh Penguins and New York Rangers, where winning has been a foreign concept in recent years, but it won't work in the Stanley Cup playoffs.   I'd be shocked if Kovalev were invited back to Montreal next season (assuming there  is  a next season, and I can't think of a team that would want to take on an overpaid prima-donna who has no clue how the game is supposed to be played.  For the record, I don't like the endless bashing of Ribeiro, who may have gotten the wind knocked out of him or perhaps hit a nerve near his shoulder. Both situations could (or do) cause temporary pain that goes away within a minute or two. What Kovalev did, though, is bush league, and it has no place on hockey's biggest stage.   Unfortunately, his behavior likely means the end is near for one of hockey's storied franchises...one that hasn't tasted Cup glory in over a decade. 

						


14,April,2004


						
						   I find the recent blogged speculation about President Bush to be quite interesting. You, by the way, can read such ramblings  urlLink here ,  urlLink here , and  urlLink here , just to name a few. The thought of Bush having to take medication before, for example, a press conference is somewhat disturbing, but understandable. We've known for a while that Mr. Bush isn't comfortable in situations like press conferences, where media types can fire off all sorts of rambling questions that question Bush's policies and motives. It's just not a strong suit for him. Doesn't make him a bad President. It just means he might not be that strong at "thinking on his feet".   Contrasting the State of the Union address, where Bush was energetic and forceful with his points, last night was like listening to a monotone 60-minute lecture from Ben Stein. Bush just didn't have any energy or pep, and he wasn't nearly as forceful in getting his point across. He had the look of a man just trying to get by. Perhaps "going through the motions" is a more appropriate phrase.   Either way, I don't think he helped himself last night. And in the face of declining approval ratings and an increased possiblity that he will lose his job this November, Bush needs to help himself whenever possible.   Next question: Will he debate John Kerry? If so, when, where, and what will the format be? Bush's advisors can't be happy with how last night went, and they can't be pleased with the thought of their guy trying to hold his own in a "thinking on your feet" forum, which is what most debates are. If the questions aren't pre-determined, I'm not sure Bush  can  do well against John Kerry in a debate setting. 

						


23,April,2004


						
						   U.S. Senator John McCain (R-AZ) statement on former NFL safety Pat Tillman, killed this week during combat in Afghanistan:  "I am heartbroken today by the news of Pat Tillman's death. The tragic loss of this extraordinary young man will seem a heavy blow to our nation's morale, as it is surely a grievous injury to his loved ones.   "Many American families have suffered the same terrible sacrifice that Pat's family must now bear, and the patriotism that their loved ones' exemplified is as fine and compelling as Pat's. But there is in Pat Tillman's example, in his unexpected choice of duty to his country over the riches and other comforts of celebrity, and in his humility, such an inspiration to all of us to reclaim the essential public-spiritedness of Americans that many of us, in low moments, had worried was no longer our common distinguishing trait.   "When Pat made his choice to leave the NFL and became an Army Ranger, he declined requests for interviews because he viewed his decision as no more patriotic than that of his less fortunate, less renowned countrymen who loved our country enough to volunteer to defend her in a time of peril. It is that first lesson of patriotism that we should reaffirm in our own lives as we celebrate the courageous life and mourn the heroic death of this most honorable American."  

						


21,April,2004


						
						   I can't believe no one is talking about the Packers' need for a quarterback, and the fact that the perfect fit is probably going to be on the board when they pick in the first round. I have thought for a while now that all the Tim Couch talk is simply a smokescreen by the Packers. They are masking their true Draft Day intent, which I believe is to draft Tulane quarterback J.P. Losman. Losman is a strong-armed, strong-willed kid who led the Green Wave to a bowl game in his junior season. Losman has better mobility than Favre has ever had, and Losman possesses the same "gunslinger mentality" that has made Favre famous. Losman has been knocked for his brash personality that often rubs people the wrong way, but this was also a trait of Favre's when he came out of college. I think an NFC college scouting director said it best in Wednesday's Green Bay Press-Gazette:  "The people that really know him love him," the scout said, speaking on the condition of anoymity. "When I met him, I thought he was the biggest jackass in the world, he comes across like he's trying to be a street guy from California, cussing all the time. The more you get into him and talk to the people that have been around him, the more you talk to the players, he's a big-time leader. He grows on you. Football is very important to him. I don't know if you watched tape on him. He gets the (crap) kicked out of him, his offensive line is atrocious, and he never backs down, not one time."  Losman, while not as polished as prospects Philip Rivers, Ben Roethlisberger, and Eli Manning (all of whom are rated higher than Losman by most NFL teams), is probably a better overall athlete than anyone in this class. He brings the ability to escape pressure and get 10-15 (or more) yards with his feet. Plus, he has a throwing arm that is at least comparable to that of Favre.  If the Packers want to replace Brett Favre, their first chance will come at pick #25 in the first round on Saturday. His name is J.P. Losman. 

						


20,April,2004


						
						   Last night's two NHL playoff Game Sevens were fantastic. Good up-and-down action, even though we didn't see many goals (only seven combined in the games). More intriguing than anything else has to be the performances of two high-profile team captains in Monday's action.  Joe Thornton had a good season. With the "C" on his jersey, Thornton was a huge reason why the Bruins won the Northeast Division and compiled over 100 points, earning them the second seed in the Eastern Conference playoffs. Thornton led the Bruins with 73 points (23 goals, 50 assists), and appeared poised to continue putting up strong numbers as the Bruins opened the playoffs with a series against seventh-seed Montreal.  While Thornton didn't get off to a good start, he was getting regular minutes (while reportedly playing hurt), and the Bruins were winning. Glen Murray's breakaway goal in the second overtime of Game Four gave the Bruins a 4-3 win and a 3-1 series lead, with the festivities shifting back to Boston.  At this point, the Canadiens were coming unraveled. Alexei Kovalev was more interested in flaunting an apparent hand injury than in playing hockey, and his blunder led to Murray's Game Four winner. Charges of embellishment haunted two other Canadien players. Goalie Jose Theodore was not playing well. All looked well for the Bruins.  But someone forgot to tell Montreal. Kovalev was put on a line with Saku Koivu and Richard Zednik, and the Habs caught fire. Montreal blew Boston out of the Fleet Center in Game Five, 5-1. They went home and used two late empty-net goals to make a close game look like a blowout (5-2 was the final).   All along, Thornton continued to do nothing. In Game Seven, Bruins coach Mike Sullivan tried to juggle lines. Nothing clicked, and nothing really worked. Thornton couldn't get on the board, and his teammates followed their captain's lead in Game Seven, as two third-period Zednik goals sunk the Bruins' dream season. The 2-0 final marked the first Game Seven road shutout by an NHL goaltender since St. Louis' Grant Fuhr blanked Phoenix in 1999. Theodore was great, making 32 saves, but the story was again the Bruins' inability to put the biscuit in the basket.  One could excuse Thornton's performance had it just been subpar. Many of his teammates were subpar in the series, and Theodore was on his game in the final three games of the series. However, it's hard to excuse a performance like this:  0 goals, 0 assists, 0 points, 14 penalty minutes, plus/minus of -6  Thornton, by the way, took a -2 in Game Seven. A Boston Globe columnist wrote Monday that Thornton should have the "C" taken off his jersey. While Thorton's playing-while-hurt performance was awful, no one on this hockey team distinguished themselves in a series it looked like they had in the bag.  On the other side of the country on Monday night, the Calgary Flames were ready to make history. The once-powerful franchise hadn't gotten past the first round of the playoffs since 1989, and the Flames hadn't even been in the playoff since 1996. The opponent was a Vancouver Canuck team that has not had the best playoff fortune in recent years.  The Flames' leader is undoubtedly their captain, Jarome Iginla. The 2002 Art Ross and Maurice Richard winner put up 73 points in 2003-2004, by far the most on his team. His willingness to work hard, battle in the corners, play defense, and play hurt has won him the respect of NHL fans and media all over North America. This was his first chance, though, to showcase his skills in the postseason.  Iginla had done well in the first six games, posting five points on three goals and two helpers. More would be needed from Iginla, though, if the Flames were to advance to play Detroit in the Western Conference semifinals.  And Iginla responded. Little did the 18,630 in attendance at GM Place in Vancouver know that Iginla was about to put on the performance of his lifetime.  The Flames' captain scored twice in regulation, the second of which came on a power play to give Calgary a 2-1 lead in the third period. As Vancouver tried to rally, Iginla missed an empty net with 15 seconds left to give the Canucks one last chance. He had his stick slashed out of his hands by Vancouver's Brendan Morrison (the hero of Saturday's triple-overtime Canuck win that forced this Game Seven), then tripped on the stick as the Canucks rushed up the ice. Matt Cooke stuffed in a rebound with 5.7 seconds left to tie the game and force overtime. Suddenly, Iginla looked like he may end up the goat for Calgary.  The good news for the Flames heading into the overtime was that they had a power play coming, thanks to a late penalty by Ed Jovanovski. Iginla took advantage of the extra attacker to get his redemption. Iginla helped set up Martin Gelinas' game-winning goal just 1:25 into overtime, and the Flames advanced.  "In the end, you have to compliment their superstar player," Canucks coach Marc Crawford said of Iginla. "He showed up and was outstanding. That was as good a game as I've seen anybody play in my time."  Opposite sides of the country. Polar opposite performances by team captains. The "C" stands for many things in hockey, and while Joe Thornton couldn't hold up his end of the bargain in Boston, Jarome Iginla was everything, and then some, to his Calgary Flames. 

						


19,April,2004


						
						   1.  I see the NBA is taking a page out of the NFL's book. The start of last night's Timberwolves-Nuggets game was delayed 26 minutes while they waited for the boring first game of the evening, New Orleans at Miami, to mercifully end. Wait...the NFL's never done that. What a stupid move by a league that really needs good PR. Someday, the NBA will realize that the most important asset it has is not television. It's the 18,509 people who paid good money to watch the game in person. For those people. the NBA handed out a free half-hour delay to the action. It's bad enough that we have to watch Miami and New Orleans throw rocks at each other for over two-and-a-half hours. It's even worse that the paying customers have to sit through an extra 25 minutes of whatever they had to sit through at Target Center.  2.  The Wolves are good. If they win this series over Denver, look out. They didn't get the #1 seed in the Western Conference playoffs by playing nobody and not winning any important games. And you don't win twice at Sacramento by accident.  3.  Speaking of Sacramento, can anyone on that team play some defense? Makes me wonder why the fans at Arco Arena waste breath chanting for "DEFENSE" from the Kings. The only reason Sacramento will win this series is that Dallas is somehow weaker defensively than Sacramento is. Asking the Kings to play defense would be like asking Miami and New Orleans to play some good basketball, if only for one night.  4.  As good as the Pistons are on defense, and as strong as they are overall since adding Rasheed Wallace, it's just a matter of time before Wallace melts down under the pressure of the postseason. When this happens, the opponent will take full advantage. The East isn't nearly as bad as people want to make it out to be, and Detroit can't afford a Wallace meltdown against either New Jersey or Indiana. The top three in the East (Indiana, New Jersey, Detroit) are pretty good, and it wouldn't be a shock if all three swept their first-round series.  5.  If the Lakers had played with any less passion on Saturday, they could have been confused with the playing-out-the-string Clippers, who share the Staples Center home floor. I've never seen a Phil Jackson-coached team stand around as much as the Lakers were in Game One. They should consider themselves lucky that Houston was the opponent, as a good team would have embarrassed the Lakers on Saturday.  6.  I understand that Yao had fouled out, so he wasn't an option, but is a three-pointer the best call in the closing seconds when you 1) only trail by one point, and 2) are shooting 2-for-11 from three-point range on the night and generally can't hit the broad side of a barn? I know it's hard to expect NBA teams to run actual set plays, but I find it hard to believe Jeff Van Gundy is worth the money Houston is paying him if that was the best play he could draw up at the end. 

						


26,April,2004


						
						   You know the writer. You know the talk-show host. You know the TV personality. You know the co-worker.  Something tragic happens that, either directly or indirectly, involves the world of sports. Something like, for example, the untimely death of a well-known sports figure (Derrick Thomas would be an easy example). Or a tragedy so deep and overwhelming that it causes the cancellation or postponement of one or more sporting events (9/11 would be an example, but so would any number of landfalling hurricanes and other weather calamaties).  "Wow. This really puts sports in perspective," the person says.   "This is real life. Sports mean nothing at a time like this," they go on to say. "It changes how I look at the things in life I prioritize."  And you just want to smack the guy in the head every time the words are said or written.  Sports are what they are: Entertainment. A diversion from real life. A way to wind down after a long day of work. Fun. No one who follows sports for a living or is truly devoted to sports would dare think any more of sports.  I get sick and tired of people who make the "This puts sports in perspective" comment after something bad happens. I heard no fewer than a dozen people, some of them actually involved in sports, make the comment after word was received of Pat Tillman's death on Friday. No one wants to diminish what Tillman did or what his sacrifice means to all of us. But it does nothing to "put sports in perspective".  They're already in perspective. You don't see Yankees-Red Sox highlights leading the national news over people getting ambushed in Fallujah. You don't hear the call of Calgary's overtime game-winning goal before you hear about deadly tornadoes in Oklahoma.   I don't need to be told about the meaning of sports in this real-life world of ours. Sports has a place for me, and for a lot of people, and we're not stupid enough to think they're more important than war...or anything else. They're our way of forgetting, even if it's for three hours, about all the bad things happening around the world. 

						


05,May,2004


						
						   ----

05,May,2004


						
						   The Stanley Cup Playoffs have had it all. They're unpredictable, intense, dramatic, extremely entertaining. They also might be the swan song of the NHL as we know it, but no one wants to talk about that.  What they also might end up producing is the lowest-rated championship round in the history of the four major sports. ABC can't be pleased about seeing a team from a smallish (by NHL standards) Canadian city joined by teams from California and Florida among the final four in the playoffs. And while Philadelphia is a decent-sized market, it's surely not enough to pick up the ratings slack.   Diehard fans of the game are probably tickled pink to see a Canadian franchise having success, and I know I'm happy for the fans who've learned how to appreciate hockey in San Jose and Tampa, and I hope the Lightning destroy Philadelphia.  The NHL, though, can't want anything to do with a Tampa Bay-San Jose Stanley Cup Final. At least Calgary would give the league a cute story to sell, and Philly would give them a pretty big city (and one with rich hockey tradition) to sell.  Maybe the lack of trapping in the Finals (none of the teams left are known for playing an Anaheim-like trapping style) will open up some eyes to the great skill that is on display. What will probably happen is that people will watch "CSI" reruns instead. 

						


10,May,2004


						
						   Will these poor players fall apart? After all, the NBA is forcing the Heat, Pacers, Kings, and Timberwolves to play games tonight, just 48 hours after their last games.  Tomorrow night, the Pistons, Nets, Spurs, and Lakers face the same fate. What will they do? Can they survive such frequent game action?  The NBA should be careful. Someone might pull a muscle. 

						


10,May,2004


						
						   The news hit like the proverbial ton of bricks on Friday night, as Twins radio man John Gordon announced the team had entered into a multi-year contract with Fox Sports Net for the right to carry Twins baseball on television.  Gordon and partner Dan Gladden painted the news as a great step. Gordon saluted both sides for getting a deal done. Shortly after, it was announced to those watching the game on television. Victory Sports was being destroyed by its creator, the Minnesota Twins.   Victory employees, 21 of them according to Twin Cities newspaper reports, will now have to look for work. Among those are network president Kevin Catoor. Catoor had been through a war with cable companies in the past, when he was with Midwest Sports Channel. Apparently, Catoor didn't learn his lesson once MSC finally appeared on televisions throughout the Upper Midwest. This time, Catoor lost the war.  With a reported starting price of $12 million, Fox Sports Net gets the Twins back. This sucks for Brewer fans like myself who were enjoying getting those games on FSN North (most of us in eastern Minnesota got those games while the Twins were still in limbo). I'd like to think the Brewers might have won a fan or two somewhere around the Twin Cities, but I can't verify that. I can verify that people in Minnesota finally get to see the Twins, and as much as I won't like missing the Brewers games again, I can certainly be happy for the Twins fans who were unjustly drug into an ugly dispute over money. One that nobody won.  The speculation that this deal only happened because of the committee vote on the stadium bill on Friday, by the way, is bunk. There's no way Fox Sports Net agrees to pay a starting price of $12 million to air Twins games when the Twins had no leverage as of the committee vote on Friday. None. This deal had been in the works for a while, otherwise it makes no sense for the deal to be structured as it is.  I'll miss Daron Sutton and Bill Schroeder. Bill is good because he's busy offering actual baseball insight during the games, and he doesn't have time to campaign for a spot in the Hall of Fame or circle drunk people in the stands. Maybe we can be reunited again soon. All it takes is a satellite dish on the side of my house, and I might just have to make that happen now. 

						


18,May,2004


						
						   "War Metaphor". Sounds like a Kentucky Derby horse.  Maybe it's already been a Kentucky Derby horse.  In this case, though, I'm not talking about horse racing. I'm talking about basketball. If you haven't heard/read (in other words, if your head was stuck under a rock all day Tuesday), here is what Timberwolves superstar Kevin Garnett had to say about Game Seven, set for Wednesday night at Target Center:  "It's for all the marbles. I'm sitting in the house loading up the pump, I'm loading up the Uzis, I've got a couple of M-16s, couple of nines, couple of joints with some silencers on them, couple of grenades, got a missile launcher. I'm ready for war."  Garnett was quickly criticized by self-righteous freaks around the country, because he would dare use a war metaphor to describe a basketball game. It didn't take long for the Pat Tillman references to start flying in, and it didn't take long for Garnett, backed into an uncomfortable corner, to apologize for his words.  What has happened to our sports media? More than one commentator had the gall last week to praise the focus of Kobe Bryant, as he returned from a Colorado court hearing to drop 42 points on San Antonio. So I'm supposed to praise a guy who couldn't keep his pants on, got charged with felony sexual assault, and is now trying to fit his basketball obligations around his court obligations? And at the same time, I'm supposed to rip into a guy who has been a class act since the second he stepped into the NBA, hasn't had one problem with the law or the league, and held back from clocking an opponent after being elbowed in the face during a playoff game, just because he used a war metaphor to describe his mindset before the biggest game of his life?  Typical NBA media. The darling, Kobe Bryant, gets a free pass despite admitted marital infidelity and alleged felony sexual assault. And the renegade, Kevin Garnett, gets ripped for a full day by media types around the country for using a war metaphor. Makes perfect sense to me.  What I love are the "How would Kevin Garnett know what war is?" takes. Because, we all know that his use of a war metaphor means he actually believes Game Seven will be like one of those firefights between the coalition forces and the Iraqi resistance in the middle of a desert.  Please.  Get off of yourselves. Stop throwing people in the fire for no reason. While Garnett was making that horrific metaphor, you allowed Brad Miller a pass for saying he'd take his ATV and "run him (Garnett) over". You also allowed Carmelo Anthony to predict a fight during Game 5 of the Wolves-Nuggets series, and then not even have the guts to put a uniform on and back up his tough talk. You let Anthony Peeler elbow the NBA's Most Valuable Player in the midsection, and then in the face, and you had the utter gall to suggest that Garnett was a lesser player because he didn't retaliate.   Get a clue. 

						


17,May,2004


						
						   --

17,May,2004


						
						   --

01,June,2004


						
						   The fuss in baseball now is over the situation with Angel OF Raul Mondesi. To make a long story short, Mondesi started the season with the Pirates. He left the team in early May, saying he needed to take care of urgent personal business in the Dominican Republic. On May 11, the Pirates placed Mondesi on the restricted list, and gave him until May 18 to report. When Mondesi didn't report by the deadline, the Pirates made him a free agent by releasing him. At this time, Mondesi was telling reporters that he might not play again this season. But within a week, Mondesi's agent was negotiating with a few teams, and Mondesi signed with Anaheim. He made his debut with the Angels on May 30.   The crux of the complaining comes from the termination of Mondesi's contract, apparently due to legitimate issues back home. Mondesi claimed that former major leaguer Mario Guerrero was "aggressively" trying to claim Mondesi's assets, after a court ruling ordered Mondesi to pay Guerrero $640,000 for helping him (Mondesi) reach the big leagues. Mondesi said his wife and children back home needed him.   The crying from broadcasters and writers (and fans) has been predictable. And it has shockingly come down, to a certain extent, on baseball Commissioner Bud Selig. Those who feel the need to be critical of Selig once a week think Selig should have stopped the signing from going through. It's another sign, some say, of Selig's "spinelessness". For his part, Selig says the issue concerns him, and an investigation is underway.  How about investigating the Pittsburgh Pirates for stupidity? The Pirates made Mondesi a free agent, even though it was certainly possible Mondesi was just trying to get away from downtrodden Pittsburgh and find a contender to play for. If the Pirates had kept Mondesi on the restricted list, he couldn't play for anyone else, and the Pirates wouldn't have had to pay him.  In a no-lose situation, a franchise that has become synonymous for losing managed to lose. 

						


22,June,2004


						
						   I know it's blasphemous to think of the NCAA doing something that's unfair, but it appears there are some issues with the structure of the college baseball season.  Namely, as  urlLink this Minneapolis Star Tribune article points out , the schools in the northern half of the country have a distinct disadvantage when competing against schools in the southern half.  Unbeknownst to me, the NCAA doesn't mandate a "earliest date of first practice" in baseball or softball, and they also don't have any regulations regarding how early teams can play games. So while teams in Florida are working out and playing games in their home stadiums, teams in the Upper Midwest, for example, are stuck practicing in gyms and traveling on long trips to southern locales to get games in.  What it leaves us is with teams that have upwards of 15 or more extra games played because of their location. The inequities in games played and in the date of first practice are staggering, considering how structured other NCAA-sanctioned sports seasons are. You don't see Duke's basketball team starting practice two or three weeks ahead of Maine, and the Florida State football team doesn't get a two-week jumpstart on Minnesota. In baseball, Sun Belt teams are routinely on the field in January, when it is absolutely impractical for teams in the northern half of the country to even dream of practice.  The Big Ten wants to do something about it. Commissioner Jim Delany is part of a committee meeting in Omaha this week. They're looking at potential reform of the system. Big Ten coaches advocate a two-week delay in the start of the College World Series, so teams can wait until February 1 to begin practice and March 1 to play games. There is also talk of a separate national championship, which would be awful for the sport, and of having more regional tournament qualification (instead of a nationally-seeded 64-team field).  After learning more about this issue today, it appears to be clear to me that reform is needed. It's not fair to expect northern schools to sink as much money into baseball as they do, with little chance for reward because of competitive disadvantages.  By the way, the College World Series, currently going on in Omaha, is the best-kept secret in sports. Do yourself a favor and catch the championship series, which begins Saturday night. 

						


21,June,2004


						
						   No one can deny that the United States Golf Association did a very poor job of maintaining it's U.S. Open Championship site, Shinnecock Hills Golf Club. No one can deny that the USGA erred in allowing the first two pairings on the course before the controversial seventh hole was playable. No one can deny that these factors may have taken away from what should have been a great weekend of golf.  However, what can be debated is the conduct of golfers once the round was complete. More than one, most notably Jerry Kelly (shot an 81 on Sunday), talked about how the USGA screws up the Open "every year". Amazingly, these comments have been put on the backburner while the USGA is raked over the coals.  Again, the USGA made its bed this weekend. They deserve to be criticized. The job done both Saturday and Sunday on this course was so incredibly poor that I don't have the words to describe it. It would be like allowing the artificial surface on a football field to peel back, forcing the football players to paly a game on the concrete floor below. So, yes, the USGA deserves plenty of criticism.  But so do those who complain on an annual basis because the USGA makes the Open course "too tough" or "too challenging". If this is an annual problem, Jerry Kelly, feel free to not play in the tournament. It's the "United States Open Championship". It's not a tournament that you are contractually obligated to appear in. If you don't like the course that is chosen, or if you don't like how the USGA prepares the course, or you don't like how the USGA maintains the course during the tournament, or if you don't like the hotel the USGA puts you up in for the weekend, or if you don't like anything else about the tournament, you may feel free to stay home. Go fishing. Read a book. Work on your swing. Being that you shot an 81 on Sunday at Shinnecock, your swing clearly could use some work.  Can you imagine someone running the Boston Marathon every year, and then complaining because the weather is never any good, or the road surface is too hard, or the course has too many hills, or anything else? If one doesn't like something about the Boston Marathon, one probably doesn't run it. Ever. And they certainly don't run it every year, unless they're a sucker. 

						


21,June,2004


						
						   --

08,July,2004


						
						   The BruceBlog is taking a bit of a vacation. I'll be very sporadic with my postings until football season starts, as I prepare my football preview material in my spare time. Links to the previews and radio show days and times will be posted here. 

						



