
18,September,2003


     
      TODAY WAS TIRING.. but GREAT.. I unno about the grade 9s but I sure as hell had fun @ grd 9 night.. (.. weird eh.. since im in grade 10..).. well anyway... it was cooll..... lost my voice for about.. say .. 20 mins..but the trusty vocal cords came back..:).. I started my day at 5:30 am.. and now its what.. 11 pm.. LONG EH.. and i got home.. from school at 10:00.. NON STOP

17,September,2003


     
      Hello.. everybody..:P.. (.. that means no one.. since no one reads this sHit.. neway).. Well All in all.. everything went pretty good today... I didn't get as much homework as i expected.. cuz.. teachers were in good moods.. except for gay history teacher.. who was being a bit of a prik.. cuz.. well.. he .. I unno Im missing his class.. Math class was cool.. bored to death.. but had my hw done for the nxt day.. and was helping other ppl.. (.. mainly Livia).. but it was cool.. cuz.. it was nice to know what the hell your doing:).. For once... :P..   ColdAsFire Aka.. ACZ
     
    


16,September,2003


     
          THIS PIC IS What Im doing.. For this WEEK.. Relates to Last Post...^.....\/
     
    


15,September,2003


     
      Hello everybody.:).. Well well.. Today.. Wasn't too bad.. Except.. Ugh.. Confusion.. :S... Ok.. Here's the situation.. this is my week.. Monday..  School and then Parliament.. (. that was total shit.. once again).. Tuesday.. nothing really just hw.. Wednesday not too much.. jus gotta do lots of hw.. that i'll miss for thursday and friday.. Thursday. I gotta go to Riverside Highschool to learn Layout for the year book.. *not too much fun* anyway.. I guess its cool cuz i don't have to pay the $50 for the 2 day seminar... but then after that I got Student parliament stuff again. GRADE 9 NIGHT

15,September,2003


     
      Hey People this Is new.. I doubt anyone Publicly is going to see this for a while. until I actually get some stuff going.. don't wanna bore ya with semi filled shitty pgs.. 
     
    


15,September,2003


     
      See I have TOO much Time on my hands @ times.. or.. Im just trying to procrastinate doing my hw.. so heres a piece.. by moi.. and Entirely me..    
     
    


26,September,2003


     
      PPl.. Im going to have to post a pic up here.. IM GETTING GLASSES

25,September,2003


     
      Ppl Whats up??? I know.. it takes me a while to post stuff.. Its cuz im a lazy ass.. + school + homework..+ Sleep= not a lot of time!!!.. History teacher has fun killing us with tOOO much hw.. IT SUX A§§. I could have actually gotten outta the house today and went to play T3NNI§ BUT NOOO.. evil.. History teacher had to fudge it up. Our English teacher is nice and all but oo So UNPREDICTABLE.. its quite annoying cuz at points she'll be nice to u then at others she'll be giving you dirty looks.. hmmm.* maybe it was cuz i was talking in class*.. HA.. caught ya.. groupwork..:P

23,September,2003


     
      THIS IS A TESt... Jus checking if this shiznat works.. changed some settings.. SO ..  Www. ARUJ.tK IS NOW A BLOG.... 
     
    


04,October,2003


     
      Im Back.. once again.. after a while of not posting any SHIZNAT:P;).. lol. I was out all day today.. it was crazy.. ( well not all day.. but by my standards i was out a lot)... It was ok.. but tiring... Well in the morning I went to go find my glasses:).. find a purdy pair.. Will get a pic up soon... ;).. * that means 3 months * .. lol. naw.. Well.. there like a rectangle frame thin.. pretty cool.. I might be getting some contacts too.. ( no colours:(.... damn ASTIGMATISM).. Ive seen colours for astigmatism ppl. but like.. am i F***** crazy to spend sooo much $$$$$$.. naw.. I rather get glasses too.. :P.. well. anywho.. Since I have to go for a fitting 2morrow.. for the contacts I wanna go to sleep.. and since its like 1:16 am EST.. I gonna lve.. but Im gonna leave u guys wit a cool pic I rendered.. Check it out when ya get a chance  urlLink done2.jpg   ColdAsFire AKA... ACZ
     
    


28,September,2003


     
      Hey People.. After Procrastinating the whole weekend I have managed to slip my self outta my hw problem just by an inch. .. Well even thought I still have to do some stuff for english I thought I might post a funky Picture I go in fwd.. It shows you How calm and beautiful yet devastating a hurricane can be! urlLink Hurrican Isabelle  Its really crazy Tell me what ya think
     
    


23,October,2003


     
                        HAVE FUN WITH THIS ONE:)     
     
    


23,October,2003


     
         This guy sure takes work seriously:P
     
    


23,October,2003


     
                A Pic of Me with New Shiny Glasses  
     
    


23,October,2003


     
      remembered something I said in the post I bymistake deleted.. I really gotta stop with the Emoticons:P..---

23,October,2003


     
      Well.. I did it again.. I SCREWED IT UP.. lol.. I was writing a blog.. at like .. 4 b4 i was leaving than.. I quickly ran cuz i was late.. and shut down the computer while at it

13,November,2003


     
      Some Funny Pix For The Christmas/ Holiday Spirit  urlLink meltdown   urlLink mistletoe   urlLink SnowmanStickup   urlLink xmas1   urlLink xmas2   urlLink xmas3  If I put these up normally they would take up a lot of room... in terms of page length.  And heres one lol...a lil off topic  urlLink Procrastination 
     
    


22,November,2003


     
      Hey Guys Well I'm Back from work.. aka CRAZY HELL.. naw jp.. it was pretty cool.. met some new ppl... (.. a hot chick thought i was some 27 yr old.... jeez i wonder what she was smoking.. .lol.. jp).. naw.. I unno.. I was jus bored.. Well of all the benefits of my job.. I barely use my ability to stay after work and watch previews.. Wondering why right now? REnts .. cuz of them i can't stay out that late.. EVEN @ work.. blah that.. o well. Still kinda pissed off cuz i could have gotten a ride home from a friend tooo.. GRRRRRR.. anywho.. Im scare.. Not even close to finished my cookbook for Foods Class( I KNOW YOU ALL ARE LAUGHING.. but i did need a social science or G3 credit.. so i chose foods.. thinking it was easy.. OO.. I should've have shot myself then:P.. lol..).. Foods is easy but LOTS of work @ the same time..Enough of my ranting. I haven't updated in a while cuz well LAziness, school ( figures) and mostly due to NEED FOR SPEED UNDERGROUND... ( BEST RACING GAME EVER!!)... Right now your either disagreeing w/ me  or saying WTF.. why does NFS UG matter to me.. but then again you are reading *MY* blog..  All in all today was pretty good I made CIP.. but for you guys that means absolutely nothing and thats good.. :P... hehehehe... (.. * evil smirk*..) ne way.. ppl. Im slightly tired.. gonna lve now.. PS Try the Submit a site and Feedback forms.. Wouldn't mind getting some ideas for the site.. and if anyone wants to make me a spiffy home pg.. ALL THE POWER TO YOU!:)  ColdAsFire Aka ACZ
     
    


21,November,2003


     
      This is a test of the IM Blogging feature.. Looks promising.. more ppl will hear from me if this works:)
     
    


21,November,2003


     
      ADDED NEW MUSIC CONTROL:).. and more links to be added.. maybe a form submit thing too.. lol.. well.. g2g.. gotta get a hair cut:P.. 
     
    


29,November,2003


     
      Well Today Work WAS HELL... Actually it would have been a lazy person's heaven.. but then again I'm lazy but I was bored to DEATH!.. The extent of non busyness plus the fact that I was put on A REALLLY FRIKIN non busy till pissed me off. To top that off I made a friend. I made a Mistake. Now that Friend hates me:P.. o wow what a cycle. Something I did cuz I was bored but hey should've known better but no. O well.  No grudge just wish I didn't do it. I finally got my first paycheck last thursday:)...:).. I was happy. Well, I'm going to call it a night. I've got TONZ of work to do 2morrow so ttfn  ColdAsFire ... Aka... ACZ
     
    


25,November,2003


     
      What Do You Guys Actually Think of The Music... Submit a reply to me at Aruj@Aruj.tk or Through the Feedback / Comments button:).. Many thanks:)  ColdAsFire Aka.. ACZ 
     
    


25,November,2003


     
      Four Tries To Grab a Hold All gone to waste Four Times My World Circles All gone to waste Four Attempts @ Education All gone to waste Four Endeavors w/ Love All gone to waste Four Struggles W/ Friends All gone to Waste Four Strives @ Life All have gathered Four times the tries All along the fifth try forgotten. - anonymous  I unno.. what ya guys think of it.. I thought it was ok:)
     
    


05,December,2003


     
      Until I get some feedback through the feedback button Im not posting anything. I don't think this site is even worth keeping up Tell me if im right!
     
    


04,December,2003


     
      Hey ppl.. Whats up?.. Haven't gotten 1 feedback response:( U ppl are tooo damn lazy( jus like me) Maybe I should post more stuff or not post at all hmmm.. whatever.. I'll decide later.... 
     
    


11,December,2003


     
      Hey Guys I know I haven't updated in a while but this isn't the best time for me in terms of business.. so .. just bear with me.. and I'll update GURANTEED after the 19th:) 
     
    


07,December,2003


     
      FUNNY ASS PICTURE This is how she was trying to express her feelings ( Her being the author @ http://www.sckamb.de/) All I know is that her name is Andrea... Awesome work!  urlLink Gummie Bears.jpg 
     
    


07,December,2003


     
      I had to Change the music because the song was no longer hosted on the website and until I find something better I have streaming Trance music for you guys :).. Enjoy and remember if you don't like it theres a STOP button:)
     
    


07,January,2004


     
      Hey Guys Been a long time eh?... 19th .. HAHAHAHa. I LIED.. lol.. Well i don't like to but REally I was working WAAAAYYY too much.. I didn't want to but I guess when i look at my check i reconsider. It never really felt like a vacation. Im tired right now.. just finished doing foods project (I somewhat cooked for my family). 2morrow I have a presentation infront of the class on how to poach frikin Eggs.. JEEZ.. like who doesn't know how to do that?       Well.. now.. lets see.. During the Christmas break I had some fun time too .. More sleep time..lol.. I realized people at work get upset really easily and others can be a lil tooo happy all the time.. I guess the ups and downs of regular people are inflated in a work environment where there is always constant pressure depending on how you perceive your work. I take it as a fun job. I don't take anything seriously .. really.. but I do always put in a fair bit of effort sometimes too much. Well people I must cut this entry short because im more interested in watching a movie in the few moments i have to spare..otherwise I would rather sleep and get prepared for 2morrow.. lol. cya.. Will xplain.. some stuff.. hopefully 2morrow..night.. all...  ColdAsFire Aka.. ACZ
     
    


16,January,2004


     
      WEll Well I started to post something yesterday and well I forgot to POST it before I closed the program.. O well. anyway schools easy right now but thats cuz EXAMS ARE here.. F******.. O well anywho.. Im just sooo tired right now but i so wanna go out and fo something fun.. HAHAHA.. I have conquered the world.. lol.. actually I just got rid of my shifts for the week @ silvercity.. ( not new mexico.. hehe.. Rat Race). Well A big Thanks to VANESSA for taking my shift:) Well For the weekend I have to study for exams finish history project=(
     
    


07,April,2004


     
      HMM... If anyone is still reading this.. Do tell.. I will start back up in that case.
     
    


21,May,2004


     
      Hey Guys, Well well, its a friday night and look what I'm up to? I should be out having fun cuz I don't work but noooooo, I fall asleep at 5:30.  To add to that I fall asleep while talking to someone=P.. figures. Anyways I guess I can't really change that so ya. OK my crappy arse plan for the weekend ---

20,May,2004


     
      Ok I guess That's Enough Pictures for Tonight. Im going to Vamoose:P.. now cuz this lightnings scaring me:.. haha .. no.. its just i don't have a power back up.. so resetting computer over nothing is worthless. That's why Im going to head out and gets some quality Z's.. Night ppl.. good morning to others:)
     
    


19,May,2004


     
       urlLink    What Is it? huh huh?
     
    


19,May,2004


     
       urlLink    Heres a Pic of me Where you can see my face. *hehe*
     
    


19,May,2004


     
       urlLink    This is a picture that you can say is Fooked up but I unno I love the night life lights.
     
    


19,May,2004


     
       urlLink    Im one of those people that never likes taking an ordinary picture. Detroit- Windsor Tunnel.
     
    


19,May,2004


     
      Hmm Testing whether or not I can post from Miranda IM.. if this is a go I might be posting a bit more but that = less pix.. trade off.. Don't worry i'll try keeping this damn blog  alive.
     
    


19,May,2004


     
      Guys when you go to Leave Comments You can either register for Blogger or other wise underneath it says post Anonymously and you can use that. If you guys pick anonymously please do include your name in your post. 
     
    


19,May,2004


     
      Hey Guys What Do You think Of The New Layout?
     
    


19,May,2004


     
       urlLink    This is a neat city view of Toronto I took. Look @ the diff levels.
     
    


29,May,2004


     
      Guys hang on a bit.. going through a rough patch of a bunch of shit going on.. so ya.. just lemme get caught up n i'll be telling stuff from stepping on a nail to Reach for The Stars Conference
     
    


25,May,2004


     
      Hey guys, I did the odd thing today of waking up early.. AHHHHH.. lol. so I thought what the heck why not post on here when i go to grab my comm tech assignment.(flash animation). Well anyways this was a short and sweet entry till next time.. ColdAsFire Aka Aruj
     
    


24,May,2004


     
       urlLink    Look At This Retard?:P JP
     
    


02,June,2004


     
       urlLink    CLICK THE PICTURE TO VIEW THE MOVIE:)
     
    


31,May,2004


     
       urlLink    DO YOU FEEL TALL? .. lol.. think again
     
    


31,May,2004


     
       urlLink    Lookie lookie.. retard has a cool gf.. hmm.. what is this world coming to:P
     
    


31,May,2004


     
      if u want ur pic here.. send me one at Aruj.Chawla@gmail.com   
    


31,May,2004


     
      Hey guys.. The business test didn't go so well.. but i guess im happy its over. *hope I did well *
     
    


31,May,2004


     
      *update* .. Business test 2morrow.. wish me luck
     
    


12,June,2004


     
       urlLink   
     
    


11,June,2004


     
       urlLink    WHAT EXAMS DO TO ME=) LOL
     
    


09,June,2004


     
      Im happy that my careers presentation is over. I wish exams were over already and they haven't even started. I wish the world would spin really fast so this dizziness would go away. Well anyway I gotta starty studying for exams. Im actually kinda worried. I hate exams they manage to put me in a 'glum' mood which means i sleep more often do less than normal. I have come to the realization all Im doing this for is to avoid studying. I HATE EXAMS.. ok enuf.. now.. to other topics.. Who knows 3DS MAX.. I wanna learn, I like experimenting.. but as much as I like it .. it takes a hell of a long time. So save me some time and help me out. I gotta get out a lot more in the summer
     
    


09,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here ya go guys.. in spirit of exams, Click on it to get a huge version for your desktop. It really makes you study!
     
    


16,June,2004


     
      Got an Exam? Come in to ask Question invite a friend too have a chat...  Chat Schedule  Thursday night SCIENCE FRENZY Friday- Business and whatever else Saturday - Anything Sunday - BUSINESS CRAM  Chats Up and U guys can enter.:P     urlLink      *NOTE * DO A GUEST LOGIN.. Choose a non popular name .. and go in..
     
    


15,June,2004


     
       urlLink    w00t w00t DE-TRO-IT w00t w00t .. DETROIT WON.. BETTA RECoNIZE=|P
     
    


28,June,2004


     
      Hey Guys,  I know its been a really long time since I updated but * not to worry * I'll be back with a couple of entries and pix bare w/ me peeps!:P ColdAsFire
     
    


05,July,2004


     
       urlLink     The Orangish picture is the one with me, James and Rizwan.In the next couple of posts you may see videos from the fireworks.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
       urlLink    This is a VIDEO from close to the end of the fireworks! ENJOY!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
       urlLink    This is a picture of Melanie and Rachel at the fireworks too. 
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I have a feeling I might end up shutting down the website due to the lack of updates/feedback. Well Anyways guys, the decisions still on the table but im gonna try straying from it as long as possible.
     
    


16,January,2004


     
      WEll Well I started to post something yesterday and well I forgot to POST it before I closed the program.. O well. anyway schools easy right now but thats cuz EXAMS ARE here.. F******.. O well anywho.. Im just sooo tired right now but i so wanna go out and fo something fun.. HAHAHA.. I have conquered the world.. lol.. actually I just got rid of my shifts for the week @ silvercity.. ( not new mexico.. hehe.. Rat Race). Well A big Thanks to VANESSA for taking my shift:) Well For the weekend I have to study for exams finish history project=(
     
    



