
31,December,2003


     
      So tonight/this morning was Emily's party.  It was a very quaint little party.  Yup.  Nice people.  Nice house.  Good stuff to eat and drink.  We all finally got to see Allison's dress.  Very yummy that dress is.  Indeed.  But she looks good in whatever she wears.  Everyone at that party looked the same as they did a week or so ago.  I got the most unexpected compliment from a certain someone about my eyebrows.  I was like "hmm... wonder what I should say in response to that..." So, I said... well, I don't remember what I said.  I'm now blind in my right eye because I was brutal poked by someone's finger! *cough* someone *cough* Oh, then she...er, I mean "someone", savagely punched me in my stomach! *cough* someone *cough* I'm just gonna think of it like this... "It was all out of love!"  Why that's in quotation marks, I don't know.  I'm most likely going bowling w/ that "someone" and a buncha other people tomorrow night/morning... maybe it's not such a good idea to put bowling balls at her disposal...  So to sum things up:  1.  Emily's party was fun. 2.  I threw a golf ball real far over a lake. 3.  Allison and her dress looked mmm, mmm good together. 4.  Both Johns looked very Johnny. 5.  I didn't expect Dale to be there. 6.  I'm blind in my right eye because of someone's finger. 7.  I'm glad I went to Emily's party. 8.  I hope tomorrow night's/morning's bowling is fun and mostly non-violent.  9.  I'm not sure how to end this list.  The End.
     
    


29,December,2003


     
      So f'n bored.  No school and no social interaction make Ryan go-something, somethin...  Emily's PT is tomorrow.  Alec's PT is on Friday.  I went to Alec's house yesterday.  Those are the only highlights of my glorious vacation (outside of the virtual world of FFXI).  Speaking of which, I got my White Mage to Lv.25 a few minutes ago!  Yay!  Now I can Raise (aka, Revive) dead people!  I'm a resurrection man forreal!  So the count is Red Mage-

26,December,2003


     
      Whoops, better change that...  Again, I don't have much to say today.  I helped Joe out a bit last night... seems he formatted his harddrive when he tried to reinstall Windows XP cause a mouse wasn't cooperating... 

24,December,2003


     
      I had to change my comment hostin' people for the sake of helping Allison get comments on her Blog.  niiice.  Anyway, it seems like "Blogspeak" didn't pay their bills cause their site doesn't work anymore.  So in a way, I guess I HAD to change it.
     
    


23,December,2003


     
      I DO have something to say today.  I think this originally came from Allison:  "Have you ever wanted to do something just to see how it feels?"  Of course I have!  Today my sister had some of her friends over + Allison's "charming" cousin, Sean.  We were in my grandmother's basement... and I was walking up the stairs... then I suddenly wondered what it'd feel like if I fell down the stairs.  I *almost* tried to find out.  But instead I opted to just ask the above question to all those people present in the basement.  Short story shorter:  I didn't find out what it's like to fall down a large number of stairs.  ;_;  ***********************  ::sigh::  Sometimes I think of the stuff I could have/be doing if I weren't so shy [when it comes to females I find attractive].  On the Discovery Health channel they said shy people are selfish people... that's bad.  I guess it kinda makes sense... if you're shy you're not really giving anything to anyone else [relationship-wise] (much like selfish people only care about themselves).  This school year, though, I've really become more..uh..unshy (?).  I attribute a lot of this to Ms. Bitters's whole parliamentary debate thing (which only happened recently).  Also, I don't know where I'd be w/o John and Allison in my SERA.  Those people are nice to let my guard down around (if that makes any sense).  But that Allison... you've gotta watch out for her... if you let your guard down too much there's no telling what she'll stick where... *cough* Lego *cough*  John... John is kinda like an innocent bystander.  /clap for John!  ********************  Stop, oh, 'den wiggle wit it!  ********************  I wonder what happened to that poetry and stuff we wrote for Ms. Wilson's class...  ********************  3, 6, 9, stand real fine, oo she can sock it to me one mo' time.  ********************  Emily's party is coming up soon... whoo-hoo-isho!  Should be interesting... I think the house (or estate) is creepy or something...  and this thing is at night?  I hope there's no graveyard outback.  I can't wait much longer! 

22,December,2003


     
      I have nothing to say today.  EXCEPT this.  The post below this one will remain.  And Zach is a metaphor for the entire human race. 

22,December,2003


     
      Posted on Zach's Blog:   "Have you ever just had your heart taken away?? Have you ever wondered why you can't get over a girl??"  Yes I have, Zach.  I wonder everyday.  A lot of people wonder about stuff like that all day, everyda.  Okay?  NOW GET OVER IT!  I just had to say that... ::goes about his normal life::
     
    


21,December,2003


     
      Emulators for old videogame systems rule over all!  I finally got my old Super Nintendo emulator back and it kicks major nostaligic (sp?) butt!  Emulators, by the way, are programs that emulate (imitate) another program (in this case, the SNES console).  I'm running it on my computer and such... I've been playing Super Punch Out and (get this...)  Mighty Morphin Power Rangers for the past few days! Whhheeee!    On a more serious note... SERA sucked today.  Neither Allison nor John was there.  I just sat there... and wrote this:  "I'm bored in SERA.  Allison is gone and so is John.  I've only got myself to talk to right now... kinda weird.  Mr. Rodriguez is still incredibly loud.  I think I should be saying "Oh God!" about now... but no one is here to appreciate the comedic value of such a phrase.  What the hell am I going to do for an entire 9 (is it 9?) days off of school?  My 10:30-11:04 and my lunch are going to be so uninteresting those days.  It's sad, really.  In no particular order, these are the people/things I'll hate being without:  Allison (aka, The Morning?  wtf?), John K., Bitters's first block class and everyone at the lunch table.  Word.  I've got so many thoughts to think right now... maybe I'll get to them at a later time.  SO...  I can't wait till Emily's party and I can't wait to get back to school!"  ***************************  As you can tell, I mentioned a certain someone (*cough* Allison *cough*) a couple times back there.  I'm still not quite sure why though... She seems to have something in her that [most] girls can't stand and [most] guys can't resist.  But I can't say I like her (yet) in the way a certain someone else does... (*COUGH* ZACH *COUGH*)  She's kinda like that one goddess in that one Greek myth...  O.o  I   ***************************  What else can I say today...   Oh, I "kilt" another bill in Bitters's class today.  Debate is so fun.  Sorry, Allison (d'oh... there's that name again), but I'm gonna have to oppose your bill... there's just too much stuff against it.    ***************************  Tomorrow is the last day before Christmas break.  Half day.  Yay.  Super.  ::sigh::  ***************************  Okay, that's all I have for now... gotta get back to the Power Rangers game!  ^_^  I love everyone!  Especially my most-like-myself friend, Allison!  And John K.!  John K. and Allison... my super Crisis Buddy Team!!  WHOOHOOO!!!
     
    


21,December,2003


     
      It's 2 o'clock-ish now... I just logged off FFXI.  Got my Red Mage to Lv.25 and learned two new spells.  Invisible, the white magic spell, let's me become invisible to everyone and everything.  Best part is that I can cast it on party members that I don't wanna see anymore!  I also learned Sleep... a handy spell that puts an enemy to...well... Sleep.  That, combined w/ Gravity (slows enemy movement speed), will surely save my *ss many times.  ******************  Right now I'm going to go downstairs and do a few exercises involving a form of weight.  I haven't done anything down there in so long... I mean, a really long time... like 6 months... so f'n long...  ******************  Tomorrow is the day... the day I profess my undying love to a certain someone... ::silence::  nah, I made that up.  But tomorrow is going to be the first time in history that I've ever spent my hard-earned money on Christmas 'gifts' for friends.  Granted, I only got stuff for three very important people... it's a step forward nonetheless.  Hopefully no one else got me anything... I don't want to be in that situation where I have nothing to give him/her except a "merry christmas."  While we're on the subject... I've still gotta write stuff in the whopping two cards I have for these people... ::makes note of that::  ******************  Damn... I've gotta read Chapter 16 of a Tale of Two Cities, "Still Knitting".  I read 15 last night and it was pretty plain... hopefully someone will die in 16.  Speaking of school!  tomorrow is another debate day! whoo-hoo!  I've got a stange feeling of pent-up rage inside of me... and it HAS to come out tomorrow!  ^_^ I really hope none of those dumb*ss teachers try to start a new lesson tomorrow... if he/she does... he/she is a dumb*ss...  ******************  For some odd reason I'm looking forward to that silly Snowball dance this year...  ::wonders why:: Also, I'm kinda looking forward to Emily's semi-formal pre-new years new years party... ::wonders why:: And yet another thing (or things) I'm looking forward to is SERA and lunch.... ::wonders why:: hmm... let's add gym next half to my list of things I'm looking forward to... ::wonders why:: Has anyone figured out why yet?!  :D  ******************  mmkay, that's all I've got for now... hopefully this post has been worthwhile for your reading pleasure.  And why I say 'pleasure' I mean your enjoyment.     (oh, and I put the * in *ss so the school's web security thing won't block the page... It still might block it though... who knows)
     
    


20,December,2003


     
      I added Zach to my friend's list.  Apparently he gave in and made a Blog thing too.  Go figure...  Anyway, this weekend is kinda different.  I haven't played Final Fantasy XI nearly as much as I have on other weekends.  Last Saturday I played from 6:45AM until 11:45PM... it was niiice.  Got 2 levels in Red Mage (combination damage/healer), 1 level in White Mage (pure healer), and 1 level in Black Mage (pure damage).  This weekend hasn't had quite as nice results.  I only got a single level in Red Mage yesterday... but that was only because I was only around 500 EXP (experience points) from level.  Today I went on a trip to one of the game's bigger cities in hopes of finding a good EXP party.  I get there... put up my party seek flag... wait... wait... wait some more...    Finally I get invited... but they're Japanese!!  Grrr... We tried to make use of the language translation feature but it was no use.  I was doomed to browse the auction house until I got bored enough to log off.  I didn't log off until I managed to spend over 5,000 Gil (Gil=money, remember?) on fishing equipment which I'll probably end up selling in a few days.  THAT'S how bored I got.  I blame it on the version update! 

19,December,2003


     
      "That's what interviews are for!"   And with that, I became, in my eyes, a person made for debating.  I didn't think I had it in me but I managed to actually...um... yell (?) at one of my classmates in the classroom environment.  I'll be doing this more often... So if I don't like something you're all gonna know about it.  Anyway, this whole thing started w/ the parliamentary debate we're doing in U.S. II.  One of the bills up for debate today was "to eliminate the use of affirmative action programs."  To cut to the chase it turned into an issue of discrimination and reverse-discrimination.  A brilliant person said discrimination is still around (DUH!) and that affirmative action helps cut down on discrimination.  She failed to realize that affirmative action encourages DISCRIMINATION against the MAJORITY instead of the minority (reverse-discrimination). HELLO?  Did you even listen to what those other people were saying, T*ff*ny??    So... I took the floor with less than a minute left in general debate.  I laid it out like this:  People are opposed to discrimination.  There is discrimination regardless of any programs.   So w/o affirmative action we have 1 type of discrimination (against minorities).  Okay, put affirmative action into effect.  Now we have a new discrimination (reverse-discrimination against majorities).  wtf?  I thought you DIDN'T LIKE discrimination! Now you want two different types?  pfft...  Question time:  Do you think (something) depends also on personal things?    Answer:  Yes, I think personality is a bigger deciding point when choosing people for a position. (not quite sure how I answered... But it was something like that.)  Question time #2: How would a job employer know about a person's persona--  ?  Answer: (cut off question asker)  That's what interviews are for!    ::DING::  Chair:  Time for general debate has expired...   I sit down and relish in what I've just done.  ^^;   It felt soooo good... like sex... only w/o the sex... you know... just the gratification... (or so I'm inclined to believe)...   w00t!  
     
    


18,December,2003


     
      Yeah, so, it's about that time again (again?...). Well, it's that time when I put up my favorite songs of the moment along w/  the chorus from each of them.  So here it is, in no particular order...  1.  Eamon - I Don't Want You Back (F-ck it)  Chorus:  F-ck what I said, it don't mean sh-t now F-ck the presents, might as well throw em out F-ck all those kisses, it didn't mean jack F-ck you you hoe, I don't want you back ------------------------------------------- Haven't we ALL felt this way at one time or another?  Maybe not towards a "her"... but to someone in general.  ^^;  2. 2pac feat. Notorious B.I.G. - Running (Dying to Live)  Chorus: You know I wonder if they'll laugh when I am dead... Why am I fighting to live If I'm just living to fight? Why am I trying to see When there ain't nothing in sight? Why am I trying to give When no one gives me a try? Why am I dying to live If I'm just living to die? -------------------------- So true... why are we dying to live our lives when we're all just living to die?  3. Kanye West - Through the Wire  (not really a chorus to this... so here's a line or so): How can you console my mom or give her life support When you telling her your sons' on life support And just imagine how my girl feel On the plane scared as hell that her guy look like Ed Mitill ---------------------------------------------------- Hmm... dunno what to say about this one...  It was written by some dude (Kanye West) after he got into some car accident or somethin.  They wired his jaw shut cause I guess it was all broken and sh-t so he wrote a song/rap about it and stuff.   Okay, that's my weekly (should I make this weekly?) list of random songs.  See y'all around.  
     
    


24,January,2004


     
      Tie tying is not fun.  I have to re-learn how to tie a tie every time I need to wear one.  I could easily grab a clip-on, but those aren't fun... they look so perfect... and fake.  It's a good thing the Internet can bail a person out of almost any situation. * With that said, the Snowball [dance] is tonight.  Ironically (?), it actually snowed last night.  Oddly enough, it's still snowing now.   * I got my hair cut this morning... at 8:30... Now it looks slightly more normal.  If not normal, it looks shorter.  /nod * I like getting dressed up [sometimes]... makes me feel important.  But then when I get to where I'm going there's always someone better dressed than I.  Stupid human individuality. * I'm gonna wear a white shirt instead of that old black one this time... and instead of that white tie, I'm gonna wear a darker patterned one.   * I hope this dance doesn't suck... I hope there isn't some sort of explosion of emotion from a certain person who's known to have sudden explosions of emotion... (starts w/ a 'J' and ends with an 'H')  

20,January,2004


     
      I could say a whole buncha stuff right now...  I could tell you how much fun today was...  I could tell you about all the funny and meaningful (and not so meaningful) words that were exchanged between myself and other people, as well as those exchanged by two or more people who weren't me... I could...   But I won't for the simple reason I can't find the words.  Or, I can just do this!.... wait... no, I can't...    I want someone to call the number 867-5309.  Please?  I'm too "shy" to be calling "numbers" this week. * I don't get why people (actually, one person) send me an IM and then just don't say anything for the next half-hour... then ask me some question... and I answer... and it's another half-hour before they reply and/or sign off.  wtf? * I hate when someone in the distance (person A) is talking to someone (person B), but you don't see person B and for some reason or another you and Person A make eye contact and, you seeing person A's lips moving, assume that he/she is talking to you and you proceed to respond by shouting across the room/open area, "what?"... wtf? * Model congress rooms... 4 people to a room, 2 beds to a room.  guys/guys, girls/girls.  Gonna be fun... We're sposeda pick who want to room w/ but I'm just letting other people handle that... It doesn't really matter... it's only one night.  Unless... if the bus breaks down or there's a terrorist attack we might be stuck in the hotel.... wtf? * Haha... Centerfold... Yes, I've definitely heard it before.  That whole "na na na nanana a-nananana" thing... classic. * Lunch table + Drama = Drama at the Lunch table.  WTF?! * SERA + John + Someone else's ID = mystery  (?(?(?(?(?(?)  wtf. *  Ms. Thompson, the math "teacher", = the !#$!# "teacher" !*@$* ever.  She doesn't "teach",  she shows the lesson.  Straight from the book... word for word... she is no "teacher"... then she has the nerve to get mad at us when we ask her "why" and half the time she doesn't even know... wtf?!?! * I dunno if there are anymore things I'd like to say/shout/boil over.  That's all.  Good night.    
     
    


17,January,2004


     
      It seems my comments are back... What a pleasant surprise.  

15,January,2004


     
      Well, all those comments are gone;  swallowed up by the incredible crushing force of the Internet.    And just because I don't want to forreal write something...  1.) Ms. Bitters's "decade" project sucks fantastically.  2.) A Tale of Two Cities actually had a surprisingly enjoyable ending.  3.) A Tale of Two Cities would have been A LOT better if the first 300 or so pages were written like the last 60 or so pages.  4.) Drama at the lunch table makes lunch a very dramatic time.  5.) John at the SERA table makes SERA a very Johnny time.  6.) Pirates of the Carribbean was an interesting movie.  Pirates=Cool (as long as they're not pillaging my village).  7.) Algebra II just got a whole lot more ridiculous... and there are only a few days left of it.  8.) In FFXI, my Red Mage is now Lv.33.  I used my 69,000 Gil scroll of Dispel at Lv.32, thus finalizing my purchase.  9.) Being that I'm Lv.33, I'm able to learn a new spell - called Phalanx - which allows me to take 0 damage for a certain amount of time.  Needless to say, this scroll will cost me ~400,000 Gil...  And I was complaining about raising 69,000.  10.) Not having Phalanx is straight though, since I can learn Stoneskin - *almost* like Phalanx, only not as good - at Lv.34.  That's only 9,000, and I bought it today.   11.) While we're on the subject, there is a spell I can learn at Lv.41 - Refresh - that provides the effect of MP (Mana Points, used in casting magic) regeneration.  This would mean I'd have near limitless MP.  Cost: 60,000 Gil (But... it used to be ~120,000 Gil... there are just a lot for sale right now, so the price is lower ; ;)  12.) My list must end now.  I have nothing else to mention    13.) Bye-bye.
     
    


12,January,2004


     
      Oh God! Why is Everquest at the top of this page at the time of this posting?   I've never even mentioned Evercrap on my Blog.  WTF is this?  Evercrack   If I keep repeating words throughout posts will they feature advertisements for that word up top there?  Like... sex!  or... Mail fraud!  Bill Clinton!  Remote Control!  AH!  Stroke door handle fondle cheese whippit whip it good super sucky foreign admirals!!!
     
    


08,January,2004


     
       A wiener says what? 
     
    


06,January,2004


     
      Check out that advertisement at the top!  FFXI?  Elemental mage power thing?  Wow... they've got a pretty high-tec thing searching our blogs then giving us targeted advertisements...    freeeaaky...
     
    


04,January,2004


     
      Oh, and be sure to scroll down past this post.  There's a good one below.
     
    


03,January,2004


     
      Mwahahahaha!  I had to read some of this horrid book today!  I completely dreaded it.  BUT!  While I was reading, I decide to play Final Fantasy XI.  I took my character to this area where this certain monster spawns on a regular basis (drops a rare shield/weapon).  I figured if I'm gonna be sitting here at the computer reading a book I might as well do somethin constructive with me time!  Anyway, I go to where the monster spawns and I find NO ONE else there!  It musta been the time when the Japanese were logging off and the Americans weren't awake yet. :D  A few minutes after I set up camp at this spot, I start reading one of the most unnecessary books ever (aka, Tale of Two Cities).  I read... read some more... read another sentence... then BAM!  Something whacks my character in the back of the head.  It's my little rare-shield-dropping friend!    I snapped up the controller and began my attack.  Hack and slash and cast a spell or two and it was dead.  Nothing dropped except 35 Gil.  :(  I was fine with it though since I'd be reading the book for at least an hour more (the time it would take for the monster to respawn).    As I was reading several other people came and went... at one time there were 5 other people waiting for this monster with me.  Only I knew when it would spawn next since I killed it last... and to my surprise everyone else left... except a lone Tarutaru (a "little bear" according to Allison).  This Tarutaru (obviously a Black Mage) stood no chance against my uber-leet crazy spell casting skillz.   At first I thought that she would impede my progress on killing the monster the next time it spawned.  Of course, she didn't!  ^_^  Anywho, the monster's counter-part spawned (the one that drops the weapon, not the shield) and I mashed F8 on my keyboard (target closest monster) and slammed down my Dia macro (fastest casting spell of mine).  Got it and I was happy... killed it and I was not.  Only 19 Gil from this one.  So... I still have about 45 minutes left till the monster I killed the first time respawns.  I start reading again.  Reading all those completely unnecessary words.  Skimming through all the fluff... trying to figure out what the HELL this guy is talking about...  DING!  45 minutes are up.  I put the crappy book down and start tapping F8 again.  Waiting... waiting... waiting...    At this point, the Tarutaru goes away (I thought she gave up).  I say to myself "Holy crap... It's all mine when it shows up."  And it was.  Around 15 minutes later it pops out... in all its glory...  I claim it as my own.  Take it in as my pet... my loving pet...  Then I slaughter it.  And as that monsterly monster died... I rejoiced.  I got my shield.  My f'n shield.  All mine.  My shield that's worth 40,000 Gil.  My shield that I'm never gonna sell.  Oh, it also dropped 20 Gil or somethin!  ^^  The funny thing was, as soon as I struck for the final time, the little Tarutaru came running back... so did some Hume (human).  I equipped my shiny new shield and I /laughed and /cheer'ed and I /joy'ed and I /cry'd.    Best.  Luck.  Ever.  SO!!  The moral of the story is this... Old British literature is NOT completely useless!  If it wasn't for that book I NEVER woulda spent an hour and 45 minutes of life standing in one spot in FFXI.  And if it wasn't for that book I NEVER woulda killed that monster and gotten his kick-ass shield.  I'd like to give props to Charles Dickens for writing a book that could keep my occupied for 2 hours while I try to figure out what's going on.  Props to Ms. Wilson for making us read that silly book.  Props to Square-Enix for making FFXI.  Props to me for being lucky.  *************  Now... I still need 10,000 Gil to buy this f'n expensive spell I NEED in order to continue leveling...  Dispel... Cost: 69,000 Gil.  My current Gil: 60,584.  ;_;  *************  Word.
     
    


03,January,2004


     
      Okay, I've been thinking since that last pretty random post.  I'm just gonna put this out there... on the Internet... for all of you read and form opinions on... and to criticize.  *************  Anyway, at this time in my short life I've come to the conclusion that there's only ONE person I could ever see myself in a relationship with (this coming from the mind/life of a 16-year old).  Apparently, that ONE person is one Allison M*******.  Big surprise, eh?  The way I figure is this:    1.) We've only known eachother (that is, actually started talking to eachother regularly) since this school year.  That means there's still A LOT we don't know about one another.  That also means we'd always have something to talk about (other than hookers, sex, and violence towards mutual friends).  2.) Since we both seem to command power (me only discovering this about myself this year), we'd share a balance of power in a more-than-friend's relationship.  This has already proved to be a VERY fun activity... arguing over extremely trivial things... only never in a serious manner (I hope).  3.) We both share a common habit: Sarcasm!  If we were together for extended periods of time it'd be like running a marathon with our friggin' brains!  Ya know, always trying to outdue the other in a game of witty comments and flames (already a proven VERY fun activity).  4.) Likewise, we share another common habit: being [mildly] anti-social.  See, in math two negatives make a positive.  Therefore, Antisocial+Antisocial=Supersocial!  I think the two of us already get along pretty well anyway... who needs other people?  5.) She seems to be the only person I've ever met that can understand and somehow relate to the things I say and do.  THAT takes talent.  6.) She's the perfect height for me plus she's just so much damn fun to be around/talking to/in the same room with.  [/joepost] ***********  So there it is.  If I'm gonna share my love w/ anyone, it's gonna be that girl.  If not... then there's always someone else out there that will accept and/or understand me [I hope].    Don't ask me what possessed me to write this... I'll just say "coincidence".  I really needed to put somethin' like this out there... take it as the softer side of Ryan.  Even if this does come at the expense of Allison's embarassment (what's there to be embarassed about, really?) and my embarassment, I think it'll really help stuff in the long run.  And I don't mean "stuff" as in getting a date/relationship from Allison... I mean it as a "sharin' da' love with others" kinda thing.  Please, feel free to bash/flame/criticize/beatdown/ridicule or praise/cry/cheer/[othergoodthing] in my great Commentss.  ***************  oh yeah, I'm completely aware of the 100 other guys that may feel the same way about Allison.  Must suck for them.  And if Joe is reading this, no offense to you, buddy.  This was all simply inspired by you.  ******  Now, off to dream land... where I hope to have a few interesting dreams... ones full of fantastic adventures and swirling colors.  God... I love sleepy dreams.... SO much better than life.  Why can't dream-rules apply to real-life?!?!?  Ya know, that whole "no repercussions" thing... and no REAL responsibilities... no death... no fear of death... no REAL anything...  ;_;   
     
    


02,January,2004


     
      Man... When I read Joe's newest "Blog" it really made me feel bad... feel bad in the sense that I don't have anyone to share my unbiased love with!  Sure, I've got the friends, but friends can only do so much... unless it's that friends w/ benefits dealy...  Thanks a lot for making me realize that I *almost* NEED someone to share my love with.  ;_;    Now... either I sit here only thinking and saying that... or I actually go out and find this person to share my love with.  Any takers?  Anyone?  Anyone at all?  I'll be back later!
     
    


02,January,2004


     
      Well, it hasn't been as boring as I thought it would be.    -Tuesday, Emily's party. -Wednesday, went bowling w/ Allison, Zach, and Joe. -Thursday... what'd I do Thursday again? -Friday (today), going to Alec/Caitlin's house where Emily, Allison and some other people will be.  I hope tonight is like the other times... only this time Allison seems to be taking the place of Amanda.  Niiice.  Oh, and maybe we'll play more Soul Calibur II... Niiiicer.  *******************  Joe updated his blog... Now, call me crazy, but I think that kid is REALLY "depressed" because of/about girls.  Girls are not the cure-all of the world, man!  If anything, they're the indirect cause of a lotta problems!  Like communism!  Of course, none of MY female friends are the indirect cause of communism.  *******************  Almost time to go back to school!  Yay!  3 days!  I've still got to read 3 chapters of Tale of Two Cities... and I've still got to figure out where I put my debate folder... and I've still got to do other stuff.  It's gonna be so nice having SERA and lunch and first block and anything else good about school back.  *******************  hmm... oh! I've noticed something lately... I've got this incredible yearning to write...uh..."deep" (for the lack of a better word) letters to someone.  Problem is, I have no one to write them to!  ;_;  I could just pick some random person and write stuff then give it to them... but then she might get the wrong idea. 

14,February,2004


     
      
     
    


07,February,2004


     
      I haven't typed anything here in 7 days... that's, like, a whole week!  O.O  Maybe I should start again soon... and I will... when we go back to school I'm be sure to type some interesting stuff about it here.  Thnikkaman! (I think...)
     
    


07,February,2004


     
      Good morning.  I'm Bored.  Good morning.
     
    


01,February,2004


     
      As you can see, my comments are gone.  The site broke for good. * Next semester starts Wednesday (weather permitting) * There was a very loud two-car collision on the road in front of my house tonight.  Lotsa "rescue" vehicles showed up. * I don't -need- a girlfriend but it'd be a nice change of pace. * Maybe I'll meet a new someone in one of my 4 classes this half of the school year. * I've got my Red Mage to Lv.41 in FFXI.  Convert + Refresh = near infinite MP.  I am going on a leveling spree tonight, all night... that is, if I find a good group to EXP with. * Allison + Harry = Love apparently. * Zach + Harry = Jealously maybe. * Ryan + [random name] = Confusion * The Superbowl is teh sux. * Holy crap, 50 yard field goal just now.  Weird. * To sum everything up:  This half of the school year is going to be extremely easy.  Maybe I'll have time to pursue the venture of "teaming up" with some girl that I can call my girlfriend.  Maybe I can become a millionaire while I'm at it.  
     
    


29,April,2004


     
      OK, w/ comments out of the way for now I guess it's time for me to say stuff.  1) South Park last night was GAY!  And by GAY I seriously mean GAY... men were doing stuff do/with each other... ::shudder::  2) Physics test today... was way too easy 

28,April,2004


     
      /sigh  I thought gym wasn't going to suck this week since I got Flag Football.  But it does.  We didn't go outside today.  Tomorrow and Friday we're doing gay fitness testing (no, not testing our fitness to see if we're gay... gay fitness testing as in "oh man, this fitness testing is gay and I don't like it).  I already know I'm not the most physically fit person ever... WHY DO WE HAVE TO REINFORCE WHAT'S ALREADY KNOWN?!?!?  /sigh   (This current sentence is written in Gay... if you can read it, then you, sir or madam, are gay.  Sorry.)
     
    


26,April,2004


     
      First, the crazycool pictures.  This one is of Ifrit, the fire elemental summon (big guy that smashes things when you call him).  He's mine to command... little bunnies fear me.      This one is of a wyvern (dragon) I found while running around all Invisible... I'm sure it'd kill me in about 3 hits if it saw me.  You can see my character's outline in the picture 

17,April,2004


     
      Oh yeah, thanks for the picture info, Mr. Alec Coolguy.
     
    


08,April,2004


     
      Yay!  It is teh worked!  Take that, Internet!   Well... since I can... I'm gonna put the other two pictures I took of my AF armors (remember, Jesusarmor).  The pictures would look a lot better if I had take them on the PC (I took these ones on the PS2).  Just look at them and /nod in amazement.  ^^;     
     
    


08,April,2004


     
          If this worked right, you should see a picture of my character in Final Fantasy XI: Online.  That's my Lv.60 AF (Artifact, aka Jesusarmor) Hat.  It's called (by most) the pimp hat because of the feather and such.  Let's have a see if it worked... ::Publish post::
     
    


08,April,2004


     
      OK, I'm gonna try to put a cool-looking picture on here for the first time.  You may note that the Comments (broken or not) are completely gone.  I changed the template because I didn't feel like picking out all the little pieces of the code or whatnot.  Also, you'll see that the Friends thing is gone; again, for the same reason.   I'm gonna need to relearn the directions for both of those things... ::looks in Alec's general direction of his Blog::  Alright, so here goes the picture attempt...  
     
    


08,April,2004


     
       .

31,May,2004


     
      I Love You, Cindy!  too!  : D
     
    


30,May,2004


     
      And thus the last 3-day weekend comes to an end...  Not much to say about the last 3-day weekend ^^;  * * * *  The last few weeks of gym are going to be crazygonuts.  Archery = good.  Cindy = great.  Archery + Cindy = grooder.  * * * *   One month tomorrow at approximately 11:49:36PM!  Wheee!!  * * * *   Good night!
     
    


30,May,2004


     
      Man... why'd I'd wait all that time?  I was/am stupid! :P  * * * *  Going out to DiLisi's w/ Cindy and Dale + Maria was mucho fun... we got free drinks because the waitress spilled stuff all over Dale! XD   poor Dale... ;;    ::Details Omitted Here::  ...which brings us up to now ^^  Good night!  but more like "Good morning!" since it's just about 2:00AM.
     
    


29,May,2004


     
      ...  ::speechless:: ...
     
    


27,May,2004


     
      Friday!   Wheeeeeeee!  No school Monday!  Wheeee!!  
     
    


26,May,2004


     
      I'm still trying to write that meaningful thing...   There's so much I want to say (or at least think I want to say), though, that it's hard to not make it just a pile of words.  Heck... it's hard to even start since there's so much I want to say (or at least think I want to say) that it's hard to not make it just a pile of words.  * * * *  Only a couple more days left of our current gym activities then we get to pick our final one of the school year...  I think I already know what type of activity I've gotta pick... Help! : P  * * * *  6 more days!  or 7... depending on if you count the rest of today as a day...    wheeeeEeeeeeeeeeeeeeEEEEEEEEEEee!!  * * * *  ok, that's all I've got for now that's G-rated ... ^_~  Now... I need to find some Pop Rocks...
     
    


24,May,2004


     
      If I said half the things I was thinking at any given time the world would be a very... interesting... place.
     
    


24,May,2004


     
      I want to write something...  something with meaning... something with heart...  I don't think this public Blog is the right place, though ;;  I guess I'll have to break out the ol' pen and paper...  Later! :D
     
    


23,May,2004


     
      If there is one person you can't stop thinking about, post this same exact sentence in your journal.  : )
     
    


21,May,2004


     
      Nothing to say except :D
     
    


21,May,2004


     
      ...  well, Friday = best day of the week.    This goes against that little rambling I went on in lunch a while back about how weekends suck and Friday sucks cause it's starting a weekend and blah blah blah ...  All of that was before Cindy, though ^_^; I'm so glad I finally got out of denial a few weeks ago!  I  
    


20,May,2004


     
      I don't have much to say...  Today school seemed so slow... like whoa...  * * * *   Cindy and Heather kicked ass (with their voices) last night at that spring concert!  w00t!  Good jobs!  * * * *  umm... :/   Let's see...   * * * *   well, that's all for now 

18,May,2004


     
      Man...   I've been so damn happy lately...      I'll just stop there since I can't think of the words right now that'll describe the full happiness.  Instead, I'll post a picture that'll pretty much show my happiness.     *EDIT*  Resized picture... less detailed now... but at least my friend list and everything isn't pushed to the bottom.   We still look good, though! :P    * * * *  On a less happy note, I've got a 90.2 in Sra. Bitcho's spanish class.  Her f'n "erh... you start the class with an 80 in participation and if you say stuff a lot you get more points and if you don't say anything because you don't feel like opening your mouth you get 0 and if you do something I don't like you get negative points.  erehh1hh..." stuff is BS.  * * * *  On a happy note, spring concert is tomorrow night!  wheee!  I've still got ~4 pictures left on that disposable camera they gave us before prom... I must use it so I can reap the sweet rewards inside.  huh?  * * * *  Archery went very well today... I hit the target 8 out of 8 total shots!  w00t!  * * * *  well... I think that's all I can say for now.  I'm happy.  So very happy.    Cindy is the greatest! ^^ Everyone else is cool, too! ^^;  P.S. I hope that picture shows up... no pictures are working when I click preview...
     
    


17,May,2004


     
      *Warning*This post contains pictures of decent sizes... give them time to load if you have to*  Not much I can say about today... but I'll try anyway :D  Everything was absolutely fine!  Hell... Spanish w/ Sra. Bitcho (Mrs. Hughes) wasn't even that bad...  Yup, today was not bad at all for a Monday.  The time immediately following school, though, was the best of all (2:45-3:19) XD    Everyone needs more days (school days at least) that end in mucho laughter XD     * * * *  Gym is gonna f'n kick ass this time... Archery is looking like a lot of fun.  Now there are two more teams I think our school needs... Fencing and Archery.  * * * *  Yeah, so, I printed some pictures... I actually USED that picture frame they gave us after prom!  Filled it with this uber-great picture!  ^_^  *EDIT* This picture was too big... it messed things up on the blog template...  I'm working under the assumption that no one minds their picture being on here... since only a few choice people ever actually look at this Blog of mine... Tell me if you mind and I'll be sure to baleete any picture.  Here's an uber-cool picture of all our hot selves!  *EDIT*  Took out this picture... way too big... again 

16,May,2004


     
      Friday, 2:30PM -

13,May,2004


     
      oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god, oh god!  Prom is only ~24 hours away!  And the pre-prom stuff is only, what, ~19.2 hours away from starting?!  oh my jesus!  The good thing, though, is that we (Cindy and I) have everything pretty much planned out and ready to start.  I   Here's the (mostly complete) breakdown:  Friday, prom day  ~2:15, Cindy 

12,May,2004


     
      Johnny and me went to pick up our tuxedos/everything else today.  There were a lotta people there, mostly from our school.    It takes so long to put on a full tuxedo outfit thing... maybe it was because it was the first time ever (to my knowledge) that I've put one on.    However, once I figured out where everything went, I looked simply stunning, if I may say so. :D  There's a downside, though... the tuxedos have to be back to the store by 4:00PM on Saturday... lame!  -_-  * * * *  Then, Johnny and me went to order corsages for our hot dates.  That's about it.  So, for me:  Tuxedo/vest/shirt/pants/shoes = OK Corsage = OK Bootaneer (sp?) = Dunno if that's OK yet A more or less planned prom day/night/next day = OK Wonderfully beautiful date = Extremely OK  Now... just to wait for Friday! ^^;  
     
    


11,May,2004


     
      Big yellow ball of gas that gives off radioactive heat make Ryan go... something-something.  Seriously...  I thought yesterday was hot.  Today is/was hotter.  So sad.    I got a haircut.  I didn't get it cut short on top at all this time.  Now I won't have to worry about small pieces of hair sticking up and ruining my self-cofidence :O   We are gonna look soooooo much hotter (as in good-looking hotter) in the pictures before/during/after the prom, Cindy! XD   I'm sure everyone else is gonna look good, too, though ^^  It's too...ugh...hot (weather hot)... to continue.    Good bye for the time being.
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      I need to get a haircut tomorrow.  Prom soon.  Today was a long school day (yeah, I know, they're all 7 hours unless there are special circumstances).  First block was first block.  Gotta love the Cool Zone.  Gym was pretty lame today.  We had to stay inside because it was too wet outside to play flag football.  We ended up playing a ghetto game of volleyball in that little 'dance' section of the main gym.  I think the only people that went outside were the people in fitness walking.  Those lucky little...  Spanish was bearable.  We talked about different kinds of clothing and what they were called in spanish and blah blah blah blah (really, I think I heard Ms. Hughes saying 'blah blah' a lot).  Physics was interesting.  A nice, long lesson on Newton's three laws.  Yup... nice and long... -_-;  Of course, all of the boring school-day stuff is irrelevant, since they always end in the nicest of ways ^_~  P.S.  When I say 'all of the boring school-day stuff' I don't mean the  whole  school day was boring :D      
     
    


09,May,2004


     
      Well... I found out why these Blogs (and the Internet in general) were behaving very oddly/slowly.  Apparently I had 3 different Trojans/viruses on my computer 

08,May,2004


     
      I've forgotten it was Mother's Day tomorrow three times today... each time I was reminded it was Mother's Day tomorrow... How could I forget 2 more times after the first time?  -_-;  It's funny... my mom won't even be home for Mother's Day XD   Her and my sister went to Delaware to shop today, and are staying overnight to go shop some more tomorrow.  wtf?  It's so quiet here w/o those two.  If it was like this ALL the time (only w/ them here) maybe I wouldn't be so high-strung at times.  * * * *  The times of pre-prom, prom, and after-prom are going to rule... so far.  I hope things go roughly as planned :P  Johnny and I went to pick out our tuxedos/vests/whatever else today.  It was quick; less than an hour.  I hate to admit it... but it was kinda fun to choose things to wear :x  heh... the time of after-prom sounds like it just got better.  * * * *  No more things to post because it's almost tomorrow.  Good night.  
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      ...  I was supposed to be at Johnny's house 16 minutes...  We were supposed to be on our way to rent tuxedos about 13 minutes ago...  My mom is running late as usual 

07,May,2004


     
      liek omigod, wheeeee!  Today was greatness/craziness and a half!  I hope there are many more in the future!  Every sentence today is going to end in a '!' because that's how loud I feel I have to talk!  * * * *  That second line pretty much sums up the point of this whole post! I could provide details of today's events but then some people might be bored to near death! The real-life events were so incredibly interesting/entertaining/worthwhile that a Blog post couldn't do them justice!  Sorry!  Good night!   P.S.  Van Helsing.... A-   It's defintely worth the $6.00 (or $8.00, depending on time)!  Tons of action (don't expect a horror movie)!  /poke /poke   /slap /slap!!!#%@#^    
     
    


06,May,2004


     
      Keep this in mind... Before yesterday, I hadn't been on a serious bike ride for a few months (or any bike ride for that matter).  Thus:  Yesterday + Serious bike ride + Decently strong wind + Not stretching sufficiently before the serious bike ride + Running in gym's Flag Football + Blocking in gym's Flag Football + Being Ryan = Major pain in basically all my thigh muscles and the outside muscles of my upper arms.  I can't believe I could easily take the pains that came with two major surgeries (and the long recoveries at home) while simple muscle... uh... ache (?) makes me go "ow, ow, ow" whenever I try to climb stairs or walk up an incline.  Being bipedal sucks sometimes.  * * * *  How 'bout this... I can't think of any one thing to say... So many thoughts going through my mind right now ;;  I think I'll just type random Alt codes and see what happens.  Here we go...  ....   scratch that... I just had to delete a whole line of cool Alt codes... It seems that Blogger doesn't like them.  It kept slowing down/freezing. 

05,May,2004


     
      Introducing... The newest character from those coolguys that work for Nintendo*...  Erectile Dysfunctioning Titmouse... Man!  He's sooooOOOo straight!  ......  (picture not available;  see Alec)  Coming soon... to a Gamecube near you!  *Nintendo is not Harry and/or Zach, becausem as we know, Harry and/or Zach is/are two guys from school.  ****  With that advertisement out of the way, let's get down to the matters at hand.  No more 'gay'.  'gay' was sooooo 3 months ago.  Let's put that behind us and let those by-gones be just what they're called, by-gones.  If you had a problem with 'gay' then that problem has been solved.  From now on I'll try to remove that blasphemes word from my hurtful vocabulary.    Rumor has it, though, that a new word is on the rise...   ****  -Who is this Merry?  He/she/it is totally going Godzilla on everything. -What's this prom thing?  It's really shaking people up like some sort of stick on a hornets' nest. -What's this about Sean being the straightest guy on the planet? -Narcaleptic Flying Squirrels?  Who knew. -OMFG!  New episode of South Park tonight... They're totally going to be ninjas and stuff! -I want to see that Van Helsing movie when it comes out in theaters. /poke - -I'm pretty satisfied with the events of today... It all "works out" in the "end". -Gotta go get a tuxedo with Johnny this Saturday afternoon or morning or whenever possible...   -John G.'s party was the best thing that ever happened to me.  Thanks, John G.!  ****  Ok, I lost the momentum for that... I got distracted for a second so I decided to just end it before somehow I exploded this part of the Internet.  And now I just got distracted by Lineage II... gah!  I just want to type an unnecessarily long post!  ****  well... I pretty much ruined this post... Better luck tomorrow!  And yes, Merry, I love you, too.  ...even if you are a dude pretending to be a chick named Merry for your own sick pleasures... Not that I think you are really a dude or anything... are you?  P.S.  No spellcheck just because this post is the straightest one ever. 
     
    


04,May,2004


     
      haha... stuff rules sometimes.      That probably makes no sense to anyone... but it doesn't matter because it makes perfect sense to me.   
    


03,May,2004


     
      Alright, tell me now...  *  If ANYTHING I say to you hurts you each and every day, please leave a comment.  *  If my words hurt you so much that you want to kill yourself, please leave a comment.  *  If you're angry because I say things that, in fact, hurt you and your dearest friends, please leave a comment.   *  If you've NEVER been pissed off by ANYTHING or ANYONE but me, please leave a comment. *  If you're not sure about yourself and feel that you have to get mad at some high school kid joking about everyone being gay, please leave a comment. *  If you think 'gay' is a sin, please leave a comment. *  If you haven't noticed the 'gay revolution' (Hello!  Queer Eye for the Straight Guy, Straight Plan for the Gay Man, ALL the reality TV shows, all those magazines, books, etc that say stuff about gay things) and think it's WRONG to joke/talk about gayness, please leave a comment.  *  If you think EVERYTHING HAPPENING WITH THIS 'GAY' STUFF IS RIDICULOUS, UNNECESSARY B.S., please leave a comment.  ---  I wish Johnny saw these things... he's the best moderator ever.  And now, a song:  Gay gay gay,  gay gay gay,  gay gay gay gay gay! gay gay gay gay ga-gay gay gay Everyone I don't know is so gay!  /end song  The word 'gay'... it means nothing after being said X amount of times.  I mean... I could understand how people would get mad if I go around MAKING FUN of for-real gay men... but as far as I know I'm not doing that.  If anything I'm complimenting the gay community by for-fake including the coolest guys I know.    I guess that doesn't mean anything, though, because ideas are already set in stone.  P.S.  To anyone reading this... If you'd like to prevent the future, please leave a comment that includes your phone number and address.    P.P.S. No one should be reading this since EVERYTHING I say is going to hurt you so much that you'll want to kill yourself.  We don't want a bunch of kids from CRHS killing themselves... that's bad for our school's image.
     
    


03,May,2004


     
      I got home at 2:48 today... totally pwned the bus!  A whole 4 minutes really makes a difference!  Thanks Cindy and  thanks foreign language honor societies (but mostly Cindy) for getting me here on the Internet, updating my Blogay.  ***  Now then, here's a site that EVERYONE (even if 'offensive' language offends you) should see/read.   ....  urlLink Maddox:  Pirate on an Opinionated Mission!    Click on Archives and read some crazily funny stuff... or do whatever the hell you like on the site... just look at it!  ***  We FINALLY got to play flag football in gym.  It was pretty cold outside... yup, pretty cold.  Flag football is fun.  ***  Today was, for the most part, good.  Started with the usual before-first-block antics and the usual during-first-block antics.    Second block is gym so that's always fun for one reason or three.  Here's where it gets sucky...   SERA:  originally M-226 (I think), instead spent in C-303 with Ms. Hughes and all the Spanish Honor Society people.  Third block: spent in C-304 with Ms. Hughes for Spanish III ... 84 minutes of it.  Fourth block:  originally D-404 (is that it?), Physics with Ms. Houghton... instead spent in the PAC with Ms. Hughes and her foreign language cronies.  Things got unsucky at 2:40, however, for several obvious reasons.  ***  That's all for my special afternoon update since I got home early!  Hasta luego!  
     
    


03,May,2004


     
      ...from about Saturday night at 7:20PM to Monday morning at 9:00AM.  Hmm... not quite sure what's wrong with people all of a sudden... but it's something.  Maybe it's because my words may have gotten twisted in one way or another by one person or another.  So gay.  To Harry:    I don't think it was necessarily called for you to bring Cindy into this by saying "...CUZ IF YOU HAVE, IT'D BE LIKE KISSING ALL THE OTHER...." as if she's the sluttiest girl on earth (which I honestly like to believe she's not and never will be).  That's a low-blow, man.    When that whole water bottle thing started it was just a *joke*.  A *joke* I thought y'all could handle... obviously we aren't mature enough.  I wasn't planning on anyone thinking about it all that much.  I wasn't planning on the idea of Johnny making out w/ Harry indirectly through a water bottle that Allison drank out of to stick around for more than 30 minutes... 45 minutes max.  I guess people have a lot of time on their hands to dwell on these things...  To Zach:  I'm not quite sure why you're angry at me every time you see me... You should know by now that I occasionally say things that are just completely random and unmeaningful.  Tune it out, man. 

01,May,2004


     
      Tonight was the best night in a long while.  The ending was a little... erm... 'shaky'... but that can be worked on over and over again... and again and again and... ^_~    That's all for now ^^;   Keep your opens for the picture of the mystical dragony dude of death!
     
    


01,May,2004


     
      First, two pictures of a cute (if you want to call them that) little Tarutaru Black Mage...    and...    ********************* mwahahahaha!   I pwned (with a capital P) that physical fitness testing stuff yesterday!  I did pretty good considering how much I haven't been doing physical things yet this year.     When we first got outside, I jokingly said "I bet I can do... 23 push ups." (that may not be 'exactly' what I said, but I know I said 23)  So we started doing the push ups and, ironically (was it irony?), I managed to do 23 push ups.  The last 2 were kinda strenuous though ;;  Next, we did the sit ups.  In order to be consistent, I aimed for 23 again XD   I did 23.  I could've done more (in 1,001 years) but, as you all know, I don't exactly have a 'six pack'.  Finally, it's the runny time.  12 minutes to see how many times we can get around the school's track.  I, again, jokingly said "I'll jog the whole first lap."  I managed to do just that, and then some.  I was shocked I didn't fall over and die after that 

30,June,2004


     
      I think I may have done more work today than I have in my entire life so far... I'm starting to remember why school isn't such a bad thing.  That's all I have to say about work...  Now then... I hope Cindy is done at Mollie's ^^;
     
    


27,June,2004


     
      Cindy is teh back!!  On the happy scale, 1 being the lowest, 10 being the highest, I think I'm at "omfgbestdayeverbecauseCindyisbackandIloveher"* (that's about a 1,000,000 by the way)  ...ok...that was just corny... but really,  it's great knowing that Cindy is here for me and that I'm here for her...  I'm at a loss for words now so I'll stop before I start rambling about all kinds of things...  Welcome back, Cindy!   I love YOU (Cindy)!!  *I had to edit this for length... originally it went all the way across the page and messed things up on the template... 

26,June,2004


     
      Cindy returns tomorrow and that's good.  I'm practicing our song a little right now (because no one else is home).  That's good.  I've come to accept the fact that I'll never sound like this dude that plays Fyerio and I'm just gonna sing to the best of my ability.  Hopefully I can improve more... and fast.  That's all for now.  'night. 
     
    


24,June,2004


     
      I have been pwned!  whoohoo?     Welcome back, Alec!$!#%!#$%@$^&      kthxbai~
     
    


24,June,2004


     
      ...no motivation to practice that song anymore at all for I don't know how long...   It's a good thing I sung it yesterday (when I had motivation) about 16 times... I think I actually made some improvement then.  But all of that improvement went bye-bye today 

23,June,2004


     
      Yeah, so, Cindy just called me from Creation... with her cell phone.  I think I missed half of what she was saying because her voice kept cutting in and out.  It sounded like someone who didn't know how to use a walkie-talkie. ;;    Wanna know what made it worse?  When I first answered the phone I thought it was Amanda Harris calling me for some random reason... Cindy sounds just like her on the phone I guess.  I broke a good sweat trying to find out if it was, in fact, Cindy calling... then I had to kinda explain why/who/what/dammit Amanda was.    And that, my friends, is one reason why I hate phones and conversations on them.  To me it seems that voices are too distorted when they go through wires.  So f'n stupid.    At least it was nice to hear her voice... although it was kinda distorted and unCindy-like 

23,June,2004


     
      Cindy left for Creation today... she's gonna be gone for 5 days and I miss her already ;;  That's all I can say about that without making myself really, really sad, as opposed to just really sad.  * * * *  The baseball game I went to with Dale, Joe, and Dale's cousin Kenny was fun.  I'm just disappointed at Dale... he knows why... 

21,June,2004


     
      The hospital was fun.    * * * *  After all that, I was trying to find the Wicked soundtrack in some stores... no place had it. 

18,June,2004


     
      ack ack ack ack ack ack! ;;
     
    


18,June,2004


     
      Second day off of school and all is well.  Monday I've gotta start cutting the grass, though, since that's when Summer really starts (or some I'm told).  That's about the extent of my complaints.  Everything else is just fine.  Really, really fine 

16,June,2004


     
      I love you...
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Gluz.com     ...   omfg... my head a'splode!!!  

15,June,2004


     
      Only two more half-days of school left!  Wahoo?...  I've got really easy exams this time.    Today: Pre-CAD, gym Tomorrow:  Spanish III, Physics  Yup, all easy... or maybe I just don't care about Spanish O.o  * * * *   What else can I say...?  This whole Ryan + Cindy thing is working out great.  There's no end in sight.  We spend so much time together I'm sure it's making some people sick (some people not being me or her) ^^  She's my first girlfriend... I hope she's the last.  * * * *  Final Fantasy XI is getting fun again.  I've stopped leveling my jobs and started focusing on making massive amounts of Gil.  I've leveled a tradeskill and taken up mining.  Right now I'm a Lv59 Woodworker and can make a steady profit by making crazygonuts items and arrows.  In mining the profit is pretty flexible... sometimes I can make more than 30,000 Gil on a trip... other times it's less than 10,000 Gil... The trick is to hope for Darksteel Ore (~5,500 Gil) and Gold Ore (~8,000 Gil), and hope for lots of it.  Current Gil: 218,965  * * * *  That's all for now.  Good bye. 
     
    


13,June,2004


     
        French Guard I'm French! Why do think I have this outrageous accent, you silly king-a?!     urlLink   What Monty Python Character are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     I am teh French ;;
     
    


09,June,2004


     
      3 more days of school... 3 more days of school...  * * * *  Friday after school was fun.  Today was even more fun.  Tomorrow should be about the same amount of fun.  We're going to play tennis with/against Johnny and Emily @ Bridgeton HS at 1:00PM. wheeee  * * * *  Coheed and Cambria is a cool little band/group/music people.  If only I could get that one song of theirs that makes you feel like you have to go on a journey... 

09,June,2004


     
      So... I tried singing today.  It turns out (in my opinion) I don't suck at it after all.  I was singing that Fame song "Can't Keep It Down" which is always fun (and relevant to my life ^_~).  I think I sound pretty good... the only problem is that I don't know where my voice is most suited.  Deep?  or not quite so deep?  I think my deep is really deep, but I'm probably wrong.  I can sing deep, but it sounds funny to me, like I'm just talking really loud but with a rhythm of some sort... maybe it's supposed to be like that? lol  Cindy!!  I need help!! :P  I think I am going to join choir and try out for the play/musical next year... that is, if I'm taught well  :) * * * *  School is almost out for the summer.  whoo-freakin'-hoo -_-   A 7-hour gap in almost all of my days until September!  What could be more fun?!?  * * * *  meh... not much else to say... good bye?
     
    


08,June,2004


     
      whooo...   
    


06,June,2004


     
      Physics project = 96% done!  I've just got to add the name and some little doodads on it...  I'm gonna call it "Cheap Thrill"  Approximate cost to build:  $0.00 Approximate time taken to build:  6 hours Hardest part:  Finding the best rubberband and height Easiest part:  a'sploding it  I'm totally making up my presentation as I go...  Ms. Houghton is not a tough teacher therefore I feel that I can effectively improvise my presentation.  * * * *  In other news, Cindy is the best.  * * * *   That's all the news for now.  Bye bye for now. 
     
    


03,June,2004


     
      I kicked ass in archery today.  I hit every shot.  Most of the hits were red.  The only problem was my freakishly large gorilla hand... for some reason I had a problem with the fletchings hitting my hand as the arrow left the bow.  That meant funny lookin' bouncy arrows :(  I never had that problem in Wuzzardo's class 

01,June,2004


     
      Happy one month to us... Happy one month to us... Happy one month dear uuuuus... Happy one month to us!  *cheer!*  wheee.  Nope, one month isn't that long, but what a month it has been.  Let's make the next one even better!  * * * *   Today was great +2.  * * * *   Archery is going to be really nice this time (as opposed to "nice" with Wuzzardo).  Ms. Sharp moves fast (in teaching gym classes...).  * * * *   Nothing else to say at 11:00PM on a school night.  Good night.
     
    


30,July,2004


     
      fah-reaking... Jesus...  This week was insanely long. We worked our asses off in the warehouse and I got my first taste of being out on the road. I almost got my second taste of being out on the road. We had left Ware's and were stopped at a WaWa before leaving, but my dad refused to let me go this time (it was 14k lbs in Wildwood... the dudes weren't back when we left at 5PM today). My brother was following our trailer with another trailer that he was going to drop in Wildwood then go back to Ware's to pick up another trailer, yadda yadda yadda... He took me back to the warehouse and picked up the guy that was originally supposed to go that I was going to replace.  Not only did all that make this the longest week ever, but I highly anticipated Cindy's return this Saturday (tomorrow!!). Less than 24 hours left! Wheeeee!!  Everything is fine, though, since today was pay-day. Yay for $425 gross for only 5 days of work, but then stupid Uncle Sam taking away about $60, bringing my total down to $362.38 <>  Bye bye 
     
    


23,July,2004


     
      Just seven more days... seven... Then my balance will be restored.&nbsp; wheee!  
     
    


21,July,2004


     
      f'n Wicked music and its f'n "For Good" song...  Everytime I sing (and sometimes just hear) that song when I'm alone I start getting that feeling I want to cry. &nbsp;ya know... that burning in&nbsp;the sinuses and the whole watery eyes thing... ;;&nbsp; It's not full-blown out-loud "whaaaa, whaaaa" crying, but just those little sniffs and hiccup-like heaves...&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; weird.  &nbsp; I think I&nbsp;miss Cindy too much ;;&nbsp; I hope her parents will let me go with them at 5:00AM next Saturday to pick her up.&nbsp; But shhhh... Cindy can't know. 
     
    


18,July,2004


     
      Cindy... I miss you.&nbsp;&nbsp;I can't wait until you get back...&nbsp; ;; 
     
    


06,July,2004


     
            discover what candy you are @ quiz me    Now that I'm done with forreal answering the questions I'm gonna go back and see what other kind of whacky candy I can become!  wheee!!
     
    


04,July,2004


     
      Happy 4th of July, people!   I think we're going to go to one of the fireworks displays tonight, but we already saw our first fireworks together last night at... 9:14 (please be the right time...)! yay for airborne explosives!  The Cumberland County Fair starts Monday at 5:00PM!  We're probably going to go there, too.  Maybe we'll see some people.  I need a haircut but I'm too lazy to deal with it growing back.  Good-bye.
     
    



