
18,July,2004


    
       Went out for 2 days, Thursday and Friday.  Wind was blowing at like 70mph.  Got sea sick, threw up a bunch of times..... got to shoot a rapid fire grenade launcher, kept an empty shell.  Got to see my gun shoot with live rounds for the first time, I sat right under it and got soaked from the lousy weather/rough water.  I'll eventually have pictures of things when the computer isn't occupied and so slow. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
         The Teriyaki McBurger at the Mcdonalds here on base.   GROSS  
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       11:00am 1-19-2004  urlLink My weather sucks   
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       It's 9:30am the 17th, I got to go out and ride the train yesterday.  It doesn't seem too hard to do as long as you can figure out the map.  It's pretty cheap to ride them, and they're always lots of people everywhere. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       11 hours and 5451 miles later, I'm in Japan. It's 4:00pm out here and about 40 degrees F. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       At LAX waiting for my flight.  Changed $50 over into japanese, now I have holes in my money. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       The day of doom has come.  Fly out to the new home in a few hours, some 11-odd hour flight.  
    
    


18,July,2004


    
        urlLink USS Curtis Wilbur (DDG-54)  My next home :| 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       Blah 1st post 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       I have  urlLink pictures  up here.  Finally back from a 2 week underway.  I have pictures of us pulling into yokosuka, but I don't have the camera to upload the pictures to the computer.  The gun was shot a whole bunch of times, which can't be good from all the stress of being able to fire 4500 rounds per minute.  The 5" gun shot something like 200 rounds or so, loading that thing was kind of cool.  I got to use my  urlLink wireless card  and for only being on a 11mbps (802.11b) network it's pretty fast, even with the amount of people on it.  I have to eat dinner now, even though it's 9:05pm... updates will be later, after I get my camera to upload the pictures. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       Ha.... back in homeport.  Last 2 ports got canceled. At least I'm back to semi-freedom here. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       Rearranged  urlLink Pictures  and added new ones. 
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       I am finally in port, the one that got cancelled the last time.    urlLink Da Nang, Viet Nam.   
    
    


18,July,2004


    
       Left Vietnam a couple days ago, just out here floating on the water now with no land in sight.  I bought a bunch of stuff when I was in Vietnam, 2 toothpick holders, 2 horn statues, a chopstick box, 2 lamps, ashtray, and a incense burner... all made of marble.  I also got 2 silk lanterns, a 4 part picture, and a t-shirt.  I took a lot of pictures, if I find somewhere to put them up I'll upload some.  The last day I got to go to the  urlLink Furama Hotel  after we did our shopping for the day, that place was really nice.  It's not everyday that I get to go to a 5-star resort.  I was going to go swimming, but didn't have any shorts to change into... there was some shops outside of the hotel and I bought some there, along with a bottle of wine that had snakes in it.  I gotta cut this short.. trying to finish my movie.  
    
    



