
21,June,2004


	 
      I hope that Microsoft funds (but not manages) a private spaceflight organization that will work on colonization.  It would be so cool.  Do you think we ever actually got to the moon though?  Hmmm...
    


19,June,2004


	 
      The first private spaceflight!  And just when I'm about to switch the theme from space to dinosaurs.  Wow, even though I hate Microsoft, it's still pretty dope.  From what I've heard, the pilot lost control, but used backup systems to regain it.  This is pretty exciting...  Maybe we'll be able to visit hotels on the moon soon.  I am slightly worried that our governments will try to take control of other planets/the moon and will not allow for private settling, which is becoming more and more possible.  Oh well, dinosaurs are better.   Vs.   The other day coming home from the wedding... the sun was in my eyes, the garage door opener fell down, and an eyelash fell in my eye so I couldn't see, and it hurt, not that this is a run-on sentence or anything, and the road was curvy, and I ran over the curb, and the hubcap fell off!!!!!!!  Too bad.  Winner?
    


19,June,2004


	 
        urlLink playlistId=5365125&selectedItemId=5365109"

15,June,2004


	 
      There isn't really much to talk about except for the ideas that are  manifested through the random things that I will be putting on here.  I have been trying to figure out an easy way to post and I've done it  probably:  This post is coming from an email!  Wow.  For real though  that "Who's Who" thing is real.  I have until July 7 to send in my  biography and it will be put in the book!  I makes me feel like I am  worth something.  Wow, thanks who's who of america.
    


15,June,2004


	 
      it's spacebattle time: I'm going to maybe get in to the who's who in america book for this one:  If This Is Love It Isn't  from the album Body Popping - Moon Walking - Top Rocking by  urlLink Happy Apple     vs.     Toxic  from the album In the Zone by  urlLink Britney Spears   who wins? 
    


15,June,2004


	 
      I'm just going to start right off quick with this "blogging" thing.
    



