
27,February,2004


    
       
      Uh oh, I have ensured the soiling of my reputation (if there is any) at school.  I have submitted not only one.. but TWO pictures of me playing Counter-Strike at a LAN party for the yearbook peeps.  Oh boy.  Why did I do that...? I'm not sure, but I guess it will be funny to look at in several years and say "Why oh why did I do that to myself."  And of course other people will still be laughing when they are middle-aged and still trucking along at whatever career they end up in.  Of course I had to go to "Xtremez II" (a nearby LAN cafe)  to play some CS with my usual buds.  It was awesome.  Although the competition isn't always very good.  It takes me forever to warm up though so I end up doing bad for about 10-15 minutes.  That's impressive for me!  Anyways, no one cares about this so I'll move on to the usual random crap.  You know that guy Macbeth?  I think some Bonespear guy or some (name here)spear or other wrote it... Hmm, the name escapes me... : )  MACTEST! MACTEST! MACTEST! *Banquo raises his outstretched grasping hand towards Macbeth out of the dinner platter*AH!  Not the final Macbeth test... MACFINAL!  *Keyzer slaps Drew and Colin in the chest repeatedly*  *Keyzer laughs far too much for his own actions*  By the way, for you geeks: New roll-up keyboard on the way soon to my humblehome from ThinkGeek.com: http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/input/keyboards/5a7f/  Que Chevere! Y Que Caliente!  Te amo Justo Lamas!  Boy, that concert was... neat!  What an awesome day, again!  Crew and school? Awesome at the same time? d00d!? I'm a geek.  I need that shirt proclaiming that....  I just have to have it. Someday. Well, either that or a gamer-type one, both links below *props to ThinkGeek.com*  http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/gaming/6119/ http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/generic/6111/  AND! El oh el??? : http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/kids/5ace/action/20ffd07/ 
      


26,February,2004


    
       
      Whooie! This week is almost over already.  I sure have been keeping busy with homework!  Must have blinded me to the time. Hmph.  Well, it sure is good that tommorow is Friday.  Fridays are always awesome! ALWAYS!  Got a few new games to keep me occupied in my free time:  Beyond Good & Evil -- in progress Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic -- in progress Need for Speed: Underground -- in progress Deus Ex 2: Invisible War -- beat in 3 days Prince of Persia 2 -- beat in 2 days  Contact me if you want any of the above and I can get you the goods!  And for those of you that have no interest whatsoever, just ask me to yell out something random and it's bound to be... HILARIOUS! AH! Well, you already knew that... I mean Keyzer can only say things that are... AWESOME! Or... HILARIOUS! AH!  iSearch was coolio.  I need to see my grade on it.  Soon.  Now!  Curse you Mr. Webster and your darned baby taking attention from us oh-so-good students and our work! BAH!  Oh, I have to shout kudos! This time to myself!  Kudos to Keyzer for passing out on migraine medication!  Luckily I'd rather be sleeping like a dead man than having that crummy migraine again... I just said crummy. Cool.  Rad!  Later my friends.
      


23,February,2004


    
       
      Well, today was mildly interesting.  Not really much out of the ordinary besides a newly found large amount of homework upon arrival back to school.  I've managed to get such an inordinate amount that I am unable to attend crew for the day.  : /  I really hate missing practice although I'm unsure if my coach is there today or not... either way missing practice is no fun, especially on a "row day" (in which we row of course).  The most prominent of this homework is the iSearch paper (boy, that sounds Mac-ish) which entails quite a bit of, well, searching.  Primarily tedious research.  I happened to choose Counter-Strike and some other elements of the online game industry and it has so far turned out fairly informative and interesting indeed.   I just bought a new mouse and i love it to death:  Microsoft Wireless Optical Mouse (Metallic Red).  The metallic red color matches my PC's case quite well.  In addition the scroll wheel (also tilts from side-to-side; Microsoft's tilt-wheel technology) is just major sexah.  Grips well in my hand; very contoured.  I h3arts t3h mu0s3!  Go buy one.  Now!!  And now the homework.  There still remains much to do.  See most of you soon and chat with the rest of you later. Tah Tah.
      


19,February,2004


    
       
      Yarg! Bikeriding is awesome.  I managed to cake about 2 or 3 pounds of mud on me today when I went out bikeriding with a good crew friend of mine.  Afterwards we proceeded to practice and had to work out a whole bunch, as usual.  That was all in good fun, especially when we show up at practice covered in such a rediculous amount of mud.  Whew!  I shall soon have Deus Ex 2 for those of you who know of it.  Should be a decent game.  I'm sure it can't live up to it's predecessor though. w00t.  Deus Ex was awesome!  I heart Kate, again. (Sorry I had to do it)  Boy, what an emotional blog.  I love it.  See most of you back at school pretty soon.  I'm trying not to think of it at the moment! ; D
      


14,February,2004


    
       
      Boy, this break has been quite good.  Of course I have to send kudos to someone, so that would have to be San Juan School District... I never thought I'd do that but hey, what the heck, they're truly good people in the long run and I'm feeling generous with my positive compliments.  In addition, props to crew for keeping me busy. Heh.  Life is pretty good.  Uh oh, slipping into one of those blogs... Yeck, my blog is better, well as of now.  Although I have been sorta busy over the break with crew and all so I haven't had much of a chance to post...  Yet somehow when I have school I always seem to find some time.  Odd.  I'm really appreciating this break.  It's awesome.  All it needs is a huge LAN party of some sort! w00t! I'm still realizing I'm off from school and how awesome that is...  Although I sure have noticed that I'm much more full of energy at 10am instead of darned 7am in the morning.  The sun being fully over the horizon in the morning is a very good thing.  No more cold.  Anyways,  I have to shout at Christina:  Good luck on the quest for erm... you know ;) May!?!? Geez! Well.  I = Never. w00t. :)
      


14,February,2004


    
       
      Oh the joys of Valentine's Day.... *sighs*  Love is in the air, everywhere I look around!  (You know that song...)  Well,  today was eventful indeed.  Had a good row in the morning at 7 and then went with all my teammates to have some breakfast at Gold Miners Cafe I believe it was (in folsom)... Dang!  That food was gooooood!  I highly recommend it to those who are interested in a great hle-in-the-wall breakfast and steak joint.  Gold Miners 

12,February,2004


    
       
      Boy, oh boy, oh boy! What a day-o!  Lots of stuff again, although less homework and time to play counter-strike! Very much yays, indeed.  (I went 40-4 for those who know what the heck I'm talking about) Also, good dayb at crew despite all the hard work.  Nothing as exciting as running around yelling "Gooooaaaaaalll!" though... That was just way awesome.  Although Brian found himself impersonating a young teenage angsty spanish girl.  That sure was good indeedy.  Anywhos, that darned Canadian National Rowing Team is making me feel odd everytime i casually say "Eh?" or "aboot". El oh el indeed.  Again, I just have to say that it isn't Sarah's birthday, just so she can pick on me for being way too excited about it.  Then again I'm scared to know what will happen when mine comes around and she has the chance to get me back for all of this.  http://members.shaw.ca/junksink/backtoschool2003/school.html  ^^^ Boy that was cool.  And comedic. 
      


10,February,2004


    
       
      Yarrr... Pirates are awesome, my day was somewhat similar accomplishment wise.  Got stuff done in school and finished most of my homework in class, which is always good.  Crew was hard! AGH! Tuesdays at crew are defined by being hard and generally lame... well, feel lame at least.  Gotta chug down that Endurox 4! Faster and better recovery and 55% better performance for your next workout! BOY! How could I refuse a slogan like that!  I mean Nukacola is pretty cool, but 55% better performance!? Whoo, count me in.  SPEAKING OF NUKACOLA!: Today's required presentations in Spanish class were quite the comedical event.  Lots of screw ups and unexpected things that end up hilarious.  And then there was me and my buddy... Heh, running around the class with a "NUKACOLA" sign over my head screaming "Gooooooooaaaaaaaallll!!!!", refering to the anouncer from hispanic soccer games that is of course.  Boy I rock.  So does that senor who gets to yell that all the time.  If only that was my job... Sarah's birthday is over. *shrugs* My birthday is long to come unfortunately. : /  The coming break should be quite a good one.  I could definately use a break.  Kudos to San Juan School District for a random February Break! I heart school... mostly.  Well, I just heart the people in it! Yay.  By the way, someone have a parteh!  I could definitely go for some celebration... of anything! w00t!  And in conclusion, Jon still has homework to go! Got to write some engililil'... ish!
      


09,February,2004


    
       
      Kate, I heart you! Homework is fun! Essays rock! I am awesome. Yay.  Macbeth rocks.  Especially the biker version of Macbeth.  Macbeth sure gives me the hots. : )  Drink Nukacola! 5x the caffeine than coffee! It's like a Nuke in your friggin' stomach!! AHH! 
      


07,February,2004


    
       
      Well, what an awesome day! Amazing for a Mond-AY! w00t.  Well, did quite a bit today.  Lots of work in class, a test in one of those... crew was reasonably challenging.  Homework is awlays good fun too eh?  Speaking of eh, the Canadian National Rowing Team has bunked up here in Sacramento to use our great lake.  Eh? I wonder what they are all aboot?  They sure are fast that's for sure.  Kudos to them. : )  Brak Show was good yesterday. Adult Swim is hilarious if you know of it, and if you don't: you sure should know!  http://www.adultswim.com/  Check it out! It's t3h aw3s0me!11! BY THE WAY: SARAH'S BIRTHDAY!!! KUDOS KUDOS KUDOS! Give her a high five!
      


07,February,2004


    
       
      I just did the newb double post! w00t! I pwn at blogging. El oh el.
      


06,February,2004


    
       
      Gah! What a toasty day of rowing (or "erging" for those who understand) and shopping and etc. busy-ness! WHOO! I heart shopping sad to admit.  For some reason I have been cursed with the craving to go and buy something new to spice up the day by day incessant and repetitive activities of my life.  It works though and I stay pretty happy. w00t. Anyways,  I have little to say but that of anticipation for the dreaded Monday... I mean, I get to see all my awesome friends and go back to crew practice!  In addition there is always room for not only Jello, but also Counter-Strike (pwnz0rz). 
      


06,February,2004


    
       
      Today was quite the Thursday... Oh wait a minute... IT'S FRIDAY!!! AHHHH!!! Well then! One awesome Friday down and a whole bunch to go.  Despite that this Friday was uneventful, I still remain suspended in anticipation for my race tomorrow, for crew that is.  Gotta get carbo-loaded tonight as I did yesterday.  Hopefully this shall assist my race to, well, victory. Boy, this week sure went fast.  Meanwhile I sit here wondering what all the people at the school dance are doing.  They must be having an awesome time and I better shout out some kudos to them in the future for going, as I did not obviously.  Dances are awesome! Keyzer is awesome! w00t!  See you later my friends.  Remember: All my base are belong to you!
      


05,February,2004


    
       
      Well, the day that Keyzer started a Blog finally tis' come. And now for my February mating season cheer:  Roses are red, Violets are blue, All my bases are belong to you.
      


29,March,2004


    
       
      "Winter JLAN!" Party Roster:  Name	PC	HL	Confirmation Me	Yes 	Yes	Yes Dave	Yes 	Yes	Yes Mark	Yes 	No	Yes Joel	?	No	Yes Dan	Yes	Yes	Yes Joe	Yes	Yes	Yes Scott M.	Yes	Yes	Yes Alex	Yes	Yes	Yes 1-5pm Derek 	Yes	Yes	Yes Brian	Yes	Yes	Yes Robby	No	Yes	Yes David	Yes	Yes	Yes  Scott Hathaway	?	No	? Matt Gandley	Yes	No	?  I assume that the "Spring Break LAN-A-Thon in Keyzer's Garage" roster will expand somewhat (2-3 people) from this but will remain the same as to the core "always-there " people.  Looking forward to seeing all you "JLAN!" (Jon's Local Area Network, naturally) people back around here!
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      My definition of LAN party:  This is defined as a generally large gathering of computer-savvy gamers (A.K.A. nerds, geeks, and etc.) who find competing with each other over a Local Area Network environment very entertaining and rewarding.  During this event players join in a marathon of gaming in a single location which typically is small and places players close together for ultimate efficiency and playability.  LAN competition is found to be largely more satisfying to the player due to the ability to interact with other players as they are in close proximity.  This almost always involves several key events which happen in a clear chain-reaction order:  1. Player becomes frustrated due to a loss.  2.  Player removes keyboard from a nearby computer.  3. Player commences bludgeoning an opposing teammate with the device.  4.  Minor injuries result.  5.  Much commotion and conviviality
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      Whooo! Keyzer is pulling another crazy insomniac all-nighter! w00t w00t!  Wish you all could experience the thrill of living off guarana and caffeine from energy drinks (and Mountain Dew of course) and doing homework at 4 in the morning!  *mutters* and playing games...  *cough*  Anywho,  I'll see everyone in the morning and that'll be awesome. wah00t (copyright Jon Keyzer, since he created the term wah00t)  h00t h00t.
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      http://www.frozencpu.com/cgi-bin/frozencpu/ram-06.html  Boy, I can't wait til' these get here in the mail!  Wasting blog space... El oh el.  Bad habit.  Oh well, this is definately awesome enough to show you geeks out there.
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      http://www.frozencpu.com/  fan-79 Quad Orange UV LED 80mm Fan   ram-06 ThermalTake Copper Memory Cooling Kit   1 $12.00 $12.00   flc-24 80mm Radioactive Laser Cut Grill  1 $11.00 $11.00   scr-08 Black Heavy Duty Fan Screw  Select Color: Black 4 $0.25 $1.00   Tailed Blue LED 1 $1.00 $1.00  pad-07 Mouse Skatez   1 $4.00 $4.00   pad-12 Bawls Guarana   1 $1.99 $1.99   bad-01 FrozenCPU.com Case Badge   1 $3.00 $3.00  
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      FROZENCPU ORDER ON THE WAY! OMG! w00t!
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      w00t.  watched Apocalypse Now!  That was a neat movie.  Also watched The Believer.  That was a pretty good movie.  I suggest both movies to you all.  Although they are both very "R-ish", meaning they have significant amounts of "R" content if that bothers you at all.  Otherwise they are awesome! w00t w00t.  LAN party in spring break is coming fast! W0W!  Got some new holes in my knuckles from aggression drill at crew with a punching bag (heavy bag, that is).  Bareknuckle; it was fun.  Lots of adrenaline flowing; blood followed close after.  Yay.
      


25,March,2004


    
       
      Cool:  http://www.chris.com/ascii/
      


23,March,2004


    
       
      Uh oh! Emo-BLOG!  Disclaimer!  (Well, for this one post that is!)  There are 5 parts of my life:  1.  School 2.  Crew 3.  Computers + PC Games 4.  Social: Friends + Girls  Status of each:  1.  Bad Grades 2.  Slow,  Not one of the 20/23 selected for races (I'm one of the three not going)  despite high "arguablility" 3.  A-Okay 4.  Quite bad; tired of other people, especially girls; particular people of course; friends losing interest slowly Crew ties in here also as I have.... HAD many crew friends.  Now I just serve as a backdrop for conversations.  or maybe a scapegoat for accidents or mistakes.  Currently, if I lose my computer,  I don't have anything left to enjoy.  In summary:  Death is appealing!  See you all!  Don't worry:  I'm not a statistic yet.
      


23,March,2004


    
       
      Lah Lah Lah!  What a good start to the week!  It seems to be gong pretty fast and that is always good!  Spring break is just around the bend and I'm sure I'll accept its arrival quite well.  Indeed I think I will be having a LAN parteh over the break... I hope.  Ah, I am pretty sure I will so you can all count on it! w00t!  New computer hardware is a'nearing! w00t!  Custom case mods and a new GFX card in about 1-2 months.  Yarr.  And for those of you non-techies:  JUNIOR PROM IS SO CLOSE!! AHHH!!! I have no idea who I will ask, but I know I will know when the time comes.  I hope.  :)  Anywho,  AP testing is also coming up along with SATs (for me that is) and that is bad, badder, more bad, and baddest.  I now I have to zombie my way over to my math homework for the evening.  Yays.
      


20,March,2004


    
       
      Whew!  Another pretty cool yet busy week!  I ended up working straight through all of the weeknights and wasn't able to post.  Oh well, you can all understand why!  Way too much homework! AGH!  Anyways,  I'm on a craze of Yngwie Malmsteen, awesome 80's era Polish guitarist!  He is so awesome!  Arguably the best of the faster-paced guitarists.  He has some pretty amazing solos...  Arpeggios from Hell! w00t  (One of his famous songs).  In other news,  quite a long Saturday...  Had to get up for crew race at 3:30, although, it was definitely worth it.  It was quite arduous but it was fun indeed.  I speak for the whole team when I say that crew instills an undeniable feeling of camaraderie in us.  And that feeling is surely not misfounded.  We've all become one big family.  Oh joy!  "Could you get that, thanks alot."  -- Rocko's Modern Life  Pre-teen nostalgia again.  Yay.
      


13,March,2004


    
       
      Crew race was today.  I think I performed well, especially so when you consider that i went to bed at 1am after the dance and had to wake up at 5:45am.  It was swell.  I did get a little sunburn though, but that is natural since I'm just a whee fair Irish boy.  Chipotle and Jamba Juice afterwards makes all the soreness and sunburn better! WHOO!  Food is awesome.  See y'all!
      


12,March,2004


    
       
      THAT DANCE WAS AWESOME! DOOOOOOOOOD!!!  Cheers to everyone that one was there, I had a FRIGGIN' BLAST WHOOOO!!!!  I hope I got to see everyone!  If I didnt yell at you and scream like a maniac that "This dance is awesome!", dont feel bad because there are way too many friends of mine for me to get to all of them! : D  w00t w00t!  I love you all!  Kudos to all my beloved friends, AGAIN!  (especially all my long buds:  Ryan,  Dan, Brad, and Colin!)  And now all I have to do is wait for another one!! AHHHH!!!  To the bed!  *ZzZzZ*
      


11,March,2004


    
       
      Humm de dumm... Here comes that sligtly emotional blog entry you have all been waiting for: I wonder how long this being single thing will be cool.  I guess I'll eventually get lonely, but what is more challenging is the trying to not think about the possibility that you have made a mistake... Hmph.  Well, I'm still in the process of figuring out where my mind lays upon this subject.  I still think much of my previous long-time accomplice... but yet I know that some things were wrong and remain so... yet do they truley overcome the significant good aspects?  Hmmm...  How long can I last without that something that I always felt before...  When will I fully feel the lack and leap back to old habits?  Peace out brothas... Oh wait, Keyzer is white.  Yeah.  Cya my fellow geeks and etc.
      


10,March,2004


    
       
      dood... For the third time.  Being single is awesome, but getting a migraine before a critical crew practice is not.  I'm on some intense medication so I need to get to bed before I pass out again  (Yes, it has happened before!) *sighs*  Good night y'all.
      


09,March,2004


    
       
      dood. again. Pretty cool day... although I did happen to end a quite extended relatonship with one of those girl-thingy-things.  You know the ones that dance and are mesmerizingly (is that a werd... werd!) beautiful often times.  Hum de dumm, I guess I'll be diving into the pool of feminine bachelors again.  I better watch my back! w00t!  Oh well, this isn't sad; it was inevitabe. *sigh*  Well,  outside of this, I've been awesome... Just thinking about me being single is AWESOME!  No regrets! w00t!  I've never really had any short term relationships so this should be fun.  Oops, back on girls again.  Ah, well I love them just like you all do inside.  Anywho,  not much else new... JUNIOR YEAR IS ALMOST OVER! OMGs! El oh el. If im this crazy this year... just imagine next year... WHOOOO!  And of course, my quote of the day: "Double the spouses, double the fun!"  And I'm off!  ...to games again of course : )
      


08,March,2004


    
       
      dood.  Mountain Dew Amp is... AWESOME!  And so is getting home after long days of school + crew.  I find the ability to sit down after such work all day incredibly rewarding.  Boy, sitting down and relaxing after a good workout.. WHEW! I'm doing it right now and I say:  "Who needs alcohol when you can get the same dizziness and buzz from running a little too hard! DUDE!"  Oh wait, alcohol has flavor.  Crap.  :) But! What the heck do I know about alcohol! I'm JON FREAKIN' KEYZER! DOOOOOD!  That sounds good... You know putting strange and repulsive "-ing" adjectives in the middle of my name.  JON MUCKRAKIN' KEYZER!  JON FUNKIN KEYZER!  Oh my, I think I'm done. WHEW!  See you all... again!  w00tz to 4|| !11!
      


07,March,2004


    
       
      And whilst I am writing this entry, my Dad commences his rant that somehow the only way to do homework on a weekend is right after you get it...  For some reason I disagree...  And now I must make up for my father's inability to do anything by doing all of his duties myself whilst he remains inside and reads the newspaper casually.  Note that he does not have a job...  Well then,  what a cool morning... err... afternoon entry.  Playing games late and waking up when the sun is fully out is awesome.  I just HAD to say that something at least was awesome.  Indeedy.  Off to my chores and homework and other bland tasks!  See you all soon! (Darned Sunday!)
      


01,March,2004


    
       
      Boy, good ol' migraine today.  Missed school but managed to make it to crew since I felt well enough to go at least.  Not much got done today,  just alot of resting/sleeping.  I managed to sleep for about 13-14 hours last night since I had woke up and taken migraine medication, which of course makes one very drowsy.  I felt myself pass out.  That was awesome!  I have to bring up a great quote given to me by my brother and spoken by one of his friends:  "I almost died.  It was awesome."  See y'all!  P.S.  ThinkGeek junk is on the way! w00t!
      


27,April,2004


    
       
      Yay, new OS up and running, RedHat Linux 9, and this time it is much more superior than my Windows (windoze) installation, and as opposed to other Linux distros, on my other HD.....  ANYWAYS for non-geeks who did not understand anything that I just mentioned:  Computer was not working properly again!  What bad luck!  Que lastima, as we would say in Spanish class.  Things are going ok over here in JonLand TM!  LegoLand is offering much competiton, but my big blocks of hulking steel arms beat their inferior little colored hollow blocks.  YAR!!  Crew meets (regattas) have been going fairly well recently, as has the rest of our racing season.  We have been dong exceptionally great this year.  It seems that we have outdone prior years in number of victories and excellence by significant margins.  This is definitely measurable in how god darn sore I have been ALL year! HARD WORK = SLEEP + EAT MORE!  In other news:  Ryans blog/"xanga" gets assaulted by some anonymous person or other.... most likely a "close friend" or other of his.  Boy, I love how we can make fun of each other over the internet and cause much commotion, and often harm.  If only I could trace the IP... : ) Well, we all know Ryan is a great guy in the end and I'm with him 'til hell freezes over!  Whoever did "this" to Ryan should tell him in person, especially if they want to just ridicule him.  I mean, people, if you are going to try and "hurt" someone do it directly to them!  Boot to the head!  Last but not least, gotta study up for those APUSH tests coming up!  Especially the official AP test near the end of May... I think it is.  Kudos to all t3h friends, later!
      


21,April,2004


    
       
      Yarg.  I've been pretty sick.  Which can again account for lack of updates here.  For those of you who actually do read this stuff.  Which probably isn't that many people.  Oh wells.  I need to add a comment option so you all can leave notes for me! : D Anywho, darn flu has got me down.  Haven't been able to egt to crew for 3 days! OH NOS! I might die from that!  ARR!  Played way way way too much CS with Joey "[Hung]M4Galore" Hensler today.  I just pubbed for about 5 hours straight AFTER 2 hours of vietnam!  Boy, how fun!  El oh el.  Im suck a dork-boy.  See y'all at sch00l.
      


18,April,2004


    
       
      AH! My darned western digital hard drive died on me for a short period of time.  I had to swap my HD into another PC to recover all my stuff and then wipe it clean for a new install.  Lame.  Now its working... so far.  *crosses fingers*  Well, that accounts for my lack of posting last week.  Didn't have the time to fix anything.  Yay for the weekend!  Race went well on Saturday.  We did exceptionally well.  Lots of pain but also fun.  You always feel good after, despite the soreness and all.  Good satisfaction factor.  Oh and I have to post this stuff.  Dan Schuchbaur quotes:  Dan:  "PCI is just as good as your AGP 8x, Jon.  Why the hell would I need AGP, my games run fine, that's all I need." -- 1 week later -- Dan:  "What the hell Jon?  Why won't my system run Deus Ex 2?" Jon:  "PCI?"  Dan:  "Jon, face it, I'm better than you at Counter-Strike.  Oh, by the way, how do I defuse the bomb?"  Dan:  "My graphics card is dead.  I need to buy a new one.  I won't bother fixing it or looking at it.  It's just dead."  ---  Ryan Neal quotes:  Ryan:  "Halo is the best FPS ever!"  (Hilarious enough in itself) Jon:  "You have no room to speak Ryan, you don't play PC FPSes because you claim we 'sucky PC gamers' need to upgrade our computers every time a game comes out.  It is decent, but how can you judge the one FPS you have played as the best?" Ryan:  "Dude, Halo is better than anything, shutup stupid PC gamer." --1/2 year later-- Ryan:  "Xbox is so dumb.  PS2 will always be the best."
      


11,April,2004


    
       
      LAN parteh was pretty coolio.  I think everybody there had a lot of fun and we managed to not play only Counter-Strike!  We actually played some Unreal Tournament 2003!  Wow!  Well, it was all tons o' fun (and Mountain Dew).  Now I have to get t wrk for school tommorow!  Ah!  Such a short break!  The break sure went fast, especially when you are in anticipation of the Saturday before it ends.  : /  Oh well, see you all!  GG!
      


08,April,2004


    
       
      Painkilller for PC is out and in my hands today!! AHH!
      


08,April,2004


    
       
      Boy oh boy, this break is awesome!  Lots of fun stuff to do (between crew practices that is).   Playing new games and going out with friends. w00t.  I haven't really posted lately with good reason:  I'm so friggin' busy! AHHH!!  Anyways,  I hope all your breaks are going well as mine is.  Get some darned sleep!  Its good for you!  Updates on the party on saturday:  12pm - 10pm; Garage; about 10 people w/ PCs as of the moment, possibly more or less  I'm not particularly organized this time as I planned it in a very short time period.  Oh well, whoever shows up, shows up!  Get ready for some awesome gaming for those of you who are sure on going!  And to all the people at school and etc. : Spend all the days of break well!  REALLY! Only so many left... just don't think about it too much!
      


31,May,2004


    
       
      Well, its working out to be a pretty long day here at home.  I haven't done anything yet but troubleshoot some problem I am having with my new Linux upgrade.  I have upgraded from Redhat 9 to Fedora Core 2 and it has worked out quite well except for a few things:  1. I cant boot into Windoze yet... 2. I need to get my nvidia video card drivers to work for games...  Been working on it all day.  Arg.  Otherwise I have all my normal apps working and then some.  The install went quite well and it seems to be faster and much improved compared to my previous Redhat 9 OS.  The Bluecurve theme for GNOME2 is truly beautiful.  http://www.linuxjournal.com/article.php?sid=6476  http://www.bluecurve.tk/
      


29,May,2004


    
       
      Leninade rocks!  http://leninade.com/  A Taste Worth Standing In Line For!!!
      


29,May,2004


    
       
      And now it begins!  Good little start to the weekend.  Played some games and got out with a few friends.  Gotta  get together with English group for video project... also need to buy me a firewire card.  In fact I think I'm about to go retrieve one soon.  Best Buy WHOOO! :)  You all 1337.  GG. --knargz0r 
      


26,May,2004


    
       
      School movie project work was quite awesome today.  Our group for the video gathered at a friend's house and we managed to get the largest part of the project done (arguabley the largest part): the story/storyboard.  What we have made is quite complex and impressive.  I didn'tthink we could produce such a masterpeice in a matter of three hours.  The script which we shall soon compile will surely be awesome!  w00t!  Cheers to Happy Tree Friends (.com) for filling in all that extra time between hard work with heaping amounts of that essential excessive gore we all need in our fabulous American lives!  I can  finally  fill that uncomfortable gap with relatives with a pile of severed human ( and small animals ) limbs and organs!  YAY!   Anywho, our script is essentially a twist on a neat blend of these films:  Ronin, Snatch, Lock Stock & Two Smoking Barrels, Pulp Fiction, and The Professional!  Oh joy!  Can't wait to brace myself between walls, my back against the ceiling, just waiting to ambush unsuspecting evil minions a la silenced Walther P99.  Indeed.
      


25,May,2004


    
       
      Hooray for Tuesday!  Frankly, nothing happened.  Drank some Jolt... for breakfast (100mg caffeine/12oz).  That woke me up.  Went to school.  Did homework.  Ate.  Slept.  How exciting!  Although... ordered my stuff from SplitReason:  Hammer & Sickle Cap: "Get yours today and remind the world of that little thing we call MAD (mutually assured destruction.)"  +  Kill Bill Linux T-Shirt: For years now Linux has fought the good fight in the OS war, only to be thwarted time and time again by their arch nemesis: Microsoft. After numerous strategic attacks resulted in failure, the Linux community realized they had to take extreme measures to avoid extinction. Their last hope for survival was devised, a prophecy was told, a solution presented, the last line of defense: Kill Bill. Grab yours today!  +  Hammer & Sickle "HTTP" T-Shirt: For the little Internet communist inside all of us, this spoof http shirt with the Hammer and Sickle logo is bound to catch some looks. If you're one of those that feel enlightened and feel compelled to flame people in a message board, this is a stylish, rugged, 100% cotton t-shirt. 
      


24,May,2004


    
       
      Just another monday!  Well, it was a little abnormal in that I purchased a huge amount of caffeine beverages from Beverages & More.... but otherwise it was ust the usual monday.  I managed to finish my homework during the day and ended up with a good amount of freetime.  Oh joy.  I think airsoft gun is in the mail...  YAY!
      


23,May,2004


    
       
      Good day!  Whoooooooo!  Well, frankly, nothing much happened but I sure did get a really good amount of sleep and woke up fresh, even after staying up so late.  Played around on computer for half of the day, had some hotdoggies for dinner and then had some icecream after from Cold Stone! WHOO!  Mint icecream with gummie bears  is the most awesomest thing since awesome was awesomely invented!  Lil John is the coolest rapper ever!  Thanks Chappelle's Show!  YYYEEEAAAAAAH!!!!  WWWWWWHHHHAAAAT!!?!?! OOOOKKKAAAAAAAAAY!  Brak ranks pretty high up there too in the comedy business, ya'll check that out:  http://www.adultswim.com/  Later alligators!
      


22,May,2004


    
       
      Today was not too fast of a day, and that is a good thing since it is indeed the weekend.  The weather was great and I hope you all went out and ran around in its pleasant feeling.  My brother and I went out to the park down the street and played frisbee for agood while prior to dinner.  I claened up and such around the house as usual.  Also worked on getting some programs in Linux to work right.  I was able to get LimeWire and BitTorrent working, which is very good for p2p (peer-to-peer file-sharing network) addicts like me!  Watched a bit of Mystery Science Theater.  Funny stuff, check it out sometime!  
      


19,May,2004


    
       
      I have been beta-testing Google's Gmail for quite some time now and I like it!  Alot!  I wish to persuade you all to send me messages at my new account instead of my older, lamer hotmail account!    My new account is: knargz0r@gmail.com
      


19,May,2004


    
       
      Fast week for me, but it sure was a pretty good one.  Got alot of school stuff done and had alot of fun with all of the friends, etc.  Karoake was pretty decent today... just about uhh... *looks at watch* 3 hours ago I guess.   Got to watch Formula One at Monaco on the HUGE flatscreens the had there!  That was quite amazing!  Although the place was a sports bar and i guess they are known for such things as huge TVs... I haven't been to a sports bar before. I was also pretty darn tired while I was at the karoake but it didn't matter much, the social element was relaxing mostly and I just wanted to see everyone again.  That was good of course. :/  Linux is going very very well!  Yay!  Heroes of Might and Magic III is a big thumbs up so far, although I just got it.  :)  See you all later --Jonny
      


19,May,2004


    
       
      Marcus's site for all of you that might be interested!:  http://www.marcusgoesusa.de.vu/
      


17,May,2004


    
       
      Great Apparel from SplitReason.com! :  http://www.splitreason.com/productdetail.php?id=99  http://www.splitreason.com/productdetail.php?id=86
      


17,May,2004


    
       
      Well, I just accidentally hit the browser back button and mistakenly hit the new post button again... Bloggers know what that means:   NO MORE OF THE TEXT YOU JUST SPENT 30 MINUTES WRITING! AHHHHH!!!!   *Sighs*  I hate when I do darn crap like that... Oh well, it was a PEBKAC: Problem Exists Between Keyboard And Chair.  The Official PEBKAC Shirt: http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/sysadmin/6692/  Boy, lots of darn projects to do within these last few weeks of school!  Although the English end-of-year video assignment/project will be  awesome , especially considering that I will most likely play the role of a transcendentalist hitman!  WHOO!  I'm ordering an airsoft gun for the project (and for general fun to slap on the table and shoot kiddies with).  ...Walther P99 Heavyweight w/ Tactical Mounts/System (Scope + Silencer).   OH NOS! 
      


17,May,2004


    
       
      Had to go to the annual crew banquet this year in which we all give our last goodbyes to the seniors and reminisce of all the events of the year.  And of course look forward to the next for those of us who are returning, which is most of us.  Yay!  I dont want to miss everyone, that would be sad. : /  Nothing much else going on besides a few projects coming up...  My Junior Video Final Project will surely  be awesome.  Im planning on doing some underground sort of stuff: social engineering, encryption stuff, cracking Windows passwords and stuff (and of course some other how-to's that all of us criminal mischiefs need).  You know, "thebroken.org" style: http://www.thebroken.org/  
      


15,May,2004


    
       
      Pretty awesome start into the weekend.  Not much to do really, but I think I really need a weekend to relax for once.  Way too much has gone on in the past few weeks AND weekends!  Especially true when I have crew alongside that huge amount of testing.  Oh well, in the end it only does me good, especially when it comes to college admissions and such.  I think as of now I want to go nto computer science of some sort or another.  I'm not totally sure of course.  I doubt anyone is.  There is no place like 127.0.0.1  Some sweet geek/gamer apparel:  http://www.splitreason.com/  
      


13,May,2004


    
       
      For the geeks:  Contact me if you want some of my Redhat 9 Shrike screenshots.  I have CVSWineX with Steam working great along with UT2k3 and UT2k4 if y'all are interested.  GNOME 2.6 

12,May,2004


    
       
      Yay for minimum days! Or maybe as previously known for those of you who have went to elementary or middle school with me: mini-mini days!  YAY!  Today was good fun, not alot of school and a whole lot of freetime considering there isn't anymore crew practice which is *smiley face* and *frowney face*.  :D / :(  Oh well, games will keep me busy all day as usual... and darned homework...  Arrr.  See y'all tommorow.  --Jonz0r
      


12,May,2004


    
       
      Great geek blog, also generally funny for everyone though:  http://www.kevinrose.com/  Good stuff, especially that of the "dog riding skateboard" footage. Boy, that is quite humorous, especially when the dog rides a skateboard better than you can.  ... Captain Jean-Luc Picard, U.S.S. Enterprise.... ;D  w00t! w00t!
      


11,May,2004


    
       
      Funniest thing I have seen this year on the internet:  http://picard.ytmnd.com/  Captain Jean-Luc Picard, USS Enterprise!!!11!!  w00t w00t!  In other pressing news:  UT2k4 (Unreal Tournament 2004) for Linux/Windows (I'm running the Linux version) is clearly a 10/10 game out of my book!  Essentially a very well re-done UT2k3 (Unreal Tournament 2003) with alot of additional content that really makes it a stellar game.  In more pressing news:  Nothing to do in AP US History! YAYS! Props to Mr. Erickson for being awesome and making us work so hard and in turn leaving us with a good amount of time to essentially just hang out during class! YAYS!  --Lates, Jonz0r
      


10,May,2004


    
       
      Yays, phatty new site revamp!  *notices the lack of posts lately*  Oh well!  I blame it all on the linux situation + having so much testing in the past few weeks...   Rowing practice has come to an end... for now that is.  I have no idea what to do with my time.  It's odd.  Very odd.  I might have to settle down and play some games.  Championships (for rowing) was quite a good bit of fun! Whoo!  Our team did well and of course we're all happy as usual.  Enormous amount of satisfaction from working so hard for two days of non-stop rowing and related activity i.e. sleep, eat, practice, warm-up, prepare, etc.  Lots of joviality!  Yays.  Less crew -

30,June,2004


    
       
      http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=pwned
      


29,June,2004


    
       
      Summer has been going along pretty well.  Not too eventful but still fun.  I don't have that much to do now but I'm sure I'll be working sometime soon.  I hope that I can get a job at Starbucks as I have previously planned.  The job fair is coming up and it is apparently a pretty easy process to get through from what I have heard.  There is a fairly new industrial rock band that I have grown quite a liking for:  Starfall.  Their music is pretty unique and I have gone to the extent of developing a background/wallpaper of my own for their band.  The GIMP is a great  program to do this in...  I'm getting alot more experience in it lately.  I also have been honing my Warcraft III 1337 skills!  :)  http://www.starfallonline.co.uk/  
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      It's been a while again, yet not much has happened.  I have been sitting about in my cave of a house, sitting at this very computer (err computers) and making my linux experience all the more enjoyable.  I have ran into many problems but they have all been tackled for the most part.  I'm enjoying the great freedom of open-source and the great support that comes along.  Windows is left pretty far in the dust compared to what I have going here.  The upgrade from Redhat 9 to Fedora Core 1 on my primary system went very well.  Fedora seems much more powerful, and elegant actually.  The bluecurve theme is once again beautiful.  KDE still sucks.  Heh.  In other news:  I hit my mom's car.  It was an accident.  Backed out of driveway and car was parked a little bit closer than usual.  Oops.  Oh well, it's minor and is very fixable.  The only issue is the amount which it will cost.  But that is okay; anything to make mother happy, right?  Marcus' goodbye party is tommorow.  That'll be fun I'm sure.  Whooo!  GG.  --Jon Jon
      


16,June,2004


    
       
      Well, this is pretty neat:  I have an extra computer now and its role is solely for that of chatting and browsing.  It has worked out quite well.  I am running Fedora Core 2 on it and it has been very stable so far.  Xchat and gAIM are going to be running 24/7 now! :)  Summer remains pretty uneventful.  I haven't really gotten to do much besides go and play games at the local LAN joint and visit with a few friends.  I have gotten in touch with some friends I have not spoke to in a long time, which is always pretty awesome.  Got alot of catchign up to do of course, been about a year.  I'll be seeing most of you around!  Whoooo!  Summer has only begun!
      


14,June,2004


    
       
      Boy, the year is over.  I don't know what to do now.  Had the LAN parteh yesterday.  That was quite awesome!  w00t w00t!11!  So coolio.  Thanks to all the peeps who came and made it possible.  The PC count was 14 this time.  Good stuff.  Biggest LAN yet this year.  And ever really!  Whoo! GG.  I'm already starting to miss those leaving for college this year.  *sniffle*  See you all around this summer!  Contact me!  You all know how!
      


04,June,2004


    
       
      Ahoy matey... Let's find out how long I can go without posting... Hmmm.  I guess it will probably be something like a couple more days considering how busy I am with school ending and teachers cramming in finals: tests and projects alike.  Hopefully after this year is over I can have some time to lay out and do whatever I want.  I need a job though.  Hmph.  Oh well, I'm really going to miss all of my beloved senior buddies.  *cry*   Diana Rios!  *sniffle*  And Brian Geist of course. : / As for all the juniors:  see you all next year!  It'll surely be awesome to be seniors finally and get to do nothing but have fun!  YAYS! 
      


31,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink http://www.battle.net/war3/ladder/W3XP-player-profile.aspx?Gateway=Lordaeron&amp;PlayerName=Knarg  
      


27,July,2004


    
       
      Yay for summer. Boo for its last breath! Agh! Almost sounds like Bella Vista's horrible attempt at "boos and bravos" in the school newspaper. WOW, biased? Noooo way! -.-   Bella Vista Class of 2005 - Chat is up at #bv05 oon EFnet! Come out of your caves IRC peeps!       So, I really want to see everyone again, yet summer ending is never good news. At least I can have a LAN party before the close of our vacation. Contact me you hosers! I'm bored as heck in this cave of a house!  gg no re  --Commander Zargon.. errr Jon Keyzer    
      


27,July,2004


    
       
      And now begins the trek to complete Metal Gear Solid 2: Sons of Liberty!&nbsp; No food til end.&nbsp; Too gosu mgs play for that.&nbsp; Refer to urbandictionary.com definition of gosu:   urlLink http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=gosu&amp;r=f   Possibly better said as "too 1337 (leet)".&nbsp; GG NO RE NOOB!  Warcraft III: Frozen Throne madness ensues. 
      


24,July,2004


    
       
      Well, I have adopted a new oh-so-awesome hobby: bowling! whoooo!  So pro.  So leet.  Going tonight for sure around 9 for the 5-buck bowl-a-thon (a.k.a. all-you-can-bowl) at fireside.  That's gonna be awesome.  
      


18,July,2004


    
       
      Oh boy!&nbsp; I went ah' campin' and it was ah' fun!&nbsp; Clmbed alot of things... Waterfall...edge of a dam...&nbsp;few cliffs!&nbsp; Boy!&nbsp; I can't stop saying boy!&nbsp; But... boy... it was fun!&nbsp; Jumped in a cold mountain lake and did some rope swinging,which was pretty neat.&nbsp; Boy, (doh! said it again) I sure am hungry for some gooooood food!&nbsp; Camping food does not cut it for me!&nbsp; I ended up hungry 24/7!&nbsp; Oh wait, I always am hungry. Doh! &nbsp; In other news:&nbsp; Things remain slow at home besides the happy puppy (Pookie/Alex) I just came home too! &nbsp; Someone give me something to do!! AGHH!!!&nbsp; I should call to see if i have a job yet... Heh.&nbsp; Good idea, indeed.&nbsp; Then I can buy loads of junk all for myself.&nbsp; Yays.  gee gee, see you all, hopefully!   --Jonz0r 
      


14,July,2004


    
       
      Well, I have opened another blog on Xanga.com.  I am not really sure how much I will use it, but it will be easier for some people to post me comments and view my site.  I have linked this site from my Xanga blog, so I can see that many of you have probably found your way here via Xanga.  Blogger IS better, yes, but the advertising is better on Xanga apperently. Heh.  The people who use Xanga are generally the "aZn" computer numbskulls who cant manage anything but typing in a little box without any other "complications" at 35wpm.   HTML!?!? JAVA?!?!? I'm so dumb! I have no idea what that is! Cheers to computer illiteracy! pwned.  --B'Jon
      


10,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    m-m-monsterkill!
      


06,August,2004


    
       
      Wow, orientation was neat-o and I had a good amount of fun just being able to see the 10,000 people i have not seen over the summer.  I can't wait til' school starts... Oh wait, I can, but that thing that I can't wait for is seeing all my great friends everyday!  *cry* 
      


06,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    w00t
      


01,August,2004


    
       
      werd. neat picture of me.  
      


01,August,2004


    
       
      My fellow Americans,  Why vote when you can play the game?   urlLink http://www.ubi.com/US/Games/politicalmachine_pc.htm  
      



