
01,August,2004


    
       how did i get so lucky?  such a beautiful world.......  senseless killing of beautiful animals makes me sad  oh, and its not who you think it is. its not her either. 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       my friend the mummy, he is unravelling 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       and all my smile shields fall down 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       falling in love with the purple backpack 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       we are too proud (arrogant) to be inspired  a nation in despair: garfield parenting children 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       God's mistake? not possible.  closet full of failures to forget 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       so much for the friend-like questions i dont want to ask  i am a pathetic attempt at pride  we are one in everlasting peace says thom 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       all things flashing are cheap, dont trust flashing things 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       woman in a little girl's body?  i don't buy it, quit trying. you make me nauseous little girl 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       we're all terminal, none of us are going to make it 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
        it's better to be the suckee than the sucker  god forbid jesus be a woman, says mom   they're all just pieces of meat anyway (strikeout) 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       Elect Thrasher  there she goes with the strange hair, with the cow face girl (this is why i dont like her, cow face with a cow mind)  dirty man licking lips, watch the young try to be the old  why can't i do 21498715610235 x 12341487921374 ?? why? why?  im dumb.  thought the second grader.  dirty thoughts in a tired boy's head make good bedtime stories  nod and yawn, shut ears, nod and yawn  clumps on eyelashes, she lost her key, again, all i see is her eyelashes, dont wannna see the rest, the rest is with the key, again.  everyone wants to be him, thats why he makes me feel nervous 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       *pop* 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       *pop* 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       *pop* 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       *pop* 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i didnt  want  her to leave.  i wanted to explore the folds of that skirt. 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i am now part of a bureaucracy.  oh the horror! the horror! 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i am so sick of hearing her yap  shes a dramatic irony 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       im not amazed by her, im amazed by her beauty, its real, unique intoxicating and i need to remove it from my memory 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       shaking head, tryin to forget images of showers...not working, impossible  the will of the people is spoken, my will is broken 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       must vanquish the evil... so close! apathy kills my mission 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i misspelled two haha 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       its kind of like this: the beautiful false balcony that serves only two hide the ugly radiator. 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       what to do..now that i'm being bombarded by subliminal messages 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       once again, its just a matter of pride 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       intoxicated by yet another celebrity... 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       do they know that  i am sleeping on the inside ? 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       I hate it when somebody makes me feel shallow in comparison. I HATE it. 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       little spiders are always interupting my reading  storms are coming, yay for rain 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i had something to write about, but then stupid television sapped my brain. 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       the movie says there's a hero in all of us.&nbsp; i'm still waiting for mine to show his face.  
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       This isn't the way I want things to end between us  I'm waiting for something to happen 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
       i can see him just standing there in the water, watching me, and i know he's thinking, someday i'm gonna be one of those.  it's weird 
    
    


01,August,2004


    
         this place is thining out.  are my thoughts becoming more concrete?  no.  they just come fewer and far between.  at least thats what it feels like.   when it counts the most, i think i might be screwed.  will god save my ass again?    
    
    



