
26,May,2004


    
        urlLink This  seems extremely interesting and i wish i could attend. But alas! no money nor the disposition to make such a long flight. 
    
    


24,May,2004


    
       Why cant some people get along? At least for their fans sake.. I mean who cares about  urlLink their  personal lives.  
    
    


24,May,2004


    
        urlLink this   is one sad story to come to on monday. 
    
    


19,May,2004


    
       alright! bring in the  urlLink  Nudy  reporters! 
    
    


18,May,2004


    
        urlLink tile machine 1.0  has got to be one of the funnest things online right now. If you're a fan of pixel art like me anyways... 
    
    


17,May,2004


    
       For an e mail account with  urlLink Gmail  
    
    


17,May,2004


    
        urlLink she shouldve went to culebra.  
    
    


12,May,2004


    
       Im not a big fan of politics, in fact I think its the worst subject to talk about (alongside religion and poetry) which are all so beyond subjective its almost imposible to agree on more than one fact. But  urlLink Michael Moore  does make it intereseting (IMO).   Again he's being attacked. And that just makes me want to see his film even more.  
    
    


12,May,2004


    
       Another moron has decided to create a  urlLink  Rave Site  based out of Puerto Rico. As if we even had raves anymore [if ever]. Also notice how in his profile he states that he loves Reggaeton.... just what all of us ravers (and by now i hope you realize im being sarcastic)  have been wishing for all this time! a Caco to run a Rave website.  its a dream come true. 
    
    


11,May,2004


    
        urlLink this man!  *lol* although i DO know people who can probably break his record, they just arent big on publicity.  
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       I think  urlLink they  got sick of the bull* thats going on in this planet and decided to cut their vacation short 
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       Last nite i watched a  urlLink show  on VH1. In it Trey from  urlLink Phish (one of my favourite bands, and Dave Mathews (who needs no introduction) visit Africa to play with Orchestra Baobabs.  I always thought Baobabs refered to the trees on  urlLink "

11,May,2004


    
       I swear  urlLink this  is almost hipnotizing. And like many of the things i will post here it has no purpose either.   but the tune's a good one. 
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       I love people who pay atention to detail. Like urlLink here  for example.   -you cant blame me, Im a virgo, we thrive on analizing the smallest details. 
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       I hear you brother! If youre a fat bastard... fine! . urlLink diets are so lame  
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       and spend every last day at the beach relaxing and enjoying the beautiful things ?  Thats what I wondered after seeing  urlLink this link.   
    
    


11,May,2004


    
       to bring forth the rhythm and the rhyme!!! (why am i quoting Marky Mark on my first post ever?)  Anyway...been saying i was gonna make a blog for years, well it doesnt get any easier than this. Hello Cybelle!  
    
    



