
30,May,2004


						
						   Before I headed with Mr. Trick Noble off to examine the scenes at the top battles of the US Civil War, I hopped over the Smoky Mountains to Asheville, NC, on May 16 to see a rare regional performance by German industrial noise gurus Einsturzende Neubauten. It was a fun, slightly trippy night of celebrity hob-knobbing.  For the past couple of years, I've "subscribed" to Einsturzende via their web site,  urlLink www.neubauten.org . Outside of their position as originators of a musical style, I like their approach to promoting themselves and retaining ownership of their art. So I was quite excited at the unexpected chance to see them live.  As a "supporter," I was told via e-mail to check in at the "supporters' desk" for special info. I received a special supporter's button and the opportunity to "pre-order" a recording of the night's concert, available immediately after the show. The price was steep, but I was enamored of the idea of an instant album, so I put my name on the list and got a nifty hand-stamp that stayed with me for days. It was also another way to directly suport the artists. I knew the whole cost of the disc was going to E.N.  Lots of Knoxville folks were there: David Wilson (of This Witch's Seed fame), Steve Greene, Regina Greene (of Regina Greene fame), Jen Corum, the ever-present Ryan Collins and a few of those folks who are at every Pilot Light show. I don't know who was back home at Pilot Light that night. I guess Jason or Bill showed some movies.  So the performance kicked in after the band's air compressors were filled up. The first song involved using airguns on PVC pipes to make tones a la blowing across the top of a Co-Cola bottle (I use the southern colloquial generic there). It created an atmospheric sound and watching them produce the sounds was fascinating. Vocalist Blixa Bargeld sang in his deep German voice, with the occasional impossibly high-pitched screech. Not only can he make the most inhuman sound with his voice, but he can change notes as he does it. It's incredible to watch, and a bit unnerving.  Bargeld was also quite charismatic as the front man. He was funny and personable. His outgoing nature was in contrast to the sterotype of German industrial noise-makers. One might expect avant garde arteests to be all business. But it seems E.N. likes to connect with fans. Bargeld was chatty between songs like Wayne Coyne of the Flaming Lips. It made for a folksy night of metal percussion and German incantations.  The Asheville show also marked the last night of the band's US tour. Announcing that they'd finished the trip with a $10,000 loss, Blixa offered the band's air compressors up for sale. I believe they were sold by the end of the show.  After they performed, they all gathered around for a meet & greet, autographing CDs of the night's performance and any other items fans brought up to them. They were all terribly charming. When Blixa saw my Kinky Friedman t-shirt, he exclaimed "Ah! Alex will go crazy when he sees your shirt. He loves Kinky Friedman." And when Alex came around, his eyes did light up at the recognition of a fellow fan of the Kinkster. "He is running for governor of Texas, yes?"  It turns out Alex Hacke of E.N. had served as Kinky's guitar tech on a tour of Germany a while back. It's a small world after all.  I also chatted with some fellow E.N. supporters from Greenville, SC. I forget their names, but they were certainly nice fellows.  The show ran an hour later than I expected it would, and I lingered to say hello to the nice German noisemakers, so I didn't make it back to K-town until 2:30 a.m. My brother-in-arms Mr. Noble was waiting in my living room, browsing a magazine. He was hungry. We headed over to Sam & Jerry's deli on Chapman Highway and shot the breeze about our trip.   Late the next morning, we set sail for Harper's Ferry, West Virginia. I left the world of avant garde music behind for an exploration of bloody US history. 

						


25,May,2004


						
						   Prof. Noble and I went time-traveling recently to the US Civil War. We started in Harper's Ferry, West Virginia, a still-quaint village on the shores of the Potomac and Shenandoah Rivers.  Some of the things I learned about Harper's Ferry and history: 1. John Brown walked it like he talked it. 2. There is an amazing view from the Hilltop Inn. 3. The John Brown Wax Museum is more comprehensive than the ones at Gettysburg. 4. Schoolkids run amok. 5. Lisa, the bartender at The Pub (uphill from Harper's Ferry proper), has two favorite shots: the "Kool-Aid" and the "tight snatch." I prefer the tight snatch.  More about all of this later. 

						


15,May,2004


						
						    This was originally published a couple of years ago in the Knoxville Writers Guild anthology "Breathing the Same Air," compiled and edited by that nice Leslie LaChance.   	It's good to own a pickup truck.  	My dad always has a truck, or at least he has for as long as I've known him.  His latest ride is a 1991 Ford F-250 with an extended cab.  It's a two-toned brown and light brown number that he bought so he could pull big trailers full of horses to horse shows.  You have to have a pretty strong rig to haul that kind of load.  Dad says this is the nicest truck he's ever owned.  	I think his first one was one of the best all around, though— a turquoise blue 1972 Ford F-150 with a state-of-the-art 8-track player.  He

13,May,2004


						
						   Not more than 15 minutes after hearing about this scam on the news, it seems like some joker decided to try it out at my house.  This guy rang the bell right about 11:30 p.m. and when I went to the door and looked out it was a guy saying his wife's car was broken down on Chapman Highway and he needed $18 to pay a wrecker. I live about a mile off of Chapman, a couple of turns into the neighborhood. So this guy's story rang false. I told him I couldn't help him while my security personnel stood by. The guy pulled off in a pretty darn nice-looking pickup truck, a "duelly" I think they call them.  There's an item about this scam on WVLT's website (http://www.volunteertv.com).  This is about the fourth time in the last three years I've been approached by scammers with what I call "The Elaborate Story." It ain't like the old days when Red Denney would say "Hoss, let me sing you a song for a dollar."  

						


13,May,2004


						
						   This is from a few weeks ago, but since I'm launching my blog, I wanted to throw something substantial on here.   Sunday, April 18,  2004  I slept very late. A good start to a good Sunday.  The sun was beating down on the dogwood trees in the  back yard. Wasps buzzing around the little evergreen  by the front porch. The lawn was mowed the day  before, so it was just right today. I headed out for Market  Square to have a late lunch and read the newspaper.  While sitting by the window at  urlLink Tomato Head  having a  veggie chef salad with tahini dressing, scanning the  Sunday crossword puzzle, I realized I was having a  perfect day.  It's like watching an undecipherable but obviously  efficient machine as the Tomato Head staff move from  kitchen to table to seating new diners to the kitchen  again etc. It's all the more impressive to a guy like me  who could never hang working in a restaurant like that.  I wouldn't last a day. These kids rock'n'roll.  The current art show at Tomato Head is photography  and paintings that mimic photography. Images of  nighttime travel. I love the ones with lights reflected on  a wet street at night. I love the blurred image of a gas  station. A gas station at night is the quintessential  American travel photo.  Outside the Dogwood Arts Festival is in full swing. John  Montgomery is competing in the bluegrass contest,  tearing it up on the dobro. Chuck Watt of Nug Jug is  hanging out and we swap tales of guitars and such.  I bought a big Denton's orange slushie (made from an  old family recipe) and listened to the picking.  Then I wandered back to South Knoxville, bought a  cheap pair of sandals at the new Wal-Mart, drove the  winding roads through the south Knox hills and settled  in for a quiet evening at home.  

						


13,May,2004


						
						   So to comment on Trickgnosis's blog, I had to register for my own. This will surely mean the end of me. Or maybe I'll finally start my novel. 

						


26,June,2004


						
						   How about Union Monkey?  Back on the vacation tale side of things, after Harper's Ferry, Herr Noble von Noble (the noted German scholar) and I left Harper's Ferry and proceeded to Sharpsburg, Maryland, and the nearby Antietam Battlefield National Park.  This park was pretty much what I always imagined a battlefield park would be like. It is on its own just outside of the town. An interpretive center and gift shop is at a central "front gates" point of the land, and a narrow road takes the visitor around to particularly historical points on the scene.  We saw the monument to Clara Barton, founder of the Red Cross; the Dunker Church, the Sunken Road (a.k.a. Bloody Lane) and Burnside's Bridge. All points of significant American history. As I learn more of the Civil War, I feel more and more that it is a part of our history that people should take better care to understand. The Confederacy tried to tear the country apart for an unjust cause. The country ultimately held together.   To stand in the places where these ancestors so violently hashed things out ... to look out across the now peaceful, pastoral locales ... stirred a unique feeling of patriotism, thankfulness and perspective. The inner dialogue becomes "Oh, I get it now. I get what it is that is worth fighting for."  Getting more and more focus on a bigger big picture really drives a lot home. To return attention to the current world situation ... boy, the Republican party has really tanked since Lincoln got shot.  After Antietam, Chris and I wandered over to Gettysburg, Pennsylvania. We checked into a motel and then hit the town to see the sights. We discovered The Flying Bull Saloon and played some pool. More on that next time. 

						


24,June,2004


						
						   Ah ... a band practice day. We hadn't convened in a week or three until today. We were a little sloppy, but not too bad. One more practice on Tuesday and we'll be more than ready for Friday's big gig with the Westside Daredevils.  "Anonymous" posted a comment on the last entry that perhaps "Year of the Monkey" sounds too "hipster" and misdirects the mind from our singer-songwriter, bluesy roots-rock style. I think this "anonymous" person might be our pal Mr Trickgnosis, and his opinion is always welcome. Especially since he is a bandmember emeritus. Hmmm ... ponder, ponder.  Band-naming is hard work. Most everything sounds too cheesy. Which is why the "New Randall Brown Quartet" label has worked so well for me. It is over-the-top cheesy, and therefore works satirically. But I grow tired of its overt goofiness. And it doesn't really advertise our style either.  So what is a bandleader to do? Monkey see, monkey do? 

						


24,June,2004


						
						   That might be more my speed. Kind of wordy, though.  Anyway ... I just picked up the first season DVD set of a Showtime show called "Dead Like Me." It's the anti-"Touched By an Angel." The angels in this show are grim reapers, and their touch tags a person's soul for safe removal. I think you'd like the humor in this show more than "Joan of Arcadia," good sir Trickgnosis.  Life is good. I'll try to get to my POV tales of Antietam and Gettysburg soon. I swear I will. 

						


22,June,2004


						
						   Today I've been pondering monkey-themed band names. I thought of Monkey Power, or Power Monkey, but it turns out there is already a Monkey Power Trio up north somewhere. Apparently they convene once a year to do a show. Where have I heard of that before?  Then it hit me like a freight train full of monkeys. 2004 is the Year of the Monkey in the Chinese Zodiac. I was born in 1968, another Year of the Monkey. So I'm leaning towards this as the title for the CD and thence becoming the name of the band. A search at Borders turned up some books about the Year of the Monkey, but no bands. I'll go check AllMusic.com next. 

						


21,June,2004


						
						   I hadn't been to a horse show in about 20 years before this past weekend. My dad, Boyd Brown, was showing a horse owned by a friend of his at the Piney Ruritan Club down in one of the more remote corners of Loudon County. I spent more time than I ever wanted at horse shows during my youth. I think it's probably one of the roots of the gap between my dad and me ... I never took to horses.  But there's nothing to do to close a gap except go hang out. So I went with my mom down to the horse show. It was amazingly the same as ever. Memories rushed back to me. The pre-recorded organ music, the rows of horse trailers, the burgers & hot dogs concession stand.  The sights and sounds of a saddlebred horse show are a particular twist on "carnival atmosphere." It shares aspects with county fairs and such, but there's a sense of singular purpose. It's a crowd that is savvy to a specific set of rules that might seem arcane at first.  I asked my dad what the judges look for. He said they call out the different walks, or gates, and then "They pick out which one looks the prettiest doing it." So at first the contestants might do a "slow rack." This is a mid-tempo gate with the horse's from feet stepping sort of high. Then the judges might have them walk, which is self-explanatory. But the big point of each division, or class, is for the horses to "rack on."  The announcer calls for a full rack, and gives the battle cry: "Rack on!" This is a high-stepping, upbeat gate, and it's the high point of each class. This is when the horses are really pouring it on. Their gates and high-stepping are in full-on equine ballet mode.  There were 21 classes on this particular Saturday night, minus two that didn't have any entries. So this pattern repeated 19 times. Walk, slow rack, walk rack on etc.  The fans of the different horses would call out for the judge to look at their favorites. I can never tell if the judge is listening, but I guess it's part of his or her job to listen without showing any bias.  My dad came in third of three after his horse broke its gate during his class. He didn't seem too put out about it. He won a sack of feed and $17 anyway. And it wasn't his own horse.  Now that I'm grown and attending of my own free will, the best part of a horse show is seeing my dad in action. This is where my dad does something he loves to do. His performance at a horse show is his version of my rock band hobby. I dare say my dad is better at his performance than I am at mine.  What I really enjoy, though, is seeing my dad back at the barn training horses. To a certain extent, he also trains the riders. Many of the riders and owners are doctors and lawyers and the like who buy a horse and get into showing as their own hobby. They might have the money, but not the decades of experience my dad has. So they become students to my dad.  My dad is basically a hard-working good old boy who never finished high school. He learned to read in his 20s when he married my mom. He career has been in construction, carpentry and (currently) on the road with the Tennessee Department of Transportation.  I don't know how he feels about it, but I get a real kick out of his authority at the barn. One of the well-to-do owner/riders will go around the practice ring a few times, not quite being able to get the horse to do exactly right. Then my dad will offer his opinion.  "Want me to tell you what you're doing wrong?" he'll ask.  The lawyer's wife will look over and say, "Yeah." And if they do what he says, the horse will do what they were trying to get it to do.  So that's my dad the educator. Sensai of saddlebreds. 

						


20,June,2004


						
						   So microphones were placed and test runs were made. The Drummer and I are convinced of our powers and we start full force this week. We require a 2nd pair of headphones and a headphone amp (distributes sound to multiple headphones). Other problems took only a glance around the underground lair to solve.  I'll be performing solo on KFAR pirate radio this Friday night. Check the  urlLink KFAR Web site  for time, cuz I don't remember. We'll also have a full-band show on July 2 with Westside Daredevils at Patrick Sullivan's.  ANother thing I've been pondering on of late: declaring a "real" band name. I'm feeling like "The New Randall Brown Quartet" has run its course. I've been thinking that accomplishing the CD would be a good point to also launch a new band name. As it turns out, The Drummer is for it because the current band name makes him feel like a hired hand as opposed to being a "bandmate." Or something to that effect.  So a preliminary idea is "The New Me." It stems from a joke I made about "The New Me Quartet." Dropping "quartet" would end the impression that we're a jazz group. Donnie says that none of his non-musician friends get the "NRBQ" joke anyway. Idon't really care about that, but the joke is getting old to me anyway.  But I'm not completely sold on "The New Me" as a name. I've been tumbling over the different connotations of it ... and also "The New You." There are just so many conventions of band naming to play with. It seems like "pick a cliche, pick any cliche." Heck, even calling it something extremely "un-band-name-like" is a cliche at this point.  Today I've been trying to think of Civil War phrases or terms and how they sound as band names. There's already a band called Antietam. Longstreet came through Knoxville at some point, but I am loathe to take on a Confederate name, even good old Longstreet. U.S. Grant is the obvious general to go for, but I think there's already been a band that mined that field.  I'm also thinking I'd like to call the CD "The Last Thing That Could Ever Happen," after an old personal saying of mine.  

						


18,June,2004


						
						   Actually my little tirade about audio engineers was more about the advice I've gotten on technical aspects of recording. On the one hand, I've gotten good advice. On the other hand, I've let concerns over producing a professional-sounding recording keep me from actually producing anything at all. So I speak out and it might come off sounding like a "lo-fi" declaration. I'd really like to make a good-sounding CD, but I've only managed to worry too much about it and not act enough.  It just feels better to forge ahead. 

						


17,June,2004


						
						    urlLink Chris  has been musing over dreams. Does anyone have any thoughts on dreams of flying, travel or death? Does anyone read this thing?  Donnie (the stalwart other half of the New Randall Brown Quartet) and I reviewed our rought mixes last evening. We just sat and listened, but dang it felt like getting something done. If there's one thing I'm re-learning about recording, it's this: stop talking about it and start doing it. You won't know how things will turn out until you take a whack at it. And for gosh sakes, don't be discouraged by conversations with "professional" audio engineers. Some of those guys can't hear the music for the sound. I have a feeling that, after two years of trying for a "professional-sounding" recording of the NRndlBQ, I will realize that what I really want is something that sounds like it was recorded in a basement. 

						


13,June,2004


						
						   I swear I'll continue the Civil War vacation tales soon.  In the meantime, I've rearranged the underground headquarters of the New Randall Brown Quartet into digital studio mode. Current plan is to lay down final guitar, bass and vocal tracks, get the guests in, and then see how things are going to go with a few more songs. There are nine to work on at this point. I'd like to manage a 14-song CD.  At this point, I'm thinking I will title it "Science Diction." Here's a preliminary track list (not in order): -Science Diction -Shine On, Shine On Arab Moon -Downtown Zurich, Saturday Night -Crosstown Waltz -Evolution Works -Yes, I'm Staring At Your Woman -Freedom of Information Act -My Dad Is Bigger Than Your Dad -What Becomes a Whore?  The other five that need to be laid down are: -That's So Gay Street Blues -I Got Drunk Last Night Just on the Thoughts of You -My Best Line -Slept Too Late -Truckstop (In My Head)  It will be interesting to see how these unrecorded five turn out. Studio conditions are quite different.  In any case, the equipment is in place and there's nothing to stop me but my own procrastination. On the plus side, most of my favorite TV shows of the last few years have been canceled, so distractions are few.  

						


10,June,2004


						
						   Dang. He lived a good long life, I reckon. And his family was with him when he passed away. What a tremendous talent he was. Cheers to Ray Charles. 

						


07,June,2004


						
						   Elvis is dead and the moon landings were real Earlier to bed would sure help how I feel In the morning 

						


03,June,2004


						
						   Photographs relating to this tale may be viewed at  urlLink The Trickgnosis Blog  of my dear pal Mr. Noble.  Dr. Noble Trickgnoble and I set out in the late morning on May 17 for Harper's Ferry, W. Va., to investigate the history of John Brown and the ensuing US Civil War. Also, Lewis & Clark began their epic journey from this river-port hamlet. With all this in its past, you'd think more was happening there on a summer Monday night.  But when we pulled into town around 7 or 8-ish, not a lot was going on. The shooting had died down and the arsenal was empty. The arsenal, in fact, was long gone. It was replaced by a railroad track and station. One interesting lack the locale had was parking. Ye olde village of Harper's Ferry is very pedestrian friendly, mostly because the only parking lot is for commuters showing up in the morning to catch the train. Lucky for us, we had a room (and free parking) at the inn.  The Hilltop Inn sits majestically atop (you guessed it) the hill above Harper's Ferry. The view from the front porch is gorgeous. Literally. It looks out upon the river gorge where the Shenendoah River meets the Potomac. It's a stunner. The old village of Harper's Ferry isn't visible, at least in late spring, but the dual railroad bridge across the river pokes out of the trees and into a tunnel on the far side of the river. "Scenic view" is an understatement.  The Potomac at Harper's Ferry is like a mega-creek in comparison to the waterways of East Tennessee. It's as wide as the Tennessee River, but with the rocky nature of the mountain creeks in the Smokies. The slight differences in geography between this part of W.Va. and my familiar East Tennessee hills is intriguing to me. It's the same but different.  Since everything was closed, Chris and I wandered over to nearby Charlestown to dine at the elegant Ruby Tuesdays by the highway. Our server, a lovely young lass named Danielle, turned out to be a re-enactor. I guess she plays "the pretty blonde-haired girl at the battle." Though she was a bit too young to get into these places, she gave us the rundown on area watering holes. We tried a nearby sports bar first. We watched a couple of televised horse races and read the questions on "Who Wants to Talk to Regis Philbin?" The fellow beside us was excitedly calling out the answers to the questions, but he was only batting about 25%.  Bored with that, we headed back into the twin village of Boliver/Harper's Ferry and took a look-see at The Pub, a small bar just up the road from where we were quartered for the night. For some reason, a patron must ring the doorbell to get into The Pub. For some reason, we didn't ask anyone why.  We settled in at the bar and made the acquaintence of a sweet young lady named Lisa. Besides being a big-eyed brunette cutie, Lisa had an odd little habit. She seemed to be keeping a running commentary to herself about her activities behind the bar, and the conversations she was maintaining with her patrons. As she set up our drinks, we got a portion of play-by-play from the chat she'd just walked away from. I have no idea what she was talking about at these moments, but it was nice of her to share. It was terribly endearing.  The Pub has a pool room and back deck, a dining area, a multi-game video device, slots and a decent juke box. I believe I would not be going too far to say it probably has the best juke box in Harper's Ferry. As far as food goes, we didn't dine there. But Lisa assured us they had excellent black angus burgers. Maybe next time.  Playing the multi-game video thingy was another temporary pal we made named Brooke, but we didn't meet her that first night. The second night, she beat us at the pool table. But I'll get to that later.  Next installment of this tale, I'll jump back to the historical investigation side of our journey. We got down with the tale of John Brown. 

						


01,June,2004


						
						   Here's a little piece on the world situation by that most charming of old cranks, Kurt Vonnegut. This seems to be actually written by him, unlike that "sunblock" essay from a few years back.  urlLink www.inthesetimes.com/site/main/article/cold_turkey/    

						


30,July,2004


						
						   I've just discovered that humorist David Sedaris will be speaking at 8 p.m. Saturday, Oct. 23, in the Langford Auditorium at Vanderbilt University in Nashville. I must go. Looks like tickets won't be on sale until one month ahead of time, though.  My, but it has been a social week for Mr. Bunni (pronounced boo-nee for those who are thinking I'm all into rabbits or something). Social in the physical and electronic world. Monday offered film and fraternity, Wednesday offered grocery shopping with Ron (an adventure amongst the shelves of multiple SoKno establishments), Thursday offered a rousing speech by the next president. It seems like I had lunch a time or two with the fellows from work. Along the way I had a fun e-mail chat exchange with action poet Julia Nance.  Also along the way, I had a moment or three alone at home when The Renter worked late. Relaxing times.  Tonight promises an actual party. My pal and co-worker Jigsha Desai has painted one of her walls an orange color (unrelated to U. of Tennessee's "Big Orange"). So she is celebrating with a soiree. Her last party was a hoot, so the outlook is good.  Sunday, Jane Crowe is having one of her seasonal pagan bonfire parties. The days are just packed.  

						


28,July,2004


						
						   "Coffee and Cigarettes" is a great little film. Fun chats with unique folks. I ran into a group of co-workers at the theater and we all watched it together. Then a few of us adjourned to IHOP for coffee and cigarettes (I had coffee, others had cigs). An unexpectedly social Monday evening.  As is suggested by a couple of folks in the movie, my dreams did move faster during the night. At one point I dreamt I'd woken up and was already in the shower. Then I woke up and had to start all over.  Brian Williams came over one night last week and we got another bass track recorded for The CD. That's turning out to be quite satisfying. I'll keep tinkering until my big push in August.  My August plan is to head out to West Tennessee for a few days to visit with my pals Rebel, Leslie and John. Then, if spirit measures up to ambition, I'm going to try and drive to Atlanta for brithday festivities with good sir Christian "Nabil" Noble, also known as  urlLink Dr. Trickgnosis Von Noblerger . He says his own anniversary of life will be celebrated on Friday the 13th. All the better, for I'll need to be back home by Sunday the 15th (his actual b-day).  I was going to stay at home and do recording for two weeks, but I've decided to do that with just my second week of vacation. I'd like to be 90% finished by the time I have to go back to work. The other 10% I count as "guest artist" time. Maybe I'll see if I can get some of that taken care of then also. 

						


18,July,2004


						
						   It seems we have a winner. That winner is the New Randall Brown Quartet because the talented Mr. Doug Engle has joined us on the bass guitar. He's quite a quick study. Confidence is restored. Soon you will witness the awesome power of a fully operational three-man quartet.  On August 6, we'll attempt to appear to be a light jazz ensemble for a free performance on the Market Square stage. 

						


17,July,2004


						
						   It's always one of my rock'n'roll fantasies to be watching a concert by one of my favorite bands and have the singer say "We'd like to call our pal Mr. Bunni up for the next song." I'm having some success in this area. Last night while enjoying a concert by my pals  urlLink Todd Steed & The Suns of Phere  at  urlLink Barley's , I was called into action to recite the R.B. Morris poem that I did to introduce the song "Smoky Mountain Dip" on Todd's album, "Knoxville Tells." It was an honor to participate on that tune, and terribly flattering to be asked on occasion to recite the four-line quip.  "It's so cold taking that first dunk enlarging my soul while other parts are shrunk."  I imagine that it went well, though I must admit that I'd had a couple of cocktails by that point in the show. I'm not sure what song they launched into after that. I took my drink with me because it seemed like a proper prop. I was perhaps channeling the late Foster Brookes just a bit. Of course, Brookes was a tee-totaller while he was acting so drunk for all those years. I tend to be more of a method actor when drinking.  But in any case, it was a fun social evening. I chatted with the inimitable  urlLink Cat Brock  and her pal Leah for a few minutes. I admire Cat for the unique personality in her songs and guitar playing. She also has that "stick-to-it-iveness" that gets things done for the DIY rockers. I aspire to the "getting things done" spirit.  Also on hand was outgoing News Sentinel nightlife writer M. Trevor Higgins III. He's an okay kid. I wish him well in his move to Chattanooga. I meant to go by his table and meet the legendary roommate hammet and Trevor's lovely lady Rosemary. It is Rosemary, right? Names overwhelm me sometimes.  I ended the evening with a cup of fresh water at  urlLink Pilot Light . Regina Greene was in charge, and I chatted with her for a few minutes. Of course, she subtly chastised me for not coming by more often. She's such a sweetheart and a rock'n'roll force, I feel embarrassed that I don't go by and check out the music as often as I used to. My country estate, Casa Bunni, beckons strongly on most evenings, though. But the efforts of Regina and co-volunteer Bill Warden keep Pilot Light open and active. It's a kind of magic, I think.  I'm going to a party at Dave & Laura Smith's place this evening. Sweet folks who always invite me over, and I have yet to see their new place. But nothing calls me away today, so I will go hang out.  

						


14,July,2004


						
						   Some passing thoughts: 1. That Natalie Portman is a hottie. 2. Little green frogs are all over my yard. It's crazy! 3. I have an extra ticket to the Willie Nelson/Bob Dylan concert in August. 4. The new David Sedaris book is hilarious. 5. Static electricity can happen almost anywhere. 

						


08,July,2004


						
						   Wow. I went looking for Monkey Power Trio, then they came looking for me. I'll have to figure out a way to write those guys back. They seem to be possible kindred spirits.  To my earlier "Year of the Monkey" entry, they responded:  "Hello Mr. Bunni, This is the Monkey Power Trio. Please know that we plan to release a compilation CD of our records every 12 years on the year of the monkey. We will likely come up with a much more clever title than "Year of the Monkey" but we just wanted to let you know so as to head off potential confusion in the future. We are a forward-looking band. Best of luck to you and your musical endeavors. (How about "Train Full of Monkeys"?)"   

						


05,July,2004


						
						   As it turns out, those nice boys The Westside Daredevils are a lot more popular than I even knew. We had a big crowd at Patrick Sullivan's Saloon last Friday. We even had radio support from West 105.3 FM, WKVL. We had a great time and even got paid.  Our next potential gig might have us pretending to be a jazz act. We'll see how that pans out.  My pal Ron and I went to the drive-in movies Saturday night to see a multiple-feature with "Spider-man 2" being the "headliner." It was an odd night out. The drive-in is always a little bit stranger than I remember.  The plus side of it was that Ron did not have to transfer from my truck to his wheel chair when we got to the place. The down side was that drive-in screens don't offer the best picture, especially for action movies with lots of nighttime scenes. But the burgers were cheap and the movies were passable. "Ella Enchanted" came on before Spidey, and "White Chicks" followed. "Ella" had a funny scene in which the cast sings a Queen song. "White Chicks" had several chuckle-worthy gags. A bargain for $7. We didn't stick around for "Dawn of the Dead." I had already seen it and Ron didn't want to.  

						


01,July,2004


						
						   We have a craft orbiting Saturn, and it is way freaking cool. When I say "we," I mean humanity. Here's a  urlLink link to groovy pictures .  The Rev. Pete and I watched a few episodes of  urlLink "From the Earth to the Moon"  last weekend. Inspiring stuff. I'd jump at the chance to leave the planet for a few days.  "So ... what'd you do last weekend?" "I did some reading ... took a walk ... stayed up and watched the Earth rise."  For a travel junkie, there could be no greater achievement than to get off the planet for a while. Except maybe landing on the moon or Mars etc. 

						


06,August,2004


						
						   Doug Engle, the new bass player on our scene, and his wife Nancy came over Thursday evening for our parctice and planning for our little outdoor gig on Friday. After going over the tunes and getting quite comfortable and confident in Doug's handling of them, we chatted for a good long while. It was nice to have casual company and nice to get to know Doug and Nancy a little better. I know Doug from some college classes a few years back (hmmm ... that would be at least 10 years back) and I've met Nancy many times at parties given by mutual friends. But I feel like I know them a bit better now and they are very nice.  Doug is also a very good musician. I'm tickled to have him performing iwth us. I think he's a keeper. His personality meshes with both mine and Donnie's, and I think his playing style will compliment us both, too.  After the show, it's a two-week vacation for Mr. Bunni. Yee haw! 

						


01,August,2004


						
						   The third practice with Doug went swimmingly well today. We'll practice as a duo sometime later this week to make sure we can plow through some tunes at Market Square on Friday. We will be drummerless, since The Donnie has to work. Oy. But we'll have fun. Still, I look forward to our first show as a new whole band. Maybe we can get in on some of that second-leg Sundown in the City action.  Film review: "Zatoichi" is a fine flick by Takeshi Kitano and friends. Tarantino must be kikcing himself for not thinking of the musical number involved in this one. 

						


01,August,2004


						
						   The Rev. Pete returned my copy of "Confederates in the Attic," which I thought he'd returned a long time ago. It was still at his folks' house, though. His sister found a box of his books, thoughtfully stowed away in a closet he never used. THusly, he never checked it when he was looking for his stuff.   In re-reading some points from the Civil Wargasm of author Tony Horowitz and hardcore re-enactor Robert Lee Hodge, I discovered that the recent trip Dr. Trick and I took to Harper's Ferry, Antietam and Gettysburg echoed the one from this book more than I remembered. Eerie. It even mentions General Picket's Buffet. Horowitz gives an excellent description of the village of Harper's Ferry. The two actually camped in The Sunken Road, a place where I had one of my biggest feelings of historical ... uh ... impact.  I plan to re-read the whole book. Then I'll probably want to go back and take our trip over again. But really, I'd like to go to Shiloh. 

						



