
30,May,2004


    
       Hmmmzz we are officially into e 2nd day of "school holidays" le...yeah "school holidays"...u know i remember when we were kids...we were like "YEAH!! E school hols r here...it's time to relaxing and play like mad!" Not tt we needed e hols to play like mad at that time...everyday at school was a day of so much joy n madness tt sometimes I wondered if e school hols might actually have been for our beloved and benevolent teachers to get a tighter hold on their heads by spending some time away from us screaming mischievous brats...doesn't help if u r in a boy's school tt seems like they r housing a whole zoo of monkeys instead...who is often monkeying around n getting into monkey business...yeah u get e idea=

27,May,2004


    
       Today had half day in sch...or rather in my case it was more like full-day...hahaz lee-ster couldn't make it for first period tut n I had 3 breaks b4 e end of school...so yeah didn't do any work at all!! ARGHZ! feel so unaccomplished...u know...e feeling when u got so much work to do but u really can't get down to doing it due to various reasons (Slackness: 98%, fat|gue: 1.99%, Not Smart Enough 0.01% No Time: Tend towards Zero) so yeah really got to get down to some serious work...I'm aiming for at least 2As and a C and a B3 in GP...hmmmzz quite a v realistic target right? I think it is...I mean it's not as if I dun have e ability plus it's really tt close to prelims I gotta aim higher a bit to give me a gd confidence boost in time for e real big-time stuff...  Went K-Box wif Nic n Kelvin n ~surprise surprise~ Hu|y|ng! hahaz she was juz tagging along i guess...too bad she didn't really sing dere...otherwise i prob got lots more stuff to blog le:p As usual Kelvin was irritating her dere ah...Nic n I were like constantly nudging each other n giving each other e *hey hey juz look at dem=p* look...seriously I think they had e most fun today...yeah n it juz convinces me more tt they r cou*** material=p it's hard to really say wat makes me feel tt...but u juz have to look at dem n u'll know...  Oh n Nic nope i'm not gonna go K-Box tml again!! tiring...hahaz u r a K-Box freak:p...hope ya voucher is still valid thou...den u can treat us next time to e longer 2-7 slot...=

26,May,2004


    
       Whoo...juz collected my pay today!!=

23,May,2004


    
       h|yo d|ary...hey e infusia concert finally over le!=

14,May,2004


    
       h|yo boyz n gals, man and beasts, the living and the non-living...let me present to you a recent major phenomena...my blog is re-launched!! Wahhahaz excited not? Your had better be...for if u dun...I can't be bothered anyway:p hahaz I 4 1 am quite excited lah...long time since I blog le neh...however, got some expectations 4 this 1...really wanna a layout tt I really like n wun change in millenias...I'm real fussy over blog layouts n I wun blog unless I absolutely like the layout...but yeah dun really have any ideas in mind at e moment so think u can expect some real heavy maintenance work over here for the next few weeks *be careful of falling debris*! =p  ~Phew~ It has been sortuv real hectic e last few days or so, n bear in mind tt I'm not even a 4 subber n i'm not taking History either...so yeah congrats to all who made it thru this week still in a ~SANE state of mind~=

29,June,2004


    
           B     Busy       E     Elitist       N     Noisy       J     Joyous       A     Appreciative       M     Mesmerizing       I     Inspirational       N     Nutty       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com   
    
    


18,June,2004


    
           B     Brainy       I     Intelligent       R     Responsible       D     Dangerous       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com    
    
    


18,June,2004


    
       h|yo peepz...long time since I blog...hahaz shows tt I was mugging kz?:P hahaz as usual crammed most of e stuff into e last week of holidays...it was quite an enlightening experience...every now n den u find notes tt seem vaguely familiar...n some even worse totally nvr see b4 de! shan't say much lah...but so far Maths is fine...it better be since I spent e longest time on it!! Physics...hahaz was relaxing lah...cuz after finish half e paper I know confirm jiu4 shi4 go "R" already...so no stress 4 e other half...got break tml...shall put in some badly needed sleeping hours...  hmmmzz since Internet is such a global tool juz wanna leave a msg 4 George Bush... "Bombing for peace is just like f**king for virginity" I for 1...can't tolerate ya bulls**T  
    
    


18,June,2004


    
       Hahaz yesterday was class outing at Sentosa Day!...bout 10 pple went...Got Me Sin Yee Mabel Bryan Ben Foo Justin Lyndon Glenda Eugene Vanessa Loyalle n surprise surprise Mr. NG was dere too!=

16,June,2004


    
       Hahaz feeling in a gd mood today I made spaghetti today for dinner!=

14,June,2004


    
       Hmmmzz kz come to think of it dere were still a few gd things tt happened today n i thank God 4 it...  4.15 p.m.: Bought a pair of berms at Baleno...hahaz seriously nice!=

10,June,2004


    
       Today totally stank... 9.00a.m.: "tu tu,, tu tu" *France 2-1 England* Sigh lost another 5 bucks to Nic...If this goes on I wun last to e Euro semis man:p  12.30p.m.: Bought New Paper...*France 2-1 England*  Lampard (ENG) 38th min; Zidane (FRA) 90th min, 90+2min (pen); Beckham (ENG) miss penalty (72nd min) wat e heck! England were winning till they kayu e last 2 mins! Arghz...if i had watched e match...I'd have been tearing my freaking hair out n cursing n swearing...mebbe it's a sign tt I shud stop betting:p   1.10p.m.: Reached School...waited for Sin Yee...but she already arranged study date wif her band members le...*Sigh* Me n my stupid idea of wanting to give her a surprise...walked to Parkway after tt...  3.00p.m.: Reached Tampines hoping to catch a movie...*sigh* no nice new movies to watch...thot of fishing at Changi Village but weather was too damn hot...Juz realized the other purpose of going to sch was to return my library book! Rats it's a week overdue le...Too lazy to return to sch...  4.00p.m.: Went Samuel n Calvin to look for bermudas because they were having cheap sale...All bottoms for $19...was trying some on when e sole of my sandals totally dropped out...ripped it off n juz walked on e sponge cushion...glad no one noticed...Getting pissed le...  5.00p.m.: Reached home...some bird flew in from the service balcony n ransacked our kitchen garbage! Rubbish all over e floor!!!! !@#$%^&*...spent half an hour cleaning e kitchen...Cursed and swear e rest of e hour...  Yup not a day worth mentioning...still feeling real screwed up...e best thing to do on a day like tt is juz to stay home n sleep...    
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       h|yo d|ar|ez...went to watch Harry Potter wif Sin Yee today...hmmmzz not a bad show actually...hahaz remember I was a kid I used to like these kinda books turned movie kinda movies...den when a certain part tt I recalled came...den I'll juz go "Mum...Hey I know this part! I read it in e book!" den I'll juz go blah blah blah...n so on n so on till I can't remember other parts...which thankfully wasn't a lot...Imagine if right now I was this brainy kid who had juz read  Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban  n my mum brought me to e movie...Den I go "Hey Mum...I know this part! I read it in e book! n den "blah blah blah" e entire movie out before each scene..."!@#$%^&* freaking wasted my $39.90 on tt stupid book HP & Prisoner of Azkaban...now also can't watch e movie in peace"...come to think of it...it's really gonna hurt book sales too...but J.K. Rowling muz feel e same way as e mum...  Hmmmzz sin yee went shopping yesterday...bought lotsa stuff at gd discounted prices...mummy pay some more...so jealous! Muz one day drag my mummy go out shopping wif me too...*Mummy I'd like this bag and this and this pants and mebbe an mp3 player n digi camera n blah blah blah* hope u'll be reading tis mum hahaz=p anyway e black sweater tt she wore today was gorgeous...& she bought it for only 19 bucks...nice=

09,June,2004


    
       hahaz these adverts r really cute...go see dem!=

08,June,2004


    
       hahaz slacked e whole of yesterday n today I'm really scr**ing up my whole hols schedule...Really gotta pick up e slack e next few days...to think I was so proud tt I did quite a bit of work during my trip to M'sia...hahz muz practise my violin lotsa too!  Today went to watch Best Bet...hahaz no surprises lah e movie is still 100% Jack Neo style...e same actors (Mark Lee, Liu Qian Yi etc.), same medium of communication (HOKK|EN!), same style of humour (FUNNY!=

08,June,2004


    
       Back from M'sia le! yeah finally can sleep in comfort at night without some pesky bugs distracting me at ungodly hours...hahz e mosquitoes dere r seriously annoying...they constantly buzz in ya ears making a great entrance as thou they r saying "Hey bro, Would u take pity on a starving mosquito n be so kind as to make a bloody donation?"...actually I wouldn't have mind taking pity on a coupla poor mosquitoes...but goodness it seems like it's like Lady's Night every night...I've got at least 10 over bites all over my body! Too bad they didn't have tabasco sauce dere...(u know e advert on tv)...if only e advert were true...I'd be having fun everyday kicking some bloodsucker's ass everyday man!  hahaz apart from some sleep deprivation e trip was quite fun thou=

30,July,2004


    
       Pon the whole of school today to go for Xian Liang's cremation...sigh it was really v v qi1 liang2...wun go into details but juz hope tt his family is coping well...  Went to watch House of Flying Daggers wif Viv, Bang, Chan foon after lunch...wah lau it's a damn freaking lousy show lah...watched till I fell asleep halfway...lousy storyline, lousy dialogue, all Andy Lau and Takeshi Kaneshiro do is get their hands all over Zhang Ziyi...e fight scenes r damn lousy too...in e middle of a fight u see soldiers cutting the leaves off bamboos and e knives of e flying sect apparently have radar sensors and r remote-controlled...hahaz all of us ended up laughing at e stupidity of e film...sigh wat a way to spend an afternoon=p  Halfway thru compiling e IBM business forum notes...shud be up soon...  hmmzz tml is Sonata Music House music marathon...they gonna start up a performing space outside e Teck Whye NTUC n get students and teachers to perform in a bid to drum up publicity and attract young kids to join e sch...sigh personally I think it is no more effective than attempting to drive away boredon by watching House of Flying Daggers...I mean come on dere r a dozen better ways to spend a Saturday morning like a) sleeping b) watching Kids Central c) play com d) Watch house of flying daggers...Ok I was kidding bout option d) but yeah...to nicely put it...hope u find a way to enjoy it...  Treated Nic to K Box for his b-day...hope u had fun dude...hahaz I love Harlem's Ming Zhong Zhu Ding man...they didn't have it e last time at k box but now they have le!=

27,July,2004


    
       Yz is it so easy to forget whatever is on e lecture notes but yet so difficult to 4get some1?  
    
    


26,July,2004


    
       Went for Xian Liang's wake juz now...hmmzz every1 seemed to have prepared themselves for it le...not so many pple broke down...hopefully&nbsp;our presence&nbsp;will be a source of strength to his family...E 2 testimonials dedicated to him gave me a flitting impression of his last moments here...really inspired by his strength and his faith in the Almighty...he even dedicated a poem to&nbsp;his frenz&nbsp;to tell&nbsp;dem to be strong (hope I can get it from some1 to publish here)...I feel it's such a cruel fate...only 18...dere was so much he wanted to do, so much he needed to do, but yet time did not permit such luxuries...to think tt when I last left Dunman he was still a strong and healthy Scout wif bundles of energy to match...how much a year can change...but the worst pain felt has to be those that he has left behind...I hope they cope well...Xian Liang would have wished dem to...  "While some pple lie on their deathbeds fighting for their lives and the right to live, yet there r foolish others living who entertain the thought of death." Life is so porous and fragile...so pls treasure it...it's a privilege to live...and privileges can be taken away as easily as it can be bestowed upon...  Take care.  &nbsp;  
    
    


26,July,2004


    
       Hey although we may not have known each other very well during our Dunman days, but I really wish all e best for u...have a safe journey n may e Gods bless u...your bravery n strength have really inspired me...  
    
    


26,July,2004


    
       Yeah the icy feeling is starting to creep back in again...feels surprisingly snug though...almost feels&nbsp;like home...hahaz I'm starting to creep&nbsp;into my shell again...building a fortress around me...but yet I know not of what I'm protecting myself against...  I hope I have e s trength to keep e fire going&nbsp;   
    
    


23,July,2004


    
       Hmmmzz ZH was asking me yz he nvr see me in lec for so long...hahaz dunno wat to tell him too...it's not e first time he ask le...   hmmmzz anyway to Nic reading this...hey anytime u wanna relaxing...juz say e word man...we can go lan, eat tom yam soup, go have drinks...certain things r juz not worth our means to bother  
    
    


21,July,2004


    
       Hmmmzz it seems like I'll have to grow up soon...or I may regret not doing so now in e future...  
    
    


19,July,2004


    
       Hey man Dick Lee is my new idol now man...My Singapore Idol=

13,July,2004


    
       h|yo today went to e Si Ma Lu temple at Bugis to pray...hahaz yeah I know it's kinda wrong cuz I'm actually a Catholic by faith but den seriously I kinda find a stronger consolation and comfort in Buddhism...so well juz hope I haben offended any of e Gods up dere *sorry sorry orh*...originally planned to go alone but den Siew Sze was kind enough to accompany me dere cuz I dun really know temple rituals plus i also not v sure how to get dere...hmmmzz she changed a bit wor...she nvr ask me to treat her to ice cream juz now!!=p hahaz nah juz kidding...but den well sure felt better after e visit...Su Wern's right...I really had to help myself first...n this time for once I felt tt I nvr could have done it alone...I feel e flame rekindling...N I hope someone can help keep it burning... 
    
    


04,July,2004


    
       Today went to e Si4 Ma3 Lu4 temple at Bugis to pray...Yeah I know I'm supposed to be Catholic...Ben Foo even offered to pray for me (thanx thanx=

04,July,2004


    
            Your love is... by  urlLink  ChibiMarronchan        Your name is...           Your kiss is...    delicious      Your hugs are...    warm      Your eyes...    light up a day      Your touch is...    heart warming      Your smell is...    beautiful      Your smile is...    amazing      Your love is...    everlasting             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !      
    
    


05,August,2004


    
       Hiyo slacking in cm lab now...hmmmzz later hope to go steamboat party at marina bay to celebrate mabel n sin yee's b-day...yeah hear tt immune system stop slacking man! having this flu bug for a week le...yeah it's starting to cause respiratory probs...I'll go see a doc soon if it does not turn out well...hmmmzz feel like playing my violin now yesterday play for 2 hours so happy...hahaz think I'm catching on Ben Foo's affection for their music instruments le... 
    
    



