
29,May,2004


	 
      Many people think, it was the last episode of 'Friends' last night. I also have my 'contacts' who have told me otherwise. there is going to be another episode if the sitcom, but as it is 'The One Where They All Die'. it is slightly unsuitable for family viewing. there you go. NOT the last, just almost.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
      I can tell you all now that it's going to be.....  AHMED 


21,May,2004


	 
      That's right! I know!  It will be very interesting, because the new contestants are somewhat, special.  But I can't tell you. Sorry. Security reasons. Just tune in.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
      I was wondering if you knew that the   world is actually a cubic shape  . It's true!   Scientists   made the whole spherical thing up  just for more money, but I know the truth. All those photos from space are  just fakes !
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
      According to my good friend Ronnie Werner, of  urlLink Ronnie Werner Illustration ,  Mr. Foreman and Miss. Beacon are getting married!    You heard it here first, folks!   Details of the most prestigous union of the year will follow.  I sure do hope they allow  Hello  or  OK  the rights to their wedding photos. They will be the most interesting and glamourous yet!
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
        


19,May,2004


	 
       I was happily walking down the dirty streets of liverpool today, when I saw Mavis Beacon.  Now it was only a shot glance, but I am positive it was here.  For those of you who do not know, Mavis Beacon is the brilliant typing tutor and black (oh, sorry, afro-carribean) woman, who found software so good,  she put her name on it !  Much like  urlLink George Foreman , come to think of it.
     
    



31,May,2004


    
       
      i've just made a 'potion' of alcohol with my friends for a laugh and it actually turn out quite nicely! lol take; 1. 1 bottle of Vanilla Coke 2. drink most of it 3. add some tequila 4. add some pimms 5. add more pimms 6. add some gin 7. add 3 bottles of Stella  8. drink up babes!!!! 
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
      i am so happy! i wonder why everything i worry about DOESN'T turn out as bad as i thought...? not that i'm complaining, as what i thought could turn into a major crisis, is now in fact not a crisis at all, but i a fabarooooo thang! x
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
      it was, unfortunately, the LAST EVER EPISODE OF 'FRIENDS'! Last night! it was rather tragic, and i thought i was going to cry, but i couldn't bring myself to do so.... But what i want to know is, if Rachel and Ross are an item, Pheobe and Mike, are married and so are Monica and Chandler, who has Joey got? BUT then i realised that he has the cutest 'Duck Junior' and 'Chick Junior' ever! (and obviously, he only has to ask and i'll come running!) 
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
      I'm soo sorry for this everone, but i have now got a bit of an obsession with crap jokes...(it was Gus, i swear!) So here goes.. 1. Why did the Chicken cross the road? to get to the other side!  2. Why did the Gum cross the road? Because it weas stuck to the chicken's foot!  3. Why did the lamb cross the road? Because it murdered the Chicken!  4. Why did the pervert cross the road? Because his penis was stuck in the chicken's arse!!!  hahahahahaha i am so sick... xx
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
      i had the weirdest night's sleep EVER last night, as i was watching BB5. Does anyone not think that Marco, although he is hilarious, is actually quite irritating? Also Jason is an arrogant twat, and i've only 'known' him for a few hours!!!! lol x p.s. try sleeping curled up on a 2 seater sofa- it's actually really comfortable!!!
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
      Having since had one of the worst weeks EVER, i feel quite a lot... um... i'm not sure what the word is, but i feel better. i would also like to apologise to everyone for being a complete bitch to you all. x
       
    
    


26,May,2004


    
       
      hey, does anyone know the site of the yr 11 ball photos? i've seen a couple from Fintan (in which he looks gorgeous, i must say! lol) but that was only 1 or 2. if anyone knows, i would be (almost) eternally grateful. xx 
       
    
    


22,May,2004


    
       
      i would just like to announce the 'illness' of my beloved best friend Megan. she is suffering froma long- term illness called 'the common cold'. the poor moose is laying in bed, as we speak, so ill to even reach for the cold gruel her parents have left her... tragic story... so very tragic... X
       
    
    


22,May,2004


    
       
      ooh i'm quite happy at the mo- the sun is shining, my friends are fabaroo(!), and 'pranking Walrus' season seems to be over!  The holidays are coming up in a few days and i have know idea what i'm gonna do, i'm just going to let the 'surf take me to my destiny'. Also i have my 'Work To  School' conference tomorrow and Friday, which (from what i have heard from my 'lushtons' in year 11) is going to be quite fun! (not just because i'm going to see all my fit guy-mates in suits! lol) xxx
       
    
    


22,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    this is moi! at halloween!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


21,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THIS IS MEEEEE!!!!!!!! AAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHA! lol i love wallys!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


21,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    this is my friend Caroline and me- she's classy! lol (soz i look a lil bit erm.. stoned! lol)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


21,May,2004


    
       
      since the recent 'pranking walrus' season has started i've decided that i don't need anyone but myself and my friends.  definition of 'friend' : 1. does not constantly ditch people and go off with other bitches instead. 2. is there for others when needed (unless emergency prevents it) 3. takes into consideration other's feelings, state of mind, and whether it will kill them if you state something. 4. LISTEN TO WHAT THE OTHER PERSON IS SAYING 5. getting the facts right before judgementing   6. giving helpful critisism not just putting them down all the FUCKING TIME!  hhmmm.... that was maybe a bit harsh...  or not
       
    
    


21,May,2004


    
       
      i am sad... can i have a hug please? a nice big bear-hug would do me just fine! xxx
       
    
    


20,May,2004


    
       
      i am really pissed off today, so i'd better not write too much otherwise i'll get carried away... I LOVE MY FRIENDS BUT THEY PISS ME OFF!!! that just about covers it... xxx missing peeps already! xxx
       
    
    


20,May,2004


    
       
      i can't help it if what i wana do 4 my birthday it shit! so if no one wants to come, it'll just be me n caz n fintan in a field...:-( (thats not the bad thing, incase u guys get offended) PLEASE COME PEOPLE! (sorry, no pervs or twats allowed...) x
       
    
    


19,May,2004


    
       
      today is actually really boring... hang on! this WEEK is actually really boring! my lovely mate Bryony is comeing over on Friday- and we have NOTHING to do!!! any ideas will be much appreciated! x
       
    
    


19,May,2004


    
       
      hey people! this is my first post ever! i haven't really got a clue how to do this thang, but i'm working it out!
       
    
    


25,June,2004


    
       
      I'm sure everyone who actually goes on this site (which is me.. and ....me.) would of read the FAB jokes that gus made up (well... some she did). the mistress of all shite jokes has once again shocked the world!  She has made a 'part B.' to the joke about the chicken and the lamb.. its a tacky one.. :-) Why did the lamb cross the road?  Because it murdered the chicken! (erm.. haha...)  Why did the pig cross the road? Because it was arresting the lamb! (erm.. )    
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
      It was my birthday yesterday and i was so excited! lol. i got The Calling's aslbum... the Muse album... lotsa money (which i did actually spend that day... :-P ) um.. a new top from Megan... a £5 WHS voucher from Rachael... um... nothing from Gus... (lol) um... an email from Fintan...:-P um.. a text from Serafina, Anna, Jess, Ben, Phil, Cassey, Megan, and Gus... a hug from the 'rents.. oooh! cakes from 'work'... they were YUMAY!... some choccy from the g.'rents.. hmm... oooh so i went shopping n got a new top.. two new pairs of trews.. and got distracted by Ben Texztin me.. so i got sum gum aswell :-)  and thats my life so far.. lol xxx   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
      oh no! i have the second week of work experience to 'look forward to'!!! AHHH!!! i'm terrified i'm going to mess it up or do something really stupid! Everyone else seems to be so confident about it, but i'm getting all skittish over it! AHHHh! x
       
    
    


16,June,2004


    
       
      we won the cricket!
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
      I HATE STUPID PEOPLE! LIKE STUPID PEOPLE WHO BEAT US AT THE FLIPIN RUGGER! GGGGRRRR!!!! 
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
      the lil frog-legged bastards think theyr allllll it! don't they? but just cuz they kicked our arses at the footie! Well! im gonna go over there and give them all a piece of my brain! EVERY LAST SNAILY ONE OF THEM! HUMPH!
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
      I would just like to announce that as of this moment, (20:32, Sunday 13th June 2004) England have scored (by Frank Lampard) against the crap team (France) in Euro 2004!!! It's a happy time for us all at the moment, but will this luck continue? Back to the studio....
       
    
    


11,June,2004


    
       
      oooh how EGGciting!i have work experience on for the next two weeks and for the second one i'm going to this FAB graphic design place in Bedminster. It's gonna be soooo kewl!i can't wait! AND!! does anyone NOT think Miss. Fitzgerald's laugh is EGGstrodinarilly EGGY!!! xxx
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
      I am seriously pissed off at myself. Majorly. i did something yesterday that i'm still feeling guilt for. Some people will probably think it's pathetic etc.. but i hated doing it and i hate it now. i smoked yesterday for the first time in about 2 months and as soon as i had started (although i felt alot less stressed) i was sooo mad at myself. So if anyone wants to be mad, feel free, i am!  DON'T SMOKE!!! IT'S A DISGUSTING HABIT N IT MAKES U SMELL REALLY BADLY N NO BLOKE WILL HAVE YOU IF U DO!!!
       
    
    


06,June,2004


    
       
      i have school tomorrow n im dreading it. thats all i have to say. i hate school. blahblah.. etc [write own crap here] x
       
    
    


05,June,2004


    
       
      Has anyone tried my 'potion' yet? i actually wouldn't recommend it, as i did get a lil bit too pissed even for my liking! (ask Ben J. and Schmeek! lol) But if u really want to try it, i would also recomment you try putting more tequila in it, and less Stella. The Stella makes it taste DISGUSTING! lol x
       
    
    


04,June,2004


    
       
      Well, seeing as no one bothered to turn up last night, it was just Me, Fintan and Loran. WE DON'T NEED ANY OF U!!! lol we had loadsa fun!!! but DON'T go and see 'The Day After Tomorrow' it's shite!!!  
       
    
    


04,June,2004


    
       
      IM BORED! 2nite. 5pm. outside the Odeon in Weston. be there. its my birthday soon and i can't celebrate it when i wana so im gonna do it now. with u guys ( i hope! ) luv u all! xxx
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
      i have to officially apologise to everyone i 'talked' to on MSN last nite. i have to say i was a bit pissed and regrettidly i think i may have said something i shouldn't have... but on the other hand, i may not have. i can't really remember. so... i'm sorry. x
       
    
    


26,July,2004


    
       
       i need to go to weston on Wednesday night and i can't get there! aaahhh! drastic measures need to be taken! is anyone going to Stars on wednesday night? PLEASE!!!??? im begging!!! it's a major crisis!!!   xxx    
       
    
    


25,July,2004


    
       
      Crisis over! i have a lift there! yay! xxxxx 
       
    
    


24,July,2004


    
       
      im gonna go n see Spiderman 2 with my friends on tues! YAY!!! n CADBY IS COMING 2!!! btw for anyone who doesn't know him, he won't&nbsp;do ANYTHING without being persuaded majorly so this is a FIRST!!! hehehe! :-D luv u really cad!xxx&nbsp; 
       
    
    


20,July,2004


    
       
      everyone has to try out  urlLink www.bustertests.co.uk  and go on all the ad sites- they don't have viruses and they're... erm..  fun... so go on them! &nbsp; NOW! xxxx 
       
    
    


11,July,2004


    
       
      :-) school's out for summmmmmmmeeeeeeerrrrr!!!!!!!! lol i know have six weeks of pure boredom to waste! Anyone free anytime soon? u know where to contact me! ;-) Luv to u all!  peace out xxxxxxx 
       
    
    


11,July,2004


    
       
      is it completely impossible for me NOT to make a complete idiot of myself with EVERYTHING?... guess so... x 
       
    
    


04,July,2004


    
       
      i can't beilieve my bad luck at the mo! i got a really bad report at school, so my parents aren't really talking to me at the mo... i have been moved down a set in two subjects, TWO!!! i can't go out with Fintan this weekend because i have to revise and run a mile for Sports Relief... my so called friends have spat in my face and told me to (and i quote) ''fuck off and die''... i had a major choccy depression binge so im feeling really fat and i have a huge spot on my face!!! i hate to sound like caroline, sorry drama-queen, but AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! xxx
       
    
    


04,July,2004


    
       
      GREECE HAVE JUST THIS SECOND WON EURO 2004!!!  incase you peeps didn't know... the greek team haven't won a single match in a major tounament... EVER!! AAAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAahahhaha!!! x 
       
    
    


07,August,2004


    
       
      Did any of you people watch the LAST BIG BROTHER last night?oh of course you did, how stupid of me... but for anyone who missed it.... Nadia won! She had been the bookies favourite for the past six weeks, but in my opinion it was either her or Dan who were destined for the stardom and money they deserve. it was soo sweet when Nadia's mother came out- she had come all the was from portugal and her and Nadia hadnt seen each other for over a year! it was... *sniff*  heart wrenching!   
       
    
    



