

24,May,2004


	 
      and I'm getting a little worried that everything won't fit into my car. I really wanted to only have the trunk packed, and with light things, but it looks like there may be some overspill. On the other hand, I had Ethiopian food for the first time tonight, and it was very good. the restaurant was pretty nice on the inside, but the from the outside it looks like a place I wouldn't look at twice. I should be better about trying small hole-in-the-wall places, but I let other people try them first and then persuade me to go. Heheheh.
     
    


23,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Then the light got softer and softer and the pictures became less spectacular. A lot of people think of California as bigcities, but most of it is really farmland.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    This was a little farm we passed where I caught a glimpse of this pond and went "Ooo!"
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The Clouds looked really weird. They were dark grey and higging the mountains in the distance.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    I love this picture. We were on our way back from Monterey, and the sun was hitting the land on one side of the car. It was very beautiful and the air was clean and cool.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom looking gorgeous and smiling despite her frozen feet.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The kelp beds behind the aquarium.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Stupid smelly sea lions. They make a noise that sounds like they're saying, "Help me, Ma! I'm drowning! Gourp! Gourp! Gourp! Gourp! Gourp!"
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Wind socks, wind socks...
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    And all the other people taking pictures, too.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    A side view of the marina.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think that this is also an otter. Was it stalking us?!
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The kayakers out of their cove.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    a fishing boat and a houseboat.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think that's an otter.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The monkey and his man.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The wharf.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The second glimpse.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The eucalyptus corridor? (Who knows if I spelled it right?)
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Taking pictures out of the car windo works pretty wel.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The sky was beautiful on the way down.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
      It's been a great weekend. Yesterday Mom and I took my car for a test spin down to Monterey. We stopped at Gilroy on the way and shopped but did not drop--and now I've got two places to wear earrings again.  Monterey was beautiful, and we spent an hour shopping for jewelery. We also took lots of pictures, and ate waaaaaaaaaaay too much out on the pier. The car held up great. Pictures will follow.
     
    


21,May,2004


	 
      There are a lot more pictures to put up, but it's taking too long with my dial-up connection.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    But it's really pretty big.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    The garden looks small here.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom happy with fluffy cotton-candy roses.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yes, more pink.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    More pink!
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Open pink bud. This is one of my favorites.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Weirdly red roses. They almost look plastic.
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    There are lots of weddings in the Rose Garden
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Driving photo. Who knew that pictures could come out well even through a dirty windshield?
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Huge
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hiding in the bushes
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Opening bud
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yellow-reds
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Fountain
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Bright pink
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Beautiful Jeanette
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Pink bud 2
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yellow-pink rose
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    More yellow-red roses
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Roses
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Grandma and Aunt Mary in KY
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
      I'm new to all this blogging, despite hours spent reading other people's blogs. What a strange way to waste time...reading the thoughts of people you'll never meet.  Unlimited photo hosting, eh? I'll have to test that, once I figure out how to add more than one photo to each entry.  
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Various roses
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom in the Rose Garden
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    A rose is a rose is a rose...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


19,May,2004


	 
      It T-minus 12 days and I'm getting ready for move number 30. What wonderful inspirational things can I post here on the internet?   Who knows?
     
    


14,June,2004


	 
      So, it's been a long trip and a long time. I'm sorting through the photos and getting ready to post them.  Patience, my non-read blog. Soon you will be full of fresh pictures...
     
    


11,June,2004


	 
      Phew! Six days of driving and a broken computer later, I'm in NY! The last day (last Saturday) I drove form Joliet, IL to East Northport, NY. For those of the lazy persuasion, that's 847 miles, according to Mapquest.   I'm online for the first time using a wireless router. The internet connection is downstairs, in a small room with a hard chair, while I'm upstairs lounging in an armchair, going "Mwaaaahaaaahaaaaaa, my bottom is sitting on a soft thing instead of a hard thing." My friends know I'm here and of course are busy people, so I'm trying to figure out how to relax. I'm not good at it.   Look for pictures coming soon; I have to sort through most of them from the trip. My computer died on the second day, so I have a lot of pics from the first day of driving that are now on the hard drive, but all the rest of the week is still on the camera.  It's strange; somehow being here in New York is making me think a lot about what it was like living in Hawai'i. Strange. I am looking forward soooo much to school starting!
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Raphael coming in from a paddle.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    What a great photo of a horse's butt.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    She helped me move the day before. We both fell asleep on the beach, and I still have the strange tan lines.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom wondered what she would look like in sepia.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom has taken the official bell and is holding it captive.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Kayack.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The beginning of my quest to take boring pictures of train tracks.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The Pacific is less pacific than the Atlantic.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Goodbye, living room.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Goodbye, bedroom.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    We ate at a fish market in Moss Landing.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Setting out.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Goodbye, balcony.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I get the feeling he didn't want to leave.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    It's rare to find someone who can beam like this and still teach me how to cange diapers regulation-style.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Alex(is) is now being dead. We developed this technique as a way to get out of rehearsal, but unfortunately he still tends to be ticklish.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The elusive 1998 The Alameda. Just like the purloined letter, it's hiding out in the open.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Trees at my old home.
     
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The obligatory photo of myself (not the famine victim). 
     
    


15,July,2004


	 
      I just realised that I'm leaving the country in a little over a month,  and I have no pants!  Perhaps I should repharase that, as I'm heading to England, where they'll think I have no underwear. All I know is, for some reason when I was packing to drive to NY I thought that I would never need pants again and threw them all away. I'm hoping it's because they were all too big, and not because my brain was rotting away...  I've been doing a lot of thinking the past few days. Yes, I know it looks like sleeping to all of you outside my head, but I assure you if I'm sleeping it's because I'm trying not to think. I talked to Leslie about this (Leslie, not Leslee) and it's just mindboggling to me how incredibly my friends are growing up. Yes, all both of them. They have retained all the essential them-ness and developed to be so interesting. Here I thought I've changed so much, and then I see them and I begin to worry that I haven't changed as much for the better as I had thought.  That's enough philosophizing for now; I've got to count sweaters. More later, oh unread silly blog of the ages.
     
    


12,July,2004


	 
      I drove down to Balmer, hon. I watched some very loud people scream for a while, then went outside to cool off. Then  Kecak   came on and my night became great. I love it when bands are better in person than they are in recordings, and  Compliance and Liability   is a damn good album. (www.geocities.com/wearekecak)   There are a few more photos than these. Email me if you want to see more.  
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A subtle hint from Mike that it's time to be on my way. 
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    No, I wasn't on herion for this shot.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Which are better: the cool but blurry photos, or the stark scary red-eye ones?
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    What these guys don't know is that while they're petting Mike's very sweaty head they're being hog-tied by Seb, heheheh.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A pre-show basement. Sweat, anyone?
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Beth has apparently hit the "smarm" button concealed in makfak's left shoulder. I'm not sure how cocky he'll look when he realises what a heavy sleeper he is...
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yes, it's blurry but it's a cool photo.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A gratuitus blurry photo.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jeannie (Jeanie? I forgot how to spell it, sorry) and Beth looking way cool among the light refracting off their cigarette smoke.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jeanie and Beth being cool without smoke-reflections.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Balmoran alley.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Can you spot my car in Balmer?
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A thingie, Balmoran style.
     
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is the last picture I took of the trip. It got too dark after this. I think this is still in Ohio. After this I finished Ohio, went across PA and NJ, then hit L.I. I hit the first bad weather of the trip going over the Poconos. It was pitch black and I couldn't really tell where I was going. By the time I got to NJ I was hitting myself to stay awake, but hey, it worked. It was a six day trip, 847 miles (according to Mapquest) the last day, from Joliet, IL to East Northport, NY.  
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    An ominous sign. I had great weather for the whole trip until now.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Maybe this is the Mississippi. I don't think so. Who cares? It's a river, ooh.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    NYC is on the radar.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    So much to DISCOVER! *squeal*
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hmmm...this looks like Nebraska. Or is it Iowa? Ohio? Nope, it's Illinois.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Heading back into familiar territory, the outskirts of Illinois.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Ohio.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    At some point I crossed into Indiana, but there was no sign up because of construction.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The last day. 
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Iowa.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Nowhere is kinda pretty.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A big something.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Illinois. Please give us your money and then leave.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Where does all this "land" stuff come from?I saw it all across the country: Nebraskaland, Chicagoland, etc. People are weird.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Possibly the Mississippi, but I've waited so long to post these I don't remember anymore.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I WAS nowhere.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is supposedly the biggest rest stop on 80. It was pretty big, but the lines were very long everywhere inside.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I have no clue what this thing is, but not bad for a view from a gas station.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Traffic?! You mean there are other people in Nebraska?!
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Nowhere.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Nebraska.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ah, the lovely soft beaches of long island.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The dolphins, empty of ferries for the moment.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Even the air here is dripping wet.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yup, it was a crowded beach.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Some sort of island. Gradiner's? Plum? Me not know.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The ferries coming in and out.
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A light house at Orient point, LI
     
    


06,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    An interesting take on a house in the suburbs with a white picket fence.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Branson holds the shirt he is purchasing, while saying "Wisconsin." This picture says "Wisconsin," in his voice, but I haven't figured out how to make it play anywhere else yet.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Went for Korean dumpings with Leslie and Branson (here they are reminiscing about either RI or Balmer);
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Helped Leslie pick out flatware at Macy's on 34 ave (it has cool wooden escalators);
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Went shopping with them in Soho, where we discussed the job interview Branson had come to NY to have, and how Land's End wants him to move to Wisconsin. Here is Leslie looking perturbed about something, possible Wisconsin.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    That's enough about the trip for tonight. Meanwhile, I've been in NY for a month, and what have I done? 
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Took surprise photos of Branson (or Billy, whichever makes him make a more awful face);
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A very loooooong train.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I don't know what this is but it gave me something to wonder about for a while.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    My huge motel room in Evanston. I couldn't believe how big it was.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Day three. Heading out of Evanston.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Moments before I open my backpack to discover my computer refuses to wake up. From here on there are fewer pictures of everything, as I had intended to empty my storage cards every night and couldn't.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mom, these are the "scattered herds of cattle" I was talking about.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    On my way to the motel. I kept having to remember that I was in Evanston WYOMING, not ILLINOIS. I was pretty tired.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I did like western Wyoming. It felt very big and free, unlike the mountains of SLC, which were pretty but really made it a lot of effort to leave SLC

03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The road goes ever on and on...
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think it's time to wash the windows again.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Wyoming, yee-haw.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    It got lumpier.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ah, meadowy.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    And then it flattened out. This is the beinning of western Wyoming.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think I would get claustrophoic living in one of these houses.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    SLC
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hello...hello...hello...hello...
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This was a really beutiful place to drive around. Salt Lake City (viewed in passing, at least) is so refreching to the eyes after the bleakness of the beginning of this journey. I really enjoyed it, especially as I didn't find out that my computer was broken until I stopped for my second night.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    In interesting ways.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The state lines pretty much make sense. All the states I've been to are different, and you can tell when one state is ending and another beginning. Here is where Utah started to change.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    More SLC. These mountinas were very pretty to look at but slowed me down a lot.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yup. Lots of trains.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Approaching eastern Utah.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I passed a lot of trains on this trip.  
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Of course I had to see Cheyenne; I went shopping there later that day at Sierra trading post. A great store. 
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Around Salt Lake City. The most cars I'd seen on the road in hundreds of miles, really since Sacramento.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    A weird shot tower or something...who knows?
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here is western Utah. It still looks like Nevada, but is a bit better.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Utah was much prettier than Nevada! 
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think this is the great salt lake. There were no signs here but it was the only huge body of water and it was in about the right location.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    It was something to think about, not just endless miles of desert.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Welcome to Utah
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I saw these and hoped very fervently that the road somehow didn't go through these. It didn't, instead it curved around, but from here it  looked like I'd have to get a snow shovel.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I should've painted black spots on my car before I set out.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    For some reason, CA likes to label their mountains (like "South San Francisco, the Industrial City; and Hollywood) but NV doesn't seem to have quite grasped the idea.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Day two: There was a big sign up about 50 miles before this boasting that the Washington Post had voted Battle Mountain, NV is the armpit of the US. Naturally I had to take a picture.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is interesting: heat shimmers on the road and snow on the mountains.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    And here is what Winnemucca looks like.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I finally found gas and was tempted to turn around and go back...but I did wonder what some place called "Winnemucca" looked like.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yee-haw, cowboy.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yup. Did I mention it's boring? 
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Nevada is very boring. Very. And the signs lie. They told me it was 40 miles to the next gas station, so I kept going, but it was 97 miles and I was worried about how long I would have to wait to get off the side of the road. I'd probably still be there.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Donner pass. Descending from about 7,000-8,000 feet. I'll have to watch the little video I made for the exact number.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This bird apparently gets carsick.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think the mountain ate some bad sushi.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    It's weird to see snow in CA.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yes, I liked the sky.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The first glimpse of snow. Remember, this was May 31.
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Okay, while technically not a knitting picture--four skeins of handspun merino having its twist set. I still have oh, probably two pounds or more of this left to spin before I leave for school. I've debated about taking my wheel with me, but I'll probably have a lot of work to do...
     
    


04,August,2004


	 
      Having just joined Secret Pal III I felt that although from this blog it looks like all I do is drive around and take pictures, I really do knit. A lot. In fact it's becoming an obsession, but fortunately I won't have a LOT of time to do it in about three weeks...hopefully. But since most of what I make seems to find its way to other people's houses anyway, I may as well find someone else to make happy with random acts of fiber thingies.  
     
    


04,August,2004


	 
      The damn school has sent my loan forms somewhere into oblivion. No wonder I haven't heard anything yet.  I'm supposed to leave in 31 days. I have no loan and therefore no visa. Hence the 3 am posting. 
     
    



28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My last view of the Pacific
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Moon
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The mist is creeping back in
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Uncle Ernie Bear, otherwise known as the wise and dignified Dr. King.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Yeah, throw it into the wave, 
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    But Mom, the sun is still up a little bit
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I like the beach
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The Bear arrives, bearing gifts of KFC. We were all very full from lunch until about 5 minuted before he got there. Then we were very hungry. Such convenient appitites, no?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Wheeeeee. Sideways-y
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Rainbowy
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Look! look! It's sunny in SD!
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Then the sun started to come out
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hello
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Ride
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Huggies
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Such cutie peoples
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Les balloons
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Happy
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HOtel
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Waiting
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Lighthouse
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    View]
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Road
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Weird rocks
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    More reading
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Cool beans
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Reading? This is supposed to be looking!
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I think Jeremy wants me to go to CO
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me taking a picture of Hope taking a picture of me taking a picture
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Um, a caption?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Ha ha, I take pictures of people making pictures.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    This one is also frightening
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    They emerge
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    'Bye
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Packing
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Now I've met three people who can sleep with one leg up, and I'm related to two of them. I'm getting worried.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    She looked so comfy
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    We could tell they were getting tired when they started falling down a lot
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Laughing at the volleyers
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Lounging
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    You can tell he's smiling if you look closely enough
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I wonder where he's going
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hey there
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Misty palm trees
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Happy
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Justin tipped over backwards only twice that day, but the second time he grabbed the umbrella on the way down. He's trying to put it back up now and remain cool.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Raphael, protector of the Pacific.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Is she eating the shark or is the shark eating her?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Mary looks like a real estate agent already, no?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    She knows cake is on its way
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    See?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    He kept his smile
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sarah thought that perhaps I chartered a helicopter to get this shot
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    She was smiling right until I took the picture
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Really, Mom, I know how to use this.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Stoned
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Blowing
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The mysterious envelopes.
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Wha?
      


28,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Happy Birthday!
      


28,July,2004


    
       
      I took millions of pictures and my CT symptoms have come back. So, not much typing. 
      



