
31,May,2004


	 
      Things I have just realised --------------------------  -- It's a bit akward writing feelings inside your blog.  -- I'm bossy -- I hate projects -- The sentence "Being alone, you will not get hurt by others nor will you hurt others" is quite true. -- I need a lot of money 'cause I want to buy comics, clothers, shoes...etc. -- Hidayat is gonna be missed by everyone as he is an important person in our class. -- If the stupid manager of the farm doesn't call soon, I'm going to... -- People nowadays have such a good life, and once danger lurks, painc is easily in the air.    Some kind of stupid realisations huh.
     
    


29,May,2004


	 
      Hmm... Am I really that bossy? Heck, I think I'm going to be like Ming. 

29,May,2004


	 
      Oh yea, yesterday was school carnival day. Heck, so tired at the end of the day that maybe my hormones went haywire...'cause I cried! OH MY GOD, I did not even know why I was such in a depressed mood... Felt like crying but cannot cry, and in less then 3 minutes later, tears came to my eyes... 

29,May,2004


	 
      Woo hoo~! Tomorrow's the day! ^^ The carnival's tomorrow! Just hope that nothing can go wrong with my class's stall. 

21,May,2004


	 
      It feels familiar... This whole thing about creating a blog! Heck, 'cause this is my second time having a blog. Hmmm, though Xanga is much, much, much, much more easier then blogger. 

29,June,2004


	 
      Waaah, who's willing to gimme $1000?? Hiaz, nv knew kendo costs so much...the uniform is already $600 to a few thousands. 

28,June,2004


	 
      Omg~~ Mudvayne's   world so cold   so nice!!! Yea~~ A bit angsty, but I like angst! Haha... Anyway, todae when to JE library with YiNgx, poOdlE, MonKey, and sh1N. I saw Charmaine!!! Omg, she so beautiful! Umm, actually, I knew that long ago~ *faintz* I was in a presence of a beauty!! AAAhh~ Anyway, saw her mum (Auntie, v long nv see le! ^0~ ). Hmmm, seems like Charmaine chinese so quite gd! She was photocopying some pages in 2  thick  chinese books! Omg, it was THAT thick and all the chinese words that I saw made me look as though they were jumbled up! And the chinese words seem to be difficult~~~ *faintz again* ~.~  Anyway, deadline for IPW GOnNA CuM~ I'm gonna die im gonna die im gonna die im gonna die *chantz and chantz and chantz* Hiaz, and i HAVE to endure seeing YiNgx phgotocopying soooooo any pages for her group file~ I seriously hate her~! =P Jk!! ^o~ OMMMGGGG~~ Stakez me jus bloody stakez me! Hiazzz.. Anyway, gonna try to see if can meet AngEl next week after B Urself Day... O yeA, MMMIIIINNNNGG~~ mi DarlIng, where's my ocean cd?? ^o^ She's so good, help me burn!! AHHHH!!! OCEAN!!!!!!!!! His voice v smooth and his songs v romantic!! Haha, the animation also quite cute~ Scarly the guy in the animation looks like him... =D  Ast  - I'm not gonna say I'll be there for you when the world ends. But all I can say is my heart is always with you. Always -  
     
    


24,June,2004


	 
       Why is the sky dark? I'm blinded by these shit I'm numb, coldness seeping in No more feelings breaking in I'm endorsed with ice The hurt won't raise I wanna shout When the lights out When no one's there And no feelings break in I promise; I swear The numbness shocking me Pull me out from this deep pit I don't wanna die alone here, please Fear's coming and gone again The hurt's all left inside of me Why is the sky dark? I'm blinded by these shit I'm numb, coldness seeping in No more feelings breaking in Halt my mind, make it stop I don't wanna hear these stupid thoughts The voice is bugging me non-stop Just shut it up, I'm begging, please I'm on my knees, I'm slumping down Into the deep pit I've dug myself I'm blinded by these shit No more feelings breaking in What's left is gone What's gone has left No more...no more feelings breaking in... 
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
      Wah...waaah...waah~ *cries* I'm seeing alot of colours right now~ Green, red, black... I v jealous of practioners of kenjutsu and kendo!!!!! So unfair!!! And some of them are able to practice with katanas!!!    info section:  (sum1 gotta pay me)  Katanas are swords with blades over 24 inches  Wakazashi are shorter swordes with blades from 12 to 24 inches  Tantos (daggers) are blades less than 12 inches     Wah!! I wan katana and wakazashi! So kool, if able to use them properly~~ I wanna learn kenjutsu...kendo~ But i'm those type of ppl whose interest dun stay long... 3 minutes hot 3 minutes cold...  Hmm... but the swords can be a decorative item! I wann!!! I wan I wan I wan...*chants and chants and chants* Hiaz, no hope de le~ Saw one ninja set with swords and the star thingie~ Costs $70 or $80 plus~! And wat's more, it's not in Singapore currency!   PLUS~   (yesh, there's a plus) you need a permit in Singapore to own a weapon...not like in the US. Freedom! *wingz*  Ast
     
    


19,June,2004


	 
      Hmmm... anyone who dun want $10 000, can just gimme a call to donate to moi, astrea... Haha, sound like some kinda avertisement... Feel like bashing someone up right now...Cuz no money to buy the things I want... AHHH!! The stupid reverse katana costs $6000 plus and it's not Singapore money... and wat's even betta, it's sold out?! Hmph... even if not sold out I also cannot buy... *Pats pockets* Yea, it's flat and empty... Hiaz, no money no honey~ (bk title) Later muz do homework le!!! Neglecting them for dunno who long, I think that are having a very peaceful sleep, so I guess I shall not wake them up by doing them... Let them sleep enough~ ^^ *cheers* no homework tonight! YaY! Tml also no tuition! Good, good.  Feeling real mad now, being accused. Wth, I dun even know I was writing in Fion's style. Yoz gal, if u reading dis, I'm sorry I wrote in your style, which i didn't  even notice . wat's in my mind I jus write out~    Ast    Shinomori Aoshi! V kool! ^^ *drools* Dark and mysterious~~ Aniwae, doubt you guys even know who the hell he is... Too bad so sad.  
     
    


17,June,2004


	 
      Yesterday went to Orchard... Bought a berretcap and a ring (specially for my middle finger =D)! ^^ Couldn't find any knee-length socks that catch my eye... Awww... 

17,June,2004


	 
      My heart is swimming in words  formed by the wind.  My voice carried  by a cloudy tommorrow.   A mirror moved  by the moon, trembled my heart.  Soft tears  filled with a stream of stars.   Isn't it beautiful?  Two of us walking hand in hand.  I want to go to  your town, your home, your arms.   I dream of lying  against your chest.  My body in your clasp,  disappearring into the evening.   Words stopped by the wind  are a gentle illsion.  A cloud-torned tommorrow is  a far-away voice.   My heart has been in  a moon-blocked flowing mirror.  Stars that swayed and flowed  can't hide my tears.   Isn't it beautiful?  Two of us walking hand in hand.  I want to go to  your town, your home, your arms.   I dream of  your face  that softly melts  in the morning. 
     
    


15,June,2004


	 
       I'm just a simple girl  In a high tech digital world  I really try to understand  All the powers that rule this land  They say Miss J's big butt is boss  Kate Moss can't find a job  In a world of post modern fad  What was good now is bad   It's not hard to understand  Just follow this simple plan   [CHORUS]   Follow your heart  Your intuition  It will lead you in the right direction  Let go of your mind  Your Intuition  It's easy to find  Just follow your heart baby   You look at me  but you're not quite sure  Am I it or could you get more?  You learn cool from magazines  You learn love from Charlie Sheen  If you want me let me know  I promise I won't say no   [CHORUS REPEAT]  You got something that you want me to sell  Sell your sin. Just cash in.  You got something that you want me to tell  You'll love me. Wait and see.   If you want me  Don't play games  I promise  it won't be in vain  Uh-uh-uh      Rox man, this song... Quite meaningful! ^^   Ast  
     
    


15,June,2004


	 
      oh man, oh man, oh man! I really  REALLY  wanna put Shinomori Aoshi's pic in here! But I can't go into applepics... Page can't be found~~ Nvm...back to Aoshi! =D He's so kool and shuai!!! Aoshi!!! =P Too bad, he's an anime character! 

15,June,2004


	 
      Ladies and gentlemen, my conclusion for today is that... I'm gonna push my promise to tomorrow! Haha...Don't feel like doing homework le! And hopefully, can push the promise to the  day after tomorrow  (no pun intended), the next day, the following day....blah blah blah... Geesh. Anyway, got guides today. March like I was going to sleep~ *yawnz*  AND MY HAIR KEPT GETTING INTO MY EYES~!! ARGH!  Hmph! Kept blowing at them but they refuse to lesten to their owner's command! Geesh, dumb hair. And now I've gone psychotic...I'm scolding my hair... Just send me to the wood bridge hospital pls! Can go on killing spree~ Woo hoO~ ^^  Anyway, tried to imitate Shinomori Aoshi today... Kept calm, cool and basically, kept quiet! Think did a good job. 

14,June,2004


	 
      I'm  ROTTING !! Hmm...not literally... 

12,June,2004


	 
      Damn...it's 2.24pm now~~~ Nooooo....the day passes tooo fasssstt!!! Omg, the holidays are ending and our doom is gonna start~~ 

08,June,2004


	 
      Bad day, today. 

07,June,2004


	 
      Went to watch moive with sh1n today! Wearing skirts!! ^^ But I think mine was too short, I felt exposed!!! 

06,June,2004


	 
      I sux at html, flash, dreamweaver... Basically anything computer programmes... *hands out stakez* Stake me to dust pls.. -.- This means I'm dead right now and you are talking to my soul~ Good luck to you 'cuz Im gonna follow you home...   *screamz in background plus evil laughter*   Ahhhh....letz talk bout today. Same old day~, like every else Sunday.  *in a robotic voice*  Got tuition, went tuition, finish tuition. *Yawnz* Every one's favourite day of the week is most likely Sunday, mine's Saturday. 

05,June,2004


	 
      Stupid stupid stupid! My chatterbox disappeared cuz I changed template. 

04,June,2004


	 
        Morpheus    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       Searching for midis to put inside blog... Omg... I want to find the perfect one!!! *screams* Okay, okay...enough whining! Now waiting for sh1n and poodle to arrive. ^^ *hints* Mushroom head! =P Anyway, gonna continue mi fruitless search. *grins*  Ast   Life is like a dream, it starts when you were born and ends when you die...
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
      Wa.... The scrollbar still haven't change yet!! 

02,June,2004


	 
        -Motherly- You're the motherly type. You love to take care of the one you love, and generally you can be a bit overprotective and possessive, but you know, that isn't always such a bad thing. At least you'll be a good mom in the future.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Lol...me? Comforting? Nah...don't really think so. Shy, yup...should be. =P *modest* Lol. Am I gentle?? Well, ask my friends and you'll know! Haha, but I think I'm v possessive... Example : (Yea, I'm giving you an example! so PAY ME!!! $$$) I prefer to own thing rather then borrow them from people! TOOOOOOOO possessive! 

02,June,2004


	 
      Went to Fion's house today to do project! -.-||| But was playing most of the time...Geez. Lol...but v fun la! Anyway, ate Zinger meal today!! Yummy! But too full, 'cause of the cheese fries and Pepsi!! *Pukes* Anyway, I bet I'm gonna grow fat! ^^ I shall be able to fly then! 'Cause I'm a  balloon !  Fion's webcam v kool!!! I wan I wan! Hui Shin kept taking pics of us!! OMG...They actually took one pic of me... Too bad I dunno where the file is on Fion's com...or else I'll....*evil laughter in background* Heheheheheheh!! ^^ Lol! Anyway, I acted possessed 'cause 1) Fion said her house used to be haunted.                      2) They never paid any attention to me!!! Boo hooo~ ^^ They were paying attention to the computer!! 

30,July,2004


	 
       OUR CLASS'S NOTICEBOARD'S THE NICEST !!!! *Cheerz* YEAH~~  Yea, we rock, yea we rockz... shake ur booty~ ^.~ haha...Liying's the mastermind of the thingie! SHe make the design till so nice... She, Fion, Sh1n all got do.. I do so little ...haha... Anyway,  THE COLOURS V NICE!!!  Black with orange and red and gold markes and silver markers! So nice!! Black mi fav!! ^^ Spent a few hours there....3 to 4 hours??? haha... The old lady had to close the gate and asked us if we r done already or not... Haha... I kept sneezing! NOO~~ On top of my flu, I'm allegic to dust!! NOO~!! *running nose like a tap* Lol...  
     
    


24,July,2004


	 
       *sniff* AHH~!!!  I'M HAVING A STUPIF COLD AND MY HEAD HURTS!!!  <>air-conditioned  room while my head hurts....So do my eyes... THEY HURT ~~ <>   &nbsp;  Got my jersey today!   YAY~!   Haha...I just lurve it! ^^ Well...except for the nick... THEY SHUDDA PRINTED THE NICK BIGGER!!!  *ahem* Er...I complain a lot, don't I? ^.~ Oh yea, oh&nbsp;yea...I'm going for detention 'cause I nv hand in two art pieces!!&nbsp;YAHHHOOOOHOO~ ^.~&nbsp;And Mr Sia's not that bad... in fact, I think he's a bit funny and cute during the time I had detention once...haha... Like a granfather kinda figure.... ^^&nbsp;   KORN!! PpL, it's not porn nor corn nor pork....Yumm...corn plus pork, anyone?? =P Haha.... Listening to Korn's songs rite now...They are so nice!!  ANGSTY !!!   YEAH~!   I like depressing songs... Hey! I used to tell Stefan to listen to more happy songs since he likes depressing songs...Now I've become a sucker for depressing and sad songs...haha...&nbsp; Is it contagious or wat?? ^.~   &nbsp; Finally le! Updated since so long... Sorry guys n gals, boys n girls, ladies and gentlemen, mad'ams and sirs, old grandmas and old grandpas, babies in pink and babies in blue....  BICTHES AND MALE DOGS  ! <>BASTARDS ! Complete&nbsp;opposites!   &nbsp; Ast  - Let's forget about everything else that has happened. Just lose youself into this magical moment that we both created outta our love. Soaring above, flying hand-in-hand... Looking through clouds and smirking evilly at those people who are envious, 'cause they know they don't have the kinda love we have. -  &nbsp; 
     
    


24,July,2004


	 
      Now, I'm gonna solemnly swear to the wall that I'm going to :  1) Study  2) Do my homework and hand it in on time 3) Er.... Save up money 4) Try to get good grades for End-of-Year examz  .... Well, at least I'm gonna try. Nowadays when I always last minute do homework, it made me realise that it's been so long since I've actually  COMPLETED  my homework at home. The first thing that I do when I get home is : *beep* on goes the computer. Hiaz....And my grades are getting from bad 2 worse~ 

17,July,2004


	 
      Today got flag day!! So fun! Though the weather so hot... We went in pairs, each pair with a wooden box to collect money... I prefer the metal tin though...the sound of coins clashing against the metal is very nice to hear ^.^ Got one person even asked us if the wooden box is made by ourselves... Helllooo~~ My D&amp;T skills v bad and lousy de! Damn...Now I remember...I have to sketch one design for my desk tidy...I can't think of any design~!!! *SCREAMZ* Stupid stupid stupid.... &nbsp; Anyway, went home at around 6 plus today! ^.~ Was in school after NYAA which ended at 2:15pm, till 5:30pm. Quite fun...cuz there's like, only a few people (the band members in the band room, red cross squad...) and the feeling it gives me is v...sad? I'm not even sure. I just like the feelings cuz the entir canteen and the traning place behind it also quite deserted. Makes me feel free and a bit high, though a bit depressing. And sh1n kept reading the comic!!!! SSSSSOOOO, I just have to entertain myself. Lol, =P. &nbsp; Then moi son finished band at around 4 plus ba... Then she met us at the piano and we kept playing it. Haha, bet it's v noisy, all three of us playing! ^.^ But still v fun~!! Then we went to JE. ly bought food~~~ *droolz* When she offered me coke/pepsi, I realised that I v long never drink soft drinks le!! So it made me wanted to drink more, but haha... Dun wan la cuz the drink's hers. *angelic smilez* Haha... Sh1n bought clips! Omg, I saw some that I like!! orange and yellow maple leaves de!! MAPLE LEAVES!!! I LIKE MAPLE LEAVES!!! *runs around* Lol... &nbsp; Then ly went to take mrt, den sh1n n i kept waving at her! Haha, for sure attract a lot of attention de! Good good.... =P Then we raced to the 98 bus cuz she tot she saw a shuai ge! But...she saw wrongly~! haha, so funny! Den I was like "shuai ge leh?" Den looked around and dun have...Haha...

15,July,2004


	 
      *Vents anger time*   STUPID FUCKING BITCH!! GO N FUCKIN DIE DAMN YOU! WHAT STUPID UNREASONABLE IDEA DO YOU HAVE, HUH?!! WHAT THE FUCK, I DON'T CARE IF YOU HAVE HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE! YOU WERE THE ONE WHO STARTED IT! DAMN BITCH. STOP INSULTING THE COUNTRY I'm BORN IN!!!! STOP GENERALISING~!!   *steamz*   I'm feeling mean today  Not lost, not blown away  Just irritated and quite hated  Self control breaks down  Why's everything so tame?  I Like my life insane  I'm fabericating and debating  Who I'm gonna kick around   Right now  Can't find a way  To get accross the hate  When I see you  Right now  I'm feeling strange inside  I want to slash and beat you  Right now  I rip apart the things inside  That excite you  Right now  I can't control myself  I Fucking hate you   I'm feeling cold today  Not hurt just Fucked away  I'm devastated and frustrated  God I feel so bound  So why'd I feel the need?  I think it's time to bleed  I'm gonna cut myself  and watch the blood hit the ground   Right now  Can't find a way  To get accross the hate  When I see you  Right now  I'm feeling strange inside  I want to slash and beat you  Right now  I rip apart the things inside  That excite you  Right now  I can't control myself  I Fucking hate you   You open your mouth again  I swear I'm gonna break it  You open your mouth again,  Oh God I cannot take it   Shut up, shut up, shut up or I'll Fuck you up [x6]   Right now  Can't find a way  To get accross the hate  When I see you  Right now  I'm feeling strange inside  I want to slash and beat you  Right now  I rip apart the things inside  That excite you  Right now  I can't control myself  I Fucking hate you   I Fucking hate you [x4]  I Fucking hate you Shut up [x2]    
     
    


12,July,2004


	 
      Lame title... Now in school, nothing to do in IT lesson. Honestly, I think the money that we paid for the IT lessons are a waste. Or maybe it's just me, 'cause I don't seem to learn anything from the lessons I've attended... 

03,July,2004


	 
      Korn's  Right Now  very nice to listen to...Hehe, it's heavy metal if I'm correct... ^.^ Today talked to my lAo pO for almost one hour! =) Talk a lot with her! SO fun! Wow, I think I miss talking on the phone for long hours! =D The period of time where I oftenly talk for more than an hour on the phone was in Pri 6! Wow...time  does  fly!   *Linkin Park's Numb came on* *Change it to Daniel Beddingfield*   Today did IPW... I lost my temper. Haha, told them that I will be hot-tempered de when I get stressed or got a lot of responsibilities de! So chiam all those people who are near me that time...Hehe, pai seh worhz to all friends! Sorry!  Anyway, I'm gonna wake up early tml... OMG~! I think 6am ba...So KooL, use the computer when the sky is still very dark! I LurvE the NigHt...(as much as I luRvE my lAo pO!!)   *chantz chantz chantz*  Korn RoCkz Korn R0cKz   Their songs quite angsty! Hahaa, LurVe angsty songs~ Yay~ depressing! ^.~ Anyway, today's the 3th~!!! 5 more days till deadline!  OMG~~! NOOOO~!!! THE HORROR~!!!  *screamz in hell*  Er... Cried today...Over some sms~!! Bcuz poOdlE accidentally deleted away  his  sms-es! Den I cry 

02,July,2004


	 
      Jus saw my ex-classmate yesterdae! So long nv see her le! ^.^ She like get along with the teachers so well! =D Saw terrence jus now too! Waah, he v shuai! Luckily he nv saw me (I was across the street) haha... I'm a big disgrace...So sad.. =P  Anyway, Yingx wore LOW CUTE shirt!!! Wow, her figure v gd! *drools* Lol, jk! I not gonna act lesbiany le! Cuz dey sae v er xin... Den like feel so rejected like dat, haha... But I'll still act lesbiany with my wife!! LAO PO~~ *lovey eyes*  Tml have IPW... When I saw the date that I wrote today, which is the 2th of July, my body went cold... It's like...only 6 days away from deadline?!!! Then I was like, keeping quieting for a while... So scared... And wat's worse, I have a phobia of the word IPW le...Haha, no la, jk! *relaz*  Gonna be dark soon... I needa bathe! Later den update ba! By the way, songs in Long Vacation RoCkZ!  Ast  - No one is gonna stop me from loving you. My heart refuse to and my body is yielding for that warm feeling of you beside me. -
     
    


01,July,2004


	 
      I'm so sleepy right now... But I still need to do IPW den hunt for papers later for the English File... *hardworking* =P Anyway, so long nv smsed ZW le... Kinda miss smsing with him... =D Wait, I miss smsing with him alot... Waaaahh, maybe he's having an outdoors camp so he nv returned my sms to him...Or maybe he's too tired to sms back or maybe he's ... ignoring me? Having smsing him for an entire week during the nights made me miss chatting with him... Even though haveta do it secretly...or else my parents will ask, "Who are you smsing?". And if I reply saying that I was smsing an online friend, they will say "Do not chat with online strangers..."blah blah blah...Hmm, but he's quite a nice guy!! ^.^ Anyway, maybe shall just try to sms him again when he's back during the weekends... *hold paper to my face* CONCENTRATE ON IPW...  Ast  - Missing the days gone, missing the talks we have. Oh babe, can we ever go back again? -
     
    


01,July,2004


	 
      OKay, my heart's starting to pump up right NOW. Damn annoyed. Jus read yiting's blog. Hey, she's mention me. Well, for the "unlike a certain SOMEONE" comment, I prefer if people mention me using my name. Hey, I'm mentioned in that comment so at least I have to right to say that rite?! It's me u r talking about. What's more, if she wanted to watch the moive, den OF COURSE we have to have IPW everyday den till Saturday, cuz we are seriously gonna rush through. Yea, and as for the "den next week u dun go watch movie lorz", okay, it is commanding, but for god's sake  dey can SURELY watch it after ipw fin rite? It's not as though we have much time for our ipw that we can spare to watch a moive... WADEVA...I said I'm not gonna be mad...breathe in breathe out...  AsT  - No Quote -   
     
    


01,July,2004


	 
      Ahh... Jus realised something... Though I dislike Ms Kokila, if I keep hating her, it will make me feel so sianz and irritation by what she did whenever I'm in her classes... And anyway, by changing the dislike to like, it might even make her classes seem interesting instead of boring. She never really did anything bad to me...(now then I realise) so there's really nothing about her that shud make dislike her... Maybe she's being too bossy or whatever,but everyone  DO  have some bad points about them. She's still a human afterall... And just like keep disliking her for no reason seems a bit childish 'cuz it's not as though she killed my faimly *touch wood* or harmed me in any way... Hmmmm... (looks at clockz) Time to bathe! With the rubber duck (quack quack!) =P  Ast  - When there's love, there's pain... So babe, can we just go through the pain first than the love? - 
     
    


01,July,2004


	 
      I'm not gonna be mad, sad or anything that is depressing. I wanna learn such skills to prepare me for kendo!!!! KENDO!!!!! KENDO KENDO KENDO!!!!!!!!! Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmm... It'd be kooL to be able to fight using a wooden sword... Able to show off to others that you know fight skills...But that is not the principle of kendo. HIazz....  Anyway, I'M GONNA SAY IT RIGHT NOW. I'm not gonna be submissive... (Where did that come from?? *looks around* ) I hate people who are submissive, but I read in a book that "What you dislike in others, you will find them in yourselves too". -.- Is that true?? Haha, so if I hate submissive people I'm submissive too?! 


