


28,May,2004


	 
      ~~IMPORTANT NOTICE~~ Please note that this fiction piece comprises of many stories and movies (range from harry potter to matrix and from van helsing to mutant x) so please bear with the various characters.   ~~DISCLAIMER~~ Most of the characters in the fiction does not belong to me, they belong to their various creators, thus I will keep this disclaimer short and simple by saying ALL characters in this story does not belong to me except from Hillary, Kay and Catherine(so much for a short disclaimer)    

26,May,2004


	 
      Title: Version 0.1  Story Overview: Thousands of years ago, Lucifer forged a set of stones that would enable their keepers the ability to control all the darkness in the world. Unfortunately for him, three of the seven stones were lost when he was banished to hell. The remaining stones he had were then passed on to his son, Count Vladislause Dragulia, for safe keeping. Now, the dark lord Voldemort wants the stones so as to rule the world, but the only way to obtain them is from Dracula, and Dracula has no intentions of giving the stones up without a fight.   
     

    


26,May,2004


	 
      This is version  


02,June,2004



       
      ~~Disclaimer~~ This fic contains characters from harry potter is is based mainly on it. But characters from the Lord of the Rings and Van helsing will also be included.  _________________________________________________________________________________________  Story Overview: As the war between Voldemort and the wizards of the light reach it's climax, new faces are begining to appear on the battlefield. The muggle born girl called Liz is no exception, this is the story about her life in a world that she did not even know off two years ago. The life where her loyalties are going to be tested and past friends become enemies.     
     

    



26,June,2004


	 
              "Kay, what in the name of god are you doing?" Gracevre asked in disbelief as she was her best friend and one time mentor Kayburen pack up her belongings in her small room in the Vatcican City Underground, headquaters of the Knights of the Holy Order.          "You can bloody well see what I'm doing Grace," pausing for only a moment to look at grasper in the eye, "and if your so thick headed as to not know what I'm doing, you can go ask to find out." A clearly pissed off Kayburen replied and went back to packing her belongings.          "But you can't leave now, not when the wizards are spoiling for a fight, your the best knight the Order has. We need you." Gracevre replied, while moving to bar Kayburen from the door.          "Ok let me get this straight with you before you, I'm leaving for two reasons, first one I can never tell you or anyone else for that matter. Second one is because..."          Before Kayburen could even finish her explanation, Gracevre had begun with her "hairdryer speech" which was so fearsome that it had won grasper the respect of the Cardinals. "For god's sake Kay! There is no viable reason for you to leave the order! And if you have sinned in any way, the Pope himself would be glad to bless you. After the multitude of Udead you have rid from this world any holy man would be honored to bless you!"          With the mention of the Pope, Kayburen's eyes flashed angrily as she turned to face grasper. "Grace just for your information, it was the bloody Pope that passed the verdict to have me exiled from the Order."          A moment of uncomfortable silence followed as Gracevre just stood rooted at the spot as she let Kayburen's last words sink in. Kayburen on the other hand just pick up her bag of belongings and pushed past grasper and made her way towards the exit of the city.          Kayburen knew that she would one day see her friend again but when that fateful day came, Kay could not guarantee that she and her friend would be fighting on the same side. She also knew that there was no hope in anyone trying to coax her back, she and the Pope had made up their minds. Kay did not wish to cause further damage to a kind that was created by her very family, and the Pope would not have a damned soul serving under his command.          Deep within her thoughts Kay did not notice that she had already made her way out of the underground and was in the bright sunshine of Rome's summer. Just beyond the gates of the Vatican, Kay could see her faithful stead still waiting for her, Joust. As she made towards the unknown, she was suddenly stopped by the voice of one she had known as a "father" for so long.         "We found out about your sentence from the Pope and just came to give you a little something that will help along the way." Cardinal Jottel said in his slow wheezy voice, with that he tossed Kayburen a leather bag and turned back towards the Vatican. "Just a little far well gift from me and Giles." He added as he walked off. To any passer-by one would have thought that the cardinal had no emotion for the loss of his friend, but to those who had spent years with the man could sense the sadness within his voice.          Kayburen caught the thick leather bag with one hand, and nodded to the retreating figure of her past mentor, and whispered "I'll miss you Jottel" With that Kayburen swung onto her waiting stead and made her way into the unknown. As she blized past the streets, only the most keen eyed of creatures could see the single tear that slipped down her cheek. At that point of time, Kay swore that she was cursed to live a hard life, little did she know that the Devil still had more plans for her and her family.   _________________________________________________________________________________________  Here's the first chapie....its only a rough draft so please kindly tell me any mistakes or places where you are not happy with. Go ahead and flame me if you wish.           
    


17,June,2004


	 
        

14,June,2004


	 
      StoryOverview: War has broken out between the Knights of the Holy Order and the Wizards (Voldemort Rules over the wizarding world) Now, a group of friends must choose, which side to stand on. For their decision will affect the course of the war itself.   


01,June,2004


	 
      ~~Disclaimer~~  OK this story is considered as an original fiction, despite the fact that some un-original characters will be chucked into it.   Story Overview:   Every two thousand years, hell is unleashed upon the earth to curb the expansion of its living creatures. The year 2005 is that very year. Now mankind will have to fight the army of darkness, before darkness claims the land they had once ruled over. But unlike the past generations that have fought for their survival, this generation has one major advantage...They have discovered the existence of magic. Despite the fact that only 40% of the population has the ability to wield magic, it still gives them a large advantage. The only problem is that the new Wizards are starting to feel superior to their "weaker" human counterparts, who are unable to wield magic. This will only lead to trouble within the ranks as now the "squibs" are starting to feel that their kind are being used as "Calvary folder" and are being killed without reason. Now the "squibs" must chose their side. To fight for humanity or for darkness. 
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
      Hugo &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    




