
30,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THAT ONE IS DEFFINETLY A KEEPER!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SOMEONE'S GOT A HANGOVER!!!!! HEHEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY GUYS.... LOOK UP!!!! SAY WAZZ UP!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY GUYS..... HOW BOUT A LIL' SMILE 4 THE CAMERA???&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink     JUST HAVING FUN!!! HIHIHI&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THIS WEEKEND IN GALVESTON!!! PIRATES BEACH!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    CAN U SAY WOW???&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THESE ARE MY GIRLSS!!! LEAVE THE HOTEL.... STRAIGHT TO THE PARTAY!!! FIRST PARTAY OF THE SUMMER!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GET THE PARTY STARTING!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AT THE DOUBLE TREE HOTEL!!!! YEAH.......&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWW....CUTIES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! BEFORE RON CARTER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GIRL POWER BABY

29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    BABY GIRLLL...I LOVE YA!!!!!!!! CAN I ASK U SOMETHING??? HIHI..... CAN I HAVE  YOUR BOOBIES?? :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    YAYY...ITS SUMMERR!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THIS WEEKEND.... THURSDAY!!! YA BABE LAST DAY OF SCHOOL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! IT WAS A LOOOOONNNGGGG YEAR!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I GOT A HAIR CUT! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AAAAAAAAAAAAhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh thats SOOOOOOOOOOOOO CUTEEEEEEEEE!!!!!!! FALL IN LOVE W IT GUYS!!!!!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Go RedSkins!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Got the whole squad??? hehe Almost&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    eeeeeeeekkkkkkk....wwe look like we're 10!!!!!!!!!! lol&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    On the was to Hooters!!! Get some grub!!!! Haha&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Spring Game.... Awwww.... dont we look soo innocent!!! Hihi&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Clint and Daniel....Ahhhh....its good to be a Senior ahn?? LOl&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I Got to dance w the pimp!!! hehehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GIRLLL U LOOK AWSOME!!! .... CANT SAY MUCH ABOUT ME THOUGH...LOL....O well who cares??? Prom is almost over!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WHERES ASHLEY BIRD??&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THE ALCOHOL IS KICKIN IN!!! HAHA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    DO IT DOGGY STYLE!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WHAT A PIMP AHN NICK?&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    BRITNEY...GOT U TOO!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    FINALLY AT PROM... HEHEHE GIRLS... U GUYS ARE SWEETHEARTS... KATIE... WE'LL MISS U NEXT YEAR!! COLLEGE GIRLS RULE!! HIHI&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I DRANK IT ALLLL!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    U GOT IT....NOW FRENCH KISS!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    O HOW I WISH THAT WAS A REAL CIG!!!!!!HIHI&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWWW JUST SMILES&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WE'RE PARTYING IT ON!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THATS A GOOD ONE!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    hehehehe...... YA WE'RE DRUNK!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Who wants to kiss a snake?????????&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The traditional Pic!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ITS A HAPPY HAPPY DAY....OR WE'RE JUST TOO DRUNK! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    mAn...I LOVE THIS PIC!!!!!!!!!!!!! GUYS THOSE ARE MY HANDS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! DONT THEY LOOK PRETTY!!!! HEHEHE.....DAMN THANK GOD I HAD GOT MY NAILS DONE!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    So So CuTE!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LoL...Calm down Burrows.... the food is goin no where!!! JK&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    MmMmMm........Check out the food DuDe!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Before Prom.....just gettin started!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    its PrOm!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    i wanna be the Maid of Honor Guys!!!!!!!!!!! HehE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    gO gO gO!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    iTS tHe whOlE gANg!!!!!!YaY&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    gETTiN fUCkEd Up!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    YO BALLERSSSS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HAPPY B-DAY COLINN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The Partay doesnt stop!!!!!!!!!!! hehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Its the life of the rich and famous BabY!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Com'on.....already???? That ones passed out.... hahaha &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My B-DAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ParTay at the InterContinental Hotel!!!!!! Its good to be a Model!!!!! Check out the guys we get!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    05 yaa BaBy!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Brownie..... SwEeTiE..... We're official PiMpS!!! hehe :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    JohN CarTer!!! Dude... Stoned? Naw!!! LOL....hehehe I've got u on camera Too!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Thats a Keeper!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SMile Girls.... we're goin to the WC PaRtAy!!!!! uHuhUuu&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    mY First Astros Game!!! Remember Carrie??? HehEhe... OMG.... how lame could i be??? LOL....&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Cheerleading TryOuts SUCK @$$!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Wakin up early sucks ahn Coutney?? haha&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL...There goes a Giant Worm!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WTF???????????? I AGREEE!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    OPSSYYY&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hey there.... i cant be that DRUNK!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    we're having fun!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    hey Priscilla... We all know y your smiling now!!!!! hehehehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LETS GO W THE CHUCHU TRAIN!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THIS PPL ARE FREAKS.... CHECK THAT OUT!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL...... KILL ME FOR DOING THAT!!! BUT.... COM'ON ITS CARNAVAL!!!!!!!!!!! AND BTW.... ITS PLASTIC!!! HIS COULDNT POSSIBLY BE THAT BIG!!! LOL HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WE'RE W THE CHICKEN!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Lets get the party startedd!!! CarNaVal...HERE WE COME! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    CarNaVal in Austin!!! Partying w the UT crew!!!!! Crazy Nite!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    RaNdOm GiRlS nItE oUt!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hot MAMAS Ready to ParTay!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    I'VE JUST BEEN PIMPED!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    YEAH...SLOW MOTION FOR ME AHN DANI?&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HOW CUTEE!!!! CANT BLAME ME.... I LOV YALL!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY BABY!!!! SAY YA!!! RANDOM GET 2GATHER AT COLINS...THATS HIW WE DO IT!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Michaels gonna Pass OUt!!! CANT HANDLE IT?? HEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sorry Chris... your tong is not long enough to reach my cheek!!! hehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY FRED... GOT THAT ONE ON CAMERA....&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GET AWAY FROM ME... U FREAK!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Just sippin on it!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    and it is!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    looks crouded!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Ya,,, theres the alcohol!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    say CHEESE DANNY!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Enter the year with a beer on your hand and partay on your mind!!!!!!!!!!!! hells ya!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ya.... NICE PIC hihihihi&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Neww yearssssssssss!!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    awww thats a cute one!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me and my mommy on Christmas !!!!! Mom u look like a Penguin!!! hahaha&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    DONT WANNA GET CLOSE!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SMILE BEN...YOUR ON HIDDIN CAMERA!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    O GOOD TIMES AT LOS CHURROS!!! Is there a better after hour&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


30,June,2004


    
       
      Gavin DeGraw  I don't need to be anything other Than a prison guard's son I don't need to be anything other  Than a specialist's son I don't have to be anyone other Than the birth of two souls in one Part of where I'm going, is knowing where I'm coming from I don't want to be Anything other than what I've been trying to be lately All I have to do Is think of me and I have peace of mind I'm tired of looking 'round rooms Wondering what I've got to do Or who I'm supposed to be I don't want to be anything other than me I'm surrounded by liars everywhere I turn I'm surrounded by imposters everywhere I turn I'm surrounded by identity crisis everywhere I turn Am I the only one who noticed? I can't be the only one who's learned I don't want to be  Anything other than what I've been trying to be lately All I have to do Is think of me and I have peace of mind I'm tired of looking 'round rooms Wondering what I've got to do  Or who I'm supposed to be I don't want to be anything other than me Can I have everyone's attention please? If you're not like this and that, you're gonna have to leave I came from the mountain The crust of creation My whole situtaion-made from clay to stone And now I'm telling everybody I don't want to be Anything other that what I've been trying to be lately All I have to do Is think of me and I have peace of mind I'm tired of looking 'round rooms Wondering what I've got to do Or who I'm supposed to be I don't want to be anything other than me I don't want to be 
       
    
    


27,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    YAY GIRLS WE'RE AT THE HOOKAH BAR...(havent been here in years)...well... AFTER THAT WHOLE FIGHT WE HAVE TO GET SOME STRESS RELEASED!!! HEHEHE SORRY BOUT ALL THAT!! U GUYS KNOW I LOVE YALL!!!!! WE'RE THE HOT TRIO!!! hehehe....WAIT A MIN... WHOS GONNA MEET MICHAEL J??? WE ARE!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THIS IS MY FAVORITE PIC!!!! WILL WE ADORE U..!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GETTIN FREAKY AT THE HOOKAH BAR!!! HEHEHEHE... NICK PIMPIN......................... HAHAHAHA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Ben u pissed me off!!!! Seriously... HaHaHa&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    This pic looks soooo good!!!! Mag girl....omg.... WTF? I still cant believe you're this tanned!!! LoL... Will u have a lot of catching up to do!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Russel!!!! you're sooo sweet!!! Loved meeting u... We all have to hang out some more!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Nick.... look how lucky u are..... u have these 2 hot girls neXt to u!!!! FEEL SPECIAL!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Damnn gurl...u look tanned!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! UhuHuuuu Brazilian power workin right there!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    awww yall are soo cute&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Tank Tank.... Nice meeting u dude.... we HAVE TO GO CLUBBIn!!! HEHEHEH I WANNA C U BUSTING OUT THOSE MOVES...hehehehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hey u guys!!!! Having a good time/???&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       
      Shouldve never told u  That I cared about u  Didnt think tha it would be, so bad  Shouldve never kissed u  Shouldve never held ur hand  How could u tell me tha u liked me When I know u were just tryin to play me  But u'r the fool  bc I kno how 2 switch the game up on u  And n the end I kno who will lose  I played this game before  And I cant play no more  Wha do u take me for  Its not what u thought  So dont play games w me  bc I play to teach  Its not tha serious  I never put tha much thought into us  It wasnt that I loved you  I was curious  Who did u think tha u were involved w  Now babe u should kno tha it aint tha serious  It should concern u tha Im always 1 step ahead of u  So tha should let u kno tha wha u do  Ive done before, its nothin new  So run those games on someone who cant be fooled  I can almost see lies coming through ur teeth  In every word u speak u make it clear to me  Tha u're playin wrong n ur game aint strong  Ive been in this 2 long, so just be moving on  Got to find a way to let these feelings go    
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWWW... I MISSED HANGIN OUT W U GUYS!!!! HAHAHA... CHECK OUT THE PIMPS!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WOW...HEHEHE... FROM THIS ANGLE U GUYS DONT LOOK THAT BAD!!! LOL.... JK&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL...NICE TRAVIS NICEE!!! LOL NOW STOP IT... YOU'Re SCARING ME NOW.... HAHAHA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LETS PLAY POCKER!!!!!!!!!!! Y DO GIRLS NEVER KNOW HOW TO PLAY POCKER??? LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWW....I WANT A TATOO ALSOOO!!!!!!! THATS SOOO CUTE!!!! LOVE THE LIL IRISH GUY MASONN!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY CAROLINE... NICE SEEIN U AGAIN!!!! HOPE YOUR LIKIN LSU..... HEHEHE :) ILL GO VISIT U THERE...DONT WORRY!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SHANNON BABE.... FORGET ALL THAT DRAMA!!! ITS TIME TO PARTY!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL...COLIN Y DO U ALWAYS HAVE TO TAKE YOUR CLOTHES OFF WHEN YOUR DRUNK??? LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


19,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY ANDREA!!!! LOL... THANKS FOR DRIVING US TO GALVESTON!!! HEHE O YA... AND BTW... THANKS FOR ALMOST KILLING US TOO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL..... &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


18,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ON THE CAR HALF WAY TO GALVESTON!!! HIHIHI.... &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


18,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A DAY AT THE GALVESTON BEACH W THE GIRLS!!! HEHEHE.... PLANNING ON GETTIN TAN AND MEETING SOME HOT GUYS!!! HEHEHEHE :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


18,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWW.... THATS SUCH A HOT PIC!!! CAT YOUR SO ADORABLE BABE.... WISH U THE BEST OF LUCK W YO HOT BABE!!!!!HEHEHE YA'LL R THE HOTTEST COUPLE!!!!!!! ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SUMMER SCHOOL SUCKSSSSSSSS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    DOUG DOUG DOUG DOUG!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    DO IT MADINA STYLE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL MAGGIE THATS ALL YOURS!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    PARTY AT DAVES AND JUSTINS!!!!! SMILE GIRLS!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL....OMG IM SUCH A PIMP!!!! CHECK ME OUT W ALL THESE GUYS!!! LOL...HAHAHAHA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Emily and the guys!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    awww yo my lil girl Shannon!!!! your awsome!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
      As we try to just be friends  I often think of what could've been However, I feel as though my heart will never mend. i wonder where we went wrong,  our relationship sounds like so many sad songs will u ever see what u meant to me? will u ever miss, what we had? or do the memories just make u mad? i try so hard to move on but i dont want to realize that u r really gone. y cant we make it together, u and me? Am i not good enough? y cant u just be w me? I think of the days when u held me tight I felt like everything, was going to be alright. But all of the sudden, we started to fight. And our feelings for each other were soon outta sight. I hope that one day u will see that u lost everything... ...when u lost ME!!! 
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A NIGHT W THE GIRLS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! UHUUUHUHUUU LADIES.... PARTAY AT THE DOUBLE TREE!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HERE COMES THE HOOCHIE MAMMAS READY TO ROCK THE PARTAY!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY SHANNON.... WE'RE SOOOOO CUTEE!!! I LOVED MEETIN U!!! YOUR AWSOME....!!! THESE GUYS DONT KNO WHAT THEY'RE MISSIN!!! F* THESE STUPID GUYS!! HEHE.... LETS GET OURSELVES SOME NEW MEAT!!! LOL JK&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWWW....THATS A GOOD ONE... BUT... CHRIS YOUR NOT SUPPOSE TO BE IN IT!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    STAN.... WHAT THE HELL R U DOING??? HAVYS' GOT HIS SHIRT ON.... U CANT GET HIS NIPPLE LIKE THAT!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GETTIN.... DRUNK DRUNK DRUNK!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Thatsss cutez!!!!!!!!!!! last moments at the Hotel...HiHiHi... check out the view!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GET THE HELL OUTTA THE PIC HAVY!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    There goes the BaLlaR!!!! hehehehe.......... Sara Kicks @ss!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


12,June,2004


    
       
        urlLink   


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    NOTHING LIKE GOIN OUT W THE GIRLS AND HAVING SOME FUN AFTER KICKIN SOME @$$!!!HAHAHA DONT I LOOK LIKE I JUST GOT OUT OF A FIGHT??? LOL NAW... DANG GIRLS... SORRY BUT... WE LOOK HOT!!!!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    GUYS.... I LOOOOOOOVVVVVVEEEEEEEEEEE THIS PIC OF US!!!!! SUPPER CREATIVE!!!! WE'RE DEFFINETLY SMOKIN'!!! HAHHAHA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    YAY GIRLS.... ARE YALL READY TO PARTAY??&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me and my girLie Maggie...LOVE U GIRL!!! SORRY U HAD TO SEE ME KICK SOME ASS TODAY!!! I KNO I KNO... PRETTY BAD!!! HAHAHA....&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Yo... U tHeRe THE CAMERA IS HERE!!!! STOP CHECKIN OUT SHANNON!!! HEHEHEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Danielle... baby... do u even kno hows that next to u??? LOL... &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hey GirLs... Look how hot u guys look!!! UhUuuhuuu lol... Loved meetin u guys!!!! U're AWSOMEE!!!! hehe&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    EkKk... HihiHi... My nEwEst BuDdY!!! HeHe...&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AwWwWw...how cute u guys!!!! LOL...&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
      Lamar is sooo f*ing full of drama!!! OMG.... like seriously ppl have nothing to do at that school!!!... These low class/white trash/slut/pot heads have absolutly nothing to do besides piss off ppl like me!!! And let me tell u... thats not a really good idea!!! Its hillarious how ppl can talk shit and when it comes to actually doing something about it, they chicken out!! They're so full of cr@p!!!See im a really nice and calm person... but dont push my buttoms!!! U'll see me go crazy! haha... I dont like fightin... that is just the lowest u can go!!! It is soo degrating... but i mean... sometimes a girls' gotta do what a girls' gotta do!!! but ya... just makin it short...        ....Dont call a fight u cant pull off!!!....                          .... LoL....                                    .... Ya Lauran Reed ....                                            .... Who kicked yo ass???? lol ....
       
    
    


08,June,2004


    
       
        urlLink   


08,June,2004


    
       
      Whats up guys???? Im finally back in town!!! UhuUuhuu... The bad thing is.... there's nothing to doo!!! I cant believe my summer school starts tomo!! What a pain in the @$$!!! But o well... u gotta do what u gotta do!!!  This is gonna be a pretty busy summer!!! cant wait till summer schools over...... ROAD TRIP... YAY!!! HEHEHE.... BTW.... GIRLS.... WE'RE GONNA PARTY TONITE, AHN??? HIHIHI MUAH XOXO KISSEXS....... LOV YALL!!!
       
    
    


06,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    EARLY IN MORNING.... ON OUR WAY TO CAMP!!!! ARGH... WE'RE ALL SOOO SLEEPY!!! WE'RE GONNA SLEEP ALL THE WAY THERE I KNO FOR SURE!! HEHE... COM'ON ITS 7 IN THE MORNING!!! THATS Y WE HAVE THE SHADES HEHEHEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    FIRST STOP IN DALLAS...WHAT DO WE DO???.... GOO EAT OF COURSE HEHEHHEE!!!! WHERE?? SONIC... HEHEHE....OMG U GUYS WONT BELIEVE... THEIR SONIC IS SOOOOOOOOOO NICE!!! WE ODER OUR FOOD THROUGH THE PHONE!!! WE SIT ON THE TABLE AND GET THAT LIL' PHONE AND JUST ORDER!!! HEHEHE ITS SOOOO KOOLLL!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    FIRST DAY AT SMU  CHEER CAMP!!! READY GIRLS??? WELL 2 LATE... WE BETTER BE!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    OMG...WE'RE SOO AWSOME!!! THIS PIC WAS TAKEN AT LIKE 7 IN THE MORNING AND LOOK HOW ADORABLE WE LOOK!!!! HEHEHE...&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THERES SOME OF THE NCA STAFF!!!! THEY'RE SOOO AWSOME!!!! TO BAD I DIDNT GET THE HOT GUYS!!! :/ O WELL...HEHEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    CHECK THAT OUT!!!! ISNT THAT AWSOME??? I LEARNED HOW TO DO THAT!! HEHEHE...WELL NOT EXACTLY..BUT... I FLEW FOR THE FIRST TIME!!! HELL YA&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOOK HOW CUTE.... THE WHOLE SQUAD W OUR OUTFITTS!!! HEY GIRLS... WE DONT LOOK BAD AT ALL W THIS RED UNIFORM!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWWW...WHAT A CUTE PIC!!! THIS IS ME AND THE GIRLS AT THE FIELD!!!HEHHE...YA CAN U SEE THE LOOK ON MY FACE?? HEHE.. THATS CAUSE I HAD JUST SEEN THE HOTTEST GUY!!! LOL... U WOULD BE AMAZED OF HOW MANY HOT GUYS WERE THERE JUST TO SEE THE CHEERLEADERSS!!! EHHE UHUUU...FUN STUFF!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY GIRLS....HEHEHE....SMILE... WE'RE DONE FOR THE DAY....WELL...ALMOST DONE!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LATE NIGHT REUNIONS!!!! AFTER WORKING OUT ALL DAY...EVERYDAY....WE STILL HAVE TO DO HOMEWORK!!! ARGH!!! BUT WE HAVE FUN!!! HEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    THE WHOLE SQUAD AT THE SMU CAMPUS PREPARING FOR THE EVALUATIONS!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HELL YAA!!! AFTER ALL THE HARD WORK... WE GOT IT BABES!!! HEHEHE.... YAY... OUR FIRST AWARDS...!!!! SUPERIOR FOR OUR CHANT AND EXCELLENCE FOR OUR CHEER!!! BTW...WE ALSO WON THE TEAM AWARD FOR BEST SPIRIT BY THE OTHER SQUADS!!!! GOOO SKINSSS!!!! WE ROCK!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ME AND OUR BUDDY!!! HEY BRI...THANKS FOR HELPIN US W/ OUR STUNTS, DANCES, CHEERS, JUMPS.... THANKS FOR HELPIN US OVER ALL!!! YOUR A SWEETIE... WE'LL MISS U!!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY ROOM MATES!!! HOW BOUT ALL THAT WAKING UP EARLY ALL WEEK, AHN??? HEHE...BUT YA...WE MADE IT!!! LET ME TELL U... IT WAS STUFF GOIN TO SLEEP LATE AND WAKING UP THAT EARLY AND HAVING TO GO TO CHEER AEROBICS!!! LOL... HAPPY 2DAY IS THE LAST DAY? HEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AWW...LOOK HOW CUTE WE LOOK!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SMILE GUYS... WE GET TO TAKE THE SPIRIT STICK HOMEE!!!! YAY....AND WE WON THE EXCELLENCE AWARD FOR CHEER AND SUPERIOR AWARD FOR OUR SIDELINE CHANT!!!!WOW...WE ROCK....BUT...ARGH... OMG GIRLSS....I CANT BELIEVE ITS THE LAST DAY OF CAMPP!!!!!  WE HAD SOOOO MUCH FUNN!!!!!! ARGHH... ILL MISS U GUYS!!! CANT WAIT TILL THE SEASON STARTS!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
      I seriously dont understand! I seriously do not understand this whole relationship thing! I mean... somewhere along the way i must have missed a clue! I must have skipped a sign....cause seriously i have no idea about what a relationship is consist of!!!  If u like a guy and u really want it to work out.... be almost sure that IT WONT happen!! And if u dont really care bout it, be positive that he'll come around!! well... i just figured since im so bad at figuring things out that i would just not try at all!! Thats were i got it all wrong!! Things seem to be even more complicated once u have no intention to make it a big deal! I was trying to take life not as serious... i was just trying to have fun! It seems that i was lookin for fun in the wrong place!!  I thought u were lookin for the samething as me... apparently not! Why did u have to expect sooooo much from me? im sorry but as i said... i was just trying to enjoy life! Im sorry if i didnt feel the samething as u did but as i told u... dont expect much from me!!! I thought u were passed all this drama...but i just realized drama will always be there! And it is so ironic that U were the one that got so involved!!! Im sorry baby...but i think u should go for another person!!! U should go for someone as jealous and so emotionally out of balance AS U!!! And im sorry...ILL BE THE BIGGER PERSON...yes... ILL BE THE BIGGER PERSON AND TELL U THE TRUTH... ILL TELL U WHAT IM FEELING....(ISNT THAT WHAT U ALWAYS WANTED?)    IM FEELING SOMETHING IVE NEVER FELT FOR ANYONE ELSE....                              ....IM FEELING DISCUSSTED BY U!!!!!                                               (SORRY...U WANTED TO HEAR THE TRUTH!)
       
    
    


02,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    SORRY PPL........... ITS CENSURED!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    LOL.......OMG WHATS GOIN ON??????????? THESE PPL ARE CRAZY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHH I LOVE U GUYS SOOOOO MUCHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    WHAT THE F* IS GOIN ON???? LOL... THE KIDS HAVE GONE WILD!!!!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    gO gO gO...... HELLOOOOOOOO????? BEER BONG!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ShOw TheM wHaT U'rE MaDe oF!!! DONT MESS W NICK... HE CAN SMASH U JUST LIKE THAT!!! hAhEHi&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HeLL yA NICK...SHow them WHAT u do BeSt!!!! HEHEHE&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    HEY JENNIFER... LOL... U'RE ON THE INTERNET!!! LOL... DID IT JUST TO PISS U OfF!!! LOV YO THOUGH...mUAh XOXO&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    TuEsDaY NiTe!!!! UhUuhuuu.... u guys are sooooo hotttttt!!!!!!! LOL..... &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    AT PAULS GRADUATION PARTAY!!! bABeS....dOnT wE LOOK aDOrAbLE?? I cANt bELiEvE PAUL IS GOIN TO COLLEGE...:/ WE'LL MISS U PAUL!!! HERE'S A PIC OF YO HOT MAMAS!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    dAViD n MiKE.......I LoVe U gUyS!!!! hEHehE..... cANt BELIEVE URE GOIN TO LAMAR NEXT YEAR MiKe!!!! wE'rE gOnNA hAVe SOOOOO mUCh FuN!!!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    awww baby....we look adorable!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I LOVE THIS PIC OF US SOOOOO MUCH!!!!!!!!!!! HIIHIHI&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
      What I choose to do is of no concern to you and your friends Where I lay my hat may not be my home, but I will last on my own 'Cause it's me, and my life it's my life... Oh the world has sat in the palm of your hand not that you'd see and I'm tired and bored of waiting for you and all those things you never 'Cause it's me, and my life it's my life...  
       
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Saturday night!!!! Clubbin night ended up being movie night!!!  &nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


26,July,2004


    
       
         "I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work."       &nbsp; Thomas Alva Edison        "The worst of times only occur to make the best of times seem even better"    


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ANthony.... i LoVe this pic!! hehehe ITS MY CELLYS BACKGROUND!!! HEHEHE :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


14,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    On the way to Burrow's before heading off to Anthony's!!! hehehe :)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


14,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    At Anthony's House!!!! Just chillin for the night!!!!!!!!!! We laughed our asses off!!!!!!!!!!!! LMAO&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


14,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Awwww.... Theres Peter, Shannon...!!! U guys do make a cute couple!!! hahahaha ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


14,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hey Shannon...lol...heres your Cabanna Boy with your I love Cabanna Boys Undies.... LOL..... very sexy... very very sexy!!!!!! lol&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    


14,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Shannon and Bengie...&nbsp; urlLink   
       
    
    



