
29,May,2004


    
       
          NO!!!!!!!!!!!Diana didn't win!!!!!!!!!!!(sob! )I have to admit that i am a Diana DeGarmo fan.  Diana DeGarmo rocks!She is  .Her is just great.I even named my neopet after her!(chuckle! )    This is   DiAnA_dE_gArMo.       &nbsp;I liked Diana when I saw her singing,"My Heart Will Go On" . I&nbsp;felt insulted when Simon said something about her being immmature.I like her because she is very cute, sweet&nbsp;and a great singer.I do like Fantasia but I very much prefer Diana.Both are great singers but everyone knew that Fantasia would win even though some(like me) still surport Diana. Even though she is the second in American Idol, there is a possibility that she might become as famous as Clay Aiken, who got second last year.    &nbsp;Some say she looks like Miss Piggy inThe&nbsp;Muppets.She does not! She is a little fat(okay, i admit)but she is just so&nbsp;cool.     &nbsp;Nice hair job!   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And how about Jasmine Trias? She is pretty but American Idol is not about looks but singing.    &nbsp;Here she is, smilimg that mega-watt smile of hers,charming boys everywhere.     &nbsp;Oh no Jas! A hair disaster!whatcha do to your lovely hair!!!!     &nbsp;She looks kinda cute with her bunned-up hair.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; And Fantasia Barrino?Some people say that she has sausage lips.(laugh )Well it is not that bad...    &nbsp;Here she is, this year's American Idol.    &nbsp;Not bad...    &nbsp;No offence but she looks like a boy...   Have to go now... Bye!!!!!!!!!!!         Ming Har     


29,May,2004


    
       
      Yes! It is the holidays again! But.... I have choir for 6 days, IT for 2 days and D&T lessons....sigh... That doesn't leave me with much time to play! 
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My Birthday2
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My Birthday
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My toys!(I am too big 4 them now.Aww...)
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My teachers
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me at the Chinese Gardens.
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Water Lily
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My sister!
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Pretty flowers swaying in the wind...
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Nice, huh?:)
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Cool!
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Trees again!(sigh!)
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Beautiful scenery, right?
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Behind me is the Istana. Wow!
       
    
    


29,May,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me at the Istana
       
    
    


13,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    me
       
    
    


11,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    me
       
    
    


11,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    me
       
    
    


11,June,2004


    
       
      God, I think I am going crazy over the moutains of homework!My mind is thinking of leisure and excitement and mostly HARRY POTTER! Here's some websites you will love if u r a harry potter fan:  urlLink http://www.jkrowling.com   urlLink http://www.harrypotter.com   urlLink Godrics Hollow   urlLink Immeritus   urlLink Magic Wands for Harry Potter Wands Fans   urlLink Accio Firebolt  harrypotterandthehalfbloodprince.com, .net and .org (Warner Bros. - who make the HP films) harrypotterandthehalfbloodprince.info, .us, .co.uk (Seabottom Productions Ltd. - related to Warner Bros. in the UK) halfbloodprince.com, .net, .co.uk (Lightmaker Group - creators of Jo's site) halfbloodprince.org (Warner Bros.) halfbloodprince.info (HPANA - Harry Potter news site) 
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Jasmine my favorite Disney princess
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Chinese Gardens
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A very beary hug
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    23
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    15
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    22
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    21
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    20
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    19
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    18
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    17
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    16
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    14
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    13
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    12
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    11
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    10
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    9
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    8
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    7
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    5
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    4
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    2
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    3
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    1
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My Birthday 2003
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me looking quite frazzled...
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My Birthday 2003 pic 2
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    My Sis
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Mrs Khoo
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Horses and me
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    ha ha!:) Simphoni scolding Wei Cheih
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Simphoni, my best friend
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Harry Potter Trio
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Agent Cody Banks
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Me on the knight bus!
       
    
    


10,June,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The Knight Bus!
       
    
    


28,July,2004


    
       
      
       
    
    



