

31,May,2004


	 
      When I went to the bank with Shawn today, something funny happened at BSN (Bank Simpanan Nasional). My queue number was (I think) 315, when a Malay guy asked me if I could deposit a certain amount of money (LOTS of RM50 notes btw, which would made up to..RM400+?) for him as he has someone waiting in the car etc. I find it even stranger when he told me his number was 320, and heck, it's only  five  numbers away!  His impatience was funny, because if I'm an evil thieving person I would have dashed out fo the bank with  his  money and he wouldn't be able to catch me as I would've caught him unawares. Or was it a random check on how honest society in Malaysia is? 

31,May,2004


	 
      I had this sort of inspiration on viewing the pictures on  urlLink Neave.com ; trust me, this guy's a genius with Flash and photography. With the inspiration in mind, I went out at about 2am today, gingerly opening the locks of my house door and went out with my trusty ol' gettin-rusty bike. I brought out the StarRewards postcard to mail it at the USJ8 mailbox as well.  You don't know how careful I was not to make any sound, but the automatic gates of my house banged together rather loudly - at least it was to me, in the middle of a dead midnight (or very early morning). Heck, I can imagine my mum's sheer horror to find me missing from the comforts of my bedsheets and rush to the police station teary-eyed while explaining to a bewildered police officer that I'm missing (hmm, but there's that 24-hour requirement, no?). I was also tempted to put up a post-it note on my door or something, saying "Am out for midnight photography." But then I wouldn't be able to answer my mum's questions as to why I would do such a crazy thing. Do y'all think I'm out of my mind?  Well, I did lotsa crazy things as well, like taking a pic of myself lying down in the middle of the road with the help of self-timer, but the pic didn't turn out that well (darn lighting, and I didn't turn on the flash for fear of um, people noticing my inane act). I guess I did felt adventurous, and that's adventurous ol' me for ya :P  When I finished cycling to USJ 8 and wandering around aimlessly at my USJ14 neighbourhood, I heard footsteps behind me and cycled ahead, as I did felt a lil afraid. When I returned to my house gate, to my horror, I saw the same guy, shadowed by the darkness of the night, sitting opposite my house gate! Well, what did I do? I went around cycling to the back of my house - to the restaurants and all to allow him some time to get out of the vicinity of the row of my house.   And near 7-Eleven's Indian 'mamak', I saw a Form 5 guy with another guy and a girl (presumably my schoolmates, I think, though I can't quite recognize them at the moment). Mr Form-5-Guy ( which I now recalled he's Ayub )(waved at me asking " Eh, dah malam tak nak balik rumah ke? " (It's already late at night and you don't want to get home yet?). I merely smiled and waved back and cycled back home, as I barely know that guy and socially-inept me prevented me from having a good conversation with him. 

29,June,2004


	 
      Shawn said, it's like waiting till SPM's over. Geok Leng agreed with me that we hardly notice that these exams stretch out to almost three weeks (technically). I remember during my PMR days, I shudder seeing my seniors "suffering" from 2-3 weeks of exams, where else we used to have only 1 week of exams (or even 3-4 days). Times change. :P  After finishing a badminton game, at about 7pm, I saw the sky beautiful with the sun's setting rays. Managed to take several (rather nice, in my opinion :P) still life pics, as well. The still life pics are inspired by Neave's site. ;)     Weird colour o_O The sky's not supposed to be this colour, but I like how the houses and their antennas have become silhouettes.           Here it is...=P      I suddenly thought of this while sitting down opposite this vision school. =P  
     

    


28,June,2004


	 
      I think I did pretty well in my Add Maths paper II today; not because I am 100% sure that I did correctly for all 12 questions, but because I actually  finished  the paper with 5 mins remaining (with um, the exception of some sub-questions that I skipped :P). And I actually managed to solve a question that most people, including Eugene, did not manage to get. =P (except for [grr], Suet :P). When I passed up my paper, Miss Then exclaimed, "Clement! You're submitting a thesis or what!?" I used waaaaaay too many papers. *sweats*  I have to thank Eugene for all his private tutoring :P Guess it really pays off now ^.^ I cant seem to er, redo the questions that I did during exams. 

27,June,2004


	 
      It was, in a way, a very weird but pleasant dream. I dreamt me and my mates - Shawn, Andy and Ryui Bynn - heading to Genting Highlands with Ryui Bynn driving a car (I can't remember the exact make of the car...). Then when we reached there, I saw my "pet sister", Whitney, who was walking through the snow. (Yeah, for some reason it was snowing 

26,June,2004


	 
      Got back from Ryui Bynn's house. The whole afternoon and night was spent at Eugene's house studying Add Maths...his dad also spent us KFC! :D And um, some of my friends were doing the farting competition thingy 

26,June,2004


	 
      Ironic, that I had a certain fixed schedule daily during my exam period. Got back from school at about 2-3pm, played around with the PC and I will usually be taking my nap from 5-7.30pm. Next, it's PC again or I will be doing my spot of studying.  Take yesterday for instance. At 12am I tried to read my econs but my eyes were droopy. I ended up using the PC for some time, felt more refreshed and studied a little =P Lost and won my bet on some matches from Euro 2004. Damn Beckham and his freaking missed penalties! That costed me RM5 

21,June,2004


	 
      On 19th July 2004, Saturday (two days back), went out with Shawn to collect our ICs from the respective department. It took about 30 minutes but because my parents wanted to make new ICs as well, we ended up walking towards a Taipan-like area searching for a cyber cafe in vain. I bought the latest Galaxie mag with The Corrs' Summer Sunshine lyrics in it :D It's full-page too! Perfectly luscious.  I had a bout of unfortunate diarrhoea, might be due to the iced coffee I took at this coffee shop for breakfast. It was...annoying and painful, to say the least.  After our IC-collecting feat and lunch at home, the both of us went to Eugene's house for some intensive Add Maths under his wing. Wai Hong didn't study much, and Andy came for a short while before he left for tuition. After studying the dreaded subject from 2pm-6pm, we had a break and played Capcom vs SNK 2 and a Harry Potter's Quidditch on his PS2 till 7pm. Then we walked to the nearby Maju-Maju restaurant for dinner, with Ryui Bynn and Andy.  Resuming our studying with the exception of RB, went back to Eugene's house and studied diligently up to 10.30pm. I think I'm good in my  Sukatan Membulat  now :D Went to RB's house nearby and  lepak  till 12am, where we played 'Monkey' with a ball or simply chit-chatted with two candles. Went back to our houses with Andy's sister's car.  Fast forward next day (20th July), I woke up at 2pm O_O At 4pm I slept again till 6.30pm. Studied Bio (as I did not study it that much yet) from 8pm to 12.30am. Went online to seal a bet with Gopi (which I lost - RM2.50, Spain vs Portagal; I took Spain). at 2am, I studied Physics till 3am and only slept at 3.30am. Then woke up 3 hours later, blurry eyed and tired.  Throughout the entire day I felt sleepy and heavy-headed - with some slight headache as well. Guess my Bio's okay as I spent that crazy amount of time yesterday (but I did forgot some of the terminology, names of parts...). Physics was horrendously hard. I felt English Paper I was the best :D I didn't have much time left as I had written 4 pages of essay and had to end it abruptly (something about my school on fire, while injecting some humour into it :D). Ms Then, who was in the class, pointed out to me subtlely while I was writing, that I had my tenses wrong. On triple-checking it, I found nothing wrong whatsoever o_O  It goes "...then all hell breaks loose." I see nothing wrong in it; and I don't think I'm supposed to change "breaks" into "broke" either. Curiously, I can't imagine Ms Then tipping me off XD She's a disclipline teacher in charge of the prefects! She was laughing out loud when she read certain parts of my essay as well XD 
     

    


18,June,2004


	 
      While pondering over my English paper II over the question "what's the meaning of 'just as fair' in the poem The Road Between?", the torrent of wind that had already blown soo hard that it threatened to tear the school to bits, managed to snatch my paper away and sent it over the edge of first floor. o__O Pn Lijah was a little funny XD She was downstairs at the assembly grounds, exclaiming, "Clement!  Kertas kamu jatuhlah! " in that squeaky voice of hers =P When I went downstairs to retrieve it, En Azlan passed the paper to me. Earlier on Jun Man from 4B suffered the same as well. :P  It's the second time that had happened this year, the first being my Moral paper from first term thrown over to the assembly grounds as well. 

17,June,2004


	 
      In my whole life, I find myself happy to be able to help people in any way, and I find myself being bombarded with people asking me to help out with their PC-related problems, which I happily obliged. Not that I'm an expert in this field, I just have lots of experience and read InTech a lot as well, plus sometimes through the GameFAQs message board which I frequent.  It just so happen that recently many, many people have been asking me for help; and I can't help but wonder if I'm being taken advantage of? *looks blankly for several seconds*  Nah :P Maybe I'm just naïve, but I'm happy enough to be able to help. Even if you can't solve their problems all the time, I feel contented. At least I tried, at least I helped. I don't consciously think of the word "help" all the time, I just thought of it today =P   Went to Joe's house to uh, try and solve his modem driver problem thingy. His parents and his sisters are at home, but not him himself. His dad's really really friendly, and in a way he reminds me of my dad (although I have my fair share of disagreements 

16,June,2004


	 
      *sighs*  So the Germany vs Netherlands (Holland) match turns out to be a draw (1-1), so I didn't lose nor win my bet of RM3 with an older friend. :P And Ms New Girl's not in our class yet, either.  Tomorrow marks the start of technically 3 weeks of exams. I'm looking forward to do Additional Maths to get over it, quickly. Which would be next Tuesday, I think. Currently I'm sick of having being told when to sleep/study by my parents, especially my mum. The incessant nagging made me unleashed curses after curses (to myself, of course), and frankly, it would be better if they trust me that I know my own life and schedule better and would they please stfu. Thank you. 

15,June,2004


	 
      Yesterday, after Miss Then, our Bio teacher, reported that there will be  yet another  new student in our class - a girl - everyone started obsessing about meeting her (including yours truly). There's the fun and excitement on meeting a new member to our class; she didn't turn up today, though.  Was reading my History yesterday midnight when I heard this song by Vitamin C,  Graduation (Friends Forever) . There's like a year and a half to go, and I wonder where all of us - my friends - would be once we grew up? Would genius all-rounder Suet Li be the greatest doctor/scientist on earth? Would Ryui Bynn be a geologist? Would someone from my class discover the ultimate cure to HIV/AIDS?  Part of the lyrics ring true to me, and made me think:   So if we get the big jobs And we make the big money When we look back now Will our jokes still be funny? Will we still remember everything we learned in school? Still be trying to break every single rule Will little brainy Bobby be the stockbroker man? Will Heather find a job that won't interfere with her tan? I keep, I keep thinking that it's not goodbye Keep on thinking it's a time to fly And this is how it feels   To all my friends and those who knew me in some way, the chorus portrayed by this brilliant song, I'm saying this to all of you from the bottom of my heart:   As we go on, we remember All the times we had together, And as our lives change, come whatever, We will still be, Friends forever...   
     

    


13,June,2004


	 
      Phone Booth, starring Colin Farrell is an intriguing movie. If you think that there can be no interesting storyline revolving a phone booth, think again, as the script-writer of this movie has managed to stretch the story beyond an hour in a most interesting manner, touching on subjects such as infidelity.  It's an emotional show too, somewhat, and has an interesting message at the end of the show - that you hear a public phone ringing, you know it's a wrong number but you pick it up anyway - and find that your life (as well as your love ones') is endangered by a serial killer sniper.   Oh, and camera angles revolved around buildings, the street and the phone booth for the most part of the show, so it's definitely interesting. Expletive are used freely in this show as well - you've been warned. :P  Kill Bill Vol 1 - it's nice as well, but too much unrealistic violence - blood spilling forth like fountain etc. Japanese accent by main character (Uma Thurman) is horrid, while Lucy Liu's slightly better (playing an underground Yakuza queen in Japan as a Chinese-Japanese American).  Did I also mention that the subtitles for both DVDs are...terrible? Horrid grammatical mistakes, and they don't follow the characters' speech as well - I just had to turn the subtitles off, for once. Bah! But that's what you get for pirated stuffs done locally 

12,June,2004


	 
      Just watched Black Hawk Down yesterday, a movie about war in Somalia. It just goes to show that war, no matter for whichever and whatever ideals, always end in greater loss of lives; how men needlessly throw their lives away, dying in the most horrifyingly grotesque manners, wounded at all sorts of odd places. War is ugly.  “This is civil war,” said a Somalian, “and this is our war.”  Why do people have to interfere in other people’s war? Why does former US President Clinton have to send his men out to do his dirty job? It’s easy to command soldiers to fight, it’s easy to place his ass onto some chair, and counting casualties “19 died, 56 wounded” like they’re simple maths, when the soldiers who fought bravely out there yelled “Man down! Man down!” signifying the importance of lives. They’re more than just numbers, they’re lives.   Seeing a man’s torso got completely destroyed; your driving comrade blasted in the face by pieces of mirror and got blinded, with you yelling, “Step on the gas pedal! Keep stepping on it!” while you semi-calmly take control of the wheel; your teammate got deafened by sudden firing of the weapon you’re using; and a man whose pelvis got wounded badly by shots, and your mates and yourself had to perform a primitive operation using whatever knowledge they have and equipments at hand, watching your men trying to restrain a screaming friend in utter extreme pain of the highest degree as he fainted, your hand digging through the pelvis trying to clamp the arteries together, trying to do everything you and your men could do but in the end, all fails.  As he slowly wakes up, he asked weakly, “Fixed it?” and you had to give him hope, and you smiled encouragingly saying “Yeah we did.” In the end, he died. Died saying, “Tell my parents that I fought really well today, that I fought really, really well…”  In war, whatever you speak might be your last words, ranging from “RPG!” to “Fuck!”. In war, your very mind is split into several decaying matters trying to survive the onslaught of upcoming attacks. Men, women, children of Somalia are all against you. War… why must there be a fucking war upheld by bastards of politicians who had the worst and most unreliable intel that results in unnecessary deaths?  Seeing them encouraging each other, patting each other on their backs, giving them hope when there's minimal chance of surviving... I could've broke down.  In SFC “Hoot” Gibson’s words, war is about looking after men next to you. SSgt. Matt Eversmann: In war, there are no heroes. 
     

    


11,June,2004


	 
      After finish using the PC and studying History till roughly 2:40am, I felt myself still fully awake. Deciding that tossing and turning around in my bed would be a complete waste of time, I watched The Hot Chick with lights out and used the ever-useful wireless headphone :D It has subtle sex-related jokes as well XD (not the actual act of sex, but um, basically anything to do with sex; the male genitalia, homosexuality...et al).  So um, watched till 5am. It's a really funnnyyyy show but I had to stiffle my laughters (which turned into mere smirks 

09,June,2004


	 
      That's what I've been doing of late. I slept at 4am for the past few days...and I still felt awake at that time! (and woke up like, at 12.30pm or 1.30pm later on 

09,June,2004


	 
      Hehe, it's great when I see lots of my friends had took up blogging because I introduced it to them =P All thanks to TheStar for featuring blogging in their previous StarEducation, which inspired me, and in turn, inspired other people around me. =)
     

    


08,June,2004


	 
      Just finished watching School of Rock. It's the type of movie that gets you all inspired and all you want to do right after watching the show is get your fingers into some kind of instrument and start rocking! Ah, but there's that one thing. I can't play. And you can say I'm tone-deaf. Oh, and I can't sing. So does this make me the next William Hung?  Ah well, I can only dream :P It's absolutely lovely when you're in a band, and you hear your bandmates play and you do your stuff. It's the best thing ever in cooperation even if it's just musically. Being an ex-vocalist, um, it's a huge embarassment when I hear myself on record, but I guess I had lots of fun. :D And that, I think, is most important when you're doing something. Go have some fun!  Quote from School of Rock: "I wasn't like this! I was fun! I was funny!" "But they, their parents! They turn me into this! They'll come to me with a nuclear bomb if something's wrong!" - Principal Miss Muller to Dewey Finn.
     

    


08,June,2004


	 
      Well...watched both shows yesterday night (or this early morning). Um, that show and its sequel are highly sexual and vulgar, but they do offer lost of laugh at the expense of the embarassment of the actors (and actresses). The former has a simple storyline of 4 hormone-charged guys wanting to "get laid" before high school is over; and their last chance to get it would be the night of their prom; the latter simply depicts their college life, and them renting a summer house beside a beach.  A quote from American Pie which I thought is funny: "There's this one time at band camp..." - Michelle starting off a conversation with this phrase almost every time. (well, you gotta watch it to get what I mean).  And another quote from American Pie 2: "I got peed on." - Stifler having an unfortunate incident. Again, you gotta watch it to get the joke. :P
     

    


07,June,2004


	 
      ...for about an hour before it finally subsides with a loud burp (and some obnoxious gaseous remains that were expelled forthwith).  Also just came back from Jon's house; borrowed 14 DVDs of various genre (and 1 School of Rock DVD which I borrowed from Shawn, who borrowed from Andy, who borrowed from Ryui Bynn). Comedies include American Pie (and its sequel) and The Hot Chick, war-themed includes Black Hawk Down, action-related includes Phone Booth and Kill Bill Vol 1 (yay!)...and, that's all I can think of for now. All in all, 15 DVDs. :D *thumps boredom out of the window*  Oh, and my new maid just arrived today. o_O Let's just hope she won't start to run away. I pity maids actually. My previous maid (who ran away) was only 17 (just a year older than me, imagine that!) and she studies Chemistry, Bio...and whatnot, before she came to M'sia. She actually studies! o_O (Okay...maybe because I have a stereotyped image of how maids lived previously in Indonesia...) I'm guessing that my previous maid ran away because my mum nagged a lot (she's a... clean-freak! 

06,June,2004


	 
      I just realized that our mind has so much power untapped. I was roused by my dad's voice when I took a nap, and I could sort of visualize his image and his voice clearly in my mind for that 2 seconds, asking me to wake up (he was in the kitchen, in my mind). Okay, I don't know how to describe it but it's weird - it's like um, a mini-premonition of sorts that's just a milisecond faster. Okay, that may not make sense 

04,June,2004


	 
      Yep, that's about one of the weirdest things I've eaten for lunch in a while (yesterday's). Been listening to my Borrowed Heaven album. :P Amazingly, Heng Li actually likes Angel too :D (a track from BH, directed to their deceased mum). It's going to be the second new single off the new album =P; the song is so uplifting that it's ironic, plus with the brilliant lyrics as well.  I especially like part of the bridge, when it was sung very quickly:  Confidence and conscience  Decadent extravagance  Never ending providence  For loving when I had the chance   Off BH, I like Angel, Borrowed Heaven and Humdrum. =) 
     

    


04,June,2004


	 
      Well, watched Harry Potter: The Prisoner of Azkaban with Soon Guan and my bro yesterday night, at 11:45pm. We went there at almost 10pm, so it's semi-dead in The Summit shopping complex, but we hung around at the arcade (Time Crisis 3: god I died pretty quick 

02,June,2004


	 
      Slept at 4.30 am after chatting for quite some time with Soon Guan while both of us were lying down on my bed (that is, after we finally turned off the PS2 at 2 am). Discussed about school, music, videoclips, movies, et al; basically, anything that can be talked about :P).  Then I just  had  to get up  at about 8.20 am as I have my Biology extra class in school. It's in the lab, and it turns out to be rather surprising to me as 4A and 4B were not together in one lab; instead we were to stay in our own labs, and Miss Then (my Bio teacher, in an outfit that's unlike her - some rather tight-fitting clothes) had to go to and fro in both labs to conduct her lessons.  Went to Burger King Taipan to eat; the Chicken Smoked Turkey set was excellent. Jon returned my RM50... said that his parents said I don't need to pay them for the disc, and to treat it as a souvenir o_O Man his parents are damn generous. =P Thanks unc and auntie!  What else? Spent the rest of the afternoon playing Power Stone 2 (on Dreamcast) and Soul Calibur 2 (PlayStation2). After taking a short nap before dinner, felt slightly refreshed now, and more alert. :P Soon Guan told me that he saw Galaxie mag with  The Corrs  on its cover! :D It was at 7-Eleven, gotta buy that later.  Also receive a phone call from my cell group leader, as to why I didn't attend church for some time 

01,June,2004


	 
      Oh lovely god and holy mother that is Mary, I'VE JUST BOUGHT  BORROWED HEAVEN!!!  Okay maybe I'm a lil emotional to the point that I might drop a tear or two, but hey, I've been anticipating this album for freaking ages!! 

01,June,2004


	 
      I had a weird dream; I dreamt I was buying Borrowed Heaven in one of the CD shops in Taipan. At first I couldn't find it and I remembered feeling disappointed until I spotted it; it has a WESTLIFE back cover, which is a no wonder why I can't find it 

01,June,2004


	 
      Seeing that I'm rather bored now, and it's already past 12 midnight and I  really  should be studying, I think I'll write what I'm anticipating for today when I get up later in the morning.   For one, The Corrs' new album  Borrowed Heaven  is slated for release today in M'sia! :D But unfortunately, I think I don't have enough money to buy one thanks to BSN's horrid processing of my gift voucher, and I don't think I'd want to withdraw from my Public Bank account either; it's there as a fund for my planned Australia trip end of next year, with Joe :D  Secondly, Jon's supposed to return today from his trip from LA (a damned 2-week trip at that, man was I freaking jealous and full of envy 

29,July,2004


	 
      Walking around in school today, I had to use the power of estimation to roughly guess who the person that was standing few metres away really was. XD I kinda got used to it, and got used to all the teasings and the stupid "guess how many fingers" game. 

28,July,2004


	 
      Without my specs, my line of vision is sooo blurred it's as if someone used a Photoshop and used the Blur effect on my world, visually. I brought my cam to school, and played around with it =P I think I looked better without spectacles actually, with Geok Leng agreeing to it as well although Xin Hui said otherwise, saying that she's not used to my spectacle-less outlook. :P          I think I looked sooo innocent. XD What dya think? :P     &nbsp;  Took some photos with Geok Leng as my model for the photography contest...I had a few ideas in mind, and I think they're nice, except that the blackboard and the mirror pic was slightly blur-ish. I'm submitting the birdie pic and the last pic of Geok Leng.       Those Chinese words represent her Chinese name =P      This pic was snapped at the girl's toilet, ground floor, shower area XD      At the stairs, overlooking the field,  bengkel pertanian , and canteen.      Was in a rush trying to snap this pic. The bird was flying too fast, and Miss Then wants a scenery pic (only knew that during the last minute).   
     

    


27,July,2004


	 
      Bah. Went for football with the rest of the team (which we called ourselves, as eXodus). Azim, Matthew, Joe, Shawn, Heng Li, Jon, Wai Hong, another ex-USJ 8er and I were there. We were training ourselves basically (...it was tough trying to kick a  straight  ball =.="), and played a game among ourselves, with Heng Li as the goalie.   After some of them Malay guys (not trying to be racist here, but they're sorta like..delinquents 

26,July,2004


	 
      Went to Jon's house at 4 something after doing a little of Moral  folio  at Wai Hong's house. Jon kindly taught me guitar - the basics, how to press them strings, etc. It hurts.  A lot.  I watched him play Gunbound while I continue pressing down the strings to get used to it. It helps in a way, as I paid less attention to the pain and to the game instead.   Next, I need to practise strumming. If only I have a guitar, I'd be able to practise =/   
     

    


25,July,2004


	 
      Earlier today, went out to Midvalley with my parents to hunt for a pair of running shoes. I thought their budget was low (they didn't want to tell me), so I found an All-Conditions Gear at about RM170, and my mum thought it looked like the one I'm wearing (which is not); it wasn't exactly that comfy aroun the ankle area. I also phoned up Joe, the shoes expert to get some advice, and he said that he would recommend me running shoes.  Well, I couldn't find one that fits below RM200. 

24,July,2004


	 
      Saturday - 24th July 2004   After spending enough aching and tiring stationing at the school entrance in a complete scout uniform - while repeatedly greeting parents with pre-programmed statements - I went hanging about in my class. It was a report card day, splendidly boring. Helped around with scout-related stuffs till about 1pm before I went back home.   At 2:45pm, I went out again to Gopi's house who took his sweet time trying on his socks and various articles of apparel. Jeremy was already at his house. After we took a wrong bus (number 10) and realized that 5 minutes later, we had to wait for bus number 4 to move. Apparently, only bus number 4 goes to Bangsar now, despite what was stated at bus number 10 that it goes to the Kotaraya.   Anyhow, the whole misadventure of this stupid bus took us a long time to reach our desired destination. We stopped at Asia Jaya to get on the LRT there (instead of Bangsar, it's further - I researched on the Net before I went to Gopi's house). After we missed the train by mere seconds, we waited a while and went on board. I misheard Suet talking over the phone, so the whole lot of us took the feeder bus to SS2, only to be told on the way that she was already at the Taman Bahagia LRT station waiting for us.   We were one hour late from the appointed time - 4pm. She had to go as well, so we chatted for roughly 5 mins before she dropped us off at the aforementioned LRT station. Hope she didn't get pissed 

24,July,2004


	 
       It’s the perfect whether of sorts when it comes to a day where we do a lot of walking. Yeah, it rained. Gloomy, droopy rain.   It all started when Gopi, Jeremy, Heng Li and I set off with high spirits to various educational institutes to request them to advertise in our school magazines. Gopi lugged his bag around that weighs thrice of my own school bag, while Heng Li decidedly brought along his lightweight bag which his connecting straps tore during the beginning of our trip.&nbsp;Mr Victor (our discipline teacher) gave us a letter, stating said students are given permission to go out of school to find sponsors for school magazine. Whee.   Gopi’s mum brought us first to Taylor’s College at SS15, braving the traffic jam along the way. “We are determined people,” Gopi reminded us several times, as we looked like some fools in a school uniform playing truant. Our first visit went okay, and the lady in charge said that he would contact us soon. So far so good.   Walking underneath the cold pelts of the rain, we proceeded to Inti with similar results. After finishing our McDonald’s breakfast, the rain seemed to be lesser than before, and we went for the Metropolitan College, again, with similar results. “We’re idiots wearing school ties,  dei ,” said Gopi.   We boarded a number 10 Metrobus to Sunway Pyramid. From there we went to The One Academy, under the pouring rain, with me shielding my precious gelled hair with Gopi’s nifty file-holder. We were made to sit down by the receptionist and waited for roughly 10-15 minutes, who told us that the person-in-charge’s line was engaged. After watching some highly unenlightening advertisements made by the academy itself on the nearby TV, the receptionist told us that that particular person is not in. Oh joy.   We went inside Sunway Pyramid and used the walkway to Sunway Hotel. I’m sure we looked like school kids playing truant, and we reaffirmed it by saying, “The difference is, we’re wearing school ties.” I mean, how many students playing truant did you see wear their school ties?&nbsp;We trotted a long distance to our next destination, Sunway College. Walking under the rain, Jeremy started singing “I’m a big, big boy, in a big, big world…” when the rain pelted down heavier (I’m sure it’s those overhanging trees with their big, big leaves 

22,July,2004


	 
      Got my haircut two days back from the salon I usually frequent to, which is opposite my house. " Zhing pok, slope! " was what Andy recommended, so uh, I tried it as well. We wanted to go to Geok Leng's auntie's salon, but it's RM16 o_O So we decided against it XD (we being me, WH, and Jon).   So the next day after school, WH and Jon stood in front of my house with their new haircut XD It's like staring at the same hairstyle, but maybe a little different individually. Jon's hair is already damn short, yet he cuts again =.=" But all of us looked better though :D   Tomorrow I'll be heading to some of those colleges near Sunway (Taylor's, etc etc) with Heng Li, Gopi and Jerm, to  beg  them to advertise in our school mag <>_

21,July,2004


	 
      ...so sayeth Ryui Bynn, in a telephone call to Suet Li (I could pretty much guess what's happening, as I was beside him at that time, and no I'm not eavesdropping 

18,July,2004


	 
      Just happened minutes ago; it's something that doesn't happen everyday XD The convo (it's short) went as follows:&nbsp;    //c l e m &nbsp;knights in shining armour  yoz, where did you go?   //c l e m  knights in shining armour  btw, my gmail is saigoheiki@gmail.com XD&nbsp;  - çLoUdež° - Everyday is a nightmare for my knee =.= sorry i'm Jon's dad accidentally login....goddnite n Jon's in bed already... &nbsp; //c l e m  knights in shining armour&nbsp; owh../swt hehe, never mind =P &nbsp; //c l e m  knights in shining armour&nbsp; was about to send him more files from&nbsp;school mag/heh&nbsp;  &nbsp; - çLoUdež° - Everyday is a nightmare for my knee =.= yup he showed me the edit on the mag...not bad...good nite then... &nbsp; //c l e m &nbsp;knights in shining armour good night!  


11,July,2004


	 
      This week, from Tuesday to Friday, I had been at the computer lab with some of my buddies from the Editorial Board of my school magazine. The computers are so fancifully equipped with outdated softwares that I had to wince. Windows98??? No Photoshop? Then how the  heck  do they expect us to do graphics?  &nbsp;  My official post stands as the school photographer, but we were pulled in to do some typing of the articles submitted to us. Once those are done, here comes the next job. Layouts (which I'm doing, with lots of hardship thanks to me using  only  Microsoft Word when I'm sure other schools are using much more higher-end programs). Jon is doing a wonderful job with the graphics, though when we refer to other school's magazines, they have like, a series of people to help with graphics, articles etc. Damn Form 5s not helping us at all (with SPM as their excuse).  &nbsp;  Heng Li never ceases to amaze&nbsp;me with his language -&nbsp;he even writes poems, which shocked and surprised all of us XD His latest work (poem), Hallucinogen, is amazing, and&nbsp;I'll have no doubt at all to&nbsp;include it into the magazine. :D  &nbsp;  So here's a little tale of the campfire that 41 scouts from my school attended. I was rushing to school at about 5pm because that's the time we were supposed to be at school; I even ran a bit. On reaching there, behold, my fellow scouts who were busy sewing badges and other appendices onto their uniform, mostly because they're missing the badge '132' (the code number for our school).  &nbsp;  We set off to SMK La Salle at about 5.30pm, with Suet Li and Suet Teng the latest to arrive; my partner sitting beside me was Ryui Zyen. Saravana Kumar made us wait for him, until we realized that he was at a tennis practice. =.=" We reached the school at about 6pm, but then it was too early (ever noticed we were always  too early ?). We sat at the nearby  mamak , and we drank and ate (I drank two cups of  teh&nbsp;o' ais,  Rebecca drank her first  teh o' ais , and realized that it tasted horrible o_O). And they even charged RM2 for a  roti telur , wtf? It costed less than that in Subang Jaya... Anyhow, when Rebecca took out her single RM5 note to pay for her drink, the guy returned 5 RM1 notes back to her XD Serves them right. 

11,July,2004


	 
      On the 9th July '04, Friday, Shawn, Andy and I set off again to the terrain at TP, with Siew Keat mentioning to me in Gunbound that there's an estate there or something o_O We didn't find it though, whichever that he meant.  We managed to climb the green hill, braving the long sharp grass and other weird plants that poked our legs. In fact, we were actually afraid some species of snakes might pop around biting our legs, as we might tread onto their nests. Luckily we didn't find any 

08,July,2004


	 
      Well, two days back, Shawn, RB and I ventured out to cycle around...and with our random cycling, we ended up at TP, Taman Perindustrian (I believe it's a fairly new area). On further exploration, Shawn led us to this Faber Castell factory (with its "biggest pencil in the world", that can't be used anyway). Near that area is a green hill with two electric towers on top. We wanted to climb it on foot, but Shawn led us further up, where there's this wonderful terrain, which I think any amateur geologists would be proud of :P  At an angle, there are some plants that looked like miniature toys... actually the entire place looked like a place where you shoot them dinosaur movies. The plants are tiny...the "cave" thingy is small...in RB's words, that entire place is like a cave without the cover.  That said, RB and I climbed up this ledge to the top, and had difficulties coming down. It's not that difficult, it's the fear. I'm semi-afraid of heights, and I believe this is worse than Solero Spaceshot at Genting, 'cause even though it's high, you have no choice but get pulled down whereas this... you have all the time in the world, yet you have to do this on your own. Jumping down metres high ledge onto the soft, wet ground.  Here are some pictures from our trip:             Yesterday's RB's birthday. Andy brought some Omega3 eggs to school, and Gopi dragged him after school to the grassy area behind the B block of our school. Nevertheless, he's wet and pelted with eggs; actually, being pelted with eggs hurts. Some of us did a mistake by throwing the eggs at him instead of cracking it over the head...the impact forces the contents of the eggs out and some of us (including yours truly) got some pieces of egg yolk and whatnot on our attire. :P  
     

    


04,July,2004


	 
      Yay ^.^ For this month of July, I'll have loads of things to watch. First off, The Amazing Race 5 is back on AXN, every Wednesday 8pm! I'm also watching this new series, John Doe, premiering on StarWorld every Tuesday 8pm. And the usual Charmed =P  Heng Li and Gopi came to my house today...after I helped Gopi snapping photos for his Moral project. They watched Basic in my room; it's an intriguing show with a most interesting plot twists ever. Highly recommended :P  We went to this mamak stall behind my house, and then it rained and thundered heavily. We took shelter at 7-Eleven shortly after, and when Gopi madly went back home under the thundering rain, Heng Li and I had some chat at 7-Eleven. He even bought a bottle of red wine that costed almost RM7, 5% alcohol. I took a sip too =P  Guess I'm gonna start writing down a schedule on The Corrs' appearances and programmes on both MTV and Channel V, so I don't miss them. XD
     

    


03,July,2004


	 
      So here's yesterday's entire trip. I went to school as usual, only to find Shawn and Andy not there. Phoned Shawn via my handphone and he said he's "coming". 

01,July,2004


	 
      After finishing our dinner at Shakey's (to celebrate Ryui Bynn's mum's bday), Shawn, Andy, RB and I talked for ages around USJ 9...then we went out to the park. Man, the moon was beautiful. We sat a bench, with my head lying on top of Shawn's shoulder...imagining how lovely and romantic it'll be with a loved one. It was shining ever so brightly with a ring of light around it, about 5cm in diameters from where I stood.  We chatted for a long time deciding about tomorrow's Genting plan. After much discussion (revolving about the same thing), we've decided to go to school to help RB with his prefect work (carry chairs, tables, PA system in conjunction with a  perlantikan pengawas  ceremony next Monday). RB phoned Miss Then and said that she allowed us to all go back at 9am o_O This sounds too good to be true. Knowing Miss Then, anything might happen 

01,July,2004


	 
      I managed to finish my Econs paper in 35 minutes (8am-8.35am) when we were supposed to gather at the school canteen. Other than some calculations of some taxes which I didn't bother to think over much with, the entire paper is okay.  As I don't have a watch with me, I'll relate the events without the time =P Left school and headed straight for this particular company called InvenQjaya, situated at Putrajaya. It's a place to train scientists and invent stuffs; they have loads of patents to prove. The building itself (its interior) is almost futuristic. The lights are bluish, they have plasma screens covering every corner of the building... We were treated to a video of the company profile, and then a 3D animation (we got to wear the 3D specs that they had invented as well, something about them being made of poly-(something) film.  This guy Julian, who was one of the managers there and became our tour guide for my group A, has the most flawless English ever. Hardly noticed any grammatical mistakes when he spoke; his pronunciation is of the high-class English, pronouncing 'power' as 'parr'. Amazing. His vocab is wide (when I asked him a question regarding artificial light used in solar panels, he answered me, and used um, 'periodically', which I think none of us would ever consider using in their everyday speech. I think some might not know of the word at all 

13,August,2004


	 
      Earlier we had the -eXodus- training session again, and I guess I kinda improved on my um, passing thanks to Jon's help last time, and Shawn's training advice this time. =P  Joe accidentally kicked the ball directly at Jon's head who was standing in front of him, his back facing him. With me not wearing specs at that time (at the power of 500 XD), I can still see that his head got knocked towards one side at the great impact :P His spectacles flew away, with both of his lenses. We managed to recover only one lens, so he's missing another. =/  Looks like there's bound to be some accident of some sort whenever we go for footie training 

11,August,2004


	 
      Hehe, for some reason unbeknownst to me, after finishing my Add Maths homework ( Penyelesaian Segi Tiga ), I kinda hungered for more so I browsed through the dreaded Red Book, the Bible of Add Maths (published by Pelangi), and tried the non-routine question number 48.  Bleh, it took me approximately 157.5 minutes, equivalent to 2.625 hours <>most of us are here against our will  today. I like it lots, though it's explicit at certain parts of the book. I like his style of writing, how he conveys his message, how certain phrases he uses are delicate and subtle, that you have to have a vast amount of knowledge and experience to understand what he's talking about :P    
     

    


10,August,2004


	 
      Ahem. Just for background info, -eXodus- was a given name to a football team that my friends and I started. (And no, don't ask me why the dashes and the capital X are used 

08,August,2004


	 
      The place that I stayed at - DutaVista - was um, quite weird. Tiny stairways and only about one elevator. The entire area wasn't that big but when I entered the room we were supposed to be staying...whoa, it's huge XD Probably the biggest I've ever stayed at of all the apartments/resorts/hotels I've been.  Not much I can say. Went to Bangsar Shopping Complex before we checked-in ('cause the management gotta get ready..etcetc), where Canny Ong was um, abducted from the parking lot =/ After dinner, went to Berjaya Times Square with my family...ate at Kenny Rogers. Walked around..that's about it. Bought Dik Cerdas comic vol 38.  Then the next morning (today), went to this..um, place (can't recall the name at the moment) with flea market. Then went to Ikano near 1 Utama. First time I've been there - I kinda like the place 'cause there are lots of walking space for you - despite not having as many shops as 1 Utama itself :P The good thing is, the shops over there are large - so lots of things to browse per se.  Meh. Many good pics I took were blur (they were mostly pics with poor lighting). Bah. Damn shaky hands. Damn camera. 
     

    


06,August,2004


	 
      Just thought I'd mention this since it's too..uncanny XD Shawn, Heng Li, Jon and I arrived school late at the same time yesterday (about 7.30-7.35am). Once in a blue moon occurence :P  Finished doing my oral yesterday. I noticed that I feel less and less nervous compared to before...looks like I'm getting the hang of it :P My topic? "The Science of Attraction". I didn't really prepare much, just jot down notes...then talk semi-spontaneously :P  Going off for some..family vacation in KL tomorrow. I dunno, of all places in KL? But I don't feel like going so far now :P I'm staying there for only one night, while my parents are staying till Monday.  My favourite pic of Jay:    I like the little Russian girl in the photos. Matched the theme of the entire album perfectly. 
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
      I cycled with Eugene Lee (who was using Shawn's bike) to the camera shop behind my house to collect the photographs I had them to print. Shawn's bike decided to fail on the way; the chains got entangled. My hands was completely black, palms, fingers, nails and all - it's like I soaked my hands into a bucket of tar. Even as of now while typing this, my fingers are still stained...it's darned hard to get them off.  Submitted two photographs - Ms Then was being completely flexible with the rules (seems like we don't need a scenery pic now?). I used the photo I had of Mei Ling's pink Nike Air (though it wasn't taken on that day) - Ms Then said I could submit that...although I think she didn't know that I didn't snap that on that particular day.  I  love  Jay Chou's photo shoots from his latest album. Very, very artistically done - I like especially the cover of his new album - him in his military uniform with the Russian girl. Here's a link to the image of the front cover:  urlLink http://www.alfamusic.com.tw/artists/jay/wallpapers/1024x768_05.jpg   Qi Li Xiang is a wonderful song. Nice lyrics. "qi li xiang de ming zi hen mei" - the name "Qi Li Xiang" is very beautiful. Joined the forums of jay-chou.net - seems like Kai Shen joined that too before :P 
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
      Yesterday, Wai Hong didn't bring the key to our class which he found. So all of us (including teachers) have to go in through 4B and use the dividers of the class to go to our class XD Noteworthy I guess :P  My friends and I are a weird bunch. I've lots of pictures to prove below XD; take Afif and Sasi for instance. Afif had a rather long hair, and as rumours of a spotcheck were spreading around (partially started by yours truly 

03,August,2004


	 
      Watched I, Robot yesterday with Heng Li and Andy at Summit. It's a holiday for us due to the  Larian Mesra  thingy and I know I'm supposed to rest. I felt sick. I had flu and fever. :P And I brought along my black long-sleeved turtleneck shirt knowing that the cinema's gonna be real cold, which it was.   I, Robot  is an interesting show - I love plot twists and this show offers it. I love futuristic shows and this movie offered it as well XD Two hours well-spent. My rating? 9.5/10 :D  On a side note, Angel has a videoclip by itself now! (The Corrs' next single) Lovely, lovely, lovely :D Downloaded it off the Net, though it's not that clear.  Washed tents today with Jo Yee and Rebecca - Rebecca was initially reluctant. I had to go to Court 8 to bring both of them to my house. I can't really count on the other males within my group. In retrospect, I realized that girls are darned reliable and hardworking :P I thought that I could make it for the eXodus football training in school, guess I couldn't. Washed, dried and kept the tents nicely all within two hours.  Had to re-enact the tents to clean them. =/ A bit  mafan.  Cleaned from 3.40pm-5:40pm XD The training was from 4-6, but Jon later told me that they left at about 5:45pm. /swt  On another side note, Jon defeated me lots in GB. I had a series of bad luck 

01,August,2004


	 
      Day 1, Friday - 30th July 2004  After spending some time at the computer lab, I went back home to prepare for the upcoming scout's camp. I rushed to school at 2.30pm, only to find it wasn't even ready yet. Pn Tuan Zainab (coordinator of the school mag) asked me if I knew Jon's number, and I said I didn't. I volunteered to go to his house and asked him to go to school because she needs certain files from the school mag which happened to be deleted off the main computer by someone. =/  It started to rain - oh phooey - and there we were at a dampy start of the scout's camp (helped by 61st troop from SM Subang Jaya).  Pasukan Kadet Bomba  held their camp with us as well, although our activities are separated. After dividing juniors (yours truly included, as I joined scouts last year) into their respective patrols, I was nominated to be the patrol leader by both Rebecca and Sheng Lim (seniors in my troop). I accepted the post (can't convince them otherwise anyway <>_


