
18,July,2003


	 
      PICS. YES.    urlLink Tiffany and Maggie   Let me go through a little history of both of them.   Tiffany (Girl in the front) - I knew her since 6th grade. We're going into 11th this year. We weren't friends back then, but we knew each other. End of 7th grade, we were in a group to perform a play, I started coming over to her house a lot, and it eventually came to the point where I came over every day just to see her. We just started off as friends, but one day, she gave me a note as I was leaving. I read it on the way home on my bike, it was about how she said she started to have feelings for me. So the next day, I gave her a note telling her how much I liked her. This went on during the summer every day or so. Finally, I had to take a trip to Canada to see my cousin. We were both saddened by it and decided to keep a diary/journal of what we did each day and how we felt. I came back a week later, we exchanged notes, and asked her out. It was horrible too. I was leaning in to give her a peck on the cheek, she thought I was leaning in to give her a kiss, so it ended up being a sloppy kiss. I said,"will you go off with me?" I was so surprised about the kiss, I messed up and accidentally blurted that out. I said I would give her some time to think about it. As I was going home, she came up running behind me with my backpack (I forgot it there. -_-) I said thanks, and as she was running off, she said yes. I rode home as fast as I could like a happy little seventh grader...which I was. The next day, we hung out, and we broke up as I was leaving. She said we she wasn't ready, as she had just broken up with a guy in the week before. So...we broke up and stayed as friends. Years went by, me and her stayed as friends while still falling in love even more as the years went by. I feel if I were to marry someone, she would be the perfect girl for me. She has just been there for me for so long. Tiff, I know you'll be reading this, just want to say I love you.   Maggie (Girl in the back) - Let's see...I've known this girl since 6th grade too. Me and her talked to each other once in a while, but not really, and when we did, we just talked about chess. Me and her played a few games against each other, if I recall correctly. 7th grade, during the time school was ending (but before I started knowing Tiffany), I used to sit next to her during 6th hour, Social Studies, we would talk once in a while, and I found her to be quite nice. I thought it would be neat if I ever went out with her, but never thought much about it, as we did not keep in contact much. 8th grade, we talked, but quite less than any other grade. Every time she signed my yearbook, it was about chess. 


