
18,June,2004


    
       So,  the June Divisional Council Meeting will be   Wednesday, June 23rd, 2004 12pm-3pm ( may end early) TIME CHANGED TO 2 PM - 5 PM  John Marshall Park ( across from Servite High School) Brookhurst and La Palma in Anaheim   we will play lots of ice breakers, like twister, roshambo, red rover, and the hugging game, etc. It will basically be a GREAT BONDING TIME for everyone in d30S.  If anyone has an idea for a service activity, please contact me as soon as possible.   Also we will be selling In n Out burgers for a minimal price of probably 3 dollars or so, bring a couple dollars!   We will also be having a mini -book drive until then, so BRING ANY BOOKS THAT YOU DON'T WANT. We'll donate them at International Convention, which I will be attending. ANY BOOKS.   Copyright 2004 Suzy Overlord Productions 

11,June,2004


    
       When: tomorrow when is that? that is saturday the 12th my friend Time: Early but you get free t-shirts it is from 6AM-10AM Meet at the one and only LOARA PARKING LOT at 6 please :) What:You'll be helping out the community by registering people in and distributing t-shirts.  What do you get?  You'll get FREE FOOD ( what most events are all about FREE FOOD ) and you get free T-SHIRTS :D be there are be squared  brought to you by wendy tran 
    
    


04,June,2004


    
        Saturday June 5th  CHairperson: Kevin Young (Me your fav. secretary ;) lolz)   Meet at skool 10:30!!  DONT BE ANY LATER THAN 10:45 or ur outta there!! lolz meaning no go to event? gotta be there on time=) losing chance for hours may persuade u to get there on time, so we can go to events on time yes?  The Event will be from 11AM-2PM Its a the Orange Mall at 1500 East Village Way                          Orange CA 92865  We are going to help out at the booths by taking photos and fingerprints of children there=D fun stuff yo=)  Rides are appreciated=D                                           -K3vy  BTW  Skip-A-Meal  is still on so donate $5 to someone who would benefit from it a lot than yourself.  100% of the contributions go directly to Kiwanis Children's Fund!!   KEY CLUBBER OF THE MONTH IS WENDY TRAN  woo goo Wendy our awesome historian=) 
    
    


01,June,2004


    
       Did we get any articles from Loara printed? Who rocked the house bringing in the most points? N what the heck is goin on? iono but this liddo dandy Newsletter tells it all=)  First off yay for Nicole Schneegas for writing an excellent article for the newletter =D Why go and try to find a newletter just to read it? Why HERE IT IS!=P  ===

01,June,2004


    
       Hello Welcome to da  GRAND OPENING  or Loara Key Clubz blogspot where Past and Upcoming events will be posted along with other news 
    
    




