
29,June,2004


     
       urlLink    5.1, but i'm kinda liking these mini heals on the sandals.
     
    


22,June,2004


     
       urlLink    8.4
     
    


22,June,2004


     
       urlLink    golfing..6_21_04
     
    


20,June,2004


     
       urlLink    inside the 180...it looks a bit used and tired, but he assured me everything works properly.
     
    


09,June,2004


     
       urlLink    This made me a bit nervous, why are we adding oil to this thing right before we go up?..shouldn't it already have enough oil?..does it leak oil or something?..i mean, it is a bit old..1967....hmm
     
    


09,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Mark buys a new plane, well.new for him..it's a 67 Piper Cherokee 180..neeeds some paint and a little TLC.
     
    


09,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sushi and beer..again.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    you go girl.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    nice.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    my cousin Joy and my Uncle Bob...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sedona
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    got something in my eye..
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    "feast your eyes on this purse baby...so sorry you don't have one."
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sushi at Kona grill, i got sick the next day and come to find out, the board of health has had problems with those rascals...go at your own risk.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    girls night out...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    4.3...too skinny.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    smoke em if you've got em...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    my friend Shamim.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Pete...looking a bit dazed.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    a solid 8 on the feet, but she's due for some new shoes.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    hiking up camelback mountain...it was hot out that day...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    7.3
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    mothership i made back in 95...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    a little twister....
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    on the way to our cabin in Prescott..you'd  think there's a better system for mail than this..
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    paul and marco on the yz50
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    flower from my front yard..
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    here i'm taking a pic of some poor catepillar that treaded over an anthill and is getting ripped apart...National Geographic would love this one.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My friend Alvin just before he gets ready to take off on my R1, scary thing is shortly after this, i was following him in my car watching him, he suddenly gets on the gas, the front end comes way up, almost going over, both of our hearts stopped and he's been scared of her ever since.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    i know..i felt silly, but i had to do it.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    9.2
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    up in Prescott with the yz400f.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sitting on my friends new Harley, this thing was brand new and he was bragging about how great it was, didn't impress me much when it dripped oil on my sidewalk..why do all harley's seem to leak oil?
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    15 yrs old...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sneaking in for a quick shot, Michelle wasn't excited about it.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    7.4
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Mark and i are getting ready to take the little cessna up...that steel rod looks uncomfortable.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    these guys are impressed as well.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    While mark and i were getting ready to take off, these studs flew in with some big jet and impressed everyone. 
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Mark looks official.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    last minute checks before we go up..i'm nervous, this plane is tiny and Mark only has like 30 hours..
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    getting ready to land at scottsdale airport...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    "now, just stay on the gas like i told you"..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    my neighbor Paul with his son Marco...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sneaking in for a quick shot...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    4.2...looks kinda sloppy if you ask me.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    6.4
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    on a scale from 1-10, i'd give these a 8.7
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    sweetheart, get some larger shoes or something...good grief...those poor piggies look jam packed in there.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Gavin...thinking about what he's got himself into after just purchasing the land to build his new house and notices his neighbors yard.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    a little playstation 2 with my friend Gavin...this pic is like 5 yrs old...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    thinking about taxes...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink     1975 Kenneth Cole suit.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    i kept telling myself to get on that thing...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    $50.00 bet at company picnic party.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    ...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    bowling for cash...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    yep, there's actualy 3 of us.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    teaching myself guitar...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    working too much..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    uncomfortable car rides..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    this one hurt.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    my evil twin.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    plastic surgery..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    dragonfly in Sedona....
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Dan's getting an earfull and then some...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    looks like dan could be in some trouble...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Tara..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Chris Mcbeth..i actualy arm wrestled this guy and lost..arm hurt for 2 days...he's a Marine, kind of a tough guy....good guy to have around if your smarting off at parties and get in trouble.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Gabe.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Hilla and Amy..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Greg and Amy..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    This is actually a small metal knob on the end of a sign i found out on my friends ranch..i liked this shot.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Carly pets bruiser, the ranch cat.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Colored pencil on wood by my friend Mark Mcdowell
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    found this guy up in Sedona in the creek..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Alexa eating some cake on her b-day....
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Went on the 1st friday artwalk in downtown phx, thought this was a bit interesting..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    painting by Greg West..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    painting my friend Greg West did....nice job.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    rear view of R1
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    my R1
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Carly again..i had just given her a home perm, turned out ok...i just doubled the ingredients on what the instructions said..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    there's that girl at the bar again...what is she doing with these guy's?..that always puzzles me...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    happy hour
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    just some girl at the bar...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    John shooting his daughter..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My friend John..he's becoming quite the photographer..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    iris flower from Sedona..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Sara and Dan on the Vespa....
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Me and my friend Amy at Devil's Martini
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My friend Sara....
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    more Crosby...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    more Crosby..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Took some pics at the David Crosby concert at the Mcdowell Mtn Musical Festival..
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Hilla..at desert Ridge, we just got done eating turkey burgers.
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My friend Chris Mcbeth get's a new air gun for his b-day...he's blowing out the candles on his cake here...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    in Cabo..at a friends wedding...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Almost got burned in NYC...
     
    


07,June,2004


     
       urlLink    why yes...i fly.
     
    


25,July,2004


     
       urlLink    my cousin joy..
     
    


13,July,2004


     
       urlLink    out at bartlet lake on 7_24_04...perfect day.
     
    


13,July,2004


     
       urlLink    incase you wanted a better look at it....here it is, i love the two oil pans that make that beautiful camel head...oh, and it adjustable, they actually put this little rascal in different positions and light him up at night..only in big sky country!
     
    


12,July,2004


     
       urlLink    only in montana....
     
    


12,July,2004


     
       urlLink    you might be a redneck if....
     
    


06,July,2004


     
       urlLink    jay's first time at stand up comedy...he did well.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
       urlLink    going up..
     
    


05,July,2004


     
       urlLink    freaking flash didn't go off...
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       urlLink    the mid air stand.
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       urlLink    pounce.
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       urlLink    climbs walls...
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       urlLink    he flies too.
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       urlLink    supercat....more to follow...
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    sara, mahsa, and jeff..
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Uncle Charlie on my old R6 that got stolen.
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    9th grade picture..had a bit of an attitude going there.
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    bad accident...
     
    



