
25,June,2004


     
      This old sea reaver's retiring, I've had fun traveling from Dagon Fel to Khorinis, Vivec to Tel Branora but I'm giving up the sea life to star in a sitcom named Method & Red, guess who I am. Song of the Day: What is and What Should Never Be-Led Zeppelin
     
    


23,June,2004


     
      so is italy, shitty shit shit, now what? i've lost interest in euro cup. Song of the Day:Monaco, oh wait that's a principality. Mayonaisse-Smashing Pumpkins
     
    


20,June,2004


     
      That's Justin Timberlake's phone number, what a little shit just cuz he's rich he gets a long phone number, infact i'm calling that prick right now. Song of the Day:Every Me Every You-Placebo
     
    


18,June,2004


     
      emerica this is skateboarding so good. Song of the Day: i already gave you a song for Friday you fucks
     
    


14,June,2004


     
      shit i missed i few days oh well, its not like the golden horde care. To catch up on news i have officially started making air conditioners as well as starring in shampoo commercials, im the guy in the background of a herbal essence commercial. Song of the Day: Saucerful of Secrets-Pink Floyd
     
    


14,June,2004


     
      Its gonna be tits. Song of the Day-The Darkness of the Matinee-Franz Ferdinand
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      i love polk audio. Song of the Day-Geek U.S.A-Smashing Pumpkins
     
    


11,June,2004


     
      i don't know that i'm a computer. Song of the Day: Wish You Were Here-Pink Floyd
     
    


10,June,2004


     
      it's a weblog i tricked all of ya with my smooth stapler businessman impersonation. Anyway back to regular schedule.  i saw an alien today, it told me to rinse then lather then repeat. but didnt repeat so it told on me, i got a time-out. ah shucks i shoulda repeated.  Song of the Day:Little Girls Pointing and Laughing-alexisonfire
     
    


09,June,2004


     
      do you believe in aliens? song of the day:curves like decoys-.hopesfall.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
      Doge Vittorio IV  The Holy Roman Empire has captured the south wall, now there is little hope for the French. Our armies are wavering as general Billy Bob Thorton has been killed at the battle of Evermore.  Yours Truly, HBC Rewards  Song of the day: Dogs-Pink Floyd
     
    


07,June,2004


     
      mysoundclick.ca the only good ska band, a two piece band that go to my school. song of the day: rhinocerus-smashing pumpkins
     
    


05,June,2004


     
      Hey kids stop downloading, it's bad for your skin like New Zealand. Song of the day: Song of the Remains the Same-Led Zeppelin
     
    


02,August,2004


     
      i feel so dirty. Song of the Day: Love Song-The Cure 
     
    



