
03,August,2004



       
       Welcome to 9694 Photo! On this Blog I post some of my best Pohtography, Give Photo tips, and recieve feedback on the pictures I post here. I am in High School, so there is not much time to take many pictures. I usually take shots of nature, but other times I will have sports shots. I'm taking a photography class at school, so I hope to get better. You can e-mail your photography to me and, if you want, I can Post It here as a Guest Photo. My E-Mail Is  urlLink j_knight@att.net .  
     

    



17,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here Is The Statue Of Liberty.
     
    


16,June,2004


     
       urlLink    If you look in the center of this picture you can see where the World Trade Centers were. I had a great time in New York.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here is my Entire 8th grade class.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here is a picture of my friends and me at our 8th grade Graduation. Compton, Caroline, and me.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       As you might can tell I LOVE to take pictures. If you are the same way I would love for you to send me your best pictures. I love to look at others picturs and learn. I take pictures with a Canon Rebel EOS. It goes EVERYWHERE with me. I'll have pictures of N.Y. City on here by Tues. 
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    I play the Trumpet at school.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My little brother and his Choir director. He actually likes to play Baseball.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    I found this little bird walking around so i got my zoom lense and got its picture. I entered it into a photo contest. I don't know if it has won, but I'll let you know.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here is my dog. Her name is Boots, just look at her paws and it will all become clear. SHE IS THE BEST DOG IN THE WORLD!!!!!!
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    There is my Grandfather on the far left. We are all pretty good at put put. (or mini golf as some call it)
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Mom in action. She is learning how to be a teacher.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My Aunt Stacie on the bottom and my Mom above
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    My Grandmother...
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Ok I found a picture of all of us. Dad is on the far left.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    Here is a picture of my family. (Dad had to work and couldn't come with us on the trip) My little brother is on the left, mom in the center, and a terrible picture of me on the right.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       urlLink    This Is A Picture I took At A Little Place Called Peach Park In Clanton AL.
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       Hey! Visit the site below! I webmaster It for my Grandfather. It has to do with cars, but I have some of my photos on it.  www.streettoyz.net Tell me what you think! 
     
    


01,July,2004


     
       urlLink    More Of My Hobbie. In Peach Park
     
    


01,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Me And My Brother In Battery Park.
     
    


01,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Here Is The Sculpture That Stood Between The Twin Towers. It is now in Battery Park.
     
    



