

26,June,2004


     
      No need to send a mail to my id. You can comment on any of my posts. :-)  BTW here is my new mail id --

16,June,2004


     
      Latest survey shows that every 3 out of 4 people  in the world make up 75% of the world's population. :-)
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day.  Teach a man to fish and he will sit in a boat drinking beer all day.  Teach a man to manufacture beer  and he will contest for loksabha elections against Vijay Mallya.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day.  Teach a man to fish and he will sit in a boat drinking beer all day.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      I always forget 3 things.  1. Names,  2. Faces  and the third one, I don't remember.  
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      There are 10 kinds of people in the world. One who believe in Binary system and the other who don't.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      A pat on the back is only a few inches from a kick in the butt.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      When things go wrong.....leave them.... don't go with them.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Help a man when he is in trouble and he will remember you when he is in trouble again.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Sacrifice anything for love, but don't sacrifice love for anything.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      The bad part about being in a rat race is that even if you win you are still a rat.
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Do you believe in Astrology ?? If you ask me the same question, then I will say "Yes I do, to some extent".   When I was in Bangalore, during my college days.  One day on of my family friends who had a fair knowledge of Astrology said to me, "You will go towards east to work when everyone will fly towards west."  Then I was dreaming about going to Singapore, Japan, Australia.. etc.. etc..   After completing my graduation, I got a job and traveled due east not to Japan or Singapore, but to Chennai. :-) That's why I said I believe in Astrology to some extent.. ;-)
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      I'm not a complete idiot, there're still some parts missing!
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      Trust no future, however pleasant, Bury the past, in its past dead, Act, act in the living future, With God above and Heart within.  ~Henry Wadsworth Longfellow. 
     
    


15,June,2004


     
      If something is so complicated that you can't explain it in 10 seconds, then it's probably not worth knowing anyway.
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      Never argue with idiots. They drag you down to their level, and then beat you with experience.
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      A single rose given during one's lifetime is better than a bouquet of orchids placed over the grave.
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      The number of people watching you is directly proportional to the stupidity of your action. 
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      Alcohol doesn't solve any problems, but then again, neither does milk 
     
    


11,June,2004


     
      Hello all,  Here is my series of some stupid but meaningful set of words or sentences which would bring smile on your face. If you want to comments on these, you have to be a member in this blog. To become a member send a mail to:  urlLink pachchaa@rediffmail.com   Hope you enjoy it.  Pachcha 18 till I die.  (not my age, its my salary :-)
     
    


14,July,2004


     
      It matters not whether you win or lose, What matters is whether I win or lose.                                                                  
     
    



