
29,June,2004


	 
      not kool man, not kool at all..
    


25,June,2004


	 
      um i guess not lol. hrphm =/
    


17,June,2004


	 
      ummm are we ever gona write in here?
    


17,June,2004


	 
       well i have arrived in alabama..im bored as hell.and tierd..i loves ya!!
    


16,June,2004


	 
       yay wo0t have fun in alabama me love i shall miss you!!!! ::mucho huggles:: &hearts; sikk 
    


15,June,2004


	 
       mUfFiNs ArE sExI!    Depressed? gah..not kool...i hate that.. i was to yesturday, but yeah its otay im over it now, just reallllllllllllly tiered. I have a lost of apitite yet im still eating, and almost through up after wards...as much as i talk vbout it i really dont want to go to alabama...erk i realllllly dont want to, but ol'well.. i mean yeah it will bee fun, but at the moment all i want to do is sleep,lol, not travel. We need to make a "blob" full of lots of peoples, like everyones, lol....  I just hope i feel better soon, damn headsches,i have a feeling our journal wont get writen in much ne more, lol....  much loves to ya babe!
    


15,June,2004


	 
       hey amber  IM BORED! erk i updated my lj. uuuuuuuuuuum for some reason im kinda depressed now. :hrmph: o i changed my layout a bit, idk what i think of it tho. hmm yeh erk ::twitch::  &hearts; SIKK
    


15,June,2004


	 
      i made it work...nanananannanaboboobobobob  hehe we have a blob..........woaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah...
    


15,June,2004


	 
       Greetings and salutations! how art thou this fine.. tuesday afternoon? is this still considered the afternoon? hmm. oh well no need to dwell on that minor question. erk hmm  blogger is alot cooler now that i know some HTML. lmao hmm yeh im going to go bugg peoples now...  &hearts; sikk  
    


20,July,2004


	 
        AMBER! ................     *     *     *     *    *   *   *   *   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   ANAL      *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ORGY     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  FREAK SEX      *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *     *       &nbsp;      &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp; 
    


03,July,2004


	 
       yay im home!! my sisters house was fun for a while but im glad im home i love my niece but im just(as my mum says) "'kid out"' u kno? lol  
    


03,July,2004


	 
       yay im home!! my sisters house was fun for a while but im glad im home i love my niece but im just(as my mum says) "'kid out"' u kno? lol  
    



