
29,June,2004



       
       urlLink Michael Moore.com : Mike's Message : Mike's Latest News   Ok,  apparently the link didn't go through.  This is the web page, so if you want to see the theater, just scroll down to Minnesota.
     

    


28,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Inside the theater.
     

    


28,June,2004



       
       urlLink    This is the theater where I went to see Farenheit 9-11
     

    


28,June,2004



       
      This afternoon I drove into uptown Minneapolis to catch a late afternoon showing of the new Michael Moore movie.  I was very impressed by the film. Yes the film is a very slanted propoganda-documentary, but when has Moore ever denied that?    I believe Moore's strength lies in his ability to combine chilling video clips with poignant music.  He is also very adept at connecting events that otherwise appear to have no connection. Nowhere are these strengths more evident than in this movie.    My biggest problem with the film was its fragmentation.  He begins with a 20 min. look at how Gore lost the election, proceedes to a 45 minute examination of the Bush-Saudi connection, continues by examining the Afghanistan war for 30 min. (along with its connections to the defense industry), and then finishes with an attack against the administration's Iraq war.  Although all these parts are interesting, there is no thread to tie them together.  Moore begins by discussing Bin Laden, and ends up on the old standby of Corporate Greed, and the plight of the downtrodden.    I think at times Moore has a tendency to go over the top, but I do believe he is genuine in his crusade, and therefore I respect him.  On tonight's Daily Show they showed an interview he did on CBS where the anchor clearly intended to ambush him.  However, Moore quickly turned that ambush on its head and confronted the Woman about CBS's supposed lack of journalistic integrity.  It was rather funny.
     

    


27,June,2004



       
       urlLink WorldTribune.com: Move over Tiger: N. Korea's Kim shot 38 under par his 1st time out   This was just too good to pass up.
     

    


27,June,2004



       
      Last night the people across the hall moved out, throwing what looked like all of their worldly posessions in front of the dumpster.  Included in that pile were a leather love seat, a chair, and a matching ottoman, all invaluable items for a poor grad student who will need to furnish an apartment in another month.    So, with the help of my roommate I emulated my good buddy Fred and pillaged the dumpster pile.  I am very happy with my latest accusitions, and will continue to keep a hawkish eye on the junk heap in case anything else of interest is added.
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    My pillaged Leather "Like-Seat"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    My new chair in a temporary holding space.  Behind it, on the other side of the wall sits the matching Ottoman.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
      Yesterday Minnesotans officially entered the 20th century with the arrival of the new light rail train.  I met my friend Elma and her roommate to check out the festivities first hand.  From the crowds of people waiting to ride the train, you would think that the people here have never ridden a subway train before.    After riding through several stations, we went back towards the university to meet up with Alec.  Following lunch at a chinese restaurant (my fortune stated:  "Don't expect romantic attachments to be strictly logical or rational!" ;) ) we headed back downtown to the Metrodome for the Twins-Brewers game.    The game itself was not noteworthy (the Twins lost 7-2).  However we were scolded during the singing of the national anthem by a militant ueber nationalist Brewers fan for not demonstrating proper respect for the country.    All in all this was a very good Saturday.
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    The Twentieth century has arrived!!!  Hooray!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    View from the Lake Street station.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    You'd think these people had never rode a train before.  This is the line just to get on the platform to wait for the train.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Waiting for the train.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Lunch at Peking Garden. I reccommend the Szechuan Chicken.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
       urlLink    My obligatory Metrodome shot.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,June,2004



       
      So, I bet you're all wondering what a bored grad student does on a Friday night.  Well, tonight I decided to try something different.  I wanted to recreate a great moment in Blogging history.  So, I got my digital camera, went to Rainbow Foods (a division of Roundys for those not in the know), and attempted to recreate  urlLink this great moment from May 30, 2004.     On this date in Blogging history, San Antonio intellectual Micah Valine astutely documented the rising costs of milk.  Placing his camera behind the milk containers, Micah artistically conveyed this serious social, economic, and potentially political issue.    Recreating this moment, I needed to place a half gallon of fruit juice under the camera to prop it up.  Also, unlike the original, my recreation can actually be accepted as the view from the other side, in that milk stalkers, uhhh. .. stockers actually place new milk in the case from the other side of the wall, ensuring regular product rotation, and fresh milk for you the consumer.    This has been a Great Moment in Blogging History. 
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Take 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Take 3&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Take four of my recreation&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    As you can see, milk prices have risen here too.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
      Tonight I went to see the Darkness play at the River Centre in St. Paul.  The concert was awesome!!!!  Wow!  Mad props to Freddie for pushing me to buy the ticket.  It is easily the third best concert I've seen, after the White Stripes, and the Foo Fighters.  At one point, the lead singer did a tour de force guitar solo, and came within 4 feet of me.  What a show!!!!
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    The Darkness rocked my socks off.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Me, getting ready to rock out with the Darkness.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink The Club For Growth - Home Page     urlLink Advertisement   This is a link to a new commercial being run by the Club for Growth.  I have no clue what the message is they are trying to convey.  This has to be the worst propaganda piece I've ever seen.  To quote Adam Sandler on SNL:  "Who are the Ad-wizards who came up with this one?"
     

    


24,June,2004



       
       urlLink CNN.com - Gene mutation makes tot super strong - Jun 24, 2004    Settling the argument once and for all.  Uebermensch ist ein Deutscher!
     

    


23,June,2004



       
      Today I went to downtown St. Paul in order to purchase a ticket for friday night's Darkness concert, sans $8.50 surcharge.  It really is a nice city.  Much more pedestrian than Minneapolis.  Below are some pictures from St. Paul, and my walk into Minneapolis on Saturday afternoon.
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Snoopy!  Part of the St. Paul campaign (like the bisons in Buffalo)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    the Excel Center&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Downtown St. Paul&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    St. Paul Cathedral&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    What trip would be complete without fowl?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    Downtown Minneapolis from the East Bank&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink    You're gonna make it after all&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink Clinton's Empty 'Life' (washingtonpost.com)    Ok Jeff, I took your advice, and read the post.  Not bad :)
     

    


22,June,2004



       
       urlLink The New York Times 

22,June,2004



       
       urlLink The New York Times 

22,June,2004



       
       urlLink CNN.com - List of 100 best movie songs - Jun 23, 2004    Well, apparently not the Ghostbusters.  The AFI released its list of the 100 greatest film songs today, but failed to list the Ray Parker Jr. classic.  How this song could not make the top 100 is beyond me.  If Eminem makes the list, Ghostbusters deserve to be on there too. Harrumph!
     

    


22,June,2004



       
      Bill Clinton, of that fabulous acting duo of Bill and Hillary.  Before the hoopla surrounding Clinton's new memoir arose this week, I was actually starting to change my opinion of the former president.  I began to look back at his accomplishments, and acknowledge, that he was a fairly successful president.    Now however, I am once again reminded why I dislike him so much.  Clinton, like his wife, is an egomaniacal, mendacious, Megalomaniac.  For a man who could remember absolutely nothing for eight years, he suddenly has an awful lot to say.   Although I have not read the book (and will not waste my time doing so), I have read enough about it to know that it contains nothing revealing, and that if anything it is just another frantic attempt by Clinton to cement his legacy.  Clinton does not confront his decision to pardon Mark Rich, a billionaire charged in 1983 with evading $48 million in taxes as well as running illegal oil deals with Iran during the hostage crisis.  Rich fled to Switzerland to evade the charges, but essentially bought a pardon with the help of his wife.  The pardon was heavily criticized by both Republicans and Democrats.   Clinton also fails to discuss the 1996 funding scandal involving Johnny Chung, a Chinese businessman who used his business connections in China to funnel millions of dollars into Clinton's campaign fund for the 1996 election.  In exchange for the money Clinton altered US Arms sales restriction laws to allow US companies to sell China military technology.  Democratic senator Joeseph Lieberman later said: "The fundraising scandal of 1996 was a very real tragedy, with very real consequences for our democracy."  Finally, in an attempt to keep up with Hillary, Clinton also compares himself to Nelson Mandela. (Hillary compared her forgiveness of Bill with Mandela's forgiveness of White South Africans).  If this does not smack of Megalomania, I do not know what does.  So, for those of you still believing this is the best administration of the century, I leave you with this:  his  urlLink rap sheet .
     

    


21,June,2004



       
      Listening to the events of and discourse over the Iraq war, I cannot help but think the world is ruled by one of my favorite authors, Kafka.    The Americans invaded the country in an attempt to remove the weapons of mass destruction, and end human rights abuses, yet turned out to be worse than the  urlLink deposed .  We have also learned that France and Russia, two of the staunchest defenders of peace, actually fought the war out of the fear that the massive corruption of the oil for food program would come to  light.   The list goes on and on, reading exactly like something Kafka himself would write.   Everyone argues that this war is the fault of the US, and that the US should therefore pay the price alone.  However, I think if anything, this is just exacerbating the problem.  Yes, the US occupation has been a disaster, but conditions could very easily be better if the world was just be more open to helping.    I'll conceede, the US hasn't been willing to ceede authority over Iraq, but who ultimately does that hurt?  Iraqis!  As the international community tries to stick it to the US for being the unopposed superpower, the situation just gets worse and worse inside Iraq.  Neighboring middle eastern countries do not want to see Iraq succeed out of the fear that a democratic government there will create problems for their despotism.     There's nothing we can do now about the war.  The US is there, and to completely pull out now would only make things worse.  Although this may be an opportunity to challenge the American unipolar order, the only losers in this are the Iraqis.    Everyone criticizes the US for acting, asking why it was so important to go to war over this.  As the corruption within the UN proved though, the relief was not achieving its desired end, and the enforcement of the No-Fly Zones was just a waste of money, material and life.  So, as my communist friends ask me all the time, why was it so wrong to take a chance?  Instead of continuing to plod along in a stagnant international environment, content contain Saddam, as long as he only made his own people's lives miserable, the Bush administration wanted to remake Iraq in the shadow of Western Liberal Democracy.    Perhaps if we start to work together, we can end this Kafkaesque nightmare.
     

    


21,June,2004



       
      I'm doing more photoshop work right now, listening to my favorite English radio station on ITunes.  Yesterday, England beat Croatia 4-2, to advance in the EM 2004.  To celebrate, the English have combined Wuhoo by the 5678s (a la Kill Bill fame) with a bunch of Soccer play by play calls and cheers.  Its kind of catchy, and they play it every 30 min.  Now having said that, its time for the daily 1:45 playing of Travis. . . 
     

    


21,June,2004



       
       urlLink The Zelikow Report   In today's New York Times, William Safire comments on the recently released Zelikow Report, an "interim report" issued by the Commission's staff.  The report, picked up by news media under headlines that dismiss any Iraq-Al Qaeda connection, has clearly been misconstrued.  As Safire clearly demonstrates, the report combines the issues of Iraqi-Qaeda relations (which there were), and an Iraqi connection to 9/11 (which there was none).  It attempts to argue on the basis of Iraq's 9/11 involvement (or lack thereof) that no connection between the two entities existed whatsoever.    I think Safire's column is yet another reminder of why the 9/11 commission is nothing but a joke.  It was designed to be a bipartisan effort to determine the root causes and failures that led to the terrorist strikes.   However, it has been more concerned with assigning blame solely on one party or the other.  As current and former top officials were questioned by the commission, the only member to question both sides with equal vigor was Bob Kerry.  The Zelikow report is yet another example of the commission's failure to do its job correctly.  Supposedly published without the commissions knowledge, the report seeks to discredit Bush more than uncover the truth.    I do not think you can completely blame either Republicans or Democrats for 9/11.  Yes the Bush administration did not fight the terrorist threat with as much zeal as it should have, but at the same time, Clinton had his chance to get Bin Laden in the late 1990's and failed.  There are also many other root failures that can be traced back to earlier administrations.    I sympathize with those families that lost relatives in the attacks.  However, I do not think it prudent to brand the Bush and Guilianni administrations as a band of murderers.  Giulianni had New York City arguably more prepared for a terrorist attack than any other American City.  Unfortunately his anti-terror headquarters was destroyed in the bombings.  At the same time, the mayor himself admitted that he believed an attack would most likely come in the form of a chemical or biological bomb, not kamikazi Boeings.  Yet, in the face of so much chaos, Gulianni's stoic leadership arguably prevented the situation from being much, much worse.  As the mayor himself has said, if anyone is to be blamed for the attacks, how about the 19 individuals who actually carried out the attack?  If we truly want to get to the root causes of the 9/11 failures, the commission must do what it was intended to do.  As Safire argues, it must show how Clinton's failure to respond to the USS Cole bombings contributed to 9/11.  It must demonstrate how Bush's refusal to replace George Tenet as CIA director would be beneficial, and finally it must demonstrate "how Congress's intelligence oversight failed abysmally."  Only then, when all parties are criticized equally will the commission regain the credibility it has so shamelessly lost.  
     

    


19,June,2004



       
      Kristof continues his saga on Sudan in today's editorial.  http://www.nytimes.com/2004/06/19/opinion/19KRIS.html
     

    


18,June,2004



       
        href="http://www.nytimes.com/2004/06/18/opinion/18FRI1.html"

17,June,2004



       
      I'm hesitant to voice my grievances with the American Media, but I just cannot restrain myself right now.    This afternoon, two very newsworthy events occurred that deserved an immense amount of media attention.  However, based on the medias coverage of these events, you would never know of the second one.    The first event I speak of is the tragic beheading of Paul Johnson.  The story has dominated the headlines, and rightfully so.  However, the second event I speak of has barely received any attention.    So, what is this event you ask?  Well, I'll give you a hint:  It will have a significant impact on the current Geopolitical environment.  Don't know?  Here's another:  The combined economic strength of this area is almost equivalent to that of the United States.  Still no clue?  Ok, one last hint:  The agreement reached today will help pave the way for this region to become a Superpower that will rival the USA.  If you still don't know, I would like to say I am disappointed in you, but I can't because this event has received virtually NO ATTENTION in the media!!!!!  Of course I'm speaking of the new EU constitution that was finally agreed upon today.  http://www.cnn.com/2004/WORLD/europe/06/18/eu.summit/index.html  Six months after failing to reach an agreement, European diplomats finally agreed on a constitution today.  Of course it still needs to be approved by 13 of the 25 members to take effect, but this is still a significant event.  However, this is the first step in creating a closer union among the EU states that could ultimately rival the US as a second superpower.  The consequences of such a union would be immense for the US.  If taken to an extreme, the EU could help usher in a new bi-polar age where the US no longer has the opportunity to create hegemonic order unopposed.   Sadly, this received no coverage in the media today.  It is currently listed #3 on www.cnn.com under the WORLD section.  That's right, this was not even important enough to make the normal headline section.  Apparently McDonald's food testing, a rapper who made a video in jail, and Bill Clinton's admission that he slept on the couch after coming clean to Hillary about his escapades with Monica are all more important than the EU.  As if this is bad enough, Fox News does not even MENTION the story.  I guess if it is not wrapped in Red White and Blue singing the high praises of W., then it is an anti-American, Benedict Arnold, Liberal conspiracy that is out to deep six everything good and wholesome.    I understand that the primary goal of American news media outlets is to focus on those events which are of relevance to Americans.  I also realize that my complaints are nothing new, and that I am just reiterating grievances raised by numerous others.  However, I am nevertheless disappointed by the coverage given to the EU today.  
     

    


17,June,2004



       
       urlLink    I just thought this was a really funny sign on my way to school this morning.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


17,June,2004



       
       urlLink    The view across the street from the movie theater of downtown Minneapolis.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


17,June,2004



       
       urlLink    The Movie Theater, part of a redeveloped stretch along the river.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


17,June,2004



       
      On the way home from school, I decided to stop by the movie theater and see the new Ben Stiller movie:  Dodgeball.  I had pretty low expectations for the film, but was pleasantly surprised in that it actually was pretty funny.    I thought the high point of the film was Jason Bateman's performance as Pepper Brooks, the color commentator for the ESPN 8 telecast of the dodgeball tourney.  Bateman perfectly captures the role of the inane commentator that one all to often finds on professional sport broadcasts.  On a different note, I was disappointed by the audience's failure to pick up on a hilarious joke involving the German dodgeball team.  I won't spoil it for anyone, but I thought it was very subtle, and well done.  I'll try to post some pics in a bit.
     

    


17,June,2004



       
      As I work on a photoshop project here at the U, I'm taking advantage of the office's subscription to ITunes.  It's great, I've got a station in the UK, and I'm listening to the 80's at 8 0'Clock at 1:15 in the afternoon.  Life is good :)
     

    


17,June,2004



       
      Today I bought an invitation for Gmail on Ebay.  It was the greatest $.99 I ever spent.  I don't know why yet, but I just know that getting in on the ground floor of this new project will pay off down the road.  When I find out how I will let you know.
     

    


17,June,2004



       
      After weeks of badgering, I've finally moved my blog to blogspot.  I feel like such a tool. :)
     

    


31,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Harmon Killebrew returns and he has Four Arms!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred is so enthused by the game!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    When the Twins fell behind 7-2 I decided to have some fun with my camera.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Random Metrodome Shot.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Me with the big Twins jersey outside the Metrodome!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Water Fowl!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred is endorsing C2.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I hiked up Fred's shorts to document his bug wounds.  Now tell me this doesn't need neosporin!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Oh no I've been spotted!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Master photographers at work!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred's mug shot at Pizza Luce.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The happy couple :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Me and my good buddy Jango.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Us at Grandma's.  Grandma's cooking is as good as ever, but since when did she start charging so much?!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


28,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The gang just got here, and Jeff could not resist showing off his motley assortment of facial cremes and deoderants.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,July,2004



       
      Yesterday I went to a party for my friends Alec and Elma, who just got married a few months ago.  I met Alec and Elma in Dortmund, so a bunch of friends who were in Dortmund then also made the trip up!  It was great seeing old friends again, and nice how we all seemed to pick up right where we left off.
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Mr. and Mrs. Alec Johnson!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Stammtisch Reunion! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Deep philosophical conversation&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Elma and John&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Alec Rocking Out!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I was awarded the prestigious honor of tapping the Keg.  I've never seen Mark so giddy before :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Debating how to move the Keg.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Mark and Elma's brother playing more fooseball.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The building where the party was held.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Alec kicking butt in Fooseball.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Random action shot of Ted&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    "Keith" trying really hard to be not-so-photogenic.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    John being photogenic.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Mark is looking for the missing Fooseball.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Wedding Party.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This was a sign posted on the gate surrounding the pool.  John was not allowed in :(  As I asked him though, what about children with Huggies or Luvs?  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
      So I finally posted my pictures from Milwaukee.  The Stadium was ok, but it was like watching a baseball game in a hockey arena.  Miller Park did not have the same feel as the parks in Cincinnati or St. Louis.  Nevertheless it is a decent building.  The high point though was the Bratwurst.  Miller Park had the closest Bratwurst to authentic German Bratwurst.  A must have for anyone who goes to a game there.
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Stadium after the Game.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    No baseball game would be complete without the Sausage race.  Go Bratwurst!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This was my seat.  It was in a good position behind the plate, but that railing on the left really sucked.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Stadium was filled with Cubs Faithful&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Miller Park as I was rushing into the stadium.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Obligatory Field Shot&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
      Recently, I have read a significant amount of material on homosexuality and how it relates to the Bible.  I also recently found a new church here in Minneapolis, (www.bethanyinseward.com) and much to my surprise discovered that they are currently on the verge of breaking boundaries by ordaining an openly gay pastor.  I personally could not be more supportive of this.    Let me return to my original thought though, the position of homosexuals in the bible.  Citing passages in Romans and 2 Corinthians, many people have argued that homosexuality is a sin, and that therefore ideas like gay marriage should not be legalized.  In a recent conversation with my friend Fred, he stated that, barring a reinterpretation of these passages (something he is not opposed to) homosexuality appears to be sinful.  I hesitate to use Fred as an example, but I believe his statement is emblematic of the problematic nature of the biblical debate over homosexuality.  If I understand this statement correctly, a literal interpretation of the Bible forbids homosexuality, however if biblical scholars chose to provide an acceptable reinterpretation, then it might be ok.    There are several problems with approaching the question from this angle.  First, if one only relies on a literal interpretation, what does that say about other aspects of life the Bible discusses.  For example, when discussing sexual perversion, and self abuse, all of the passages argue that it is unaccepatable for a man to abuse himself, and lust after other women.  Clearly this could be interpreted to understand that masturbation is frowned upon.  However, since it only mentions men, does that mean it is ok for a woman to masturbate?  Based solely on a literal interpretation of the Bible, it would appear so.    I believe it is extremely problematic to take the Bible literally.  The scriptures so often cited have been translated numerous times through different cultures, periods, and by different types of people.  Therefore, how are we to know that this is actually the original text?  For all I know, the passage that explicitly forbids homosexuality could have been purposely altered by a 12th century monk who had a personal disdain for the practice.  As a historian, I am constantly tought that one must be sceptical when researching, that one cannot always take a document at face value.  I believe the same must be said for understanding the Bible.  Its quite possible these passages were altered repeatedly to reflect the general norms of society at the time it was translated.  I think its safe to say that 13 century Gaul is not the same as 21 Century Western society.   So how then is one to understand homosexuality?  I do not believe it is necessary for one to rely on other people to interpret the scriptures for us.  A central tennant of Lutheranism is that every person is his own intperpreter.  Therefore, when trying to understand the Bible's position on homosexuality, it is necessary to properly contextualize the passages.  For the purposes of this post, I will rely on Romans 1: 26- 2:6.  In this passage it appears that Paul explicitly rejects homosexual acts.  I find it interesting to note on a tangent, that the verse before states that women should be condemned for having sex in "unnatural ways."  (Does this mean Missionary style is blessed, but that Doggie Style is a sin?  :) )  However, I arrive at a different understanding, once it is contextualized.  As Paul condemns homosexuality, he is also very critical in his letter of Idol worshiping, and emphasizes that salvation can be found in faith and faith alone.  It appears, that in his condemnation of idol worshiping, he uses sexual perversion and homosexuality to emphasize the selfish nature of these people.  He indicates that these people are sinful because they place more emphasis on self-gratification than on worshiping God.  Could it therefore also mean that homosexuality itself is not sinful, but is only sinful when one places sexual gratification above God?  It's now 3:18 am, and I really should get to bed, so let me conclude by saying, that we do not need to rely on scholars, or priests to interpret the Bible for us.  If you want to believe homosexuality is a sin, thats fine, its your interpretation.  However, I believe, through personal interpretation, its also possible to accept homosexuality. 
     

    


13,July,2004



       
       urlLink Chicago Tribune | New spin for Rock 'n' Roll McDonald's   Heresy!  Wesley is spinning in his grave!
     

    


12,July,2004



       
       urlLink FOXNews.com - Foxlife - 'Jeffersons' Actress Isabel Sanford Dies at 86     "Isabel 'Weezie' Sanford expires of natural causes in Los Angeles"  This was the subtext of the fox news headline.  Could this possibly be phrased any worse?
     

    


11,July,2004



       
       urlLink ESPN.com - MLB - MLB PREVIEW    Jeff and I have recently been arguing about which team is better, the cubs or the cardinals.  Although the Cardinals are well beyond the rest of the division, one can see that the two teams are virtually equal in all the major statistical categories.  There is one glaring difference however.  The Cubs have a slew of players still out with injuries.  I think that once these players come back, and the Cubs are whole again, they will once again be one of the best teams in the league.  A complete roster will make them very dangerous in October.
     

    


08,July,2004



       
       urlLink       
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      So, here are the pics from St. Louis on Tuesday.  I have several photos of Miller Park in Milwaukee to post as well.  I will do that perhaps tomorrow. Perhaps I will also post more closing comments.  In any event, enjoy these pictures of St. Louis.  It was by far the best city we went to, and the stadium had the most character.  In conclusion, Go CUBS!
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Metro Link on the way home&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Batting practice&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Go Cardinals!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Construction on the new stadium next door&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Stadium from Center Field&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Big Mac Land!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    there's so much character in Busch stadium, you can't find it anywhere else.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Outside of Busch Stadium&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Savvis Center.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Inventive advertising in St. Louis&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The fan shop in the mall&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Art Deco!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Union Central Station in St. Louis&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    One of the many court houses in St. Louis.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Arch behind the Jefferson Memorial.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Arch behind the Jefferson memorial.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The entrance to the Horse's Anus ride, operated by the plutonians.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Underneath the Arch.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    East St. Louis, where we parked the car and took the train in.  We were later accosted by a Crack Whore on the way back afterwards.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Busch Stadium from the car.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Carshot of Downtown St. Louis.  Jeff wanted to kill me afterwards because he was trying to change lanes while I was taking pictures.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Jeff in the train.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    St. Louis, keep Left!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Welcome to Louisville.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Welcome to Illinois.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Car shot of downtown Louisville.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Here's why.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    We wanted Dairy Queen, but it was closed :(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Another Random Nashville shot.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This is the Chemistry building.  We took this photo for Joe.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Nashville, Indiana.  The wierdest place ever.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This is my Schrockesque action shot at the U.  I'm reading an alternative paper.  :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    University of Indiana&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Entrance to the University of Indiana&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Jeff after using the facilities in Bloomington, Indiana.  This photo was taken in the same style as previous photos of Fred and Joe in Europe.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      Yesterday we went to Cincinnati to see the Reds play the Indians on the fourth of July.  The game was good, even though the Indians lost, and I got really sunburned.  After the game we drove to Dayton, and decided there to cancel the next day of the road trip for an off day.  Jeff bought a baseball glove at Meijer while I purchased Aloe Vera Gel for my sun burns.    When we got home, we watched Meatball and Milkshake, but Jeff was unimpressed.  This morning we played catch on the rolling green pastures of Terre Haute.  Tommorrow:  St. Louis!
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    We ate dinner at a Big Boy restaurant.  Jeff on the ride from Cincinnati:  "I really want a Big Boy!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    On the way there.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    We stopped at Dunkin Donuts to get coffee and Bavarian Creme Donuts.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Welcome to Ohio!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Pepsi Powerstacks.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Cleveland Indians, and Dunkin Donuts Coffee.  Could life get better?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Ballpark after the Tribe blew it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Paul Brown Stadium&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    It's the lawn mower/bath tub.  Fred, we thought about getting this for you.  It seemed like something you would be interested in.  :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Downtown Cincinnati&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I almost missed this shot.  Jeff sped up so I couldn't get it, and threatened to swerve the car.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Back to Terre Haute!  We decided we needed an off day on the Baseball Odyssey.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


03,July,2004



       
      Today the Odyssey almost encountered a setback with severe thunder storms.  However, with the help of Fred and Megan's skilled weather analysis, the storms passed by and allowed for just enough time for the Indians and Bats to play ball!    Before the game, Jeff once again failed in his quest to find a renewable energy source, which led us to the Indianapolis convention center to make a pit stop. Apparently today the African Methodist church was electing its bishop for the year, which led to massive last minute campaigns.  As Jeff said upon entering the building:  "Do you think they'll know we aren't here for the conference?"    Tomorrow, on to Cincinnati!
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Jeff and I took pictures of Squirrels today.  This one approached us at ISU this morning as we tried to Blog in front of the student union.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    If only Vinnie Cook could have dorms like these. . . .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This is Depaw College, a really rich, aristocratic, plantation-esque liberal arts school outside Indianapolis.  Believe it or not, this is the Math and Science building.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Aloe Vera, the underground cult punk rockers of Indianapolis play their most successful show to date!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Art shot! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


02,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I support Winston Hill for the Bishop of the African Methodist/Episcopal Church. . . . &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
      After Jeff and Fred unceremoniously blew out of my apartment like bats out of Hell at 6:36 AM, Megan and I followed in close pursuit at 6:48 as we headed to New Ulm, MN.  New Ulm was a German utopian community founded in the 1800s by a group of German immigrants.  Everything was in German, and the atmosphere of the town was a quaint cross between Europe, 1920's Architecture, and the old west.  The high point was definitely Schell's Brewery, the second oldest family owned brewery in the country.  All in all, a great day!
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan is trying to sexually arouse the peacock so he will show us his feathers.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Another Peacock!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The wide assortment of beers&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Nice, but not as many kegs as in Bremen.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    A peacock with his tail feathers!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Guten Tag!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    A fountain in the garden&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    A garden at the Brewery.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Schell's Brewery&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    My Gosh there are Peacocks!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Can you find the Chipmunk?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    One of the scenes&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    This is the hill for the Way of the Cross.  It was organized by a group of German Nuns at the turn of the Twentieth Century, and features 12 scenes from Jesus's crucifixion.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    my skirt shot of Herman&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Wilkommen!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Herman's box&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The view from atop the dome&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    After lunch we went to visit Herman the German, but unfortunately he was taken off his dome for cleaning.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan descending from the top of the dome&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    an art-deco gas station.  Actually, its late art deco because it has curves!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred and Jeff opted for more traditional German fare&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan and I ate lunch at the Kaiserhoff restaurant.  Sadly the Spaetzle were sub-par. :(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The Glockenspiel&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Can you spot the Butter from Tops?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Musst du deine Kleidungen waschen?  Denn bitte gehst du rein!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    New Ulm   urlLink    
     

    


08,August,2004



       
      Last Sunday we went to play Golf at the Walker Sculpture Garden after another rousing Twins Game.  After the game we went to Stub and Herbs for dinner while we watched the Cardinals game on TV.
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Before this picture, Jeff told me:  "You don't have respect for anything. . . get inside that sculpture so I can take your picture!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    I was just so affectionate after Golf!  Here not even a hug from me can stop Fred from taking pictures!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    I wanted to hug Jeff after the game, but he kept running away from me!  Almost like a homophobe. . . :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    This bird started some serious crap with me after the game.  It was just asking for it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    White ball go down da hole!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan putting, and Photog at work!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan is thuroughly perturbed that I continuously shoot pictures of her.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    This hole was constructed out of the old city hall bricks.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred and Jeff "shacking up" on one of the golf holes.  urlLink    
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The Walker Sculpture Garden!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The Twins congratulate eachother after a well deserved victory over the Red Sox.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
      Ok, I'm a little behind in my blogging.  These are pictures from the Twins REd Sox game last Friday, as well as pics from our trip to Downtown St. Paul on Saturday.  Both were awesome excursions, eventhough we were almost killed by a never ending pack of bike riders in front of the capitol building.  
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    I am fascinated by Fred's random neck hairs in St. Paul!  I can't remember if he decided to document my random facial hairs at the same time. . . &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Snoopy is everywhere!  I think Megan is hiding behind the green one up front.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Downtown St. Paul from Cathedral hill&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Church Altar&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    My Voyeuristic up the dome shot of the Cathedral ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Unfortunately Charlie Conway's mom wasn't there to serve us :(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The Facade of the St. Paul Cathedral.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    HA!  And you didn't believe me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Second largest free standing marble dome in the world!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Megan is so enthusasitic about our tour!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Jeff is mad at me because I made fun of his shirt.  I think he's threatening me here :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred thinks he's Rocky!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Our wonderful State Capitol building!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    St. Paul is falling apart!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    This was my "surprise" that was hyped all week.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    The Twins were getting blown out so I decided to have some fun with my camera. . . &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    AAAAAHHHHHH!!  Harmon Killebrew has grown 4 arms!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Standard candid action shot.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred is so into the game!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    This was almost as good as the Expos!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Obligatory water fowl shot&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred endorses Coke 2&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Oh no!  I've been spotted!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004



       
       urlLink    Fred at work!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    



