
21,June,2004


	 
      Our freedom can be measured by the number of things we can walk away from.  We cannot walk away from anything we falsely value, including exciting but pointless involvements.  Non-attachment is the secret, and non-attachment is a product of valuing true life above all else.  What a difference it would make if human beings loved their own lives, but instead they love their unconscious illusions, like children who hide forbidden and dangerous toys in the cellar.  The spiritual adult knows how to walk casually away from all that is not worth his attention.   --The Daily Guru
     

    


20,June,2004


	 
      okayy.  ten things i freakin' dislike and  things that irritates me  as of 929 pm, june 20..  hmmm..  10. i am in front of the pc, desperately thinking of things i could do. i should be sleeping 'cause i have classes tomorrow, but i can't sleep. so, im posting some shit in here. and, i have to go to school tomorrow. again. hi classmates.  09. i won't be able to go to davao on the 26th! darn school sched..im gonna miss my bro's wedding!putangina..  08. my dog hasn't eaten her dinner yet. bitch!  07. i wasn't able to talk to my best bud today. ben, i miss 'ya!;)  06. gays are everywhere. it's really hard to see if the guy you're talkin' with nowadays is gay, bi or, plain straight. one minute you're admiring this guy 'cause he's like your ideal man, then the next sec, he's calling you, 'sister', 'lola' and uses the expression 'charing'!buhsht!  05. i'm starting to hate somebody i really like~ SHIT! darn di!think, think, think!  04. i hate liars. but then, i'm a liar. i have a lot of liars in my friends' list. *wink* im actually good at lying. it's my talent. skill..

18,June,2004


	 
      this one is from friendster..just want to post it..Ü        When I stand up for myself and my beliefs, they  call me a bitch.        When I stand up for those I love, they call me a  bitch.        When I speak my mind, think my own thoughts or  do things my own way, they call me a bitch.        Being a bitch means I won't compromise what's in  my heart. It means I live my life MY way. It  means I won't allow anyone to step on me.        When I refuse to tolerate injustice and speak  against it, I am defined as a bitch.       The same thing happens when I take time for  myself instead of being everyone's maid.       It means I have the courage and strength to  allow myself to be who I truly am and won't  become anyone else's idea of what they think  I "should" be.  I am outspoken, opinionated and determined.  I want what I want and there is nothing wrong  with that!  So try to stomp on me, try to douse my inner  flame, try to squash every ounce of beauty I  hold within me.  You won't succeed.  And if that makes me a bitch, so be it.  I embrace the title and am proud to bear it !!!!   B = Babe  I = In  T = Total  C = Control of  H = Herself   B = Beautiful  I = Intelligent  T = Talented  C = Charming  H = Hell of a Woman   B = Beautiful  I = Individual  T = That  C = Can  H = Handle anything  
     

    


18,June,2004


	 
      WALA AKO MAGAWA KAYA I DID THIS SHIT. YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT INTERESTED IN THIS ARTICLE SO, JUST DON'T MIND THIS.. my life..what about it? i dunno..i guess i just have to write something in here, something for mr. good bastard to read. --

18,June,2004


	 
      what the hell am i doin' in here?darn, i have not a clue. anyway, im not really into posting to the world details about my life~ anything about it..but then, there's someone making me do it!!hi there mr.good bastard..is this thing like a journal of some sort?..eww!!;)anyway, aside from me creating this thing ~an account~ called blog, there's nothing much going on yet.so, maybe next time i have something more interesting to post..later..
     

    



