
15,August,2004


	 
      NOTE:  This one's been circulating on email.  I thought it would be fun to share... Go on.  Check your Zodiac Sign.    ARIES  Drinking style Impulsive Aries people like to party and sometimes don't know when to call it a night. Their competitive streak makes them prone to closing-time shot contests. They're sloppy, fun drunks, and they get mighty flirty after a couple tipples. Getting Aries people drunk is a good way to get what you want out of them, should other methods fail. Aries can become bellicose when blotto, but they will assume that whatever happened should be forgiven (if not forgotten) by sunrise. They can be counted on to do the same for you -- so long as you haven't gone and done anything really horrible to them last night, you sneaky Gemini.  Trademark cocktails Aries, born under the hot-stuff planet Mars, is the ruler of spicy food and red things ! -- and for balance, astrologers recommend they eat tomatoes, onions, olives and greens. That's right, Aries, you were born under the sign of the bloody Mary...... Aries also rules grapefruit, and they've been known to kick back a salty dog and a sea breeze or two. For extreme hotcha, try a concoction with cinnamon liqueur in it.  Drinking buddies Marlon Brando, Lawrence Ferlinghetti, Sarah Michelle Gellar, Al Gore, Thomas Jefferson, Elton John, Eric McCormack, Rosie O'Donnell, Sarah Jessica Parker, Reese Witherspoon,   Dr. Love (Marc), Crystal, Chad, Carlow, Luis.    TAURUS  Drinking style Taurus prefers to drink at a leisurely pace, aiming for a mellow glow rather than a full-on zonk. Since a truly intoxicated Taurus is a one-person stampede, the kind of bull-in-a-china-shop inebriate who spills red wine on white carpets and tells fart jokes to employers, the preference for wining and dining (or Bud and buddies) to body shots and barfing is quite fortunate for the rest of us. This is not to say that the Bull is by any means a teetotaler -- god, no. A squiffy Taurus will get, er, gregarious (full of loudmouth soup, some would say) and is extremely amusing to drag to a karaoke bar when intoxicated.  Trademark cocktails Early-to-bed Taureans need a picker-upper -- try a Red Bull and vodka. They also have a leviathan sweet tooth and are fond of drinks with names that sound like dessert (50-50 bar, mudslide). Sweetly caffeinated drinks, like Irish coffee or white Russians, are ideal. More macho Taureans  will go for something unpretentious, like a Jack and Coke or whiskey sour.  Drinking buddies Cate Blanchett, Tony Blair, Pierce Brosnan, Cher, Penelope Cruz, William Randolph Hearst, Jerry Seinfeld, Barbara Striesand, Uma Thurman, Renee Zellweger     GEMINI  Drinking style Geminis can drink without changing their behavior much -- they're so naturally chatty and short-attention-spanned that it's just hard to tell sometimes. They can amaze you by conversing with finesse and allusion, then doing something to belie an extremely advanced state of intoxication,  like puking in your shoe. Geminis possess the magic ability to flirt successfully (and uninfuriatingly, which is very tricky) with several people at once. They like to order different cocktails every round -- repetition is boring -- and may create a theme (like yell! ow drinks: beer, sauvignon blanc and limoncello) for their own amusement.  Trademark cocktails Easily bored Geminis need some stimulation in their drinks -- those with two part! s, like a b! lack and tan (or just a double), are particularly appealing. Otherwise, they'll drink all over the map, ordering frou-frou drinks to add to their collection of cocktail monkeys or going for whiskey  rocks because they're feeling rather noir. Gemini rules the herb anise -- 

15,August,2004


	 
      Fueled by the desire to break free of the almost oppressive Valentines fever (read: the need to get hooked, have a date, etc...), my predominantly single-conditionally-attached clique and I set out Saturday night (Feb 14) to dance the V-blues away and perhaps get nicely sloshed in the process.  And sloshed we were, by 11 o'clock of that wonderful evening, with a liter of Johnnie on the rocks at prime real estate at the second floor bar of Vudu at the Crossroads, Banilad.  My friends and I had earlier gone to a rock concert where we were unsurprisingly --- uhm --- overdressed despite our sincere efforts at grunge.  It was then no surprise that by the time we made our way to north of the city, and a barrel of beer later, we were quite satisfyingly "happy-gay."  This is what happens to Merriam-Webster Word of the Day subscribers.  Despite the degree of alcoholic beverage induced, we felt compelled to coin our "word of the day" however ridiculous it may sound.  Haha.  Crossroads was packed by the time I stole the right of way of a canary yellow Mini Cooper but my little highway indiscretion hardly made parking any easier.  I managed to secure a slot on the banks of the main road a bit past Tinder Box.    There we were, a "happy-gay" trio teetering on stilettoes across the asphalt parking lot.  To the men who are reading this, imagine walking barefoot on spiky gravel.  Today's shoes are notoriously slim soled.  Add to that the demands of the bump and grind dancefloor and we have shoes that not only look killer but also literally kills!   But we wear them anyway.  'Nuff of that and back to our Valentine's Eve scenario... So, we made our way across the parking lot.  And here, I daresay, the after effects of binge drinking sink in, I lose my train of thought.  Nevertheless, IT was quite an eventful night.  I'll make a beeline for my point, here's a rundown of my realizations:  1  Make sure your pre-festivities evening meal is compatible to the beverage you later plan to ingest, e.g., mayonnaise doesn't go well with alcoholic beverage.  But that's just me.  Maybe your Achilles Heel is different.  2  Don't go techie in a bar.  It is not a good idea to re-start your cell phone when you're in a virtual jungle of writhing bodies.  If you've had some to drink, you are most likely going to mis-encode your PIN number and end up getting PUKed.  And even if you call your service provider hotline for help, it is unlikely that you would hear the operator's voice above the din of pounding dance music.  3  I got this cool tip on bottle-keep from a friend:  Always ask for a sticker to mark your bottle with and a permanent marker for notches.  All this you have to do while you still have your wits about you.  Legibly write your name on the sticker and make sure you marker the contents of your precious bottle of liquid gold before you give it up to the bartender.  Did I already say you have to do this before you lose all coherent thought?  Well, I suppose I did.  This piece is finito.  I can go back to sleep now.  
    


15,August,2004


	 
         Welcome to the official web log of Crystal.  This blog documents the party scene as experienced by the author.  It's not going to be all pretty and pink so brace yourself for a raucous ride!  
    


15,August,2004


	 
       Missy Misdemeanor Episode  Feb 2004  So I allegedly did karate kicks on the deserted parking lot, talked my head off at a relatively crowded dining area, and gobbled up 5 really strong after-coffee mints right in front of the barista.  All in all, I had a hell of a lot of fun!  Who wouldn't?!  At Habib Nirvana, (that is, if my memory serves me right) I had two Super Dry's, a shot of tequila chased down with a slice of lemon (never again! I still prefer Johnnie), and a shot of the Official Friendster Drink, the Ganesha Sutra.    Some of you may be of the opinion that I made a complete fool of myself but please keep in mind that foolish is quite closely relative to happiness.  Hehe.      Drumbeats at Vudu...  Feb 2004  It was half past ten and the second floor bar was relatively packed.  There was a throng of prom-ditchers hanging out by the counter but I had "ditched" my usual prime real-estate for what's usually the DJ's booth.    As I write this piece, flashes of my sequined skyblue top flash in my mind's eye...  Much of what I remember is a blur although I can well remember the whining pain of my extremities due to excessive dancing brought on by the interminable yet inexorably enticing beat of the La Carlotta Drumbeaters.  At this junction, you may already have noticed that my choice of words thus far have been rather redundant.  And yes, i will be redundant in saying that there's nothin like a drum beat to spur you on and incite some primal drive into letting loose.  
    



