
18,June,2004


    
       
       \/\/ell, I'm out of my first year in high school.  I didn't take any hard classes as a freshman though. here's my grades from the classes I had Health-       A Photography-  B- Physical Ed.- A+ Science-      B English 9-    A- Algebra 1-    A See, they weren't that hard, and I frankly did little homework.  I still worked hard though, before I didn't do ANYTHING and I was a D student, but now I feel like I did much better.  Next years is going to be harder too, and I'll have less time because I'm joining more curricular activities. I allready know my schedule (well not the order my classes are going to be in, but I know what classes I'm taken)  Us History Biology Geometry physical Ed 11 French 1 English 10  Then I formed a sport for extra curricular activity so I have a sport for every season. At the beginning of school I'll take Cross Country when Cross Country is over then winter will be here and I'll be taking Nordic Ski-Cross Country then when that is over I'll be taking Track (like I took this year)  Well other than that my freshman year is over and in a couple of months I'll be starting school as a sophmore (yikes!!!).  My first week for the summer I jogged like 10 miles a day and visited my grandma at my dads house and did a few piano recital's. Which reminds me I should go practice piano. (I'll do that right when I'm done typing in this blog) Then my second week for this summer I wanted to help daddy, so I removed all these sticks from the backyard which took ALL DAY!  I dragged tons of heavy logs that were twice my size and you bet I developed some arm muscle from that!  Well I also developed something else from the logs.  POISON OAK (T_______T) it's pretty bad too.  It's all over my body, yes even on my chest! The worst part is it's on my chest and my right side of my face. On my right side of my face it's swollen up and red and bubbly, and oh it's horrible.  I'm too scared too go outside and do my four mile jog (since I'm at my dads house I have not much places to jog too) but since I get beeps from jogging without poison oak on my face, I don't even want to know peoples reactions when they see a girl jogging which looks like a big red bubbly faced mutant.  They probably do something worse than honking I'll tell you that. (T____T) so I'm not going out in public or jogging. I might as well just do my power work outs like-1000 crunchies, and 100 leg lifts.  That'll work (T____T) but it's not the same.     Most the time I'm either playing DDR Max 2 or DDR Max 1, working on heavy mode, to pass the time. That even annoys my grandma and aunt, so I'm usually hesitant to play it, but HEY! I can't stay on the computer all day, can I?      I should also shower, I'm all icky (as you need to know, I'm so sure).  I might as well aisle do a couple of my fanfics here, that'll work ^^! (gosh) I just realized, I wonder what Don (my piano teacher) is going to think when he sees me this all poison oaky and stuff. Today I got yelled at by my dad and aunt because I'm not eating right.  I'm only eating at lunch, but when I eat lunch I totally binge.  Like yesterday I had 2 nectarine, 2 peaches, 3 handful of grapes, 1 sandwich (with cheese/meat/mustard/jelly), 2 bowls of oats (it's actually good, I think I developed a taste for it). Yeah, I totally binge. That's like four meals in one, which leads me full for the rest of the day. I'm not really into the snacking on little meals every two hours, which my mom does because she joined this thing called 'Curves' which tells you to do that to help maintain your metabolism and yadda yadda yadda to help you lose weight. I already know what I'm going to do today I'm going to A-take a shower B-Practice Piano for a while C-Play DDR MAX and DDR MAX2  D-Do Crunchies and leg lifts E-Brush My teeth and hair *of course* F-Have Dinner (I'll just not eat anything till dinner) G-Go on the internet and do my live journal H-Go To Bed  Interesting, right?  
      


19,June,2004


    
       
       Well nothing new to say, I still got bad poison oak but the swelling went down. In fact, the only swelling happens to be part of my cheek and my ear.  Other than that it's all good.  OH! I had a heroic dream last night. It was about I'll just start at the beginning.    It was at my moms house and I guess she was hosting a party or something because a lot of people were there.  I mean, a lot!  I'll list the people. A fat lady--she was black skin and she was very nice to talk too.  She was enjoying the punch at the party.  The Phipps--all of the Phipps it seems from Dallon, john, Ammon, Laura, (oh Barbara wasn't there, probably still off in college), Aaron, Sarah, Don, Jason, (Jessica wasn't there either, perhaps she was at her house which seems miles away), Mrs. Phipps, and Mr. Phipps were there included---they were all enjoying their time too (odd everyone seems to be enjoying their time at my MOMS house).  There was also Sabrina and her parents their (mom and dad).  Jessalyn and her dad (I wonder why she's at my moms house, I actually wonder why she's even at my house).  Tabitha was there but her dad wasn't so I guess she came with Sabby same with Tiffany.  There was this banker too (which I'm guessing is my moms new boyfriend).  Plus a lot of kids ( I mean A LOT)tons of little kids, I guess this was a party for the little kids, because there was a lot, I guess a baby-sitting-party.  Weird.   Well anyway the little kids I suppose had parents too but they weren't there I guess it was a babysitting party, and well everyone was having fun talking.  The fat black skin woman was the funniest one I remember in my dream, she actually cracked out some jokes. Then we heard a loud bang and we were all outside in the backyard. I was with Dallon (a three year old) and talking with him while walking.  He was talking about a pokemon adventure or something like he always does.   Well we all heard the loud bang so I let Dallon play with a flower while I go and see what the heck it was, everyone stopped talking and in a few seconds Sabrina comes running full speed in the house screaming, "TIGERS ARE IN THE FRONT YARD" and we instantly hear a "RAWRRRRR" which made everyone scream and run in the front yard.  I ran back to get Dallon and picked him up (oof he's heavy) and ran straight indoors too.  We all looked in our front window to the front yard and saw our front yard was packed with tigers and they were chewing on the banker... (not a pretty site).  Everyone was basically screaming or the little kids were crying.   That's when I realized our screams and crying was a bit too loud, in fact it was attracting the tigers they were looking at the window and one actually pawed at it! So I realized something, and locked the door/windows/everything!!! Everyone was in a panic.  Sarah looked around too and yelled out at everyone, "You all need to be quiet, the Tigers hear us, nobody make a sound." which we all did.   Then I grabbed the phone and dialed 9-1-1 and exclaimed to them that there was tigers out front of my yard and they started laughing so I gave the phone to everyone in the room, and in the end believe me, they believed me and asked us if we could get out of the house in any safe way possible? And I went, "No-there's no safe place" then they say, "we'll be right there with help." and I'm all, "I hope to god so!" (sorry for saying Gods name in vain in front of you Laura and Mrs.  Phipps..And why am I apologizing .. I didn't apologize in the dream 


