
25,June,2004


	 
      hfdjhghdhfgsdhgs
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      ;njpkjolojk
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      lkjhp;i;
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      jhkhfkjhg
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      hgfhkfgvjgh
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      hgfhgfhgf
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      fghgfhf
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      fgdgsdyfgrs
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      ewytrytry
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      wqewqeqrwe
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsada
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      sadasdsa
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsadsad
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsadasda
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsadsadsa
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      sadsadsad
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsadsa
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsadsa
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      asdadsa
     

    



25,June,2004


	 
      hahga
    


24,June,2004


	 
      do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do 
    


24,June,2004


	 
      fdsfdsfdsfdsf
    


24,June,2004


	 
      jldgjlsfdgsdfsdfdsfdsfsd
    


24,June,2004


	 
      sdfsaffyhdg
    


24,June,2004


	 
      fvasvfavdsfa
    


24,June,2004


	 
      vfsafvavfdsavfdsa
    


24,June,2004


	 
      gafvsdvtdaetvgdsdf
    


24,June,2004


	 
       fvghjf
    


24,June,2004


	 
      lkokh;
    


24,June,2004


	 
      lkjlkjhlkjhjkl
    


24,June,2004


	 
      jhgfj
    


24,June,2004


	 
      fdhgkljh
    


24,June,2004


	 
      gfdsgjfg
    


24,June,2004


	 
      dsgfsdgfd
    


24,June,2004


	 
      dsadsad
    


24,June,2004


	 
      dasfdaffvafvdasfvsafvdsa
    


24,June,2004


	 
      My first day off, I jsut went to the bank, then Raghi's. I bought some Coke and Redbull. I will update later if I have something to actually do.
    


24,June,2004


	 
      Call me if you got some summer plans bitches.
    


23,June,2004


	 
      LAST DAY OF SCHOOL BIATCHES!!! w00t. I dont have to be bothered, no more stressing out.. its coffee and Counter Strike from here on in. This rocks, because now Im really focused on making some cash.Will post later, need to see some stuff. BUH BYE
    


23,June,2004


	 
      OH and PS. Watch site construction at http://www.g0dd.b3gze3.com
    


23,June,2004


	 
      Todays my last day at school. Gonna cause some troubles. I feel good today, I drank some more coffee and will shoot peptobysmol in one second. Coffee really starts all my mornings, but it leaves the ass-tasting aftertaste in your mouth. I get out 12:30, so thats about a....4 or so hours of staying in one class and skipping all my other ones. My stomach hurts now.. damn coffee. Well, today, even after school is going to be a busy day, lot of website stuff to do because all the people are wating for the 1337 site. :D
    


23,June,2004


	 
      Its time for me to sleep. Well not yet, but soon. I'm getting off the PC right now. I was trying to fix my PHP include, but its a crap... Let my nigga Zach fix it for me :D So 'nite.
    


23,June,2004


	 
      Im back from school and am waiting for the last day of school. Report Card day.. 

23,June,2004


	 
      Im posting before school :D Drank up on lots of Starbucks, shot some Peptobysmol down, and I think I'm ready. Don't wanna really go to school, but theres 2 more days left, and there half days, so I guess I will live.. :[ Somebody stole my math book, I might have to pay a whopping $60. Yeah, right..... Ok, Off so school. BUH BYE.
    



25,June,2004


	 
      i own you suckaay suckaaay sucak,fkmsdmk gmaifcill fadsjfjds :Ls i erox0r bit-tech niggasadgds :D dsa sd D:Dw 00t
    


25,June,2004


	 
      vgsdfgwsgdf
    


25,June,2004


	 
      234tgretgfgvcx
    


25,June,2004


	 
      r32423444324
    


25,June,2004


	 
      bnvcnjv,jcxnvxcnvxcv
    


25,June,2004


	 
      xzbvxbj,n
    


25,June,2004


	 
       fdsfdsfs
    


25,June,2004


	 
      drip drpi
    


25,June,2004


	 
      cxzcxzxz
    


25,June,2004


	 
      vcxvcxzvc
    


25,June,2004


	 
      vcxvdsferww542
    


25,June,2004


	 
      fdsfdsfdsfgrtr
    


25,June,2004


	 
      fds,mfnvscvxc
    


25,June,2004


	 
      fdvcvcxcxzv
    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsafedfsf
    


25,June,2004


	 
      dsaafdsafdaf
    


25,June,2004


	 
      wassssaa
    


25,June,2004


	 
      cxzcxzcxz
    


25,June,2004


	 
      !& traacks
    



