
25,June,1999


	 
        1ST time use blogger? No lar juz feel lyke changing cause my cousin access it and change everything anyway I haf already decided to change it so happy get to change  as I lyke dis name better.kzzz todAE IST time type u noe so...  
     

    


08,August,1999


	 
      vari long never use le about 3 months...hey yo email me at nicholas_cjh@hotmail.com.....1st time leah publishing mi acc on line so wats up yo ppl plus still mi bdae leh so hapi 
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
          T     HERE       I     S       A            S     UCKER       B     ORN       E     VERY       M     IN     

    


25,June,2004


	 
          N     EVER       S     AY       D     IE             
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
          N     Naive       I     Industrious       C     Cute       H     Hardworking       O     Overwhelming       L     Lively       A     Adventurous       S     Skillful       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    


14,July,2004


	 
      hizzz so sian todae got com class i dunno tat com class com clubber dun need to go so i waste 2 hour on it doing 1 poster and in the end it landed in the recycle bin. so wat....nvm dis is not the problem leh...y? cause derrick tml bdae ...so so sian must go and see wat he want in the end i buy 1 thing that cost around $70 dunno he like a not leh nvm....
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
           What piece of ART are you? by gentlewound      Name           Age           I like this book...      "Romeo and Juliet" By WS "The Divinci Code" By DB "Lord of the Rings" By JRT "On The Road" By JK "Sense and Sensability" By JA "The Dark Tower" By SK "Mostly Harmless" By DA "Dracula" By BS "The Tell Tale Heart" By EAP "Left Behind" By TL & JJ "Heart of a Woman" By MA "Harry Potter(SERIES)" By JR "Lord and Ladies" By TP       I like this music...      Celtic Rock Classic Rock Punk New Wave Pop Heavy Metal Dance Trance Christian Classical R & B Jazz Speed Metal Alternative Grunge Rock Country Folk Spoken Word Disco       I like this color...      Blue Red Green Purple Orange White Black Lilac Puce Off White Yellow Brown Gold Silver Bronze Eggplant Burgandy PASTEL COLORS BRIGHT COLORS PRIMARY COLORS       You are this ARTIST    Matisse      You are this piece of ART    "Liberation 1955" By Escher      You are...    Clandestine             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
          var chatterbox = 'no';         urlLink target="flooblechatterbox"  onClick="window.open('about:blank','flooblechatterbox','toolbar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=no,menubar=no,scrollbars=yes,resizable=no,copyhistory=no,width=480,height=400');return true;"

01,July,2004


	 
                  nicholas Highway    bank    9      Loony-Bin Lane    24      hospital    65      police post    104      hospital    382      Please Drive Carefully               Username:      urlLink Where are you on the highway of life?   From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com 


01,July,2004


	 
          Information  i   	   nicholas's blog is a restricted area. Authorised personel only     Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
      
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
       /moodImg.asp?mID=27450"


04,August,2004


	 
      
    



