
28,June,2004


    
       
      -*if u couldnt find happiness n ur own backayrd u never riLly knew what it was*-  --

17,July,2004


    
       
       no more eNtRiEs guys..2 much 2 talk about!! much   
      


11,July,2004


    
       
      hEy YaLl!! 2day i got 2 jcc n had a perdy good time!! we saw codys butt yeahya!! 1st i hung w/ the skaters n they made a video n then i went w/ melissa kelly n lauren! we threw coins @ ppl!! haha 2day wuz prolly the best day. 2night ima go 2 the movies w/ melissa n cody!! whoop whoop..then wen i was leaving austin came over n we made up yay n then adam came over n george n we jus hung till i had 2 leave.. austin wuz like no u cant go..she isnt here shes invisible u cant c her!! lol..toodles!! RACHAEL IS BACK!!
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      hey yall..im very..tired! i was outside all friggin day watching ppl skateboard n fall off. then i went sumwhere else wen connor came round. gosh i hate that girl. austin n all them were completely ignoring me 2 go hang w/ connor n lauren [but shes coo] . so that pissed me off n austin comes over n says..oh whats wrong nikki..wtf he nos whats wrong he jus chooses not 2 egnolege it!! URGH! some1 needs 2 call meeee!!! ok i ono what im doing 2maro n its so hot outside i think ima go take a nap. toodles
      


09,July,2004


    
       
      OMG 2NIGHT I SAW COLIN PRICE!! I HAVENT SEEN THAT KID SINCE JANUARY..I THINK HES GUNNA KILL ME..HE HAS GLASSES N LONG HAIR. I THINK HE LOOKS KINDA CUTE W/ HIS PUNKY STUFF ON. BUT THE FUNNY THING IS WEN I WALKED NTO THE RESTURAUNT I GO MAN THAT LOOKS LIKE A GUY WHO WOOD B FRIENDS W/ GREG N HE WUZ FRIENDS W/ GREG. I THINK HE NEW WHO I WAS 2. GG BYE! 
      


08,July,2004


    
       
      today wuz a blast cuz the hole *posse* wuznt thurr. las night i talked 2 austin on the fone 4 like 2 hrs bout who signed our yrbooks n how his cds got jacked. 2day austin wuz the onli wun thurr till sammy.grace.george.jacob. n brecklyn came. alex wuz thurr 2. its raining outside. 2day me n austin spent a lot of time 2gether...i wuz watchin him skateboard n he wuz skateboarding while adam wuz doin trix on his bike [tryin 2 sho off] then we looked @ ringtones n there were these guys that called em posers!! urgh, they didnt even no how 2 skate!! then..i went swimmin w/ meredith @ the club...we onli got 30 mins of swimmin cuz the LIFEGUARDS SUCK! so it wuz a pritty nterestin day. now im talkin 2 alex m. n drew left 4 michigan 2day..whoo hoo!  linkamm1: me 3 pinkNblack316: me 4! linkamm1: its like sesime street all over again!!!!!!! pinkNblack316: ok...? linkamm1: or however u spell it linkamm1: u know...1 2 3 linkamm1: never mind linkamm1: with the pupet people linkamm1: and the big yellow bird linkamm1: and the blue guy who eats cookies   lol convo w/ me n alex. we r goin 2 verizon 2night so thats why i cant go 2 alex's [not that above alex] sleepover. then im gunna b home alone 2night. guess who i saw @ the pool 2day..JOE! urgh!! the one day i thought i woodnt have 2 c him!! ok well toodles.
      


08,July,2004


    
       
      ok im sittin n the jcc cyber lab. the past 2 days have been soooo-

06,July,2004


    
       
      2day wuz sumwhat a depressing day...it all started out by me waking up 2 the sound of my cuzin crying n my g-maz kitchen 4 sum reason but it wuz lowd!! it wuz storming like CrAzY here!! HOLY CRAP! it wuz sooo hot outside!! i wrote a note 2 laura w/ cussing n it @ my g-mas n a drawer n i REALLY hope she doesnt find it..i dont wanna b n truble agin! 2day i went 2 dooleys 4 lunch n then the jcc. all the holy spirit ppl were there n so wuz my crew [george, brecklyn, austin, grace, n sum otha ppl that i 4get cuz im so dumb. bReCkY pOo who is starting 2 feel good bout herself, got told she wuz FAT by cody. but lissenin 2 cody is like lissenin 2 george..it jus comes out as blllaaahhhh. cody had the nerve 2 break up w/ caty 2 go out w/ connor..wtf! by the way: drew actually called back! thanks hun! i love lauren n kelly, they r funny n cool n rock my sox wayyy off! there is sum mad shit goin down btwn melissa/brecklyn n connor. no offense 2 the holy spirit ppl but we have been @ the jcc since we were lil n its our terf so u cant jus come n n try 2 take over n b friends w/ everyone..no it aint gun work hunny! then we all went outside n skated n im glad austin doesnt like connor most of the time! hes a cutie! oh yeah the one thing that wuz fun wuz goin nto the comp lab n sittin by lauren n seein that hot pic of the guy! good times n then goin swimmin. i jus wish 1) deena wood come home n 2) everyone wood git along. i gotta find my swimsuit soo toodles!
      


05,July,2004


    
       
      aYy! aHhHh! my toof hurts!! I LEARNED THAT ALBERT N DREW PLAY THE ELECTRIC GUITAR!! haha soo cool! yall rock my sox! I ACTUALLY GOT 2 TALK 2 DREW!! AHH I MISSED HIM!! we were tlkin bout the diff. btwn gurls n boys n we cood make a book!! holy crap theres like sooo many people online...i cant take it no more!!  i had a serious/not serious talk w/ sam t. hes coo! n he might come 2 jcc sometime diz summer w/ greg n quinton!! 2day i went 2 jcc n hung w/ brecklyn, george, austin, grace, n melissa! whoo hoo! we went 2 mc donalds n went swimmin. n then it started stormin like HELL! [as drew wood say] now im tlkin 2 sunny n chris n emily. ahhh...my family wuz fightin @ the dinner table 2day..haha it wuz HILARIOUS!! oOoOok ne ways...im tired so ima go 2 bed soon. i <3 chris n drew they r 2 coo boos! xoxo
      
>

03,July,2004


    
       
      Ever Been Called-  Dumb?: duh Retarted?: yea by my dadday Ugly?: yes Hot?: yep Fat?: yea, by myself Anorexic?: no A waste of space?: no  Useless?: no Smelly?: no A Slut?: no Beautiful?: yeah  Smart?: yea  Quiet?: no Boring?: no  A Bitch?: yes Rebel?: sometimes Conceited?: nope  Currently-  What are you wearing?: louisville shirt, black soffes Who are you talking to?: adam..cuz theres no one on n im gunna die! How is the weather?: warm// cloudy What are you listening to?: my comp making noise What/Who are you thinking about?: i have no idea What are you eating/drinking?: nothing What are you looking forward to?: 4th of jUlY What are you dreading?:going bak 2 skool...urgh How are you feeling?: pritty good 4 a change How is your hair?: uMm..why dont u ask my hair nstead of me? What time is it?: 201 pm What are you annoyed by?: waking up early n the summer Emotions-  What emotion do you feel the most?: HAPPY! What emotion is the best?: EXCITED! Worst?: uMm..sADness! What songs make you cry?: i hve no idea What movies make you cry?: SAD ONES! What always cheers you up?: chocolate n talking 2 a friend What makes you madder than anything?: wen people boss me around n tell me im wrong What hurts you the most?: when people r fake..hey if u dont like me or u gotta prob. tell me Depressed?: not @ the moment no What do you do when you're depressed?: write poetry, swim, go to Kels What song do you think was written about your life?: too many When Was The Last Time You-  Burped?: 2day @ lunch Went to the movies?: w/ camp  Went out to eat?: 4 lunch Cried?: sometime earlier than summer? Got dumped?: nevr..n happy 4 it! Dumped someone?: nevr! Threw up?: last summer wen i was sick Peed?: uMm a cuple a minutes ago, why? Went skating?: @ the end of the yr, but i didnt skate Went for a walk?: 2day Ate ice cream?: las night Got into a fight?: umM yesterday Issues-  Do you do drugs?: mabay .. i mean no Do you have a mental disablity?: no  Are you on any medication for any type of disorder? wtf kinda questions r these? What kind?:  Do you or have you ever had an eating disorder?: nope What kinds of illnesses run in your family?: ask them! Who was the last person you-  Talked to?: my g-ma  Yelled at?: deena i ono why tho  Kissed: memory block Hugged?: mema Went out to eat with?: mema Flirted with?: chris   Talked to on the phone?: grandma IMed?: adam//debbie E-Mail?: dont remember, 2 many Got flowers from?: oh jeez..uhhh mom Danced with?: prolly... my friends Fought with?: everyone [brother]  Worried about?: no one rilly Cried over?: nothing Thought about?: some1 getting on the fckin internet my gosh!! theres no one 2 talk 2!!  Are you-  Understanding?: in what way? Pretty?: yes Nice?: not rilly, wen im n a good mood A bitch?: a lot..lets not go there Hard to get?: i ono Confident?: yes Depressed?: nope Hyper?: YEA! Friendly?: yea Hungry?: no Original?: i ono Shy?: no Emotional?: no Messy?: yes Immature?: n what way? Sad?: can be  Trusting?: yes Healthy?: yea Sleepy?: yes Lonely?: no Independent?: yea Romantic?: i can be  Do you drink [alcohol]?: r u a cop? Do you party a lot?: often-

02,July,2004


    
       
      hey yall!!!!!!! ok haha...here we go!  on june 30th i met zoe @ the jcc @ like 10:30 n we hung out there n went swimming 4 a while n then sophie came n we walked up 2 dooleys 2 git something 2 eat. some guy honked @ us! otherwise...wen my mom came 2 pick us up we were talking 2 drew on the fono n drawing on the stairs w/ permanent markers..zoe is gunna send drew a pack of pokemon cards that she finds n cat's couch n deoderent!! lol! he asked if he stank n i told him i dont think so..lol. wen we got home we dicided 2 make a voodoo doll of zoe! but we lost her hair n the doll..so we went on the net n didnt find a chant [damn] so zoes gunna order a kit. LOL! 4 30 bux! we were lissenin 2 the 1st now cd n jazz music n we started 2 swing dance!! haha!! WEN I WENT DOWN 2 GET A PERMENT MARKER FRM THE BASEMENT I HEARD A ROAR! N THERE WAS A SQUIRELL N JAREDS WALL!! so emily is n my brothers bed-room wall n theres a lion down my basement named elpantalon! then i sed that if we called baskin robbins n named all 31 flavors we cood have ice cream!! but we only got like 15 lol.. then we woke up @ like 10 on july 1st n we had a beenie babay fight n zoe had a inflatable chair around her waist!! tata is zoes best friend!! lOl!! yesterday i went over katizzles house 2 watch movies n eat dinner n c alex b4 he leaves..im gunna miss that fuzzy walrus! xoxo. so i got scared of the movie n i told alex he had big feet n i hid behind him. lol..brad pitt is hot!! then me n ashizzle went upsturrz n talked 2 people n it wuz sooooo funny!!!!!! heres my profile frm kts house-


