
29,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Although there isn't any best cadet from my secondary school  during the NCC Spec Course phase 2. I was kind of pleased to know 8 out of 17 got 2sgt, this was the batch that i saw, trained and guided  since they were in Sec 1.Haha...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


29,June,2004


	 
      Hey and hi to you...yes you or the groups out there reading this website, i am wei ren and nice to meet you, i'm suppose that you might be curious or something about me well ya i have lots of exciting things but so far i thought that i have nothing to write for this column and i'm sure that you will get yo know me more in times to come. All The Best And God Bless You!  
     
    


22,July,2004


	 
      I am so sorry for not updating for those who like to know me more. I was kind of busy with my studies nowadays. I did not do well for mid year i got 2 A Level pass and 2 AO pass, i was able to meet the criteria but i was beinf forced to drop my fmaths, lucky i was given a chance to prove my teachers wrong. It seems that Jc lifes is too stressful. Much worse with the sickening PW work that i cannot imagine that i have to spent 50% of my time jus for the sack of a mere 10% of Alevel results.  Couldn't be botherd with it. ALL I WANT NOW IS TO WORK HARD FOR S PAPERS.......i am hoping for a SAF SMS scholarship if i do well.   Took part in the national swimming championship, my timing deproved got last for my 200m breasts heats and an average results for my 100m breast.Took a lot time then to mug and do&nbsp;my work and I PRAY EVEN HARDER TO HOPE FOR EVEN MORE LORD'S BLESSING.  I couldn't go down for my sch NCC training as they have switched it to Friday when i am still having sch lesson. It's pathetic and i am not sure about how they are doing but i am hoping for a good results back.  Knew that Hafiz and farhan were posted to bv i was so happy it's seems that it's better.  HEY NEED 2 STUDY PHYSICS NOW MUG MUG MUG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    hey got it out of nowhere in my cupboard got to see the first time i ever try out to teach during my 2002 specialists course, brings back lots of memories. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


04,July,2004


	 
      AND YES...TANJONG KATONG IS THE WINNER FOR THIS YEAR BAND OF THE YEAR!!! i am so happy for them   and yes SYFOC was rather chaotic as you can see all those schools were rather incooperative...came late. Shen An and I went to escort as many school as we can adn all i can say is that we were so tired after the whole event. Got to know some 47th intake clts and yes they were kind of a little dao at times but overall still can lor.  After the whole event we went to eat at geylang.Hmm they said that the food there was quite nice true...but kind of oily for me when i took a bowl of prawn hor fan soup then went to another stall to eat youtiao, i l'm luving it o man it's so crispy but anyway yes i am going to be busy this week and erm ya so haiz another week has gone.
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    EXAMS OVER...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
      At last u can see from my face how constipated i am when i was having a hell week of examinations. I just took my examination and all i can say is a hell... 1st dae C MATHS...did not really know how to do, did not do 4 question but still can pass. 2nd dae Chemistry...SCREW UPPPPP...the paper was king of horrible i did not do 15 marks worth if questions, looks like not an A for me 3rd dae Physics and Chinese ok tis 2 papers are the only paper that i tink i can excel on hee 4th dae FMATHS er....i hope i can get at least an A LEVEL pass......  o and to day i jus got my chinese oral and is kind of funny cas they ask question always social 1 u noe.. all u need 2 do is jus state the reasons feelings and how u tink?haizz another dae has gone and 2morrow is SYFOC....so i am going to sleep now!!!!!!
     
    


12,August,2004


    
       SORRY GUYS WELL YA I AM BUSY JUS GOT ONTO MY COMP AND WROTE SOME THINGS..... i have been busy with saf open house dance rehearsal and was kind of tiring u noe.....  I did not have time to finish all my homework and was so horrible when my gp tutor said"GET OUT OF MY SIGHT"!!!!!!!!! when i was like requesting to hand up mw work on Friday and he said i was like giving so much of excuses.....furthermore my harddisk was like kind of sick or something i'm using my dad comp now!!!!!!!!!  Guess wat me and my other fren are working hard for the performance for the saf open house we r dancing and basically we will be doing s

04,August,2004


    
       SORRY GUYS WELL YA I AM BUSY JUS GOT ONTO MY COMP AND WROTE SOME THINGS..... i have been busy with saf open house dance rehearsal and was kind of tiring u noe.....  I did not have time to finish all my homework and was so horrible when my gp tutor said"GET OUT OF MY SIGHT"!!!!!!!!! when i was like requesting to hand up mw work on Friday and he said i was like giving so much of excuses.....furthermore my harddisk was like kind of sick or something i'm using my dad comp now!!!!!!!!!  Guess wat me and my other fren are working hard for the performance for the saf open house we r dancing and basically we will be doing some stunts and pds and i am quite excited over it  I got back my test and guess what i got 12/16 for my f maths and 25.5/40 for my chem......i think i did ok but i knew i can do better god will bless me always!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  
    
    


04,August,2004


    
        urlLink    A recent photo while i was studying, test and exams suxxxxxxxxxxx may be i need 2 smile more often.......&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    


04,August,2004


    
        urlLink    Hey so how u think twins right......NOOOOO....he's a friend i noe who looks quite like me in ncc....HEY HEY guys pls look carefully nxt time before calling us our name.......&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    



