
30,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    My two very handsome boys&nbsp; urlLink   
    


30,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The three of us...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


30,June,2004


	 
      Beautiful 9 lbs baby boy! Born to Gracie & Matt on May 20th, 2004
    


30,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    My baby &nbsp; urlLink   
    


30,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Baby Matthew&nbsp; urlLink   
    


24,July,2004


	 
      Aaah...  urlLink   
    


18,July,2004


	 
      Such a cutie  urlLink   
    


18,July,2004


	 
      9 weeks  urlLink   
    


18,July,2004


	 
      Tired...  urlLink   
    


16,July,2004


	 
      Close up  urlLink   
    


16,July,2004


	 
      Beginnings of a crawl  urlLink   
    


16,July,2004


	 
      Wonder  urlLink   
    


12,July,2004


	 
      At Rest  urlLink    
    


12,July,2004


	 
      He is HUGE  urlLink   
    


12,July,2004


	 
       2 months.   14lbs and 23 1/2 inches long.  Two month vaccines were absolutely heartbreaking. Have you ever seen a human being feel pain for the first time? Well, that's what it's like. Four vaccines, two in each thigh and you can hear the pain in his cry. It's like nothing you could ever imagine, to watch your child&nbsp;feel pain for the first time and you can't do anything about it.&nbsp; I know there's more to come...tripping while on a run, scrapped knees, falling off bikes, etc. I doubt I'll ever get use to it.  &nbsp; 
    


12,July,2004


	 
      Finally, he decided to sit back and relax...Spa time for little Matt.   urlLink   
    


11,July,2004


	 
      Huh?   urlLink   
    


11,July,2004


	 
      Here we are again, decicing if he should like it or not.  urlLink   
    


11,July,2004


	 
      Our most significant event of the day would have to be THE BATH. He doesn't know weather to love or hate it...I would say he is still deciding.   urlLink   
    


11,July,2004


	 
      7 weeks It's incredible. I can't imagine how I ever existed without him... He is the most excellent state of perfection   urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
      Bad hair day but still feeling good   urlLink   
    


08,July,2004


	 
      Looks just like his Dad   urlLink   
    


08,July,2004


	 
      Two roads diverged in a yellow wood, And sorry I could not travel both And be one traveler, long I stood And looked down one as far as I could To where it bent in the undergrowth; Then took the other, as just as fair, And having perhaps the better claim, Because it was grassy and wanted wear; Though as for that the passing there Had worn them really about the same, And both that morning equally lay In leaves no step had trodden black. Oh, I kept the first for another day! Yet knowing how way leads on to way, I doubted if I should ever come back. I shall be telling this with a sigh Somewhere ages and ages hence: Two roads diverged in a wood, and I- I took the one less traveled by, And that has made all the difference.  Robert Frost   urlLink   
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    en route to Carmel...stopped near Big Sur...absolutely beautiful
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    kitchen
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    view of family room from master
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    family room entrance
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    dinning & kitchen entrance
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    living room entrance
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    side yard
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    partial backyard
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    partial backyard patio
    


04,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    My little Matti&nbsp; urlLink   
    



