
25,July,2004


	 
      Something is funny about how things are going for me recently.&nbsp; I haven’t been able to open my eyes to many things.&nbsp; I preferred to stay oblivious to the happenings of my life.&nbsp; The majority of these things deal with Kelly.&nbsp; I still haven’t acted as I should have when it comes to her.&nbsp; Reasons for this vary, but the prevailing one is that I just was blinded by love.&nbsp; Love that deep can be misleading at times. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I told Kelly on many occasions that I just wanted to be there for her.&nbsp; Her response to me was that she told me, on these occasions, that she would call me when she needed to talk to me.&nbsp; So I tried to do that for her.&nbsp; I gave her the space she wanted, and allowed myself to play second-fiddle to her life.&nbsp; But when I needed her most, she was not there for me.&nbsp; This last full semester, I felt overwhelmed with pressure from school, work, parents, death of a friend, Kelly, etc…&nbsp; I was full of questions, doubt and fear about what direction my life would go; if I would be successful or not, if I could make it through these tough times and emerge stronger than I was previous to this. My life had become a whirlwind.&nbsp; Those two weeks before she left me, I was really struggling.&nbsp; That was when I was reaching the breaking point.&nbsp; Kelly decided that would be the opportune time to drop the bomb on me.&nbsp; I crashed hard.&nbsp; I hit a very low point.&nbsp; I didn’t even get to enjoy my own college graduation.&nbsp; But I couldn’t turn to my best friend.&nbsp; She wanted nothing to do with me and treated me like a piece of shit.&nbsp; This took me to a place beyond a low.&nbsp; I became someone else.&nbsp; I couldn’t handle it.&nbsp; It was just too much in too little of time.&nbsp; And she wasn’t there for me.&nbsp; She would rather party, drink, smoke, and sleep with other people than be there for someone she shared three years of her life with, shared her hopes and dreams with, someone who supported her every decision, up-lifted her on any occasion, stood by her and held her hand when she needed it, trusted her to be loyal, and someone who loved her unconditionally.&nbsp; How selfish was that?&nbsp; It still hurts to this day.&nbsp; In her weakest moments, she seemed to show some remorse.&nbsp; But I think that was just a blip in time because after I comforted her and told her how good of a person she was, how desirable she was to me, how much I loved her, and how beautiful she is, she stopped calling me and continued back down the road she was on before she stumbled.&nbsp; I was used. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; When she started to contact me again, she sounded like she wanted to reignite things again.&nbsp; But I was wrong. &nbsp;Who knows what is going through her mind?&nbsp; I can’t read her anymore.&nbsp; I don’t know when she is telling me the truth, or just trying to spare my feelings anymore.&nbsp; But I did realize one thing (I believe); the reason why she called me was that she only wanted to use me at her own convenience for her own pleasure and self-confidence and not because she actually wanted to be around me.&nbsp; She merely didn’t want to feel alone.&nbsp; She wants to feel desirable; like she has something available to her at any time she wants.&nbsp; It’s a sense of security she needs on a short-term basis and I am something familiar that will solve that temporary problem for her.&nbsp; If she needed someone, why didn’t she turn to those people she likes to think are her friends or the guy she ran to when she was done with me?&nbsp; She has admitted to me that she has made a practice of keeping me around (i.e. keeping me from dating) so she has the option of returning to something safe if all else fails.&nbsp; How do you think that makes me feel?&nbsp; I feel like I am worth no more than the toilet paper sitting in my bathroom.&nbsp; She has the impression that I am going to be waiting here at her beck-and-call.&nbsp; But I can’t be used as her safety net any longer.&nbsp; She will just continue to take advantage of my kindness and generosity.&nbsp; I truly love her and care for me more than any other person out there, but that does not give her the right to abuse my feelings like she has.&nbsp; I have a ton of love to give, but I need to feel loved also.&nbsp; No man is an island and I desperately want to be happy.&nbsp; I want to share my life with someone who is willing to rejoice in my successes, cry in my failures, support me when I need it, stand by my side, love me like I love her, and trust me to do the right thing for the benefit of us both.&nbsp; What more could a person want? &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Some things just don’t hit you until days after the fact.&nbsp; To notice some trends, they need to happen for a few days before you can start to see the pattern.&nbsp; I don’t think she realizes that she hasn’t called me since she decided not to sleep with me anymore.&nbsp; The only times we talked and hung out was because I initiated contact.&nbsp; Is that the only reason why she called me in the first place?&nbsp; I have yet to receive one phone call from her and she hasn’t even asked to see me since this all went down.&nbsp; I am now going to put this to a test.&nbsp; I am going to not call her and see how long it takes until she folds and gives me a call.&nbsp; I am really curious to see if she will even call me at all.&nbsp; I’m sure she will eventually, but who knows how long that will take.&nbsp; It most likely will happen when she either feels like I am walking away or when she gets lonely again.&nbsp; The ironic part is that I will probably be dating someone else when that happens.&nbsp; That’s the way things unfolded last time.&nbsp; She mentions that possibility so much that I wonder if she really wants that for me so she doesn’t have any remorse about treating me the way she has.&nbsp; In fact, sometimes I think she really despises speaking with me, but hangs out with me to merely humor me.&nbsp; Why do I need thoughts like this?&nbsp; All it does is make me question my self-worth.&nbsp; I don’t like thinking that I am that worthless.&nbsp; I know it is not true.&nbsp; I am a diamond in the rough.&nbsp; But still my confidence suffers because of her. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This entire situation reminds me of something I have watched a good friend of mine do many times before.&nbsp; What has been done to me is precisely what Brandon does to many of the girls he comes across.&nbsp; The ma

22,July,2004


	 
      Something is funny about how things are going for me recently.&nbsp; I haven’t been able to open my eyes to many things.&nbsp; I preferred to stay oblivious to the happenings of my life.&nbsp; The majority of these things deal with Kelly.&nbsp; I still haven’t acted as I should have when it comes to her.&nbsp; Reasons for this vary, but the prevailing one is that I just was blinded by love.&nbsp; Love that deep can be misleading at times. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I told Kelly on many occasions that I just wanted to be there for her.&nbsp; Her response to me was that she told me, on these occasions, that she would call me when she needed to talk to me.&nbsp; So I tried to do that for her.&nbsp; I gave her the space she wanted, and allowed myself to play second-fiddle to her life.&nbsp; But when I needed her most, she was not there for me.&nbsp; This last full semester, I felt overwhelmed with pressure from school, work, parents, death of a friend, Kelly, etc…&nbsp; I was full of questions, doubt and fear about what direction my life would go; if I would be successful or not, if I could make it through these tough times and emerge stronger than I was previous to this. My life had become a whirlwind.&nbsp; Those two weeks before she left me, I was really struggling.&nbsp; That was when I was reaching the breaking point.&nbsp; Kelly decided that would be the opportune time to drop the bomb on me.&nbsp; I crashed hard.&nbsp; I hit a very low point.&nbsp; I didn’t even get to enjoy my own college graduation.&nbsp; But I couldn’t turn to my best friend.&nbsp; She wanted nothing to do with me and treated me like a piece of shit.&nbsp; This took me to a place beyond a low.&nbsp; I became someone else.&nbsp; I couldn’t handle it.&nbsp; It was just too much in too little of time.&nbsp; And she wasn’t there for me.&nbsp; She would rather party, drink, smoke, and sleep with other people than be there for someone she shared three years of her life with, shared her hopes and dreams with, someone who supported her every decision, up-lifted her on any occasion, stood by her and held her hand when she needed it, trusted her to be loyal, and someone who loved her unconditionally.&nbsp; How selfish was that?&nbsp; It still hurts to this day.&nbsp; In her weakest moments, she seemed to show some remorse.&nbsp; But I think that was just a blip in time because after I comforted her and told her how good of a person she was, how desirable she was to me, how much I loved her, and how beautiful she is, she stopped calling me and continued back down the road she was on before she stumbled.&nbsp; I was used. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; When she started to contact me again, she sounded like she wanted to reignite things again.&nbsp; But I was wrong. &nbsp;Who knows what is going through her mind?&nbsp; I can’t read her anymore.&nbsp; I don’t know when she is telling me the truth, or just trying to spare my feelings anymore.&nbsp; But I did realize one thing (I believe); the reason why she called me was that she only wanted to use me at her own convenience for her own pleasure and self-confidence and not because she actually wanted to be around me.&nbsp; She merely didn’t want to feel alone.&nbsp; She wants to feel desirable; like she has something available to her at any time she wants.&nbsp; It’s a sense of security she needs on a short-term basis and I am something familiar that will solve that temporary problem for her.&nbsp; If she needed someone, why didn’t she turn to those people she likes to think are her friends or the guy she ran to when she was done with me?&nbsp; She has admitted to me that she has made a practice of keeping me around (i.e. keeping me from dating) so she has the option of returning to something safe if all else fails.&nbsp; How do you think that makes me feel?&nbsp; I feel like I am worth no more than the toilet paper sitting in my bathroom.&nbsp; She has the impression that I am going to be waiting here at her beck-and-call.&nbsp; But I can’t be used as her safety net any longer.&nbsp; She will just continue to take advantage of my kindness and generosity.&nbsp; I truly love her and care for me more than any other person out there, but that does not give her the right to abuse my feelings like she has.&nbsp; I have a ton of love to give, but I need to feel loved also.&nbsp; No man is an island and I desperately want to be happy.&nbsp; I want to share my life with someone who is willing to rejoice in my successes, cry in my failures, support me when I need it, stand by my side, love me like I love her, and trust me to do the right thing for the benefit of us both.&nbsp; What more could a person want? &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Some things just don’t hit you until days after the fact.&nbsp; To notice some trends, they need to happen for a few days before you can start to see the pattern.&nbsp; I don’t think she realizes that she hasn’t called me since she decided not to sleep with me anymore.&nbsp; The only times we talked and hung out was because I initiated contact.&nbsp; Is that the only reason why she called me in the first place?&nbsp; I have yet to receive one phone call from her and she hasn’t even asked to see me since this all went down.&nbsp; I am now going to put this to a test.&nbsp; I am going to not call her and see how long it takes until she folds and gives me a call.&nbsp; I am really curious to see if she will even call me at all.&nbsp; I’m sure she will eventually, but who knows how long that will take.&nbsp; It most likely will happen when she either feels like I am walking away or when she gets lonely again.&nbsp; The ironic part is that I will probably be dating someone else when that happens.&nbsp; That’s the way things unfolded last time.&nbsp; She mentions that possibility so much that I wonder if she really wants that for me so she doesn’t have any remorse about treating me the way she has.&nbsp; In fact, sometimes I think she really despises speaking with me, but hangs out with me to merely humor me.&nbsp; Why do I need thoughts like this?&nbsp; All it does is make me question my self-worth.&nbsp; I don’t like thinking that I am that worthless.&nbsp; I know it is not true.&nbsp; I am a diamond in the rough.&nbsp; But still my confidence suffers because of her. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This entire situation reminds me of something I have watched a good friend of mine do many times before.&nbsp; What has been done to me is precisely what Brandon does to many of the girls he comes across.&nbsp; The manner in which he treats them, speaks to them and uses them is identical to what Kelly has done to me.&nbsp; He uses them to his benefit without any regard to their feelings.&nbsp; Kelly has done the same to me and I am fed up with it.&nbsp; I can’t do this to myself anymore.&nbsp; She hurt me.&nbsp; And I can’t easily forget how willing she was to be completely selfish on a whim.&nbsp; If she can do this now, she will be capable of it in the future.&nbsp; I really have doubts that a serious relationship can be re-fabricated between the two of us in the near future.&nbsp; Once a piece of paper has been crumpled up, it does not ever take on its original flat, smooth form again.&nbsp; It becomes tainted and is no longer useful or beneficial. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I loved her.&nbsp; I loved her as much as anyone could possibly love another person.&nbsp; Feelings like this ran so deep that I would have done anything to make her life happier.&nbsp; But these feelings were not reciprocated.&nbsp; When you love someone that much, you are willing to give up anything, make any sacrifice to ensure their happiness.&nbsp; I tried to do this.&nbsp; She does not see it that way. &nbsp;Rather than seeing what she had, she tossed me aside for the sake of emulating the empty lives of those around her in her classes and those of her friends.&nbsp; These lives consist of cheating on their mates, drinking, partying, sleeping around, etc....&nbsp; To sacrifice something of substance (such as she had with me) merely to pretend she doesn’t have a care in the world is hypocritical.&nbsp; I did all that was in my power to see this relationship through.&nbsp; I never gave up on us.&nbsp; Everything I did was geared to see that she lived a full, balanced, rich life.&nbsp; I deprived her on nothing but time with me.&nbsp; I could not be there as much as she demanded.&nbsp; And the ultimate reward for my loyalty, trust, and love is to receive the treatment I got these last 10 weeks.&nbsp; Why I put up with it, I will never know. 
     

    


15,July,2004


	 
      What am I supposed to do now?&nbsp; I did what everyone has been telling me to do and that was to let go.&nbsp; I walked away from her and was prepared to never look back.&nbsp; That took a firm commitment from me to bring myself to do that, but I did it.&nbsp; But these things are funny.&nbsp; Right when I walked away, she started to contact me.&nbsp; This represents one the life’s idiosyncrasies.&nbsp; My guess is, she still isn’t sure what is to be done with “us.”&nbsp; She sees me walking away as a threat to her happiness.&nbsp; Maybe not now, but in the future.&nbsp; I think she sees the bigger picture and is scared that she may miss the boat.&nbsp; Therefore, she wants to maintain some contact with me.&nbsp; But then comes the curveball she and I should have expected, but didn’t.&nbsp; We both are pretty sexually charged right now.&nbsp; It had been about 2 months since we really had some good strong sex with each other, or anyone for that matter.&nbsp; We just jumped right into it the first time we hung out.&nbsp; We have hung out twice and both times we have gotten into bed together.&nbsp; Now don’t get me wrong, I am NOT complaining.&nbsp; I love being intimate with her.&nbsp; The quirk comes into play when I sit down and consider what the long-term effects of such an arrangement will be; especially since I still feelings for Kelly stewing beneath the surface.&nbsp; I’m sure she has the same going on with her, but she is not so apt to acknowledge them.&nbsp; She does think about it, but not in front of me.&nbsp; It was a little premature of me to bring up the subject to her.  &nbsp;  Now I have found out something about what Kelly has been doing that took me by complete surprise.&nbsp; She has been sleeping with other people, as well as with me.&nbsp; I have mixed emotions about this.&nbsp; I do like having sex with her, but damn if I am going to be ok with her going out and screwing other guys while we are going at it.&nbsp; For one thing, how do I know that I am safe from disease or other?&nbsp; I don’t appreciate being put at risk to catch something unknowingly.&nbsp; It is almost as if I have been deceived. &nbsp;She didn’t want to tell me because she knew I wouldn’t sleep with her.&nbsp; Another thing about this whole situation is how am I supposed to stand by and be ok with the girl I love sleeping with other people and myself.&nbsp; She must know how much I care for her.&nbsp; Why would she think it would be ok for her to treat me like a fucking yo-yo with this back and forth bullshit?&nbsp; Doesn’t she know that this is going to have me invest my feelings in her again?&nbsp; I’m not the type of guy that is willing to do that with the person that I love. 
     

    


12,July,2004


	 
      Have you ever taken a step back and looked at your life and realized that things you worked and planned for just didn’t turn out like you thought they would?&nbsp; It’s a funny thing this life is.&nbsp; I’ve known this for a while, but I really only just learned this recently.&nbsp; I recently sat down and looked at the developments in my life these last few years and I see my life in a completely different place than I imagined it would be just a few years ago.&nbsp; Even plans I had even 3 months ago have been altered or just plan shit on.&nbsp; For instance, a long time ago, I thought I would be a chemical engineer and now I’m getting a job as a Financial Planner.&nbsp; Another example is what happened with my girlfriend of 3 years suddenly calling it quits and walking away from me; right when I was ready to commit myself to her 100%.&nbsp; Talk about a 180 degree swing.  &nbsp;  Some might argue that there is only one lesson to be learned from situations like these.&nbsp; That lesson, they argue, is that we should not allow ourselves to become to attached to any given person or dream without complete confidence and assurance that they will prevail or succeed.&nbsp; In other words, should we allow ourselves to put all our eggs in one basket and risk being left with nothing when our plans, dreams, and passions turn to crap?&nbsp; Others feel differently. They would argue that if we believe in something so adamantly or want something badly enough, shouldn't we be willing to risk everything we hold sacred(Our self-respect, loved ones, sanity, careers, or anything else of worth) just to see that our plans and dreams come together as we initially planned?&nbsp; These are difficult questions to answer.&nbsp; Not because I do not want to broach the subject, but because each situation and each person would answer that in their own way.  &nbsp;  In my particular situation, the steps I have taken in response to the wrinkle that has occurred in my life recently have been quite discouraging.&nbsp; What has happened to me in terms of my love life has taken a turn for the worse unexpectedly and I was left at a loss as I tried to remedy the situation.&nbsp; But there is one thing I have learned; when it comes to love, to make it work, you have to put yourself, your heart, and emotions into the hands of another.&nbsp; I agree with the later suggestion that you should be willing to risk it all for the sake of your happiness. You must leave yourself completely vulnerable to disappointment and heartbreak.&nbsp; This was a tough decision that I made a few months ago as I surrendered to dedicating myself to her completely.&nbsp; I was blind to the fact that, in just a few short months, it would all blow up in my face.&nbsp; Furthermore, I was ignorant to how I would respond to such rejection.&nbsp; With reckless abandon, I managed to turn a bad situation even worse.&nbsp; I fear I lost the one thing I wanted to hold onto.&nbsp; I decided I would lay it all out there and risk it all on the gamble of winning her heart again. I knew what I was risking, but I thought it all worth it. I laid it all on the line and did whatever I could to hold this relationship together. I showed determination, faithfullness, patience, love, kindness, and generosity mixed in with a little bit of emotional trama. But the moves I made were contrary to what she wanted and it only made her upset with me to the point where she hates me now.&nbsp; The shitty part is, I can’t even explain that to her because she won’t care.&nbsp; She has turned her heart into stone.&nbsp; We have reached the point-of-no-return and pissed all over it. She would rather rub it in that she is talking to, flirting with, and dating other guys.&nbsp; Ah, love… It’s a motherfucker.&nbsp; It does things to a man you would never expect. 
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      We were supposed to go to Lake Perris today and test out John’s new boat.  It didn’t exactly turn out that way.  Raffi and his brother were playing golf and that took much longer than expected.  I suppose we will go on Monday or next weekend.  One of those will do.  It’s better actually.  I was able to do more studying for the Series 63 exam.  I have to be ready to pass this exam.  This is the future for me and my future wife and children.  I can no longer mess around.  John finished his DVD today. John is one of my long-time friends whose life ambition is to be a big-time Hollywood director.  The short movie he made for one of his classes is actually really good.  He is going to be a great director one day.  I can see he has the drive to make it in any business he chooses to associate himself with.    Around 2 p.m., I got a call from an ex-coworker about the 4th of July BBQ at my friends’ house.  She indicated she wants to go but I need to pick her up in Diamond Bar.  I feel kind of bad since I really do not want to date her like she does me, but I already asked her and I can’t really take it back for no reason.   It would not be fair to another girl if I jumped into a dating them if I don’t deal with my other demons first.  My concentration would not be in it as it should be. I would rather not have to deal with making that decision at this time.  That won’t occur until I can get over Kelly. So i suppose I will cancel with this girl. No harm in backing out, but I need a good excuse.  I did something stupid and told Kelly that I am keeping this site.  What was I thinking?  That she could log on and see what I am up to and get jealous? She is already doing more than I am and dating more than I am. I CAN”T make her jealous. Did I think she would take pity on me? Not a chance.  She has not taken pity on me and I don’t want it.  It is hard to fix upon my driving motivation behind this. I do like to write and usually write things down, especially when I have things wieghing on my mind. Guys do some dumb things. I think I told her so she can keep up with my life on her own accord without me bothering so much.  I try to justify it as a way for me to distance myself from her and give her what she wants while still letting her know what is going on with me.  Even now, I want to call her, but I know she will just get upset. She has already called me twice today to scoff at me for doing dumb shit that I know is dumb.  I got to stop the shenanigans.  She is justified to some extent.  Whatever. But I have a feeling that something is going to happen soon.  I’m not sure what or to whom or to what extent, but I know that something is going to happen and it will affect me for the better. I guess I can best liken it to the “gut feeling” Kelly got about us.  Whatever it is, I welcome it without abandon.  Bring it on.  I can handle it.  I’ve made it this far and I’m still standing.  Some people think that I am letting my ego get in the way of my life.  They think that I am holding onto Kelly merely so my pride is not hurt.  I do not agree.  During the relationship, I did all I could to encourage her to do her best, to expand her horizons, to continuously make herself into a better person.  I encouraged her to make girlfriends.  When I met her, she didn’t really have friends.  Her previous boyfriend discouraged that.  I tried to be everything he wasn’t.  She claims that is the reason she went out with me in the first place.  But the freedom was too much and she came to like it.  So here I am.  A victim of my own creation is what I have become.  That is part of the reason why I say that this breakup is my fault.  My other fault, which was largely beyond my control, was the issue of the amount of time I was able to spend with her.  However, that would have only held us together for just another period of time.  Sooner or later, she would grow the itch to see other people or check out her options.  How am I to demand the attention of a girl for a long period of time?  I can not control other people’s personal issues.  But I wanted to be there for her.  Unfortunately, I did not do all I could.  I only gave 80%.  At the end there, I learned a thing or two about how to keep a relationship working and was putting in 100%, but it was too late. Her mind had already left me. 
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
      Today was a tough day. At around 7:00 p.m., I got a phone call from a friend of mine informing me that one of our good friends from my high school years was murdered today. He was shot when he entered a 7-11 by some robbers who thought he was in the way of their escape. He died on the spot. I have seen this friend only sporatically these recent years. He was one of the kindest, most gentle men you would have the pleasure of meeting. He attended and graduated from Stanford Univ. and was continuing on in Law School there. He was an only child and the pride and joy of his parents. I can only imagine the pain they are going through. I will miss him treribly. My heart goes out to them (what is left of it at least).   It has hit me, but not to the fullest extent. I am still somewhat numb from the blow struck me by my ex. Kelly, my ex, and I were together for 3 years. She was my lover, confidant, and my best friend. Our relationship began to slip, in her mind, in February. She was disgruntled about her birthday and that my school (my last semester) would demand so much of my attention. She wanted, and needed, alot of attention; attention that I could not give. I did all I could to make her happy; to be there when I could. It wasn't enough to demand her loyalty though. She became unhappy with our relationship because she was unwilling to wait. Then she began looking beyond the boundaries of our relationship to other men. When she finally decided to breakup with me, I was 2 weeks from graduation and already in the process of kicking our relationship into a higher gear. I was seeing her more often and, in my eyes, giving her more of what she had asked for the previous 4 months. But she was already enamored with this other guy from her class. Initially, she couldn't even be up-front with me about WHY she wanted to breakup. She hid behind a wall of lies to spare my feelings and disolve any guilt about not being faithfull to me. She says she is just not ready to be latched down. She doesn't want to settle down in a serious relationship. This is what I get for all my loyalty, love, kindness and wanting her to be the best woman she can be. I suppose I gave her TO much freedom and she walked all over it. I do not hold myself blameless for the our demise. There were lots of opportunities for me to show her my appreciation that I just passed up. Had I not concentrated on my life so much, I probably could have saved the relationship. But, being heartbroken, I still get the feeling of betrayal. On top of it all, I had to find out the hard way about this other guy by catching her. Now, because I tried so hard to win her back, she doesn't even want to talk to me at this time. She claims that I have pushed her to hard. She says I will just make her second guess dating other people. Can't she see how much I love and care for her? She just does not care anymore. So why do I care so much and why is it so hard for me to let go? Anyways, it's kind of a shitty thing that i must go through; What a fucked up situation to be in. I have become so reclusive. I do not want to think of another girl at this time and she is already seeing people. On top if it all, she tells me that she loves every second of it. Shitty.  It seems to me that when it rains, it pours. I am doing my best to keep my chin up and my feet moving, but I still miss her. I really want to talk with someone who cares for me about these things, but the emptyness inside me consumes my motivation to go out. Sooner or later, this pain will die. I will fill in the holes during a series of my future posts.
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
      This is my first entry into this blog website. I have been through alot these last few weeks. I have started to keep a journal on my laptop, but I will begin to transfer everything to this website in the form of future posts. I will attempt to keep a daily listing of the daily events of my life as well as my feelings and expressions. I hope any readers of this blog (if any at all) can relate and hopefully take something away with them as I discuss my life. If you ever feel the need or would like to comment, reply or give advice, please do not hesitate to do so.    I suppose the proper initial entry should be used to introduce myself. My name is Lucas. I am 24 and just graduated from California State University in Fullerton. I am a good looking, white, middle-class guy raised in the suburbs of Southern California. I recently obtained a job/potential career at a small financial planning firm in Orange County. I will be a Financial Planner/Advisor; and a good one at that. As you will probably notice if you continue to read my entries over time, I am a stand-up, honest, and trustworthy individual. I am Christian but do not practice (or should I say go to church) on a regular basis. But that has no effect on the faith I have in God. For the most part, I am your typical guy. I am not a partier, bad-boy, choir-boy, hoodlum, gangster, asshole, etc... I am recently single (against my will). My ex-girlfriend, Kelly, broke up with me two weeks before my graduation to date other people. I will comment more on that in the future. That has been a large portion of my life these past few weeks. To be quite honest, my heart has been broken and I am struggling to regain control of my life.  This will be the end of the first post. For those who read this, those I know or don't know, there will be more to come and I hope everyone has an opportunity to enrich themselves and myself through these posts. 
     

    



