
28,July,2004


	 
      OK... today was an ok day... But i really need ur trusty advise... The thing is that today this girl who i was playing basketball with purposely threw da ball at my face real hard at close range... She didn't say sorry... this was during class... and the teacher dun know wat happen... she just know i chucked a spazz n threw the ball away real far after she did it... then the whole game resumed as normal... wat should i do now???
    


27,July,2004


	 
      Crazy fi likes going to uni? well i suppose uni aint that bad-yep get to c friends.... and for me go play bridge, chess, pool, snooker (which i'm terrible at but anyway ^^).... but still!! as for self-expression-whenever any of u 2 feel the 'need to express yourself' please tell me in advance so I can run first!! =P   
    


27,July,2004


	 
      &nbsp;  i should realli read more of ming's enteries to see what ancon was all about. i've also been out and about and haven't written much for the last few days!&nbsp;    &nbsp;  its ok lysh, we all have our psycho days... and bit of self-expression ja mah!!     &nbsp;  i get so bored at home sometimes though. don't quite know what to do wif myself. and uni is good , so many ppl to mingle wif!!whohoo!   
    


26,July,2004


	 
      haha-there there alysha-its alright!! I mean if u think that's unfair-well, in my mum's classes whenever the girls start chatting to the guys, the guys always get busted-doh!! now that's unfair!! mmm tho i sympathise-my parents are kinda like that too sometimes :/  meh getting kinda annoyed at uni-8AM starts everyday! and statistics? well yeah we're learning stem and leaf plots, histograms..... fun eh =P was kinda sleeping thru that-uhoh =S and that was the first lecture of the semester!!  btw-look on the positive side-u've won the most negative post award so far for the site ^^ 
    


25,July,2004


	 
      Damn it... i got in this really big fight with one of our teachers... and I'm made to apolligize... that's stoopid! Not fair! They neva apolligize to us! She really pushed it... telling me wat to do... nope! I'm not gonna take it... coz i was talking in the library! Geeezzz... everyone talks... selective hearing. Since when have we lost our freedom of speech??? Damn it! So sick of people telling me wat to do. It's pissing me off... whether it's at home, sku or church! Anywhere! It's fine if they tell me the do things nicely I'll probably do it... bit damn it... if they use their authoity on me... i get really pissed... Like really pissed... damn it. So freaking pissed.  Bleh... I s'posed to practice my piano... but decided not do anything and piss of the teacher... so now I'm listening to Boyz... Keke... they are so good looking... and i like their songs... Yep yep!!! All is good... Damn it... i can't believe i cried infront of that COW!!! :@ soo pissed... Maybe i should turn this music up and drown myself in this stuff... yep yep...   Sigh... i think i have the record of having the most negative post so far!!! Oh wellz...  
    


25,July,2004


	 
      ANCON was really good :D learnt alot and had tons of fun :):):) Alysha's missed me? And I'm starting to think pigs might fly too =P aaww shucks yeah I missed u peeps too :') lol though I might have been a tad slack on you this Sat ^^ but hey you started it!! though silliness only goes so far I suppose...   Yep, the song "Your love changes me" has really nice lyrics-you ppl'll have to show me how it sounds sometime-by u 2 singing it would be nice too coz u 2 have nice voices :):)   Somedays I really feel frustrated by my own inability, often hiding behind a mask, sometimes trying to be someone I'm really not-but God knows our hearts, our reasons, our motives. With God, we are laid bare-one of my favourite songs I learnt from ANCON is Rock of Ages, and one of the verses goes    &nbsp;   Nothing in my hand I bring,    Simply to the cross I cling;    Naked, come to Thee for dress;    Helpless, look to Thee for grace;    Foul, I to the fountain fly;    Wash me, Savior, or I die.     &nbsp;  At ANCON one point which really hammered home to me is that we, as Christians, have been called to freedom from sin. But so often, we laden down ourselves with our own guilt rather than accepting that God has given us freedom. The bible teaches us that guilty feelings&nbsp;has no place in Christian life, but instead rather we have constructive sorrow-a love motivated desire to change. Another was thinking about how God loves us so much-that if I was the only person in the world who was a sinner, Jesus would probably still die just for me.&nbsp;It's mind-boggling-never really thought/considered it too much before-that God loves us that much!! And then just comparing it to how much I love God... food for thought...   mmm well I'll go bak to writing up on my own blog about ANCON-soo much to write up or i'll prolly forget them all by the end of next week so yeah :):)   
    


20,July,2004


	 
      I love that song soooooooo much! I wish we could do it for band... but i dun know if they have it in sheet music or in tabs. Oh... Ming's at camp if you didn't know... Sigh... no mucking around with Ming for a whole week! I'm starting to miss him... Apart from the fact that i have to seek revenge on him... Mwahahaha! Yes... he will indeed recieve judgement this time... he's not getting away with it even though he lead the forgiveness study... haha...  &nbsp; I dun know why, I just feel like I have the energy to do wat is right now. It's just I've been lacking that energy for sooo long! I just decided to hate the world. I could see hope, but I just didn't live in hope. There is so much knowledge in my head but it just does correspond to the way I think and act. Oh wellz... Maybe if you went out for a run Fi, you might feel a little better? I dun know... &nbsp; I can't make it to this week's Band coz it's on thursday. I've made a commitment of Friday and unless it suits me I won't be able to come. It's not becoz I dun love the Band like crazy, it's coz of sku and parents. It's annoying, I know, I'm sorry, I really hope that you guys can understand. When I go to Uni then maybe we can practice every week!!! : P 
    


19,July,2004


	 
       I am always humbled and thankful by the fact that God's love for me is not based upon my performance as a Christian but rather on the life and death of His own perfect Son. This is love indeed!"1 John 4:9,10 - Nathan Tasker     &nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;      Your love changes me        &nbsp;     I look in the mirror/At the man in front of me/Just a hazy reflection/Of all the things I want to be/I’m so frustrated by all the compromise/And I’m so embarrassed by the way I feast on the hollow lies/When your truth is so much sweeter/ And your love is so much deeper//Chorus/  You cannot love me more/And you will no love me less/Though I come to you with nothing/ And receive your righteousness/I come just as I am/Oh, but here’s the mystery/While I can come without changing/but your love changes me  //I sometimes imagine/ When I am all alone/ That given some more time/ I could have done this on my own/How could I be so blinded by my pride?How could I forget I was dead before you gave me life? For you are The Great Life Giver/and you are The Promise Keeper// Chorus // Bridge:   Nothing of my own I bring/ Simply to your cross I cling/ Well, nothing of my own/So I know it’s you alone/That gives me everything….For you loved before I loved you/And you’ve done what I could never do!  //Chorus// &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;   
    


19,July,2004


	 
       thnx to everyone who love me as i am. Like alysha, i think lately i've just fallen so far. so fast. a tumble right down to the bottom,&nbsp;not a stumble. everything seems to be so wrong these days. Everything is so&nbsp;flawed, nothing seems to realli b going right. not satisfied with much.     &nbsp;   i guess ive been a bit strange lately, but yeah, i realli treasure those who accept me as i am, and nothing more. while i was watching the&nbsp;'birthday bash' on&nbsp;"oprah" , it was talking about CSI. crime scene investigation for those who are so naieve.&nbsp;(bot forensics)&nbsp;They go through all the scientific devices they use&nbsp;in reali life to solve crime. There was one bit that realli striked me. There was a doctor who investigated carcass for a few months up to a&nbsp;year or two.&nbsp;These people die a natural death, and the family wants to know why they died. She slowly unpackages them, and takes samples to be screened etc. Trying to find out why they died.     &nbsp;   In one of the carcasses, she takes apart the body. Like an animal in the butcher, the body is dissembled. i see a row of ribs, like the spare ribs u c in the butcher. It reminds me of how fragile the human body is. We are NOTHING much realli, than a bit of flesh and meat. So fragile to disease and&nbsp;accidents. We are vulnerable, though when we are alive, there's is soooo much life in the voice, in the expression, in the face, the warmth of the palm.&nbsp;In reality, we are very vulnerable, and just like the animals u see in the butcher. We are no less than them, in a biochemical sense. Life is truely precious.     &nbsp;   There's a song by nathan tasker. Lysh and i realli like it.     &nbsp;   We go to God as we are.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;We can offer him nothing, and bring him nothing&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;but   he loves as JUST AS WE ARE.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;the amazing thing is that he will&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  love us no more,      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; and he cannot love us any less.     A  lthough we bring him nothing, we are changed by his love.    
    


19,July,2004


	 
      Hmmm... wat should I say??? Thank you all of you for being who you are. It's just really touching at times that we care abt each other. I really want to get people to come into this blog but i think they have a really high filter on so i can't get to them so easily. This is really a good way to share how he feel and how we're going spiritually. I mean I can truthfully tell you that I'm not going that well. But I'm starting to pick it back up again I'm starting to feel the energy and love that God has given me to give others again and so I shall start my term very happily. &nbsp; I believe that any put together with God = 100% goodness. Sometimes we stumble, so wat! If it was in God's will that we stumble, then so be it! I've stumbled this time along with you Fi, this time. And I'm glad to do so coz at least we know that we will 4eva be there 4 each other. The more we go through, the stronger our friendship will be. Ming, I'm not leaving you out of this. This ain't just girl talk! This applies to all of us... Hmmm... just need others to come in first lol... &nbsp; Thx for being who you are, so let us be 4evafriends. 
    


16,July,2004


	 
      well its not too bad an idea IMHO-like most crashes after that time'd probably occur due to drinking and/or speeding.... with the curfew it might help reduce the amount of crashes due to these factors... so yeah i'm not sure-it might save lives, but similarly banning knives'd probably also save lives.... 
    


15,July,2004


	 
      what do u guys think of a curfew 9pm for those who have p plates? just wondering. thanx
    


15,July,2004


	 
      yes, it was quite a bit of work preparing that study. anyways, i reali hope its not too badly written. hmm.... hope its ok and not too bad and everyone gets ALOT out of it!!!and hope everyone leading it does it with much love and effectively. i also wish i did strand 2 at kylc though, it would make writing it so much easier i think!! nevermind. life is so fast sometimes. e.g. after holiday everything has just been happening, as in lots of things to do. and exam results were ok. not great or anything. hmm.... still annoyed at ppl who get more marks than me, who distract me during lectures though!!! =S i'll just have to play it fair, and be content with the way things are. maybe* i will try a bit harder next semester!! 
    


15,July,2004


	 
      Mmmm Alysha and I'd just like to give Fi a big thankyou and hug for putting so much effort into preparing our study this Sat-even tho she's been sick and everything! so yeah go Fi-you're practically a 1 gal team ^^ so yeah tx so much-without u were'd we be! prolly wouldnt have finished the study by this Sat and wouldnt be half so good so yeah -_- its so bad i'll give it a 11/10 :P mmmm tho Fi is a SPAMMER :O, sending like 8 emails in the past few hrs lol. so yeah Fi thx so much and we hope u'll get better!!
    


14,July,2004


	 
      Sigh Poor Ming... I have a feeling that Eric dun wanna join! That leaves you all alone... Mwahahahaha!!! Dun worry... us girl will take 'good care' of you. After all Kathy, Fi, Amanda and I aren't horrible people! Actually... we might be too nice to you!!! We'll c if karna comes in... then you might not be so lonely! Lol... yeah... Eric dun wanna join... sigh... he dun like us... oh wellz...
    


14,July,2004


	 
      bah some1 should go ban american idol-i'm starting a protest right here!! the show's twisted-it has corrupted my sister :'( she's singing 'lean on me' at the top of her voice at the moment!! *sigh* not to mention the fact it also brings my dad to start singing 'yellow submarine'(horror of all horrors 

10,July,2004


	 
      lol hey all!! finally got thing to work so yeah :D mmmm looks like i'm the only guy on this blog-uhoh (tells self to be careful of what to say)... where's eric?! E!! and karna da bum...*sigh* then we could talk about gals-keke mayb not :P  So what's there to talk about-well 3 uni results are out but i wont bore u all with wat i got (pretty good results considering ^^...but bio! :@ grrr) Just started tutoring a 4th grade guy and an 8th grade gal-pretty nice family!! was an experience-teaching shapes and symmetry and basic algebra for the 4th grader, and going thru some more diffucult algebra, and chem for the gal :) they've got a really cool house! wish my house was like that but anywayz 

10,July,2004


	 
      So... wat to say... I'm at Fi's place right now... typing away... and for the first time... i go to sleep ova! Kool! Eh??? Today... lets see... we went to Meroo and had a great day with margaret with a bible study on Romans and basketball... Oh and the pray house... it's so cool... except we didn't stay long enuf... cos the scenery there was really nice and all... Yes... i currently have Kathy and Fi beside me telling wat to write... Yeah... we have girl talk and we talk abt GUYZ!!! Haha... guys you scared??? Lol... Fi's devising lots of new mean way so scared of guys... Lol... Mwahahaha... Yeah... we had a whole day of fun and we had band... Here I am to Worship is really good!   We're gonna make food for you guys tomorrow! For core Group!!! :P Good luck on not having food poisoning!!! Well... gonna talk more abt hot guys now... :P
    


08,July,2004


	 
      hi everyone,  i have the honour in writing the first entery.. 
    


15,August,2004


	 
      Yeah been quite busyish-not that much sleep either-I mean, my parents forcing me to get up on Sunday at 10am, even when I have nothing on-it's not as if I get much sleep on any other day. Then after waking up, having to listen to them argue like children-and this occurs on an almost daily basis. I could shut them up by telling them they're behaving like children instead of adults but I'm too tired to. And anyway it seems insignificant to what's happened this morning-yeah Eddie's mum died of cancer this morning... it'd be nice if you ppl could pray for his family in their time of need.  mmm i betta go bak and *try* working.
    


15,August,2004


	 
      are ppl just too busy to write on the blog or can't be bothered or just don't go online that much because u sleep alot?  hmm yup i haven't been online since wednesday! luckily there wasn't any urgent emails.. cos i didn't read any of them that fast =)  personaly i sleep alot and spend more time at uni these days.  oooo and its beeeeeen super sitting in quincy's car. in the *distant* future, quincy said i can b on a roster wif him for driving to uni!! how cool. so quincy can sleep in the car half the time and i can sleep in the car half the time. (becos all the other guys are no where near getting their ps - but then again, they could learn faster than me becos im soooooooooooo SLOW !! ) lol....    and its not worth driving to uni by urself because the petrol costs too much!!! so for the next few years, i think i'll be car pooling still  =) its sooooo much more economical and time efficient when u see the sign "T3"!!!!!! whoohooooooo............ zooooooom zoooom zoooooooom ooo the other day, we were drivin in T3 lane, and then two policemen comes out from the corner. The car infront of us didn't have 3 ppl, so they got fined !! =) 
    



26,July,2004


     
      Uni's just started again-yay :/ 8am starts everyday! gonna be sooo fun 

25,July,2004


     
       Wednesday-Day 3    In the morning session we studied 2 Corinthians 5. We were learning about the motivating factor of the cross in lives. We, as Christians, are new creations, where the old is gone and the new has come. We have a new relationship with God, with whom we are now friends with. We are set free from our past, and we are reconciled with God, having a restoration of intimacy with God. Everything we do should be out of love-for example, Paul was under the spell of God's love, and that's why he did everything out of Christ's love for us. The question we should be asking is, how do we become a person controlled by God's love?   In our free time, we had the Lekabio(?) cup (I don't have a clue how to spell it so I dont know!!). It's a touch football competition between the various faculties of the EU. The teams this year were engineering, science, ag/vets/CaL(com/law), and ACES/ecos. Our team, ACES/ecos, won our first game ever at ANCON!! It was 1-0 vs ag/vets/CaL so yeah :) tho how we won seems more than a tad suspicious lol-we only try we scored was from a intercepted pass from&nbsp;Joyce from the other team, who is incidentally an ex-ACES member =P  The night session was about salvation from God-its history, what the NT has to say about it, and understanding atonement.  1) The history of God's salvation plan-we looked through various areas related to salvation in the old testament-the passover/exodus, the day of atonement, sacrifices, and the practice of redemption. 2) The new testament as a witness to the cross as God's salvation for us 3) The various ways we can understand atonement- &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; a. A condemnation that brings justification-God condemned sin in the flesh, Jesus, so that we may be justified &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; b. A sacrifice that cleanses us before God-Christ is our high priest, who by his blood, through the eternal Spirit, offered himself without blemish to God, purifying us &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; c. A ransom which redeems-We were redeemed from sin by the payment of Jesus' precious blood, like a lamb without defect or blemish &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; d. An obedience which makes us righteous-just as Adam's disobedience led to condemnation for all, Jesus' act of obedience brings justification and life to all &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; e. A propitiation&nbsp;(*properly signifies the removal of wrath by the offering of a gift)&nbsp;which&nbsp;reconciles and brings peace-Jesus was put forward by God as a sacrifice of propitiation by his blood, effective through our faith &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; f. A dying under sin which makes us alive-one died for all, so that in Jesus we have died to sin, and may be set free form it  Meh-too tired 

23,July,2004


     
      Weeeeeee!! just got bak from&nbsp;the EU&nbsp;ANCON (annual conference)&nbsp; at Collaroy Conference Centre-learnt SO MUCH and had heaps of fun along the way! It seems really short now-wish it was longer :/ oh well-still-made the best of these holidays so yeah its been good =) and Collaroy Conference Centre is such a nice venue-with the beach, shops.... and us from ACES got the ensuites!!which were like 2-3 ppl in a room with its own bathroom-with hightech showerheads which do different weird stuff when u twist them :):):)    Monday-Day 1    Okay, so I woke up around 7:00AM on Monday morning as Nat was meant to pick me up around 9AM-after eating brekke (ham+eggs, and honey nutri-grain), waited up till around 9:15AM when Nat still hadn't turned up :/ so yeah called Eddie who was at Jeremy's place and found out they hadn't been picked up either-and they were meant to be picked up b4 me!! well-yeah found out that Nat was 1/2 an hr late..... and then he went to the wrong 74 Murray Farm Rd!! doh-yeah he went to the carlingford side instead of beecroft 

17,July,2004


     
      Hi again-yeah we had a "party" today - tho half the time we were working on the workshop on forgiveness today :/&nbsp;As usual E and Fi got here early, and me and Dad went to pick Kat up from the station-it was due in at like 10:04am but the trains were late as they often are nowadays :@ and Mandii-yeah well she kinda slept in ^_^ &nbsp; So yeah we started off by going through the study-to make sure of all of us knew the material we were leading with today. And of course, Eric just had to eat chips right in front of Fi who has a stomach ache-aren't we nice ppl? :P then we ate some spaghetti, fruit&nbsp;and drank some soft drink for lunch-with icecream for dessert which we all ate in front of Fi (mwahahaha!! no icecream 4 u!!) - wasn't the icecream great?! mmmmm yum!! &nbsp; then we went thru making the 3 skits we performed today-haha kinda last minute but oh wellz -- if u dont know what it's about its about 2 kids (E and Kat), and Kat's listening to Ghetto Superstar... then E comes along, doesnt like the music and so takes the CD out and breaks it in front of Kat-yeah i told u we were nice ppl ^_^ then we had 3 different hilarious cut scenes where they forgive each other, dont forgive and the last where they pretend to forgive each other. I think performing these skits were the highlight of the forgiveness workshop today-yeah E and Kat are really funni ^^ &nbsp; As for the workshop overall? Well we kinda started 10 minutes late and the studies took a tad longer than we thought-the game were nice and humorous-(with some last minute modifications), which illustrated the principle of grace quite well. We didnt end up symbolically burning pieces of paper at the end-but otherwise the workshop went along pretty good :) &nbsp; Yeah-was a good experience leading-and yeah now I'm bak home-kz bb!! 
     
    


16,July,2004


     
      mayb i shouldnt have introduced alysha and shen yesterday-tho the 3 of us really are quite silly ^^ oh well tho i was the one being teased most of the time 

15,July,2004


     
      mmmm end of another day ^_^ well yeah got bak all my uni results now - and if u really wanna know-3 HDs and 3Ds for a HD average :D so yeah i'm pretty happy bout that... except for bio which is "supposedly" my best subject -_-  other than that nothing much happened today-mmm went out with dad to eat at carlo village, yeah that's bout it... mmmm not that much to do this week compared to last week 

14,July,2004


     
      hi all-yeah just started this blog today ^_^ still figuring things out-totally confused atm by all the html and javascript but hey-hopefully i'll be able to figure out how to use this darned thing-but dont get ur hopes too high!!  cant believe 2 and a bit weeks of uni holz are already gone so quick-but mayb that's coz these holidays i've been really busy for a change which is good -_- yeah this holiday's seen it all-HS again (lol yeah just visiting the teachers ^^), movies, b'days, uni ACES RACES thingy, chess tournaments, piano concerts.... and of course working- oh yeah did i mention i got 2 new tutorees?! there's a darned smart 4th grade guy, and a yr 8 gal whos cute in her own way :P yeah wish i had a house like theirs....... *dreams*   and then there's still ANCON to go!! if u peeps dont know what ANCON is, it stands for annual conference-all of u should go!! u dunno what ur missing out on!! keke mayb i should go to the camp first b4 commenting but anywayz... mmm cbb typing anymore-mayb another day-okies cya
     
    


14,July,2004


     
      mmm just gonna try this out....
     
    


15,August,2004


     
      Why can't parents act like parents instead of little kids? Getting kind of sick and tired of their arguments everyday-you get the impression that they hate each other's guts. I won't get into the icky details-but it's like they live to annoy the hell out of each other, without caring what happens to me and my sister. Well, they do care about me and my sister, but often you wouldn't think that. What should I do? I could probably shut them up by telling them to grow up and behave like adults, but then they'll continue arguing some other time and I'm too tired at the moment anyway... sometimes (like now)I wish could kick them out of the house by calling the police due to them being a domestic disturbance but hey... it might help like when I called them and my sister left for a few weeks... but then they own this place hmmm...  yeah I know this is a very pessimistic post but hey that's what happens around here on an almost daily basis... Could you people please pray for my family (if that's not being selfish)? It seems to be getting worse and worse each week. Well, one good thing has happened though-my sister has started coming to church again! :D even though it's a different church to where the rest of us go to (Epping Baptist) but still. I suppose things could be worse (like my parents being dead)-oh yeah so could you people pray for Eddie's family? His mother died this morning from cancer so it'd be nice if you could pray for them in their grief.  Mmmm they're still at it-really quite hard to study-I think I'd better go and *try* to do some work...   Psalm 42   As the deer pants for streams of water,  so my soul pants for you, O God.  2 My soul thirsts for God, for the living God.  When can I go and meet with God?  3 My tears have been my food  day and night,  while men say to me all day long,  "Where is your God?"  4 These things I remember  as I pour out my soul:  how I used to go with the multitude,  leading the procession to the house of God,  with shouts of joy and thanksgiving  among the festive throng.   5 Why are you downcast, O my soul?  Why so disturbed within me?  Put your hope in God,  for I will yet praise him,  my Savior and 6 my God.   My [3] soul is downcast within me;  therefore I will remember you  from the land of the Jordan,  the heights of Hermon-from Mount Mizar.  7 Deep calls to deep  in the roar of your waterfalls;  all your waves and breakers  have swept over me.   8 By day the LORD directs his love,  at night his song is with me-  a prayer to the God of my life.   9 I say to God my Rock,  "Why have you forgotten me?  Why must I go about mourning,  oppressed by the enemy?"  10 My bones suffer mortal agony  as my foes taunt me,  saying to me all day long,  "Where is your God?"   11 Why are you downcast, O my soul?  Why so disturbed within me?  Put your hope in God,  for I will yet praise him,  my Savior and my God.  
     
    


10,August,2004


     
      Aaargh soo annoyed - I'd written out this post before, and it was fine, and then when I edited it only part of it was sent ruining the whole thing! sigh and now I have to post it all again.... oh well 


