
30,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Solfusion playing live and basic at orchard paragon for the tapersy gig.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Set up and tune my guitar&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    This photo was taken by my photographer&nbsp;friend,Eric Ang. He wanted to enter this photo for some photography competition. &nbsp; urlLink    
     

    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Solfusion performing at orchard cineleisure.Tapersy gig is a charity event to raise money for the poor students in school who needs pocket money.The solfusion demo CD was sold there and the profit of our CD was donated to the charity.Interesting thing is,after the gig,people who buy our CD requested us to sign our autograph at the CD.Thank you to all people who appreciated our music.keep on believeing.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapersy gig at orchard cineleisure&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapersy gig at orchard cineleisure&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


24,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapping freaks&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Solfusion playing live and basic at orchard paragon&nbsp; urlLink    
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    My bassist thomas the man&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapping on rain&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapersy gig at orchard paragon&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tapersy gig at orchard paragon&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    steve vai index triangle&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Blue hair dude&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    solfusion at planet paradigm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Solfusion at singapore street festival&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gig at planet paradigm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gig at singapore street festival&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Wearing the Solfusion T-shirt for the first time for the tapersy gig.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Solfusion performing live and basic at Orchard paragon.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Having fun!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rock on for life ! Click on the July archives for more pics of the paragon performance.  urlLink    
     

    


08,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Took this picture at siloso beach.Really really cute. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


07,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Having a relaxing swim at Sentosa Siloso beach.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


07,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Beautiful beach at Phuket in Thailand.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


06,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Snorkeling at Phuket.The sea water was clear and the view was beautiful.Saw lots of beautiful coral there.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


06,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jetski at Phuket beach in thailand.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


06,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Guitar heros of all time.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Steve vai is the most amazing guitarist I have ever seen.He is truely inspirational.Caught his concert in Singapore on the 29th of july 04 at Suntec conventional hall.The performance was totally mind blowing.Freakin super cool!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    One ass kicking performance of all time&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Playing the song biaxident&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Setting up the Boss GT6 and Morley bad horsie wah.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    



