
20,July,2004


	 
       Time : 2:23 P.M.  Date : July 20, 2004 Tuesday  Status : Tired  First things first, I have no classes and tomorrow will be my PE classes! ^_^ yipee! Since I have no classes today, I decided to pay a visit to my school and buy myself a PE uniform and a textbook for English. After the ride, I made my way straight to the school bookstore, look for the textbook and uniform and *poof*! Guess what?! The PE uniforms were SOLD OUT!   But it’s ok, there are more thing that have happened later this day ^_^.   After that surprising moment, I decided to go to the mall *harharhar*. But, the thing is, I rode a different jeepney! O_O. But my optimistic mind said that “Hey! This is your chance to make an adventure in the city!” So there I was, with my little “adventure” in the big city! ahihihi.   From Herrera Street, I started walking and guessing my way to G4. While walking, I realized that “Hey, there are so much business people walking around within the feet of the buildings with towering heights!” I know it sounds so much like “promdi” but hey!, I’m just a 15-year-old kid walking alone!   While walking at the other side of the street, I passed by the building of Allied Bank of the Philippines. I was impressed by their security system! It’s like, you’re going inside an airport! Before I continue, I would like all of you to know that I am carrying Kuya Lance’s laptop because my other files and documents are there AND still not uploaded by Kuya Lance, that’s why his laptop was on my hands.  Where were we? Oh yes! Te Allied Bank of the Philippines! I was passing it by and got amazed by it’s security system. So, while passing their main door, I was looking at their entrance, a security guard so me and *poof* the guard became a genius an suspected me as a *drum roll* HACKER!!! If you can imagine me, wearing casual clothing, carrying a bag and a laptop, will I look like a hacker? (Kuya Lance, you owe me one again!)   The guard approached me and asked me some questions. After some time, I was finally clear! I have no idea that that’s the only thing I need to do! And “that” is to show my ID to prove that I am a legal student. So finally, the security guard let me go and still, I have my mission, “To find my way to the mall!”  After minutes of walking and seconds of breathing, I’m finally here! Outside Greenbelt, sitting here on a platform, watching the cars and jeepneys pass by.  That’s all for now.  Ciao!  P.S.: Kuya Lance, you have one kick-ass laptop!!!
     

    


19,July,2004


	 
       Time : 8:47  Date : July 19, 2004  Monday  Status : Tired  Well… the first week of college is over and guess what? I SURVIVED! ^_^ So… I want to share with you guys what happened from Day 1 till today (yipee! sharing time!)   	 DAY 1 : A fresh start 	 monday  The first day (of course!) It all started in the hallway. I don’t know what I am going to do! Then… the bell rang… everybody was gone… they were in there respective rooms… but me, I’m having doubt entering the room because I heard someone saying “Alam ko hindi pa pwede pumasok sa room ‘pag walang prof…”.  Since I don’t see any “Prof” that time… I decided to stay in the hallway. After 15 minutes of doing absolutely NOTHING… I decided to enter the room since the lights are open… And after 10 minutes of sitting and behaving myself in the best manner… someone stands up and said “Sige na nga! Simulan na nga natin!” And there goes the first subject!  The second one… well… we met a professor who speaks like a very popular person in politics!   As for the third class… I don’t really want to blog about it ^.^ just IM me if you want to know what happened…    	 DAY 2 : I’m one lazy bum! 	 tuesday  Nothing special ‘bout this day… except for the fact that I finally got my ID! That’s all!  	 DAY 3 : My “piss off” day! 	 wednesday   This day was supposed to be my first “PE” classes so I woke up early, got on a bus, and at last! I finally made it to school! I arrived 30 minutes earlier and waited there for my classmates… After a few minutes, I saw Ronnie and Joel (I met them during our medical examination) and chatted with them a little bit… After I told that it’s my PE classes that day, Ronnie told me that there are no PE classes until July 19! So to make the long story short, I came to school for NOTHING 

18,July,2004


	 
       Time : 9:06 A.M  Date : July 19, 2004 Monday  Status : Sad... very sad  They finally bid their farewell to me... To clarify things up, here is the story...  I'd rather not to mention their name -_-  It all started in a message board when we met, then we decided to meet up in a mall... and that's where our "FUN" time began  After our little "adventure", we decided to form a group... with that group came contacts to each other... with that contact came our little "bonding" (awwww...)  After days of laughter and months of sharing insights... One of us decided to leave... It's okay for us if that one will just leave the group, but, that one decided to leave the country...  We were all shocked of that announcement. Now, I proved it to myself that whenever there are laughters, there will be tears... T_T  As of now... our friend is now on the way to the other part of the globe... We don't know if we will have contact again because of the timeline in other countries...  That's all for now, I'll blog again later 'bout some "school experiences"  Have a nice day!   
     

    


12,July,2004


	 
       Time : 1:14  Date : July 13, 2004 Tuesday  Status : Blank  Well... my first blog in here so... nothing special...    
     

    



