
13,July,2004


	 
      To be honost, I fucking hate the internet. World Wide Fuck.  AHAHAHA AHAHAHA    AHAHAH  

13,July,2004


	 
      One thing I can't stand: lesbians.  one thing I REALLY can't stand: lesbians who hate the internet!  I think they only hate the internet because they find it hard to type through their lover's vaginal membrane. Maybe if they stopped FISTING the girl, and TYPED, they would have better luck!  that is, if they weren't all fat with sausage fingers incaipable of typing less than 3 letters at once..
    


13,July,2004


	 
      One thing I love about the internet is google!!!   If you need to find anything, !1, give it a whirl!!   http://www.google.com !  i wonder why more people don't know about it!?1
    


13,July,2004


	 
      Boy howdy, I love the internet! but i don't like people who don't 


13,July,2004


	 
      Zero Nothing
     
    



13,July,2004


	 
      This will be my last post.  I am lying.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      I will make a shared blog where I post pictures with two other fellows.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      The show is a good show, I guess. I want it to be an hour of him turning on and off the lights while locking the door and walking in circles.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      I don't watch the show Monk, but i am watching it now.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      That post was pointless.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      The rumor about the man in the closet isn't true. I'm sorry.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      This will be the blog I put effort into. Since nobody reads any blogs on this site, and nobody makes comments, this doesn't matter. I say this begrudgingly.    a ha. ha ha. ha ha ha. ha ha ha ha.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      if one is expected to cross the street in such an amount of time, one must also like chilidogs.  a ha. ha ha. ha ha ha. hee.
    



14,July,2004


	 
      I wasted 4 blogs. I'm sorry.    WTF
    


13,July,2004


	 
      NET WT 4 OZ. (113g)
    


13,July,2004


	 
      If the ingredients seperate, a few vigorous shakes will restore the original mixture.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      KEEP CLOSED WHEN NOT IN USE    a bit fucking harsh, salt container.  A bit harsh.
    




30,July,2004


	 
         On one of the first days, there was light (or something).   Now there are giant isopods, and with them comes the end of human reign.  I wish it could be prevented, but not even Sean Connery in his Zardoz attire can stop this one.   
    


29,July,2004


	 
       Clinton, how we pine for you now.       If we all could just admit that we are racist a little bit...     
    


29,July,2004


	 
       &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
      &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    WAH YEES I DOOOOO!
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    SHAZAM DEMOCRATIC BIATCHES!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


27,July,2004


	 
      DON'T FUCK WITH THE BUNNY!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


27,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    karma 2.0&nbsp; urlLink   
    


27,July,2004


	 
         What The Fuck is up with that series?&nbsp; I dunno.&nbsp; The movie dunno.&nbsp; Nobody fuckin' knows.&nbsp;  
    


26,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    SCOOBY-FUCKING-DOO! IF THAT ISN'T THE BEE'S KNEES THEN I JUST CAN'T COMPREHEND WHAT IS! I NEVER LIKED THE PS2 BEFORE BUT NOW THAT I HEAR THE STUPID SLUTTY GIRL WHO I'VE WATCHED SUCK SOME GUYS DICK  LOVES  THE PS2, I MIGHT JUST THINK ABOUT PURCHASING ONE!  THANKS YOU INTERNET. THANKS YOU.   
    


26,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    unTItleyourFACE!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


26,July,2004


	 
      because it is  dancin' time        
    


23,July,2004


	 
      Chris Tucker starred in the Fifth Element.    He played a whiny radio host.  Then he did this for a while:     The End.  Seventy Six Outtie, LOL!     Bye kids! 
    


18,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    finish your doughnut, you  GREEDY BASTARD  FUCKASS  &nbsp; urlLink   
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The haunting continues&nbsp; urlLink   
    


15,July,2004


	 
      Ahhh, the sweet feeling of torn and tattered feet.&nbsp; &nbsp;   &nbsp; Just so ya know, the weird thing on the left is a Berimbao (pro: bedibow), the thing that looks like a sun is a Pandeira (tambourine, pro: pandéla) and the drum is a Atabaque (pro: atabaki).&nbsp; Go Capoeira!!! 
    


15,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Testing 'Hello'&nbsp; urlLink   
    


14,July,2004


	 
         
    


14,July,2004


	 
       
    


14,July,2004


	 
      Do celebrities use Kazaa? And if so, how much porn have you shared with them?
    


13,July,2004


	 
       urlLink The Sceams of Many Tortured Toads   All you sucker MCs best recognize. Not even Michael Bolton could top this tune!  Warning: May cause brief, psychological damage.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      Cool animals like the zebra melon should exist.  Here's an Amoeba with teeth - and a soul.  Woo.   
    


13,July,2004


	 
      In contrast to black and white, here is something colorful.                                                                                   - ACK 
    


13,July,2004


	 
      One might remember when everything in the world was black and white.  All you have to do it turn on the TV and switch to a channel showing old shows, and there's the proof.  This is my black and white tribute, getting rid of all that halabaloo about color.  Seems there's a bit of an octo fetish here too...     PS - the weird thing on the bottom is him spinning a plate on a stick.  FYI
    


13,July,2004


	 
      the skin is of an orange peel.  
    


13,July,2004


	 
       urlLink A Degree in Funk   A whymsical remix of a wonderful classic. Download it.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      Since this is, as of now, a place to archive old shit, here is some more old shit. Make sure you download the corrupt dr mario remix above, done by one Mr. Swan.      
    


13,July,2004


	 
         A bit more awe-inspiring than a fish in a bathrobe - although fishes in bathrobes are pretty awesome (like hotdogs! (Eddie Izzard!!)) - a Lunar Octopus for your enjoyment.
    


13,July,2004


	 
      I bring the world Angry pissed off bathrobe fish: Sleekversion1.1  
    


13,July,2004


	 
      SECRET WINDOW BROKEN: Johnny Depp reported crying  
    


15,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Deep in Moon Volcanoes, moonicorn larvae are born. Fiery eyed assassins of celestial proportion. Though fishy in appearance, they are demons at heart. A coal black heart that knows only one thing: to kill.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,August,2004


	 
      History is always fun,  especially  when by history you mean urban legend, and by urban legend you mean crap made up to sell cothing. Capitalism is grand, ain' it. Hitler knew it, and so should you.      Now, if only he wasn't a mass-mudering fuckhead... 
    



