
27,July,2004


    
       
         (For my princess whose love I shall forever chase)        &nbsp;  I long to see who you really are    &nbsp;  I have always cinched myself in the confines of your past   Wallowing in the puddle of memories long forgotten   I built myself a wall what denied any specter of the future,   And the present as well   Only the murky past that continues to envelope my being   Eating what's left of the devotion we sowed with seeds of love.    &nbsp;  I know the time shall come   When I have to rise from this abysmal pit of mud   (Before I drown in it completely)   To face the ghost that I myself had created,   Conquer it finally   And like the Berlin, my wall shall come down in shambles   Revealing a path to a promising tomorrow to be spent with you.    &nbsp;  It is then that I can see your entirety.   I only wish you'd still be there.    &nbsp;    The very first poem my fiance has ever written for me. We were still dating then. After 3 days, I said yes!! :)    
      


31,July,2004


    
       
       I have to go to the bookstore this weekend. For the longest time, I have been searching for the perfect journal. The same kind my bestfriend, Janet, gave me 3 years ago. I could still remember how I cried when I received that. The note inside read:    Farah girl, To remember all the good times we shared and all the bad times we've gone through. With the way you're coping up, you're making me proud more than ever!!!   Then at the upper right corner of that page, she posted one of our funny pics together (taken in one of those neoprint booths in sm city). I just hope I get to find one this weekend.       Also, I have been longing to go to Divisoria and Quiapo to get some beads. But just thinking of how far these places are, stops me. Besides, my dear dear hubby won't let me. (KJ as ever!). I want to make do with the little time I have alone. I want to be a tad domesticated. Harharhar!!! Maybe, next time...  
      


04,August,2004


    
       
         


05,August,2004


    
       
             It’s funny when you see yourself in someone else’s eyes. More so when you see yourself in someone else. Oftentimes before, I would wonder if it's possible to have someone act, think, feel exactly like you do. I never really believed in soulmates until I met Arthuz.      The moment I met him, I knew for a fact that I have already found my true north. My world suddenly turned upside down. There was peace and total bliss. And happiness and contentment.      I have been involved with a few men before, and unlike all of them, Arthuz never promised me the stars. He was a poet but I did not fall for his words. All these years, and until this very moment, he still proves his worth to me. Yes, he never promised me the stars but he wrought a garland of stars and placed it on my neck.       He kisses me good morning and hugs me to sleep. He brings me water when I get thirsty in the middle of the night. He makes sure I take my vitamins on time. He hurts when I hurt and he smiles when I smile. He gets mad when I start bitching but kisses my tears away the moment I cry. And I know that for as long as I would hold onto his hand, I will never fall. He is my guiding light. My wall. My home. He is my partner and my friend. My twilight. He is family to me.      My fate is intertwined with his. I am chained to my promise, to the vow that I will be making, before God and man, that I will be with him whatever happens. Come hell or high waters, I will stay with him. And we will see life through together. Because I know that our souls are linked by an unseen rope, pulling me wherever he goes.       He used to take my breath away. Now, he breathes life into me.   When I look into his eyes and I see my reflection, I couldn't help but sigh and say:  "I'm just so glad I came crashing into you".     * * * * * * * * * *    Wow!! I never thought I could still write an article. Well, this just goes to show that I don't need to be in pain to be able to write something. Maybe, I just need to try a little harder. I've never really had the chance to sit down and scribble down my thoughts. It has been a while since the last time I wrote something in my journal. I'm happy about this article. I hope you'll like it. The sun is up, I have to sleep!!!         
      


06,August,2004


    
       
       If I just do my thing and you so yours   We stand in danger of losing each other   And ourselves       I am not in this world to live up to your expectations     But I am in this world to confirm you     As a unique human being     And to be confirmed by you        We are fully ourselves only in relation to each other     The "I" detached from "Thou"     Disintegrates        I DO NOT FIND YOU BY CHANCE;     I FIND YOU BY AN ACTIVE LIFE     OF REACHING OUT       Rather than passively letting things happen to me   I can act intentionally to make them happy       I must begin with myself, true        But I must not end with myself        The truth begins with two        * * * * * * * * * *      One of Arthuz's many poems given to me as a gift. Written 18August02.    
      


07,August,2004


    
       
         "Be, we hav faced more difficult situations dan dis. We will nvr let go of d only gud thng we hav ryt nw.  I love u my Beatrice. Mor dan Dante evr luvd his.   Gudnyt!"        this was the text message i got from him one night after we fought big time. after reading this, my heart smiled.           having someone as loving and as understanding as the person i have now makes my life beautiful. and i just can't ask for more. *sigh*    
      


08,August,2004


    
       
             me, be and the beach.. how can you not enjoy Boracay?    
      


12,August,2004


    
       
             ANGER     1. Who did you last get angry with? myself 2. What is your weapon of choice? pen knife 3. Would you hit a member of the opposite sex? who wouldn't? 4. How about of the same sex? of course!! 5. Who was the last person who got really angry at you?like really, really, really angry? my hubby. just last sunday. darn mood swing. 6. What is your pet peeve? a lot 7. Do you keep grudges, or can you let them go easily? i have to say it outloud. it will not be me if i keep grudges. i am a very transparent person. when i'm mad, i kill. you can ask my friends.    SLOTH     1. What is one thing you're supposed to do daily that you haven't done in a while? do something more productive re: D-Day.. (slacker!!) 2. What is the latest you've ever woken up? a couple of hours. i just love to sleep.. :) 3. Name a person you've been meaning to contact, but haven't. my bestfriend Janet --

12,August,2004


    
       
          Turn your lights down low And pull your window curtains Oh let Jah moon come shining in Into our life again Sayin' oh it's been a long long long long time I kept this message for you girl But it seems I was never on time Still I wanna get through to you girl On time   I want to give you some love I want to give you some good good loving Oh I oh I oh I I want to give you some good good loving   Turn your lights down low Never try to resist oh no Oh let my love come tumbling in Into our life again Saying oh I love you And I want you to know right now Oh I love you And I want you to know right now Cause I, that I I want to give you some love   I want to give you some good good lovin I want to give you some love I want to give you some good good lovin   Turn your lights down low Never try to resist oh no Oh let my love come tumbling in   Into our life again       _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _     THIS IS THE SONG THAT KEPT US TOGETHER.. THROUGH THE YEARS..        THE SONG THAT WILL BE PLAYED ON OUR FIRST DANCE AS Mr. & Mrs. Arthuz Cloyd Dela Rosa :)       
      


13,August,2004


    
       
           


13,August,2004


    
       
       What's up with me and these survey thingies? It's 7 in the morning, I'm done with work.. just waiting for my buddy, Cheng. You see, we're going to the gym in a bit. Can't wait to go to the sauna. Just the thought of it excites me!! ;)       1. Grab the book nearest to you, turn to page 49, find line 5. Write down what it says:  Around this great circular depression runs a series of ledges, each of which Dante calls a CIRCLE [the INFERNO]    2. Stretch your left arm out as far as you can. What do you touch first?  my cell phone. (currently charging)    3. What is the last thing you watched on TV?  Lionel Ritchie and his adopter daughter Nicole in Oprah.    4. WITHOUT LOOKING, guess what the time is. 7:20 AM    5. Now look at the clock, what is the actual time? 7:11AM    6. With the exception of the computer, what can you hear?  Toni Braxton singing Bestfriend..    7. When did you last step outside? What were you doing? outside the office? hmmm.. i went home.    8. Before you came to this website, what did you look at? Friendster. MSN Messenger. my office email. my yahoo account. peyups.    9. What are you wearing?  my congo grill attire (khakis)    10. Did you dream last night?  i can't remember. i was too sleepy to dream.. make sense? ;)    11. When did you last laugh?  half an hour ago. before my superfriend xtine went home. nasa bully-mode na naman kasi ako kanina eh ;)    12. What is on the walls of the room you are in?  a poster of Beatles mounted on the wall    13. Seen anything weird lately?  hahahah. i won't tell.    14. Last movie you saw?  Spiderman!! :)    15. If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first?  a big house somewhere in the East, a jaguar x-type and a pair of manolo blahniks    16. Tell me something about you that I don't know:  i'm an ambidextrous.    17. If you could change one thing about the world, regardless of guilt or politics, what would you do?  i'd want people to stop fighting. i'm an advocate of world peace. (no bull.)    18. Do you like to dance? Yup. Hah!! Arthuz even bought a dance pad and a lotta Britney Spears CDs on PS2 so that I could practice my talent in dancing. Right, Be? ;)    19. George Bush: is he a power-crazy nutcase, or someone who is finally doing something that has needed to be done for years?  i plead the fifth. I know zilch about politics.    20. Imagine your first child is a girl, what do you call her?  shobe. i'm no chinese neither is he. we're both dark, round-eyed filipinos, but i just find it so darn cute.    21. Same question for a boy?  andrei. (kuya in the long run)    22. Would you ever consider living abroad? Yes. We're actually in the process of migrating abroad. We're just waiting for the wedding in March and we're off.. I'm kinda sad but I find comfort in knowing that wherever I may be, Be it in Timbuktu or Alaska, I'll be right beside the man I want to spend the rest of my life with..    
      


14,August,2004


    
       
             Cara before she turned 1.. With her Nanin in Manila Zoo.. Isn't she adorable??? She looks exactly like me when I was younger. I know I could very well pass as her mom. :)         Cara in one of her more recent pictures.. This was taken in Baguio City. With Tito Arthuz. She's grown to be mischievous but still very sweet, smart, funny and loving.           Still in Baguio City, this time with her Nanin (with me). I call this photo-op "me and my mini-me"..          _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _      friends, i'd like you to meet cara.. my angel. she's my brother's daughter. i love her like hell. she's so adorable. she can be pesky and many times, i have given up on her.. but at the end of the day, i'd realize she's a child and she deserves to act like one. and i'd remember my role in her life.. i miss her so much and i can't wait to see her next month. i know you still can't read darling though you have fooled me a few times that you know how to read already (smart kid!).. i love you, kulit. be a good girl to mom and dad and nice to kuya and tammie. 


14,August,2004


    
       
          We were in Xaymaca last night. It was nostalgic for me to be there. It has been close to 4 months now since we last visited the place. After our good friends,   Indio I   disbanded last Summer, we were never impelled to go back. What for?      But because we've got nowhere to go and we didn't want to spend another weekend at Seventy7 in New Manila (our almost-ultimate tambayan), we decided to give Xaymace another try. We watched BMR play. There were still a handful of familiar faces there. Plus the fact that the warmth of the staff has never changed. Francis, the bar discjock was beside us throughout the show. A few friends dropped by our table to say hi. It was a reunion of sorts.       I still miss Inkee and the rest of the gang. But things have to go on. Vic has decided to form a new band. Ian, I guess, decided to work full time in a recording company. All the rest are uber-busy rehearsing. Last we heard, they have found a vocalist to replace Vic. I'm not really sure but I'm still hoping things will be sunny again for Indio I.      We still text and call each other from time to time. But it ends there. After the group disbanded, our Saturdays have never been the same again. And will never be.      I so miss   Indio I.            SONG:  Let's Stay Together by Al Green... "  never leave you baby, whether times are good or bad happy or sad.. "    BOOK: I'm finishing up " In the presence of my enemies" by Gracia Burnham.    
      



