
24,July,2004


	 
      one of mine are smokes...I love to smoke...I think I've grown up to be a smoker...earlyist I remember smokin was my grampa....he had an old wood tobacco pipe...next would be when I lived with my dad and my brother (wasnt living with us) had a friend stayin in my room...so I musta was lookin threw a dresser an I found a metal pipe an sum green stuff in a baggie...didnt know what it was...but ended up gettin him kicked outta the house cause i told my brothers ex wife an blah...so I smoked for awhile durin the summer with a bunch of friends...prolly elementary school kids I think...stole smokes from dad so we could smoke ended up stealin beer too...that quit when dad asked where his smokes went tho...ended up quittin till I was about 16.

22,July,2004


	 
       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I had a love life once.......it got lost sumwhere a couple years ago....I have an ex that keeps runnin threw my mind....kinda funny they all run threw my head....either that means I haven't had many or I need to have more heh....So this ex'es name is heather...We dated on an off during highschool...prolly the closest thang to my first g.f....so were gonna call it a very immature&nbsp; childish relationship....Up down forwards backwards sideways inwards outwards blah....So right its a really f**ked up relationship...     &nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So the meat an taters of this whole problem with her is that I have stuff left undone involving her....as the story goes...I think we broke up for the 5th time...we had a couple of the same classes...I was tryin to get out of the classroom an she stopped me...and sed thoses famous words "I Love You"....and I can remember turnin to look at her and sed "what am I saposed to do about that?"....and walked right out the door....so here inlies the problem....so Yes I Love heather...problem yes.....an a man would say its all her fault...heh...but i'll say it was cause it was...:)...and its buggin the&nbsp;**** outta me           &nbsp;    
    


17,July,2004


	 
      Well, UKFC, I may call you ukfc, yes?&nbsp; You were right I should have gone to the party.&nbsp; It strikes me as I'm blocking out one of the possibly worst sitcoms ever, Everyone Loves Raymond, with my portable cd player and my 'photo booth'--that yes even sitting at a party full of egotistical wanna be artists would be better than this.  &nbsp; So credit where credit is due, you were right.&nbsp; Now I must go as my cd is skipping--and the canned laughter is creeping in.....  
    


16,July,2004


	 
      so I was sittin at work readin the paper from yesterday an see an article...about how they caught sum guy they named "mall rapist"...I read what this guy has done and made me wanna drive down to the jail an rip his balls out :)...that put me in a really bad mood...an now i'm just depressed...I wanted to do sumthang before i went to bed but it's no use I will sit here an look stupid...so I worked my friday night away.....I felt completely &nbsp;useless for atleast 2 hours:)...it felt like when I'm helpin my brothers....they usually do all the work an let me watch....1 if you dont do it their way they get mad.... an 2 they know everythang an can do it faster :)...so f**k em :)...I really dont like feelin useless...I like to work...but when I dont know what todo or sumone doesnt say what they want done, I stand around an look dumb...thats enough  
    


16,July,2004


	 
       So okay...second day around....will not babble like previous day..... heh...its friday I should be happy..should be starting my weekend right now....tho I sed "screw it an will work my friday night away....oh well life could be worse...so i'm tryin to figure out how to use this blog? eh...dont wanna improperly use it...sittin here in a dull chatroom....watching a scary movie....tryin to chat with lala.....she is my bestestfriend so if people read my work hehe i guess they will read alot about her :o)....so yea...so an ITT tech commercial is on t.v...i know must jump start a life eh....next week I plan a lil vacation to canada yayayay :o)....sumthang to look forward too...in the meaningless thang i call a life...lala is keepin me busy with everythang...she talks alot hehe but i still love her :op...so more about me.....jeepers creepers aint a bad movie....mase my friend from canada...the one i will be visitin an a couple other friends hehe...so must chat....laterz :)  
    


15,July,2004


	 
      just got home from work...so I started a blog eh? lala started one and i've always wanted one so i got one:o)....so i must find thangs to blog about an stuff :o)
    



