
31,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mommy, where are my socks, my feet are cold?"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


29,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Daddy, what are you doing down there??"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


29,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Oh, so cute.....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


29,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "What color are my eyes going to be ???"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


29,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Look Mommy, no training wheels.."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


27,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Latesha is certainly growing up......  Nadia and Hannah really enjoyed their afternoon with their  favorite cousin.....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


27,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Latesha is joining the girls for supper...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


27,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Cheeessssse"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


27,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara is having a good stretch (11 weeks old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


27,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    &quot;But Mom, I&#39;m so comfortable......&quot;&nbsp; urlLink   
      


22,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Our little "duckie" is sleeping...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


19,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah had a little accident riding her bike and she wants everyone to know it - LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
      


19,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mommy, do you think I have big toes???"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


19,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mmmmmmmm, that icecream looks delicious...."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


19,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Now I lay me down to sleep..."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "I could be a model........"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Do you really mean it Mom - I can have a puppy....."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Getting taller everyday... now 21 1/2 inches&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    What a beautiful baby.......&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Life can swing you any direction....."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Madison enjoys some time at the park with Nadia and Hannah&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Cousin Darrell holds Sara for the first time....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Nadia and her Daddy relaxing at Nanny's...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah's loves to play (5 years old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Madison, Hannah and Nadia love their Nanny !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    What a cutie (Madison 2 years old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A cuddle from cousin Stephanie (July 18th)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Ouch... Hannah, that hurts....."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Aunt Nicole reading a book to little Sara....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A bubble bath........&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara enjoying her mobile (10 weeks old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    She can't stay still !  At 8 weeks old Sara is already moving around by herself.  We put to sleep with her head at the top, but she always finds a way to turn around.......&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "That's hilarious........." (Sara at 8 weeks old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara getting a feeding from her Godmother Jill...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Aunt Evelyn and the girls on June 20th&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Looking adorable again...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara at 7 weeks old&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Daddy getting ready to bathe little Sara...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara at 5 weeks old relaxing in her "sitter" (a gift from Aunt Janet...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


18,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Do you really think I look like my daddy?"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Oh Mommy, aren't you tired of taking pictures of me"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "That's soooo funny........"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Do you really mean it?"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "What are you looking at ????"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    4 weeks into the world and already bored...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Quiet please, I'm taking a call on my little cellphone"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "I can feed my little sister all by myself...."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara at 4 weeks old&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "I'm sooooo cold........."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
        Following are some pictures from Hannah's Kindergarten Graduation that was held on June 21st.  
      


17,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Our little girl doing the calendar for her classmates......&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Receiving her award for "Always knowing right from wrong" !  Are they sure they have the right Hannah ??????????&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Singing for the audience...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The Pre-K and Kindergarten Class (and Nadia)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    The two Kindergarten Graduates - Hannah and Melanie&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Our teacher, Julie-Helene, is so much fun !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah thinks her Godmother is the GREATEST !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Best Pals Forever.......&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    What a cutie !!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Proud Poppy !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A proud Nanny !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Uncle Gerard and the girls...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Help Mommy, I can't hold her !"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Auntie Janet giving little Sara a feeding...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Poppy loves to tease...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
        Please check back often as I will try to update every couple of days.        


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Six days old and already loves the camera !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Nadia loves to show off her little sister...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Proud Daddy and new BIG sister !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    A new little angel in the family&nbsp; urlLink   
      


16,July,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah, Sara & Nadia having fun !&nbsp; urlLink   
      


11,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mom would you get me dressed - I'm cold....."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mommy's Little Alarm Clock"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Aren't they adorable???????&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah really loved all the games at the Bakeapple Festival.  She won at lots of them too....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Posing for a photo with the Bakeapple Festival Mascot in Forteau, Labrador...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Hannah and Nadia enjoying an afternoon with their friend Naomi...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Nadia and Hannah watching "their shows"...&nbsp; urlLink   
      


04,August,2004


    
       
      Hi Again,  For those of you who are wondering why all the pictures are not being shown (Jill that means you....), you can access them by clicking on the archives on the right side of this page.  All the previous pictures are under July Archives.  The way this thing is set up is that only the present month shows on the front page, all previous months are put into archives.  Hope you have no problem accessing them (when I tried, I had to open the link in a new window).  More later.......
      


03,August,2004


    
       
      Thanks to everyone that has visited our site.  It seems as if we have had quite a few visitors since we started.  I am trying to add more pictures every couple of days.  I'm hoping to start a new blog site soon with pictures of the Blanc Sablon area and hopefully with some news about the region.  When I get it up and running, I will email you with the address.  Sara is growing quite a bit everyday and she is already quite active.  She loves having her daddy to talk to her and she baby talks back to him.  She loves to have Hannah sing to her and loves to be held by Nadia.  The girls absolutely adore her.  Thanks again for visiting.
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Fun in the sun (it doesn't come out in Blanc Sablon often LOL)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "If I close my eyes will the waves go away???"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Oh Daddy, this is soooo much fun...!"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Daddy and his two "big" girls..&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Watch out Madison and Uncle Rick, the wave is going to get you..."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Let's go catch the waves..."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Oh daddy, the water is sooo cold.."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Little Madison loves exploring.....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Rick enjoying his afternoon at the beach....&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mommy, don't let anyone see me like this..."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    Sara loves her baths....... (12 weeks old)&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Looking at the world from a different view..."&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Mmmmmm, this candy tastes great!"&nbsp; urlLink   
      


01,August,2004


    
       
       urlLink    "Daddy, what are you doing to me?????"&nbsp; urlLink   
      



