
20,July,2004


	 
      I have 5 extremely goody frends during my P6 times... they are: Hui Chi Myself Xue Fen Serena and Wei Ting!haha...like the TMG we usually hang around...haha...now we all in different sch liao so less communication betweent us..but i realli miss the good and enjoyable times we had that time... Hui Chi's the mad(still) Myself also the mad(still) Xue Fen's the quiet and polite gal...(pretty) Serena's the farni&nbsp;1 and Wei Ting's the tall 1...haha...we usually do projects together 1 but always in the end never got started on the project coz&nbsp;we playing mah...haha..lol! I still remember that we broke the lock on Wei Ting's room's door!HAHA! in the end she had to tell her parents and go find the locksmith..lol!haha...realli miss the time we had together...maybe we could gather together 1 time and carry on laughing together again!TTS ALL! 
    


19,July,2004


	 
      hihi!!!let this be the first to be post out on my bloggy! haha...in my school...i have 10 best frends with 1 realli best frends among the ten! well...we are called the TMG which stands for 10 mad gals... my gang members are: ME(loretta), Cynthia, En Ci, Sheila, Ann, Sophia, Jess, Vanessa, Nellie and Eli...cool rite! Dis names are our "nicknames" to be called onli by TMG! Yep! we are current available except for Eli...she juz got a bf! cool! Sometimes we will go somewhere to hang out...like..going east coast to cycle, go watch movies...erm..juz hang out!   Recently we got ourselve a pledge..which im still not sure..its abt being a loyal servant! Inside theres sth like dis--

18,July,2004


	 
      GO DIS PLACE---

06,August,2004


	 
      WaT aN uLtImaTlY bOrInG dAe I hAd iN sCh ToDaE!!! Todae's the national day as well as the speech day so called "celebrations"! wat we did was juz stand there like a lifeless log or as idiot! its as if we are being punished!! ArGhZ!!i hate it..we still have to stand at attention when the 'guest-of-honour'  came..lame! We also sang some idiotic boring national day songs that we alreadi sang for abt..erm..as if..10 years! i can even hum the song whenever i want now! stupid day! i should had stayed at home instead of going to school! They never even take the attendance! Waste of my precious time! SiCkO!!  Yesterdae's cross country i got top 60!! HAHAHA! but i got all kinds of pain on my sickening body now!! hiaz..so tired..when i reached home i immediately lie down on my bed..YaWn!!ZzZ..  Tt's all i think..tata!;) 
    


03,August,2004


	 
      Todae dunno why...in a bad mood..sad........ I felt so left out in almost everything...a friend of mine made me upset..sob..then i felt so down..... almost all of my frends are in 3E2..so maybe thats why i felt so left out.. and...DAMN..i ate too much sweets during lesson time todae..but i never got caught..haha..but i gave some of my frends..and the moment i gave them the sweet and they started chewing it...haha..guess wat happen..haha..the teachers caught them..unlucky chaps..heZ.. I gAVEmyself a DAMN promise..i will reduce the amount of sweets from todae onwards...1st reason..--


