
24,July,2004


	 
      As blogs go, this is my deflowering. And as its been said, the first time is always memorable, but not necessarily  great. Here we go...  ---------- As if I didn't already have enough of a problem. Now, blogs.   I've known about them for quite some time but managed to resist the temptation to get involved, given my enduring state of life-chaos.  Until the day I did something I occasionally do for my own amusement.  I did a Google search on my name to see what all the other Lisa Palumbos who somehow managed to get their names on a web page were doing to maintain our cyber-ethos. (Curiously, musical and educational proclivities have afflicted more than just me.) There are three bona fide sources where the LP results are actually references to me: UNO Marketing Department Faculty Page, Tipitinas.com-where I interviewed my client/friend Sherman before his show, and my own web site.  That's how it always was until one day a few weeks ago when a new entry popped up and it was not one of the other LPs, but indeed, me.  It was one of those moments of ecstasy that occurs when you discover that another human being actually thinks enough of you to mention you by name on a published web page.  You're not there because you do some kind of work for someone else or because you cleverly populated all of your own web pages with meta tags and other references to yourself. (I didn't do that on my pages- Google picked up the copyright notices.)   I jumped to the link to see what this was about, and lo, I find via blog that my old pal and musicaliterary cohort David Oliver has once again chosen to be Saudimized in the Middle East.   Here are the archives containing the posting:  urlLink "

01,August,2004


	 
       Irk:   Grading, grading, grading.  Delight:  Being finished with grading.   Irk:  Typing.  Irk:  Browswer suddenly quitting after I had just typed a long blog entry without having saved it. (I know, I know. There are many ways around this.)  Irk:  Trying to remember HTML tags when I haven't published a web page using anything but Dreamweaver's WYSIWYG interface in years.   Delight:  Four guilt-free days of post-semester decompression spent doing little or nothing productive.  Delight:  Sleeping more than four hours a night. (Although I admit that my body has become so accustomed to the short shift that I actually feel better with less sleep than more.)  Delight:  Discovering that Netscape for Mac supports WYSIWYG blogging, so I don't have to remember those HTML tags for formatting, linking and inserting pictures. This means I'll be more likely than not get on with my blogging pursuits. But I think I'll take a nap first.   
     

    



