
26,July,2004


	 
      1. what are you doing now? checking all my acounts... 2. what were you doing before this? cramming for a chinese test 3. what are you thinking about now? why is "he" not online?!! arrgh! ;0) 4. what time is it? 5:22 5. what time did you sleep last night? around 2:00 6. what did you do last night? fixed my room and replied to all those who sent me text messages--

24,July,2004


	 
       Meet me in outerspace  We could spend the night, watch the earth come up  I've grown tired of that place, wont you come with me  We could start again  How do you do it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  Meet me in outerspace  I will hold you close, If your afraid of heights  I need you to see this place,  It might be the only way That I can show you how, it feels to be inside of you  How do you it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  How do you do it, make me feel like I do  You are stellar  You are stellar  How do you it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, its better than I ever knew  How do you do it, make me feel like I do  How do you do it, make me feel like I do, Yeah.    
     

    


24,July,2004


	 
       here's a joke...    why is money called "dough"?    answer: because we "knead" (need)&nbsp;it.    corny...;0)    bonus dumb question: if the dough is made into a fruit loaf,    does that make it a currants-y (currency)?    corny tlga..;0)    
     

    


23,July,2004


	 
       my siensi (teacher in chinese class) &nbsp;asked us what we would want to be when we grow up...   my classmate chi-an&nbsp;answered: " lao shr, wo chhang tah i hou si wang chuo gong1" (teacher,&nbsp;when i grow up, i want to ba a janitor.)--

23,July,2004


	 
      haha;0)   
     

    


23,July,2004


	 
       today is the "monthsary" of my friendship with michi.&nbsp;&nbsp;She thought of the idea of celebrating our friendship&nbsp;when i went with her to visit her former school last june 23. ;0) ain't she sweet? ;0)    wla lng..share ko lng...     
     

    


22,July,2004


	 
       today, i finally feeel like i'm shredding off that&nbsp;princess costume... i don't understand why people just love making&nbsp; stories about me... in school, i feel like i'm an actress with all those lights focused on me...i just hate the attention i get from everyone..it's like they know every single move i make...every little thing i do. they expect me to be someone i'm not...and just because i'm not to change my being, that doesn't give them the right to judge me.   there's a time to breakdown and a time to build up....  so to all those people who's been backstabbing me, here's what i got to say:   GET A LIFE! and pls stay away from mine cz nothing you say can ever make me falter in what i believe in...and if you think you're way better than me, well, just keep telling yourself that! ;0)  
     

    


22,July,2004


	 
        and now for the world's stupidest court cases:  a local lawyer tried to convince the court that it wasn't his client but his client's pet rooster who was guilty of owning illegal objects in the rooster's cage so the lawyer argued that they were actually the rooster's property and the rooster should be punished...;0)  uhm, yeah, and the dog ate our homework...;0)      
     

    


21,July,2004


	 
        i was struck when somebody approached me today and asked -- " why are you always so busy?" it made me think and i ended up with a conclusion that being busy for me is like a defense mechanism..im busy not because i should be but because i choose to be..it somehow helps me forget what my real problems are..having to worry about deadlines, things to do, etc. makes me feel better because i know that at least these problems,&nbsp; i believe, i&nbsp;can easily surpass... &nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;   later in the day, i came to realize a lot of things like...     &nbsp;   #1 sometimes i get sick of that "me first" attitude... and having to spend 8 hrs in school surrounded by people who believe that they should always be first, can really get you insane.. its tough to try to get along with people who like you&nbsp;but just love hating you whenever you achieve something they know they cant.&nbsp; i just want to be in a world where nobody will judge me...     &nbsp;   #2 the main problem&nbsp;of our society is apathy towards poverty and discrimination..     &nbsp;   #3 strange is really different from weird--

13,August,2004


	 
       Should you find yourself a victim of other people's bitterness, ignorance, smallness, or insecurities; remember things could be worst...you could be one of them.  
     

    


07,August,2004


	 
       my baby......hehehe ;0)      
     

    



