
28,July,2004


	 
      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Sun Jul 18 22:55:59 2004  mobynathan: easy  mobynathan: click the yellow dot to connect  Jaggonmaster: um  Jaggonmaster: what do mean  mobynathan: in the main window  Jaggonmaster: i have a greenconnected to a black  mobynathan: There's a little yellow circle at the bottom  Jaggonmaster: yeah  Jaggonmaster: to connected  Jaggonmaster: im talking to you on it now  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: cool  Jaggonmaster: uh  Jaggonmaster: how do i turn off aim  Jaggonmaster: ?  mobynathan: right click on it  Jaggonmaster: on what  Jaggonmaster: i closed it  *** mobynathan signed off at Sun Jul 18 22:59:36 2004.  Jaggonmaster: shit  *** Error while sending IM: Local privacy restriction - make sure this user is not being blocked  Jaggonmaster: shit  *** Error while sending IM: Local privacy restriction - make sure this user is not being blocked  *** mobynathan signed on at Sun Jul 18 23:02:02 2004.  Jaggonmaster: um   Jaggonmaster: its kind of annoying, when you msg me the aim box opens  mobynathan: yes, right click on the AIM icon in the lowerright  mobynathan: then click Exit or whatever  *** You have been disconnected. Sun Jul 18 23:04:17 2004.  *** mobynathan signed on at Sun Jul 18 23:04:29 2004.  *** You have been disconnected. Sun Jul 18 23:04:54 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Sun Jul 18 23:04:56 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Sun Jul 18 23:06:05 2004  Jaggonmaster: um, no  mobynathan: okay  Jaggonmaster: it doesnt say exit  Session Close (mobynathan): Sun Jul 18 23:07:38 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Sun Jul 18 23:09:01 2004  *** You have been disconnected. Sun Jul 18 23:11:06 2004.  *** mobynathan signed on at Sun Jul 18 23:11:16 2004.  Jaggonmaster: what?  mobynathan: nadda  Jaggonmaster: i seems that i can only talk to you if i have aim  Jaggonmaster: on  Jaggonmaster: im confused  mobynathan: that's f'ed up  mobynathan: It shouldn't be that  mobynathan: +way  Jaggonmaster: cant i just use trillian and nothing else?  mobynathan: Yes  mobynathan: I do  Jaggonmaster: how  mobynathan: Just keep AIM closed  Jaggonmaster: i tried tat  Jaggonmaster: s/tat/that/  mobynathan: Well it works for me  mobynathan: You must be doing something wrong  Jaggonmaster: i just closed it  Jaggonmaster: and you came up anyways  mobynathan: you have to CLOSE IT  mobynathan: Ctrl-Alt-Del it  Jaggonmaster: i hit the x button  mobynathan: that's not good enough  mobynathan: It goes down to the systray  mobynathan: Right click on the icon and select Exit  Jaggonmaster: what icon  Jaggonmaster: the yellow button  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: the AIM icon  mobynathan: right click on it  mobynathan: And select Exit  mobynathan: Second option from the bottom  Jaggonmaster: the second option is personal options  mobynathan: THE AIM ICON IN THE SYSTRAY  mobynathan: NOT THE ONE OF TRILLIAN  mobynathan: It's the AIM dude  Jaggonmaster: i dont have in the system tray  mobynathan: Then use Ctrl-Alt-Del  Jaggonmaster: i did, it gives me the options of closing aol, xchat, and trillian  mobynathan: go to the proccesses tab  mobynathan: processes  mobynathan: And select the one called aim.exe  mobynathan: End Task that  Jaggonmaster: there isnt one  Jaggonmaster: waol.exe  Jaggonmaster: aol.exe  Jaggonmaster: aolwbspd.exe  mobynathan: aol dot fucking exe  mobynathan: oh shit  mobynathan: don't close that  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: you have AOL  mobynathan: So...  mobynathan: I don't know what to tell ya  Jaggonmaster: msmsgs.exe  Jaggonmaster: whats that  mobynathan: Microsoft Messneger I belive  mobynathan: +e  Jaggonmaster: what program do you use for seeing your bandwidth  mobynathan: hmm  mobynathan: I don't  mobynathan: The Ctrl-Alt-Del menu works fine though  Jaggonmaster: i thought you had one  mobynathan: not really...  Jaggonmaster: talking to rachell  mobynathan: really?  mobynathan: 'boot what?  Jaggonmaster: huh?  mobynathan: Aboot what?  Jaggonmaster: nothin  mobynathan: ah  Jaggonmaster: spell radar backwards  mobynathan: radar  mobynathan: bitch  Jaggonmaster: sdrawkcab radar lleps  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: fun fun  Jaggonmaster: (ns)  mobynathan: (ns)?  Jaggonmaster: hmm, i think im gonna put some gun powder in a bottle and add a piece of paper to the top and light it on fire, and see if it explodes  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: do that  mobynathan: and tape record it too  Jaggonmaster: comma after it is needed  mobynathan: What?  Jaggonmaster: you needed a comma after it  mobynathan: no I didn't  Jaggonmaster: and tape record it, too  mobynathan: no, it's not needed  mobynathan: If you say it aloud  mobynathan: Tape record it too sounds better than Tape record it, too  Jaggonmaster: you should tape record it, too  mobynathan: fuck  mobynathan: j00  Jaggonmaster: what is s/ from?  mobynathan: Regular expressions  Jaggonmaster: it isnt programming lingu  mobynathan: Regexps are used in text editors and stuff  mobynathan: But lots of programmers know about them  Jaggonmaster: u got kicked  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: shouldn't you be in bed  mobynathan: no  mobynathan: fuck off  mobynathan: I don't go to bed  mobynathan: I'm just not allowed to use the computer  Jaggonmaster: you sound like mark  mobynathan: Mark  mobynathan: bleh  Jaggonmaster: he tells me to fuck off when i tell him to go to bed  mobynathan: I wonder why...  Jaggonmaster: he likes seeing me have sex  mobynathan: because he's gay?  Jaggonmaster: how much does park place cost?  mobynathan: hmm, 350 I think?  Jaggonmaster: thats whaT  i thought  Jaggonmaster: its 450  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: Boardwalk is 500 then  Jaggonmaster: ha ha  Jaggonmaster: should of shut up  mobynathan: suck it  Jaggonmaster: fucking jaggon  mobynathan: you are the jaggon  Jaggonmaster: actually, i was the jaggon, but now it seems that you are the jaggon  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: no  mobynathan: you are still the jaggon  mobynathan: You just asked who someone (Tiffany) was  Jaggonmaster: so  mobynathan: When clearly people should be asking that about you  Jaggonmaster: i didn't know that  mobynathan: So I didn't say ban  mobynathan: I said kick  Jaggonmaster: so  mobynathan: so  Jaggonmaster: what do you mean, you said kick?  mobynathan:   Perhaps not pure. Okay, I'm arguing with myself. Someone kick me.  Jaggonmaster: whos fault is that  mobynathan: I GOT BANNED ASSWIPE  mobynathan: I didn't say BAN  Jaggonmaster: well  Jaggonmaster: one guy banned you  Jaggonmaster: and the other kicked you  mobynathan: Yes L1quid  mobynathan: Wrong  mobynathan: rOn is set to autokick anyone who gets banned  mobynathan: when you get banned you can stay in the channel until you leave  mobynathan: Unless someone kicks you  mobynathan: You just can't -reenter- the channel  Jaggonmaster: but you cant see anything  Jaggonmaster: the new stuff  mobynathan: of course not  mobynathan: I'm not in the channel  mobynathan: I got kicked  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bbye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bye  Jaggonmaster: bey  Jaggonmaster: eybljfdkljf  Session Close (mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 00:44:06 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 00:44:17 2004  mobynathan: huh?  mobynathan: later  mobynathan: then  Jaggonmaster: oh, i thought you were off  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hey  Jaggonmaster: horney toad  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hid  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: hi  mobynathan: no I'm here  *** You have been disconnected. Mon Jul 19 00:45:09 2004.  Jaggonmaster: um  Jaggonmaster: i have been disconnected  Jaggonmaster: i thought you were supposed to be off at midnight  *** mobynathan signed on at Mon Jul 19 00:47:10 2004.  Jaggonmaster: hello  mobynathan: what  Session Close (mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 00:47:45 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 00:47:51 2004  Jaggonmaster: pwned.nl  mobynathan: I don't trust that url  Jaggonmaster: its funny  Jaggonmaster: its a little movie  mobynathan: I'm downloading some music off Tiffany  Jaggonmaster: who sets a date for marriage  mobynathan: eh?  mobynathan: WASTE  mobynathan: rocks  Jaggonmaster: what in the hell are you talking about  mobynathan: WASTE  Jaggonmaster: one who sets there marriage in advance is desperate  Jaggonmaster: meow  mobynathan: woof  Jaggonmaster: your still on  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: fuck it  Jaggonmaster: aren't your parents going to be pissed  mobynathan: they don't know  mobynathan: so  mobynathan: oh well  Jaggonmaster: oh hell  mobynathan: that's hard to read  Jaggonmaster: yup  Jaggonmaster: how aboot that  mobynathan: that's okay  Jaggonmaster: and this  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: that's splendid :)  Jaggonmaster: (Link: http://technewslive.com/?doom3)http://technewslive.com/?doom3  mobynathan: 03-Aug-2004 man  *** You have been disconnected. Mon Jul 19 01:28:34 2004.  Jaggonmaster: um, am i talking to you?  *** mobynathan signed on at Mon Jul 19 01:30:54 2004.  Jaggonmaster: heh  Jaggonmaster: don't click on that  mobynathan: what?  mobynathan: I didn't  Jaggonmaster: good  Jaggonmaster: im not that mean  mobynathan: Maybe you are  Jaggonmaster: um, save that link  mobynathan: What is it?  Jaggonmaster: and give it to mark the next time you talk to him  Jaggonmaster: he'll trust you  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: hahaha  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: What is it?  Jaggonmaster: click it  mobynathan: does it crash your browser or is it just something nasty?  Jaggonmaster: both  mobynathan: hm  Jaggonmaster: its gay pr0n that just keeps coming up and you have to close it  Jaggonmaster: its fucking gross  Jaggonmaster: fucked up  mobynathan: hah  Jaggonmaster: the most fucked up thing i have ever seen  mobynathan: lol  Jaggonmaster: and it says our lawyer has told us to warn you   Jaggonmaster: you can only see it flash  Jaggonmaster: it twirls around the screen  mobynathan: goatse.cx  mobynathan: have you ever seen goatse.cx  Jaggonmaster: and some guy keeps saying hi everyone im looking at gay porno  mobynathan: There's this guy  Jaggonmaster: no  mobynathan: Who is stretching open his asshole  mobynathan: It's like 6 inches wide  mobynathan: fucking sick  Jaggonmaster: yeah  Jaggonmaster: there was a guy doing that  mobynathan: You've seen it?  Jaggonmaster: i guess so  mobynathan: ha  mobynathan: it was probably from goatse.cx then  Jaggonmaster: wouldn't that kill you  mobynathan: goatse.cx is closed now  Jaggonmaster: good  mobynathan: for some reason  mobynathan: Oh well  mobynathan: Good that it's gone for the world I guess :)  Jaggonmaster: almost 2 hours over the limit  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: I'm gonna stay until futurama I think  Jaggonmaster: bah  Jaggonmaster: you bad  Jaggonmaster: your  mobynathan: fuck it  Jaggonmaster: hi  mobynathan: hi  Jaggonmaster: did you find out why you cant use the computer  Jaggonmaster: wrong hi channel  mobynathan: Oh I know why  mobynathan: It's because I sleep in too late  Jaggonmaster: pr0n?  Jaggonmaster: oh  Jaggonmaster: so wake up   Jaggonmaster: earlier  mobynathan: So they tell me I'm not supposed to use the computer after 12am  Jaggonmaster: don't spam  mobynathan: I can't because then I'm tired  mobynathan: I hate being tired  Jaggonmaster: take a shower  mobynathan: I'm not spamming  Jaggonmaster: wrong person  Jaggonmaster: eat an apple  mobynathan: sex  Jaggonmaster: no, i think that would make you tired  mobynathan: sex is cool though  mobynathan: I have 3.07gb of music  Jaggonmaster: how many hours is that  mobynathan: 2 days, 2 hours, 33 minutes, 36 seconds  Jaggonmaster: how many songs is that  mobynathan: Machinae Supremacy rawk  mobynathan: 772  mobynathan: What ya think?  mobynathan: Small isn't it?  Jaggonmaster: your back in  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: :'D  mobynathan: What/  Jaggonmaster: (duck)  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: trillian  Jaggonmaster: whats the principals name in ferris buller  Jaggonmaster: nm  mobynathan: Hmm  mobynathan: Rooney  Jaggonmaster: yeah  mobynathan: That's it  mobynathan: Ed Rooney  Jaggonmaster: how much memory does a movie take up?  mobynathan: er  mobynathan: disk space?  mobynathan: 800mb or so  Jaggonmaster: on the computerr  mobynathan: If you mean a full-length good quality movie  Jaggonmaster: yes  mobynathan: yep  mobynathan: 700-1gb usually  *** mobynathan signed off at Mon Jul 19 02:11:44 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 02:13:06 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Mon Jul 19 23:04:02 2004  Jaggonmaster: can gmail use outlook?  mobynathan: not yet  mobynathan: You mean more like can Outlook use Gmail though I think  Jaggonmaster: nate  Jaggonmaster: give mark that link  mobynathan: yaha  mobynathan: ah  mobynathan: I can't  mobynathan: I'm not that mean  Jaggonmaster: why?  Jaggonmaster: well, then give me the link  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: (Link: http://technewslive.com/?doom3)http://technewslive.com/?doom3  Jaggonmaster: :)  Jaggonmaster: please let him click it  mobynathan: (Link: http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/bloody.jpg)http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/bloody.jpg  Jaggonmaster: um  Jaggonmaster: no?  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: it's not bad  mobynathan: I promise  Jaggonmaster: thats lame  mobynathan: you're lame  Jaggonmaster: no  *** jaggonmaster wants to directly connect.  *** mobynathan is now directly connected.  mobynathan: wtf  mobynathan: I keel you  mobynathan: if you send anything gross  Jaggonmaster: hi  Jaggonmaster: whats directconnecting?  mobynathan: you can send pictures to me now  Jaggonmaster: how?  mobynathan: figure it out  *** Error while sending IM: Request denied  Jaggonmaster: i wonder if mark clicked it?  mobynathan: I don't think so  Jaggonmaster: why  Jaggonmaster: he's away  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: he went to sleep  Jaggonmaster: sllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllleep?  mobynathan: yes?  Jaggonmaster: si sen~or  Jaggonmaster:    Jaggonmaster: mobynathan is typing  Jaggonmaster: very slowly  Jaggonmaster: no hablo espanol  mobynathan: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: aha  Jaggonmaster: ah  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: ha  Jaggonmaster: mobynathan is typing . . .  mobynathan: I'm not typing  Jaggonmaster: no you arent  mobynathan: Right  mobynathan: I'm not  mobynathan: I like music  Jaggonmaster: gollum gollum  mobynathan: MY PRECIOUS  Jaggonmaster: spiderman 2 rocks  mobynathan: yeah that's what I hear  Jaggonmaster: i mean the game  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: Didn't hear anything about that  Jaggonmaster: germ banned me, for no reason  mobynathan: What'd you say before it?  Jaggonmaster: i didn't say anything  Jaggonmaster: i just joined  Jaggonmaster: and then got banned  mobynathan: hmm  mobynathan: dunno  Jaggonmaster: i said "no hablo ingles" in #xbox-linux and this guy believed me  Jaggonmaster: and asked his question in spanish  mobynathan: haha  Jaggonmaster: :-)  mobynathan: Lamers  Jaggonmaster: whos the lead singer in yes?  mobynathan: No idea  mobynathan: Never even heard of them  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: pensi  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penis  Jaggonmaster: penissssssssssssssssssssssssssss  mobynathan: stop  mobynathan: annoying  mobynathan: me  Jaggonmaster: YES, MAJOR CUNTAGE  Jaggonmaster: IM LEAVING  Jaggonmaster: BYE BYE  Session Close (mobynathan): Tue Jul 20 00:10:03 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Tue Jul 20 02:51:17 2004  Jaggonmaster: shouldn't you be in bed  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: I'm going to brush my teeth then go  mobynathan: I was watching TV and didn't disconnect  Jaggonmaster: yes, major cuntage  mobynathan: bitch  mobynathan: die  *** mobynathan signed off at Tue Jul 20 02:57:10 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Tue Jul 20 02:57:13 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Wed Jul 21 02:14:05 2004  Jaggonmaster: gollum gollum  mobynathan: yar  Jaggonmaster: gi matey  mobynathan: gi?  Jaggonmaster: matey?  mobynathan: blah  mobynathan: TV  mobynathan: bye  *** mobynathan signed off at Wed Jul 21 02:32:54 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Wed Jul 21 02:33:07 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Thu Jul 22 02:15:18 2004  mobynathan: (Link: http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/hiddeninside.jpg)http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/hiddeninside.jpg  mobynathan: RAWK, I do  Jaggonmaster: how do you make scripts for irc?  mobynathan: learn a scripting language  mobynathan: Why do you want a script?  mobynathan: What for?  mobynathan: Like my picture?  Jaggonmaster: ugly shit, like reaper527's ugly ass words  mobynathan: the colors?  Jaggonmaster: yeah  mobynathan: You want it to do that automatically?  Jaggonmaster: and larger fonts  mobynathan: I'm sure there are scripts out there already  Jaggonmaster: no  mobynathan: hahahah!  Jaggonmaster: like  mobynathan: No larger fonts on IRC  Jaggonmaster: i want to type it  Jaggonmaster: yeah  Jaggonmaster: there is  Jaggonmaster: nghtshd  mobynathan: nope  mobynathan: One font size only  Jaggonmaster: always sends me yes major cuntage in huge fonts  mobynathan: hm  mobynathan: Must be some bug or something  mobynathan: I'm pretty sure there isn't a way to send fontsize info  mobynathan: maybe EFnet supports it or something  mobynathan: never seen it before  Jaggonmaster: am i still banned from nullsoft?  mobynathan: hm, I"ll check  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: is germ's nick germ?  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: he's away  mobynathan: for like three hours  mobynathan: Here he comes  Jaggonmaster: i should find an ircop and get him banned  mobynathan: To snuff the rooster  mobynathan: haha!  mobynathan: dude  mobynathan: Why?  mobynathan: First off  mobynathan: That network's incredibly small  mobynathan: #Nullsoft is like THE channel there  Jaggonmaster: 1 irc op  mobynathan: how do you check again?  Jaggonmaster: it tells you when you log onto the server  mobynathan: oh yeah  mobynathan: well  mobynathan: time for TV  Jaggonmaster: see yah  mobynathan: bye  *** mobynathan signed off at Thu Jul 22 02:26:50 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Thu Jul 22 02:26:54 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Thu Jul 22 20:10:25 2004  Jaggonmaster: YES, MAJOR CUNTAGE  Jaggonmaster: hello?  mobynathan: what?  Jaggonmaster: i found that ircop  mobynathan: who is it?  mobynathan: Picasso?  Jaggonmaster: slush  mobynathan: THEMike?  Jaggonmaster: slush  Jaggonmaster: slush  mobynathan: slush?  Jaggonmaster: yeah  mobynathan: wtf is that?  Jaggonmaster: he was on the beastieboys  mobynathan: lame  Jaggonmaster: i'm pretty sure its slush  Jaggonmaster: he said "you" can come in the beastie boys and talk about boobs and shit  mobynathan: [07:54:26pm] --- 1 :IRC Operators online  mobynathan: [08:34:08pm] --- slush :No such nick/channel  Jaggonmaster: maybe there is another  mobynathan: I'm almost positive it's not him  Jaggonmaster: it may be tpk, as well  mobynathan: nah  mobynathan: It's someone in #Nullsoft, I bet ya any money  Jaggonmaster: ill get in nullsoft when i get my isp changed  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: but probably get banned again :)  Jaggonmaster: im gonna pm him now  mobynathan: Germ?  Jaggonmaster: yeah  mobynathan: good luck  Jaggonmaster: (&)  mobynathan: Hm?  mobynathan: And?  Jaggonmaster: i didn't do it yet  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: let me know when you do  Jaggonmaster: i'm talking to him now  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: what's he saying? ;)  Jaggonmaster: not much  mobynathan: [08:45:27pm] --- Germ sets modes [#nullsoft -bbb *!*@aquarium-18.mmc.ro *!*@62.53.76.120 *!*@dsl-lprgw4j56.dial.inet.fi]    [08:45:33pm] --- Germ sets modes [#nullsoft -bb *!id1128@195.182.95.* *!*@c-24-118-191-158.mn.client2.attbi.com]  mobynathan: You're the only ban left  Jaggonmaster: i was banned for a week last time  Jaggonmaster: can you get on irc.ircnet.net?  mobynathan: I've never been banned that long, I don't think  mobynathan: Yes  mobynathan: or actually  mobynathan: I haven't tried yet today  mobynathan: yes, I can  mobynathan: I always can  Jaggonmaster: what do you do?  Jaggonmaster: --- Looking up irc.ircnet.net..    --- Connecting to irc.ircnet.net (216.115.95.70) port 6667..    --- Connected. Now logging in..    --- Please wait while we process your connection.    % Servicing ident request from 216.115.95.70    --- Closing Link: supertool[me@172.163.6.7] (Unauthorized connection)    --- Disconnected (Remote host closed socket).  mobynathan: I don't do anything  Jaggonmaster: unauthorized connection?  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: google for help about that  Jaggonmaster: what is it  mobynathan: no, I'm on it :)  mobynathan: [08:48:53pm] --- Looking up irc.ircnet.net...    [08:48:56pm] --- Connecting to irc.ircnet.net (216.115.95.70) port 6667..    [08:48:58pm] --- Connected. Now logging in..    [08:49:02pm] --- Please wait while we process your connection.    [08:49:04pm] % Servicing ident request from 216.115.95.70    [08:49:07pm] --- Welcome to the Internet Relay Network Nate!nate@205-162-139-103.surferie.net    [08:49:07pm] --- Your host is irc1.us.ircnet.net, running version 2.11.0a10    [08:49:07pm] --- This server was created Sat Jul 10 2004 at 12:37:28 EDT    [08:49:07pm] --- irc1.us.ircnet.net 2.11.0a10 aoOirw abeiIklmnoOpqrRstv  Jaggonmaster: i'll check the xcat faq  Jaggonmaster: nothing  mobynathan: yes  mobynathan: I told you  mobynathan: Google search  mobynathan: But no  Jaggonmaster: how would i google that  mobynathan: omfg  Jaggonmaster: i'll be back in a bit  Session Close (mobynathan): Thu Jul 22 21:00:29 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Fri Jul 23 22:29:29 2004  Jaggonmaster: what mozilla should i dl?  Jaggonmaster: ({)(})  mobynathan: um  mobynathan: just a second  mobynathan: (Link: http://ftp.mozilla.org/pub/mozilla.org/mozilla/releases/mozilla1.8a2/mozilla-win32-1.8a2-installer.exe)http://ftp.mozilla.org/pub/mozilla.org/mozilla/releases/mozilla1.8a2/mozilla-win32-1.8a2-installer.exe  Jaggonmaster: it's gonna take a while  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: i'm downloading that karaoke thing also  mobynathan: What thing?  mobynathan: gay.nsv?  Jaggonmaster: it's for the #karaoke shows  Jaggonmaster: The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the selfish and the tyranny of evil men. Blessed is he, who in the name of charity and good will, shepherds the weak through the valley of darkness, for he is truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children. And I will strike down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger those who would attempt to poison and destroy my brothers. And you will know my name is the Lord when I lay my vengeance upon thee.  mobynathan: What the hell is that?  Jaggonmaster: pulp fiction  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: I've never seen that :(  Jaggonmaster: (food)  mobynathan: okay  Jaggonmaster: :-$  mobynathan: sex  Jaggonmaster: (Link: http://www.garnersclassics.com/good99.htm)http://www.garnersclassics.com/good99.htm  mobynathan: I don't click links  Jaggonmaster: it isn't bad  mobynathan: Especially from you :)  *** jaggonmaster wants to directly connect.  *** mobynathan is now directly connected.  *** mobynathan direct connection is closed.  *** jaggonmaster wants to directly connect.  *** mobynathan ignores request; no connection was made.  Session Close (mobynathan): Fri Jul 23 23:10:13 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Sat Jul 24 02:08:04 2004  Jaggonmaster: wanna spam with my group?  mobynathan: nope  Jaggonmaster: its so much fun  Jaggonmaster: its on efnet  Jaggonmaster: huh huh  Jaggonmaster: i know you hate efnet  Jaggonmaster: come on  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: nah  mobynathan: I don't spam  mobynathan: No matter how much I hate something  Jaggonmaster: its fun  Jaggonmaster: randomly pick a channel and spam it  mobynathan: no thansk  mobynathan: thanks  Jaggonmaster: die bitch  *** mobynathan signed off at Sat Jul 24 02:27:45 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Sat Jul 24 03:02:48 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Sun Jul 25 23:09:51 2004  Jaggonmaster: yo  mobynathan: hi bitch  Jaggonmaster: thats easier  Jaggonmaster: how much is memory is python?  mobynathan: I don't know  mobynathan: Because that's not a valid question  mobynathan: If you asked how big it is, I'd know what you meant  mobynathan: Not that I didn't  mobynathan: But I like to bust your bawls  mobynathan: It's less than 10mb as I've said before  Jaggonmaster: bitch  mobynathan: I want to get the AIM screen name "omgtehpwn"  Jaggonmaster: gay  Jaggonmaster: some guy told me how to get 2gb from msn  Jaggonmaster: its a bug  mobynathan: nah  mobynathan: leet  Jaggonmaster: huh?  mobynathan: like me  Jaggonmaster: i've got 2gb from gay mail  mobynathan: 2gb?  mobynathan: of email storage?  Jaggonmaster: yes  mobynathan: What the hell are you talking about?  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: hotmale  Jaggonmaster: i'm lost  Jaggonmaster: i have 2gb on gmail  Jaggonmaster: you can get 2gb on msmessenger  mobynathan: (Link: http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/thehole.jpg)http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/pictures/thehole.jpg  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: you said fucking MSN  mobynathan: go away  Jaggonmaster: why?  mobynathan: 2gb of WHAT?  Jaggonmaster: email storage  mobynathan: MSN Messenger != EMAIL  mobynathan: gah  Jaggonmaster: yes  Jaggonmaster: its the same thing  mobynathan: I am so lagged  Jaggonmaster: i noticed  mobynathan: this is gay  Jaggonmaster: i just pinged you  Jaggonmaster: still no reply  Jaggonmaster: ch   --- Ping reply from Nate : 57.50 second(s)  Jaggonmaster: :O  mobynathan: fucking dialup  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: hell  mobynathan: I am teh lagmastah  Jaggonmaster: yup  Jaggonmaster: :cp  mobynathan: wtf  Jaggonmaster: :  Jaggonmaster: :I  Jaggonmaster: :v  mobynathan: I'm lagged so bad  Jaggonmaster: stop dling pr0n you sick  Jaggonmaster: o  mobynathan: by a minute  mobynathan: at least  mobynathan: it varies to over two minutes  mobynathan: You've been banned for like... a week  Jaggonmaster: on what?  Jaggonmaster: nullsoft  Jaggonmaster: i didn't even join there  mobynathan: I'm uploading a log from #Pascal  mobynathan: and not downloading anything  mobynathan: no  mobynathan: oh yes  mobynathan: On #Nullsoft  mobynathan: 19-Jul-2004 is the ban date  mobynathan: [11:33:09pm] --- #nullsoft Banlist: Sun Jul 25 19:38:10 *!*gtaidol@65.75.167.* furan!furan@ript.net    [11:33:09pm] --- #nullsoft Banlist: Fri Jul 23 23:55:06 *!*shoutcast*@* Germ!~germ16@cs2416269-50.jam.rr.com    [11:33:09pm] --- #nullsoft Banlist: Mon Jul 19 21:23:00 *!*@*ipt.aol.com Germ!~germ16@cs2416269-50.jam.rr.com  mobynathan: I hate furan  mobynathan: Fuckin' fag  Jaggonmaster: man  Jaggonmaster: your really lagged  Jaggonmaster: i didn't even join though  Jaggonmaster: funny  mobynathan: But I hate liquid more  mobynathan: Fucking L1quid  mobynathan: He's just a dick  mobynathan: Nothing else about him  mobynathan: Everyone else there is tolerable  mobynathan: I reckon  mobynathan: I know  mobynathan: It's fuckin' hell  mobynathan: Don't even upload anything with dialup ever  mobynathan: Download doesn't even come CLOSE to lagging you this much  mobynathan: I'm gonna reconnect after this upload is done to get around teh ban (I got banned)  mobynathan: :)  Jaggonmaster: stop the laggage  mobynathan: My upload oughta be almost done soon  mobynathan: As soon as the upload's done  Jaggonmaster: i hate you  mobynathan: Why's that?  Jaggonmaster: you lag so much  Jaggonmaster: and then everything comes at once  mobynathan: (Link: http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/#pascal.rar)http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/#pascal.rar when it's done  mobynathan: You can download and read it  mobynathan: Goes back to 2001 I think  Jaggonmaster: good  mobynathan: Those were the good old day's of #Pascal  mobynathan: I know  mobynathan: It's awful  mobynathan: I've never experienced lag this bad before :)  mobynathan: It's got a bit better?  mobynathan: hm  mobynathan: I don't know   mobynathan: Seems less worse now  mobynathan: I wrote tom a snailmail letter  Jaggonmaster: bah  mobynathan: I wonder if he'll write back  mobynathan: I love Germs by Weird Al  mobynathan: You know who that's a style-parody of?  mobynathan: Nine Inch Nails  Jaggonmaster: yes  Jaggonmaster: i know  Jaggonmaster: i sold that cd  Jaggonmaster: for like  mobynathan: OMFG  mobynathan: This upload is only about 2/3 done  mobynathan: :(  Jaggonmaster: 3 bucks  mobynathan: I thought it was almost done  mobynathan: ha  mobynathan: Nine Inch Nails are creepy  mobynathan: Picture yourself in a boat on a river  mobynathan: With tangerine trees and maramalade skies  mobynathan: Somebody calls you, you answer quite slowly  Jaggonmaster: h  Jaggonmaster: e  Jaggonmaster: l  Jaggonmaster: l  Jaggonmaster: o  mobynathan: ell  mobynathan: sex  mobynathan: h  mobynathan: ow  mobynathan: a  mobynathan: r  mobynathan: e  mobynathan: y  mobynathan: o  mobynathan: u  mobynathan: t  mobynathan: o  mobynathan: d  Jaggonmaster: ay  Jaggonmaster: all right, this is gay, what was i thinking, everyone, back to the pile  mobynathan: THEY TOOK UR JAERBS!  Jaggonmaster: te to r je  mobynathan: eh?  Jaggonmaster: thats how the last guy sounds  Jaggonmaster: it makes no sense  Jaggonmaster: hey bitch  Jaggonmaster: why can't i get on pascal?  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: pickles  mobynathan: I mean  mobynathan: wtf  mobynathan: Pickles?  Jaggonmaster: laggage bitch  Jaggonmaster: stfu  mobynathan: I don't know  mobynathan: What does it say mang?  mobynathan: Jagaru davah  mobynathan: yes quite  Jaggonmaster: its irc.ircnet.net  Jaggonmaster: right  Jaggonmaster: ?  Jaggonmaster: ?  Jaggonmaster: --- Looking up irc.ircnet.net..    --- Connecting to irc.ircnet.net (216.115.95.70) port 6667..    --- Connected. Now logging in..    --- Please wait while we process your connection.    % Servicing ident request from 216.115.95.70    --- Closing Link: supertool[me@172.174.230.126] (Unauthorized connection)    --- Disconnected (Remote host closed socket).  mobynathan: try another server  mobynathan: irc1.us.ircnet.net or something  mobynathan: I'll find it  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: guess what   mobynathan: try the one I said  mobynathan: above  Jaggonmaster: i got killed from efnet yyesterday  Jaggonmaster: :)  Jaggonmaster: nope  Jaggonmaster: didnt work  mobynathan: cool  Jaggonmaster: wtf  mobynathan: irc2.us.ircnet.net ? :)  mobynathan: you can always get a bouncer somewhere  Jaggonmaster: i didn't get anyof that  Jaggonmaster: weird  mobynathan: If you know the right people  mobynathan: I had a bouncer  mobynathan: But quit using it  mobynathan: wtf what?  Jaggonmaster: nope  mobynathan: Any of what?  Jaggonmaster: didn't work  mobynathan: Hm you have to explain more because everything's out of context due to lag  Jaggonmaster: i only got the server you told me to use  Jaggonmaster: on trillian  Jaggonmaster: i got it on aim  Jaggonmaster: weird  mobynathan: Did you get the stuff about bouncers?  mobynathan: oh, yes  mobynathan: That is weird  Jaggonmaster: yah, about how you can always get a good bounce  Jaggonmaster: well i didn't  Jaggonmaster: i love the thundercats  mobynathan: Who are they?  mobynathan: Find someone with a linux box  mobynathan: Ask them for a bouncer  Jaggonmaster: what is a bouncer?  Jaggonmaster: and what do you mean ?  Jaggonmaster: xbox-linux  mobynathan: It's a connection to an IRC server  mobynathan: But it acts as it's own tiny little IRC server-type for you  mobynathan: A Linux box == a linux computer  Jaggonmaster: bah  mobynathan: box doesn't necessarily mean Xbox  Jaggonmaster: your gonna have to say it in english  mobynathan: You connect to the bouncer with your IRC client  mobynathan: I am  mobynathan: It's easy  mobynathan: The bouncer connects to an IRC server... you connect to the bouncer, and you use it like an IRC server  Jaggonmaster: and where is a bouncer?  mobynathan: It's on a computer, running as a program  mobynathan: I have one on aiwendil.mine.nu  mobynathan: That is connected to IRCnet  mobynathan: Aiwendil gave it to me, of course  Jaggonmaster: hey  mobynathan: nope you can't use it :)  Jaggonmaster: um  Jaggonmaster: free ipod?  Jaggonmaster: have you heard of it  mobynathan: where at?  mobynathan: there's lots of free iPods things right now  mobynathan: iPods suxx0r though  Jaggonmaster: its fuckin free  mobynathan: 150 Connecting to port 8190    226-1069.5 Mbytes free disk space    226-File successfully transferred    226 4890.353 seconds (measured here), 0.77 Kbytes per second    ftp: 3869763 bytes sent in 4888.52Seconds 0.79Kbytes/sec.     mobynathan: omfg  Jaggonmaster: have you heard of the one where you have 5 people  Jaggonmaster: sign a petition?  mobynathan: nope I haven't  mobynathan: unlagged  mobynathan: thank God  mobynathan: one and one and one is three  mobynathan: (Link: http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/%23pascal.rar)http://aiwendil.mine.nu/nate/%23pascal.rar  mobynathan: go ahead and download  Jaggonmaster: what is it?  mobynathan: 20.4mb of #Pascal logs from 2001 something  mobynathan: to 2002 something  Jaggonmaster: holly hell  mobynathan: Fun stuff  Jaggonmaster: hmm  Jaggonmaster: i'm gonna get us  Jaggonmaster: a couple of ipods  Jaggonmaster: :)  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: do it  mobynathan: I'll sign your petition  Jaggonmaster: yup  Jaggonmaster: when you sign  Jaggonmaster: it  Jaggonmaster: you get  Jaggonmaster: one  mobynathan: Can I get a url?  mobynathan: to this  Jaggonmaster: and you have to get 5 people to sign it  Jaggonmaster: im not done yet  mobynathan: Because I'm not quite sure I believe it  Jaggonmaster: me neither  Jaggonmaster: but   Jaggonmaster: i'm talking to a guy that i can trust  mobynathan: hm, are you sure about that?  Jaggonmaster: he's on gmail  Jaggonmaster: and ive been talking to him for a few weeks  Jaggonmaster: and he just brang it up  Jaggonmaster: :(  mobynathan: I shall join  Jaggonmaster: join what  mobynathan: #Gmail  mobynathan: Where is this guy?  Jaggonmaster: wait  Jaggonmaster: i gotta see it  mobynathan: See what?  Jaggonmaster: if it's real  Jaggonmaster: cause i need  Jaggonmaster: you to sign  Jaggonmaster: up to me  mobynathan: Okay  mobynathan: well hurry up  mobynathan: It's probably fake anyway  mobynathan: some pyramid scam or something  mobynathan: haha  mobynathan: I'm not seeing any proof  mobynathan: (Link: http://www.neilturner.me.uk/2004/Jul/16/a_free_ipod.html)http://www.neilturner.me.uk/2004/Jul/16/a_free_ipod.html  mobynathan: omfg  mobynathan: LAME  mobynathan: scamcentral  mobynathan: oh well  mobynathan: I reconnect  mobynathan: to get back into #Nullsoft  Jaggonmaster: i read it  mobynathan: see  mobynathan: It's cheap and lame  mobynathan: bbiab  *** mobynathan signed off at Mon Jul 26 01:01:01 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Mon Jul 26 01:02:07 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Mon Jul 26 01:20:43 2004  Jaggonmaster: i just got another gb email for free  Jaggonmaster: and it isn't gmail  mobynathan: who cares  mobynathan: You're not even going to fill up your 1gb  Jaggonmaster: i know  Jaggonmaster: :)  Jaggonmaster: free ipod  mobynathan: hm?  Jaggonmaster: i don't think there lieing  Jaggonmaster: liiing  Jaggonmaster: ling  Jaggonmaster: :)  Jaggonmaster: :*  mobynathan: buy you have to join a DVD club  mobynathan: or some lame shit  Jaggonmaster: no you don't  Jaggonmaster: they found a loopol  mobynathan: Well I'm not signing  mobynathan: I'll just buy an eVic  Jaggonmaster: all you have to do is sign up for me  Jaggonmaster: and not even do it  Jaggonmaster: it makes sense  Jaggonmaster: you bid on something   Jaggonmaster: that has days left on it  Jaggonmaster: and wait 20 minutes and win  Jaggonmaster: (  mobynathan: er  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: whatever  mobynathan: I'm not signing up  Jaggonmaster: =:-}  Jaggonmaster: (r)  Jaggonmaster: boobies  Jaggonmaster: nate its al bototlk booibies  mobynathan: erhS?  Jaggonmaster: hey, you there?  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: i'm signed u  Jaggonmaster: p  Jaggonmaster: this is for real  Jaggonmaster: you wanna do it or not?  mobynathan: nope  mobynathan: I'm buying an eVic  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: I don't want an iPod  Jaggonmaster: but this is free  mobynathan: They don't play Vorbis  Jaggonmaster: you could sell the ipod  Jaggonmaster: and buy a evic  Jaggonmaster: sell it on ebay  mobynathan: hmm  mobynathan: Well, I don't trust it still  Jaggonmaster: it's simple  mobynathan: Okay, you go for it  mobynathan: Good luck  Jaggonmaster: you bid on an ipod on ebay  Jaggonmaster: get hi bid  Jaggonmaster: and thats it  Jaggonmaster: your done  Jaggonmaster: they make money off of refersals  *** mobynathan signed off at Mon Jul 26 02:31:29 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Mon Jul 26 03:41:50 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Tue Jul 27 20:07:02 2004  Jaggonmaster: free ipod bitch  mobynathan: yeah sure  Jaggonmaster: tis true  Jaggonmaster: :D  mobynathan: okay  Jaggonmaster: the company that does this is in the top ten businesses in north america  mobynathan: When you get it for free let me know  Jaggonmaster: ok  Jaggonmaster: once i get my ipod  Jaggonmaster: i'm gonna get a flatscreen   mobynathan: take a digital picture  Jaggonmaster: i don't have a digital  mobynathan: Get a flatglass monitor  mobynathan: Not a LCD flatscreen  Jaggonmaster: why?  Jaggonmaster: how do you say i don't know in spanish?  mobynathan: i don't know :)  Jaggonmaster: lol  Jaggonmaster: freeipodguide.com  Jaggonmaster: check it out  Jaggonmaster: mike is going to do it, too  Jaggonmaster: i like mozillllllllllllllla  mobynathan: me too  mobynathan: Mike Marsh?  Jaggonmaster: yup  Jaggonmaster: are you checking out that site  Jaggonmaster: ?  Jaggonmaster: ({)(})  mobynathan: yes I am  Jaggonmaster: remember when yahoo was popular  mobynathan: Yeah but I never used it  mobynathan: I used Altavista because I'm cool  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: And knew how fucking bad Yahoo! was  mobynathan: I bought this kickass keyboard on eBay today  Jaggonmaster: woopie  Jaggonmaster: should i get this ipod  Jaggonmaster: and sell it on ebay  mobynathan: no, really  mobynathan: It ownz  mobynathan: I paid $13 for it  mobynathan: Plus 4.24 shipping  mobynathan: I'll show you  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: The keyboard's older than I am :)  mobynathan: Shows you how durable it is  *** mobynathan signed off at Tue Jul 27 20:19:31 2004.  Session Close (mobynathan): Tue Jul 27 20:24:10 2004      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Tue Jul 27 22:45:59 2004  Jaggonmaster: how do i get a bounce  mobynathan: r  mobynathan: um  mobynathan: Ask someone with a Linux computer that you know  Jaggonmaster: i am  Jaggonmaster: but they don't know how  mobynathan: okay  Jaggonmaster: like  mobynathan: well then  mobynathan: Find someone who does  Jaggonmaster: what do they have to do?  mobynathan: Or tell them to 'apt get muh'  mobynathan: If they have Debian  Jaggonmaster: what's that?  Jaggonmaster: nickv111 is doing it  mobynathan: Well first off  mobynathan: If his computer (Xbox?) isn't up all the time  mobynathan: Your bouncer would be useless  mobynathan: muh is the name of the bouncer I used  Jaggonmaster: oh  Jaggonmaster: now what  Jaggonmaster: after it's installed  mobynathan: Uh, I don't know  Jaggonmaster: what?  mobynathan: I never set one up  Jaggonmaster: ask that one guy  mobynathan: learn to be self-sufficient  mobynathan: Google is your friend  mobynathan: no  mobynathan: fuck that you figure it out  mobynathan: I don't need one  Jaggonmaster: hello  Jaggonmaster: um, why not talk to me here fuckwad  mobynathan: because I like IRC better  mobynathan: And because that's less Alt-Tabbing for me  Jaggonmaster: you are a jackass  mobynathan: and stop using my word, 'fuckwad'  Jaggonmaster: ok fuckwad  Jaggonmaster: ::D  mobynathan: do you want a warm bun  Jaggonmaster: sure  Jaggonmaster: :(  Jaggonmaster: (sick)  mobynathan: You want a Warm Bun(tm)?  Jaggonmaster: yes  Jaggonmaster: i like buns  mobynathan: faaaaaaaaag  Jaggonmaster: who doesn't like a good ass, and a pair of legs  mobynathan: Only if they're female  mobynathan: and human  Jaggonmaster: no shit sherlock  mobynathan: Next comes an AIM block  Jaggonmaster: what?  Jaggonmaster: why?  mobynathan: You are abrasively annoying  Jaggonmaster: you asked me if i liked buns  mobynathan: Bun = BAN  Jaggonmaster: oh  Jaggonmaster: um, how do you use muh with a windows comp and a linux comp  mobynathan: well the computer connecting to it can be any os than can run an irc client  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: The Linux comp runs muh 24/7  Jaggonmaster: its irc.ircnet.net  Jaggonmaster: right?  mobynathan: yes  Jaggonmaster: cool  mobynathan: oh there's a windows port of muh now  mobynathan: (Link: http://mind.riot.org/muh/)http://mind.riot.org/muh/  Jaggonmaster: i shouldn't need that though  mobynathan: nope  Jaggonmaster: have you linked your computers together yet?  mobynathan: oh yeah, a while ago  mobynathan: works great :)  mobynathan: when I was talking to you earlier I was upstairs leeching the connection off my dad when he was online  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: Why do you ask?  Jaggonmaster: cause   Jaggonmaster: i'm gonna need a long ass cable  Jaggonmaster: but it's gonna run outside  Jaggonmaster: and into my room  mobynathan: HAHA!  Jaggonmaster: haha?  mobynathan: Better get an outside-certified one  mobynathan: Can't use normal cat5e for that  mobynathan: Not if it's outside  Jaggonmaster: cat5e bites  mobynathan: it's 1gbps capable  mobynathan: not 10gbps though  mobynathan: But 10gbps is pretty much horrible overkill  Jaggonmaster: i'm getting an ipod  Jaggonmaster: and i'm gonna sell it  mobynathan: right now computers can only do about 200-300mbps before all their processing power is used by the transfer  Jaggonmaster: i don't like your ugly green colore  Jaggonmaster: colour                                         Had to take out this little bit  Jaggonmaster: what's wrong?  mobynathan: nice pass :)  mobynathan: parse error  Jaggonmaster: oops  Jaggonmaster: don't tell anyone  Jaggonmaster: please  mobynathan: Um, I would guess a setting is set incorrectly  mobynathan: nah I won't  mobynathan: Just tell him to make sure he followed the proper config-file format  mobynathan: So did you get it fixed yet?  Jaggonmaster: no  Jaggonmaster: the guys at debian are dead  Jaggonmaster: #debian  mobynathan: (Link: http://mind.riot.org/muh/documentation/Introduction.html)http://mind.riot.org/muh/documentation/Introduction.html  mobynathan: Probably not the right place to ask anyway  mobynathan: file:///C:/Nate/mind.riot.org/muh/documentation/Muhrc-Commands.html  mobynathan: oops  mobynathan: (Link: http://mind.riot.org/muh/documentation/Muhrc-Commands.html)http://mind.riot.org/muh/documentation/Muhrc-Commands.html  mobynathan: curious if my bouncer's still up  mobynathan: I know I trashed it before by deleting the configfile  mobynathan: logging into my shell account  mobynathan: Just tell nick to give you a shell account on his box  mobynathan: s/box/computer/  mobynathan: rewriting my config file :)  Jaggonmaster: hey, want a free ipod  Jaggonmaster: ?  mobynathan: no dammit :)  mobynathan: It's only 15gb anyway  Jaggonmaster: 20  mobynathan: and no Ogg Vorbis support  Jaggonmaster: they ran out of 15gb ones  mobynathan: oh  mobynathan: well anyway  mobynathan: I don't want a shitty iPod  mobynathan: Because I don't trust that thing still  Jaggonmaster: ssh?  mobynathan: What?  Jaggonmaster: what is ssh  mobynathan: When did I say SSH?  mobynathan: SSH == Secure Shell, a method to log into a shell account and use it remotely  Jaggonmaster: i just want to know wha it is?  Jaggonmaster: i fuckin hate acronyms  mobynathan: Who mentioned it?  Jaggonmaster: nick  mobynathan: I love 'em  Jaggonmaster: i need a link to putty  mobynathan: omfg  mobynathan: GOOGLE DOT FUCKING COM  Jaggonmaster: damnit  mobynathan: it's the first God damn link  Jaggonmaster: thats what he said  Jaggonmaster: hello  Jaggonmaster: i'm in putty, what do i do  mobynathan: log in  mobynathan: jackass, don't ask me how to use everything you need to figure out  Jaggonmaster: i am logged  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: have fun  mobynathan: it's linux  Jaggonmaster: thanks, nate  mobynathan: okay  mobynathan: welcome  Jaggonmaster: damnit  Jaggonmaster: it still won't let me on ircnet  mobynathan: yeah I got that same error:  mobynathan: [Wed 28 Jul 05:48:14] + parsing configuration file...    [Wed 28 Jul 05:48:14] - parse error on line 1!    [Wed 28 Jul 05:48:14] - terminating...     Jaggonmaster: i thought you could get on it?  mobynathan: I can  mobynathan: I'm just setting up my bouncer again  mobynathan: I'm on IRCnet already  Jaggonmaster: so, can i get this bouncer through here  mobynathan: here == where?  Jaggonmaster: putty  Jaggonmaster: ssh  mobynathan: you can install it and run it  mobynathan: But you connect with XChat  Jaggonmaster: is it like a personal server  Jaggonmaster: like how do you get to it  Jaggonmaster: /newserver   Jaggonmaster: or what  mobynathan: yeah  mobynathan: you connect to it just like any normal server  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: It does the rest of zee majik  Jaggonmaster: can that guy that's giving you the bounce get on through xchat  Jaggonmaster: or does he have a bouncer too?  mobynathan: no, he uses Linux, and irssi  mobynathan: He's also living in sweden  Jaggonmaster: ok, so maby it's only in america  Jaggonmaster: fuckin bastards  Jaggonmaster: wish dmp was up  mobynathan: well I can get on :)  mobynathan: So it's not America  mobynathan: Europe has their own servers anyway  Jaggonmaster: but your using a bounce  mobynathan: no I'm fucking not  Jaggonmaster: (talk)  mobynathan: I connect normally  Jaggonmaster: i thought you were  mobynathan: No  Jaggonmaster: i'm so confused  mobynathan: I'm setting one up just in case  Jaggonmaster: so how are you on it now?  mobynathan: irc.ircnet.net  Jaggonmaster: i'm gonna come join nullsoft  Jaggonmaster: then  Jaggonmaster: don't tell em  mobynathan: I won't say anything  Jaggonmaster: give me a nick  mobynathan: Zed  mobynathan: I don't know :)  Jaggonmaster: moby  Jaggonmaster: :D  mobynathan: how 'bout no  Jaggonmaster: yes  Jaggonmaster: :D  mobynathan: Noggaj  Jaggonmaster: can you get on more than one server through issri  mobynathan: i'll tell 'em it's you then  Jaggonmaster: ok  mobynathan: yep  Jaggonmaster: i'll be someone else  Jaggonmaster: jaggon  Jaggonmaster: how  mobynathan: I can't remember  mobynathan: ^X switches server though  mobynathan: ^X == Ctrl-X  Jaggonmaster: wtf  Jaggonmaster: you tolled them  mobynathan: nope  mobynathan: I didn't  mobynathan: I promise  mobynathan: [12:14:43am] --

29,July,2004


	 
      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:the jerilu truck): Wed Jul 21 16:41:24 2004  Jaggonmaster: EAT A BABY  the jerilu truck: With butter  Jaggonmaster: and cheetos  the jerilu truck: I like cheetos  Jaggonmaster: :'D  Session Close (the jerilu truck): Wed Jul 21 16:57:20 2004    
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:MadSh00ter): Sun Jul 18 22:59:19 2004 MadSh00ter: good MadSh00ter: 

04,August,2004


	 
      Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:KorgSaballon): Thu Jul 22 21:35:56 2004 Jaggonmaster: uh, mr marsh KorgSaballon: hello? mike perhaps Jaggonmaster: um, do you have live? KorgSaballon: no it expired KorgSaballon: why do you ask? Jaggonmaster: you have linux on your box right? KorgSaballon: no beacause someone jacked my usb hub Jaggonmaster: so Jaggonmaster: you can use a controller Jaggonmaster: m$ started banning a lot of people from live for having linux and other crap on there boxen KorgSaballon: ok ill be sure not to renew my subscription Jaggonmaster: do you use irc? KorgSaballon: no Jaggonmaster: i see Jaggonmaster: yes, major cuntage *** KorgSaballon signed off at Thu Jul 22 22:24:12 2004. Session Close (KorgSaballon): Thu Jul 22 22:24:16 2004   Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:KorgSaballon): Tue Jul 27 19:58:06 2004 Jaggonmaster: ah, yes the michael marsh Jaggonmaster: bah KorgSaballon: ello michael Jaggonmaster: um, bah Jaggonmaster: damn, i'm gonna get a free ipod KorgSaballon: oh really Jaggonmaster: yup Jaggonmaster: :D Jaggonmaster: you can get one too KorgSaballon: i already have one KorgSaballon: but how do you get one Jaggonmaster: umm, how lond are you gonna be online? KorgSaballon: not to long Jaggonmaster: damn Jaggonmaster: um, you want me to email the instructions to you? KorgSaballon: yes please KorgSaballon: (Link: mailto:mike_marsh89@yahoo.com)mike_marsh89@yahoo.com Jaggonmaster: ok, what's your email address? Jaggonmaster: ok KorgSaballon: but im leaving now KorgSaballon: thanks Jaggonmaster: is that an underscrool? Jaggonmaster: l KorgSaballon: yes Jaggonmaster: ok, see yah *** KorgSaballon signed off at Tue Jul 27 20:03:40 2004. Session Close (KorgSaballon): Tue Jul 27 20:22:49 2004   Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:KorgSaballon): Tue Aug 03 16:53:36 2004 Jaggonmaster: jagonmaster@walla.com? KorgSaballon: its not mike KorgSaballon: sorry Jaggonmaster: ok KorgSaballon: who is this?? Jaggonmaster: mike s., and who am i talking to? KorgSaballon: names LaRina KorgSaballon: you don't know me.. @ least i don't think you do Jaggonmaster: do you go to fort leboeuf? KorgSaballon: nope Jaggonmaster: i see KorgSaballon: but  im friends with a ton of people that do Jaggonmaster: hmm KorgSaballon: mike smith?? Jaggonmaster: swift KorgSaballon: is that your name? KorgSaballon: ahh i see Jaggonmaster: do you know dave barron? KorgSaballon: yesury Jaggonmaster: i haven't seen him in years KorgSaballon: yeah KorgSaballon: he was in a band with my two close buddies.. andrew and shane KorgSaballon: andrews my bestfriend.. and me and shane are very tite Jaggonmaster: yeah, i'm friends with them Jaggonmaster: there band had a lame name though Jaggonmaster: can't remember it KorgSaballon: haha KorgSaballon: o actualy it was lame all together KorgSaballon: BRAIN WIDGETS Jaggonmaster: yup Jaggonmaster: that's it KorgSaballon: i didn't know them back then... they don't ever talk abuot the band KorgSaballon: its an imbarasement to them Jaggonmaster: that was 8th grade KorgSaballon: they have 2 other bands now tho KorgSaballon: not with dave.. cause he's into rock of course KorgSaballon: yeah Jaggonmaster: yeah, i don't like punk Jaggonmaster: and andrew is into hardcore a lot KorgSaballon: yup KorgSaballon: as am i KorgSaballon: are you implying you don't like hardcore as well?/ Jaggonmaster: i like some hardcore KorgSaballon: like what Jaggonmaster: mudvayne Jaggonmaster: if that counts Jaggonmaster: slipknots pretty good KorgSaballon: eeewww Jaggonmaster: thought you would say that KorgSaballon: NEW METAL!!! GROSE KorgSaballon: i used to be heavy into korn Jaggonmaster: wasn't everyone? Jaggonmaster: and then they kept releasing albums every year KorgSaballon: lol Session Close (KorgSaballon): Tue Aug 03 17:45:46 2004
    


05,August,2004


	 
        "The path of the righteous man is beset on all sides by the inequities of the  selfish and the tyranny of evil men. Blessed is he, who in the name of charity  and good will, shepherds the weak through the valley of darkness, for he is  truly his brother's keeper and the finder of lost children. And I will strike  down upon thee with great vengeance and furious anger those who would attempt to  poison and destroy my brothers. And you will know my name is the Lord when I lay  my vengeance upon thee."  


06,August,2004


	 
      Jaggonmaster: i posted a blog mobynathan: you posted an entry mobynathan: a blog is a collection of entries Jaggonmaster: o whatever Jaggonmaster: cuntface mobynathan: OMFG I JUST WON A FREE DIGITAL CAMERAAAAAAAAAA Jaggonmaster: no way Jaggonmaster: click it Jaggonmaster: do you get a free virus too? Jaggonmaster: cause if you get a virus Jaggonmaster: then i get the camera Jaggonmaster: that's only fair mobynathan: I didn't click it mobynathan: :) mobynathan: Sometimes I do click them just for fun though Jaggonmaster: if you got norton, might as well Jaggonmaster: :D mobynathan: I do mobynathan: I got a message earlier mobynathan: I only have 31 days of virus defintion upgrades left :( Jaggonmaster: so, go to best buy and buy the new one Jaggonmaster: it's free Jaggonmaster: penix? Jaggonmaster: you dead, or something? Jaggonmaster: up for a game of reversi? Jaggonmaster: are you touching yourself rapidomente? mobynathan: oh mobynathan: sory mobynathan: sorry mobynathan: I hid this window mobynathan: I'm back now mobynathan: I read your blog mobynathan: well mobynathan: looked at it mobynathan: and commented Jaggonmaster: well, you read it before Jaggonmaster: anyways mobynathan: I liked this part: " Had to take out this little bit" Jaggonmaster: biath mobynathan: Yes, I did Jaggonmaster: yeah, it had the pass mobynathan: 'A chat' though? mobynathan: More like... many chats mobynathan: Btw, I linked to it Jaggonmaster: yeah, i'll put another one up in a week Jaggonmaster: gmail isn't loading mobynathan: okay mobynathan: I was going to laugh my ass off if you put up your password mobynathan: To the bouncer mobynathan: Did you get that fixed btw? Jaggonmaster: um, no mobynathan: oh Jaggonmaster: he can't get onto to it either mobynathan: I know how to fix0r it Jaggonmaster: ok Jaggonmaster: what's my site? mobynathan: supertool.blogspot.com Jaggonmaster: ok mobynathan: (Link: http://mobynate.blogspot.com/)http://mobynate.blogspot.com/  Jaggonmaster: ok Jaggonmaster:  I HEART BREASTS mobynathan: Yes what a wonderful title Jaggonmaster: i know Jaggonmaster: at least it's honest mobynathan: haha, I guess so mobynathan: Like my picture? Jaggonmaster: sure, why not mobynathan: But seriously? Do you like it/them? Jaggonmaster: the keyboard? mobynathan: no, my images that I create mobynathan: The keyboard is nice though mobynathan: I can't belive I got it for $17.24 mobynathan: And that's a good one... it's old Jaggonmaster: lame mobynathan: has a detachable cord and everything Jaggonmaster: i got a keyboard just like that for free mobynathan: oh well mobynathan: I'm pretty rich right now :) mobynathan: $243 in my wallet I think Jaggonmaster: i posted a comment mobynathan: okay mobynathan: I hope it's not rude mobynathan: Or I might delete it Jaggonmaster: meow mobynathan: Trend? Jaggonmaster: don't trend on me Jaggonmaster: you never heard of that Jaggonmaster: i think its trend on me mobynathan: TREAD Jaggonmaster: it might be tread Jaggonmaster: yup mobynathan: TREAD YOU MORON : Jaggonmaster: i thought it was that mobynathan: now mobynathan: Futurama is on Jaggonmaster: might as well delete it mobynathan: yeah mobynathan: no mobynathan: I mean, mobynathan: no mobynathan: I'll leave it mobynathan: Anyway Jaggonmaster: ok Jaggonmaster: i'll post another one mobynathan: I'm getting some mountain dew and watching Futurama mobynathan: I'll check back during a commercial brake Jaggonmaster: i heart mountain dew mobynathan: So, goodnight, maybe mobynathan: Me too mobynathan: So tasty Jaggonmaster: night biatch mobynathan: It makes it hard for me to sleep though :( mobynathan: -off- Jaggonmaster: wait Jaggonmaster: check the posts mobynathan: hm? mobynathan: (commercial break) Jaggonmaster: penix? mobynathan: ?xinep Jaggonmaster: viewer discretion is advised? mobynathan: oh well mobynathan: I added another (lame) comment Jaggonmaster: um, what's the link Jaggonmaster: hello? Jaggonmaster: anyone Jaggonmaster: biatch Jaggonmaster: yes, i posted another, too mobynathan: okay Jaggonmaster: :'C mobynathan: okay mobynathan: I'm done mobynathan: Time for bed Jaggonmaster: nn bisnatch mobynathan: same biznatchola *** mobynathan signed off at Wed Jul 28 02:58:05 2004. Session Close (mobynathan): Wed Jul 28 02:58:08 2004   Session Start (AIM - jaggonmaster:mobynathan): Wed Jul 28 16:56:36 2004 Jaggonmaster: can you resume a download off of mozila? Jaggonmaster: s/mozila/mozilla/ mobynathan: er mobynathan: Sometimes Jaggonmaster: how mobynathan: s/mozilla/Mozilla/ Jaggonmaster: stfu Jaggonmaster: how long you gonna be on? mobynathan: Well, if your cache is too small and you restart a download that were previously getting, it'll just start over mobynathan: I recommend getting Wget for downloading files Jaggonmaster: wget? Jaggonmaster: new xebians out mobynathan: Yes, wget.sunsite.dk mobynathan: Then go to the Windows section mobynathan: nifty for you I guess Jaggonmaster: i'm asking ppl if you can get carpel tunnel from handjobs Jaggonmaster: :) mobynathan: haha, EFnet? Jaggonmaster: yeah Jaggonmaster: not gnu? mobynathan: (Link: http://xoomer.virgilio.it/hherold/)http://xoomer.virgilio.it/hherold/ * mobynathan got Dizzy Up The Girl from his cousin, yay! Jaggonmaster: how'd you do that? mobynathan: Do what? Jaggonmaster: purple asterick mobynathan mobynathan: Goo Goo Dolls are awesome mobynathan: Oh, take a guess :) mobynathan: Think IRC * Jaggonmaster got Jaggonmaster: thought so Jaggonmaster: 097c SSL Libraries mobynathan: ate Jaggonmaster: ^that one? mobynathan: oops mobynathan: Yeah I think so mobynathan: Just get the one it says Jaggonmaster: If you don't know which version to get: GET THIS ONE: 1.9.1 complete  This is a bug fix update to 1.9. SSL libraries included in the archive. For source see entry in the following table(ordered by release or compilation time). mobynathan: okay do that ten Jaggonmaster: see, if dmp can set me up a bouncer mobynathan: He's on dialup anymore isn't he? mobynathan: It'd be pretty useless if he's not on all the time like I said before Jaggonmaster: i don't think he is Jaggonmaster: um, he might be Jaggonmaster: pretty tiny file mobynathan: Wget? Jaggonmaster: yes mobynathan: It's not that small mobynathan: it's great though Jaggonmaster: 3kb mobynathan: Small == less than 64kb mobynathan: nah Jaggonmaster: i meen 746 mobynathan: That can't be right mobynathan: Yeah, more like it mobynathan: anyway mobynathan: Command-line interface program Jaggonmaster: know what mobynathan: wget (Link: http://www.bleh.com/file.exe)http://www.bleh.com/file.exe is for downloading file.exe mobynathan: wget -c (Link: http://www.bleh.com/file.exe)http://www.bleh.com/file.exe --

10,August,2004


	 
      Hello.  My name is Inigo Montoya.  You killed my father.  Prepare to die. - Mandy Patinkin 
    



