
29,July,2004


    
       
      Hiya, hiya, doing some surveys. Here's the first.  Personal Background and The Basics  Full Name::&nbsp; MuRong Bi   Birthday::&nbsp; June 30th 1979  Nationality:: Canadian&nbsp;  Heredity::&nbsp; Chinese & German  Location::&nbsp; Ottawa, Ontario, Canada  Eye Color:: Gray  Hair Color:: Black  Hair Style::&nbsp; Bangs, chin length  Skin Tone:: As white as computer paper.  Body Type::&nbsp; Ugggllllyyy with 34-DDD boobs  School Grade::  Not in school  School::  Not in school  Usual Grades::  Not in school  Favorite class and why::  Not in school  Favorite teacher and why::  Not in school  Who do you sit with at lunch?:  Not in school  Going to college?:  Not in school  Which one?:  Not in school  What are you going to study?:  Not in school  What career are you going to pursue?:  Well I already have a career that's ok, I do HRP for En An Productions, also a DJ  Favorites  Favorite color::  Black/Neon Pink/Neon green/Blue  Favorite soda::&nbsp; Pepsi, Coke, C-plus, Barq's  Favorite food:: None  Favorite band(s)::&nbsp;Loads  Favorite music style(s)::&nbsp;Anything&nbsp; except  country.&nbsp;  Favorite cd::  I like so many I can't choose a favourite one.  Favorite song::  Same as above  Favorite flower::  Wow, I"ve never been asked that before..uhm, probably red or black roses.  Favorite food scent::  None  Favorite time of day or night::  either 2:30am or 3:00am, lovely productive time of night.  Favorite season::  All of them have their good points and bad points.  Favorite holiday::  Anything with presents, lol!! *evil greedy smile*  Favorite store::  GW, CD, some others that I can't think of now.  Favorite celebrity (male)::  None  Favorite celebrity (female)::  None  Favorite tv show::  Simpsons', South Park, King of the Hill, Family Guy, Futurama, Puppets Who Kill&nbsp;  Favorite movie::  Hmm, HPLOTRPOTCM, lol  Favorite book/author::  Hmm, lots  Favorite accent/language::  Scottish  Love  Any S/O (S/O meaning significant other)?:  Yes  Are they male or female?:  Male  How long have you been with him/her?:  Over 2 years  Where did you meet him/her?:  Through friends at a party a looonngg time ago, ever since then we've gotten to know eachother better and now we are partners.  (for an actual S/O or a wanted S/O) What is their name?:  Hugo Vigus  What is their background nationality-wise?:  Australian  How old are they?:  45  Where are they located?:  Greely  What physical feature on a fe/male do you find to be the sexiest?:  I like feminin looking men, and pretty girls  What personality traits are a must?:  Please don't seek me for the wrong kind of attention, because I don't give it that easily.  What does your ideal fe/male look like?:  Men with long hair, lol geeky computer girls, aw, let's say geeks of both sexes!  Who was your first kiss?:  Hmm,&nbsp;Will?.., can't remember that well. 

29,July,2004


    
       
      Hiya, another new blog, meh. I'll be posting one of those little quiz thingies in a couple of&nbsp;minutes. Have to go do something now.  Toodles, CMC 
      



