
15,August,2004


    
       
      8-15-04  Today i just got back from my friends house ** i stayed the nite **... but anyways, my name is Casey but my nickname is Kitty.. i am in the 9th grade and I live in Flordia... i play the gutiar and i love metal and rock... and i like pop *when i feel like singing*.. i have three younger brothers **annoying as hell, but what can i do**...and i live with both my parents = dads in afganastan for now.. he'll be back soon.. i only have a couple best friends... i used to have more but, best friends are so hard to find these days... to many people talk shit.... but enough about people.. now back to me... lol.. i like to draw, write poems, sing, talk on the phone & internet, watch movies and read...  i dont know what i want to be when i grow up 

03,August,2004


    
       
      GoodBye: She turns off the phone Shuts her eyes Drops it Can't believe it's goodbye She knows she loves him He loves her too But the hell with the game She says thier through No more waiting  For him to return Still very sore From where she was burned She knows she'll have to try  Not to give in She'll make herself believe That she doesn't love him She knows it's hard Almost impossible But she'll have to believe  That the pain is stoppable She has to get rid of him As fast as she can  To erase him completely  For that is her plan And if he were to come near She'll have to turn her back With a thousand of her tears    Every Moment: Every moment my heart races mind lost and confused in many cases anything could happen  on the dangerous path that lie ahead cuaght between the heart and mind bad news is what i dread  chained to my depression thats imprisioned me for years every second of everyday is a thousand of my tears running through my nightmares like a horror movie scene Knowing that your nervous just makes my heart bleed i lay there at night i dream that your okay i close my shaking eyes whisper to myself and pray i pray that you will stay safe  and that you will always know that i love you more than air... and i'm waiting here at home By: Me       
      


03,August,2004


    
       
      Whats up?.... If your bored here are some questions you can ponder over...Are children who act in rated 'R' movies allowed to see them?  Can you make a candle out of your earwax? When French people swear do they say pardon my English? Aren't the 'good things that come to those who wait' just the leftovers from the people that got there first? If the swat team breaks down your door do they have to replace it later? Can a fire truck park in the fire lane? Can it be cloudy and foggy at the same time? "Cute as a button" Is that supposed to be a compliment? Since when are buttons cute? Can you breathe out of your nose and mouth at the same time? Are marbles made of marble?  Why does the last piece of ice always stick to the bottom of the cup? If you pay for a vacation and your plane crashes on the way there, do you get you money back? (Granted you lived) Why did Yankee Doodle name the feather in his hat Macaroni? Who was the first person to look at a cow and say, "I think I'll squeeze these dangly things here and drink what comes out"? Who was the first person to say, "See that chicken over there ... I'm gonna eat the first thing that comes out if its butt"?   
      


03,August,2004


    
       
      GOOD LUCK in highschool Devin: glad we hangin agian.. I miss you sis!!! Becca: stay smart, pretty and fun... guys will notice you!! ¿  Ariel: Hope you and your boy work out.. lucky bitch... lol.. I miss you Katie: Hope you and Deriek stay together.. at least one of us is happy.. lol Kelsey: Born to be WILD!! Us two stick together... WE HATE PREPS.. well most Beth: i better see you soon.. Good luck with Caydin!! He IS your son.. lol Megan: LOADS and LOADS of Fun at work    
      


03,August,2004


    
       
      Hey.... I can't wait to see you agian... I miss you... make sure your here to drive me to school... lol 

03,August,2004


    
       
      Hey Kid.... You better come down.. I mean it... lol, Dont forget the glow in the dark condoms and the drinks... LOL 


