
09,August,2004


	 
       Ok I know the whole sayings and things was a very bad title idea. OK so it was very very stupid, but hey... It popped in to my head, and I wrote it down. That is how I am MOST of the time. Anyway just saying that most of the stuff on this page is just pretty much just what ever randomness comes out of my mouth, or what I hear, or worse... What I think!  ~L8R  
    


08,August,2004


	 
            I will eat your face with a spoon!         Kill me with a spork!         Bite me!         Dun even fawk wif me!          ~L8R          



08,August,2004


	 
         When something goes wrong, I look into your eyes, And everything turns out alright.  When I am depressed, I look into your eyes, And I am filled with happiness.  When I am in pain, I look into your eyes, And all of my pain disappears.  When I cower in fear, I look into your eyes, And my fear goes away.  When I feel that I might loose you, I look into your eyes, And I know that I can trust you.  When I am worried, I look into your eyes, And I know that everything will be ok.  


07,August,2004


	 
           It hurts me to breath, When I see what has been.  People's minds being tromented, Their bodies being devoured.  No where to run, No where to hide.  Running around looking for something, Something that just can't be found.  I look around, I see the pain.  There is a place to run, A place to hide.  This is a place I just can't seem to find!         


07,August,2004


	 
       Like cold, crying clouds, Pouring through the sky, Sinking to the ground.  Like a silver dragon, Flying through the air, Landing in a cave.  Like a glowing light, Flickering in a lamp, Suddenly extinguished.  Like a star being born, Than a fast explosion, And it dies.  Like getting a wild buzz, Hiding in the clouds, Dreaming a luring dream.  Like rain splashing in puddles, slithering in anger, Stealing a metal-iron obsession.  Like everything that begins, Something has got to end.   
    


07,August,2004


	 
       When I look at the world around me, I see people laughing in amusement, But I cry in vein.  When i look at the world around me, I see people people's enjoyment, But i am in agony.  When i look at the world around me, I see forgiveness, but i feel revenge.  When i look at the world around me, I see happyness, But I feel sadness.  When i look at the world around me, I see what I want, But it doesn't want me.   
    


07,August,2004


	 
       Hiding in dark allies, A place to run and hide, There is nothing to fear when all alone.  Running from my fear, Hiding in the darkness, I am getting away from all that I fear.  Darkness hides me when I am alone, No one can hurt me, I am hidden from the world.  There is nothing to fear anymore.   
    



07,August,2004


	 
       Sorry, I couldn't find anything else to talk about. I haven't really done anything sense the whole 'Some coffee and talk' thing with Mark. But anyway... yeah...   

07,August,2004


	 
      This is just a list of things that keep my mind occupied, things that have just ran threw it, or just poped in it... 


