
07,August,2004


	 
      Whilst talking dirty shouldn't be a problem for most men, I know it ain't for me. But the other day when in the middle of some great sex my girl friend suddenly had the brain wave that my talking to her during intercourse would be a real turn on for her I was at a loss of words. I prefer the sighs and the aahs but actual talk requires processing of signals in the brain which are not instinctive thus, requiring “concentration”. Now good sex does not generally inspire me to think (well at least not while I am indulging in the actual act).   So here I was "committed" to the "hilt" with my girl friend urging me to converse with her and all I could think of was "Honey, you more than make up for my absence of conversation in our relationship" Hmmm.....apparently not a very bright thing to say under the circumstances. Translated ---------

06,August,2004


	 
      Girl friend took me to this movie last night called  urlLink "Julie" ) The promotions promised skin and sleaze aplenty, the actual movie fell way short. If you expected a decent script you had better chances in  urlLink Spidey   ) which was running on the next screen ! Can't call it a disappointment as I never really did expect anything ! Just went because I was asked to.....  Although it did inspire my girlfriend for some weird reason (that only babes would related to) to introduce some kewl variations under the sheets later on. For some reason she decided that love making should be something that should be dictated by a man with the woman as a guide on the trip to the great venus ! Whose complaining ?!! I had a marathon session lasting a good 90 minutes and finally ended when my neighbour rang the bell coz he heard someone screaming ;-)  Why is it that girls would go an extra mile to compete with another woman that she “presumes” to be competing for her man's fantasies ? Don't they reaslise that fantasies are some place where 'real women' hardly find a place ?!! Anyways I am not going to complain anytime soon. 
    


06,August,2004


	 
      So my dear friend has gone out and done it again. Impressed my boss with MY idea ! Its getting riduculous having to sit there and see myself get outmanouvered !  Always thought I was a good chess player .... well well....back to checkers I guess. What I am wondering is should I be reacting to his plays (my colleagues) or should I be content in the knowledge that at the end of the day my work shall come out on tops by its merits ?!! Somehow the idea of responding to someone's agression seems petty when in the long run it hardly seems to hold any importance.  Immediate versus Future is that the debate? Or, my lack of response to such manouveres gives my boss the impression that I am laidback ?  
    


06,August,2004


	 
      For the last couple of days boss has been behaving a bit weird. On one side he has been contstantly reminding me that “I am the next in line to the throne”! Translated -------

06,August,2004


	 
       Had to travel to Bombay recently to meet couple of companies that we just made an investment in. One of them is in Vashi and develops a cool product for automotive manufacturers. But the promoter is a damn bore.....so is his financial guy....can you believe CA's in India make a bomb just for introducing a client to a bank??? I mean the chap is giving collateral and on top of it a 12% interest ! This after the company being listed on the Stock Exchange for the last couple of years. Anyway, I think the company is highly under-valued and there is hardly any movement in its scrip so we decided to buy a healthy portion of its stock and join hands. Just made some introductions to auto manufacturers which have ended in the company getting huge orders. There revenue should more than double this year. Translated --------


