
22,August,2004


     
      hmmm!!! a very boring sunday to start off!! online the whole saturday nite !! tired!! woke up 12.30 p.m [sunday]  ouch!!! went cook lunch than wentback to sleep.. huh!~~ so boring!!!! why my weekend so boring!! arggg... stomach ache!!! 
     
    


21,August,2004


     
        83, 84, 85, 86, 90 ...kg.. argg!~~ my gosh.. i am growing fatter!~~     y? y god made me so fat? sob sob.. i need to loose weight..     lolz.. btw.. one of my friend name RYAN.. bet with me said if i loose weight.. he treat me lunch..     ooOOoo.. how i wish i can loosee weight..      how to lose weight? i dont go gym, nor lazy to diet? how? how? how?     no determination... lazy boy.. how? god plss show me a sign...    
     
    


19,August,2004


     
         ring ring ring!~~

19,August,2004


     
      OooOOOoo.. weekend is coming when it hits friday. huh!! oo how much i hate weekend.. boring boring week end.. nothing to do.. stranded inside a room. no where to go. how sad. lolz well today, its friday... i actually attended my 9.30 applied maths class.. finally i understand what my teacher gordan was teaching.. all these hardwork.. lolz.. after classs.. went mc D n eat.. lolz.. i am eventually declare myself broke and it should be said "SERIOUSLY BROKE" muahahaha. concidering i am broke, i actually left 5 dollars and finally i end up using the $5 to play arcade.... lose lose lose... wasted my money.. hahaha after that went have a stroll along swanston street..and after that head back to home. slept till 6.30 until a stupid prank call woke me up [@#%$&amp;@#@^]....... yishhhh!!!! finnally go online... went play gunbound on9 game.. hulalala its my luckly day and i actually won 4 matches out of 5 wah!!!! --

19,August,2004


     
       oh yes!!! after days and nites wondering about the blog...hahaha.. (happy). finally i know how to control the studpid blog. muahahaha.   i took me the whole 3 hour class to figure out how to do it. huh!! frustrated. now i am back!!!      - challenges always confront us   - make sure we accept it   - and fight until the last breath      - from time you fail   - never ever give up so easily   - as u fail, you learn from mistakes       -akimoto-        
     
    


11,August,2004


     
        ooo... headache.... today i've been trying to change all the blog skins n stuff but i still dont know how to operate it. uh!~~ making me crazy. y can't i fix it? stupid enough? yish!!!     i dont know why its so hard to modify the blog skin n stuff?     uh!~~ i really gave up doing this.... make me sick n also waste my time.     well, i think i have to do it tomorrow.          ARggg!!!   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       arg!~~ decision need to be made by today. i am ask to go to my foundation winter party and now i still havent decided that should i go or not? will it be fun? exciting? hmmmm.....   ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------    ohh ohhh.. yeah. finally i've made up my decision to go to the party. well after being advice by my friend. [not really wanna go but there's no harm right]hmm.. today a very simple day for me. actually miss my pure maths class coz i am too lazy to wake up n hate to see my add maths teacher that is RAUHA!!! [she makes me SICK] than i eventually attend my computer science class.. lolz.. nah.. i am a very bad student.. didnt even do my comp science work.. online the whole period. hahaha.. hmm. i felt bad for my god sista --

10,August,2004


     
       Hmm. What should i say? lolz. Nothing much happen to me. As usual, i went to uni and attend class and sitted for the english exam. pretty easy i should say but hope i can get high marks!~


