
21,August,2004


	 
      Have you ever wondered which hurts the most?    Saying something and wishing you hadn't?    ?or-    Saying nothing and wishing you had?    I guess the most important things are the hardest things to say.    Don't be afraid to tell someone you love them. If you do, they might    break your heart...if you don't, you might break theirs.    Have u ever decided not to become a couple because you were so afraid    of losing what you already had with that person?    Your heart decides whom it likes and whom it doesn't.    You can't tell your heart what to do.    It does it on its own.... when you least suspect it, or even when you    don't want it to.    Have you ever wanted to love someone with everything you had, but that    other person was too afraid to let you?    Too many of us stay walled up because we are too afraid to care too    much...for fear that the other person does not care as much, or even at    all.    Have you ever denied your feelings for someone because your fear of    rejection was too hard to handle?    We tell lies when we are afraid...    afraid of what we don't know,    afraid of what others will think,    afraid of what will be found out about us.    But every time we tell a lie, the thing we fear grows stronger.    Life is all about risks and it requires you to jump.    Don't be a person who has to look back and wonder what they would have    done, or could have had. 
     

    


19,August,2004


	 
      bkit kya dumdtng sa point ng isang tao yng nag-d- dlwang icp ka? afraid tht u might pick d wrong decision N regret it 4d rest of life!?  hav ya eva felt tht uve been so gaga over sum1 N yet we call it cRaZy... but we neva thght how stupid we bc0me until we felt tht we've been hurt ??!  and how cum aftr ol d shtz uve been thrgh 2sum1, hurt u lyk no one elz did, still u say... "MAHAL KO PA RIN SHA..." shetz... sumtymz wre confused kng mkknig tyo sa tkbo ng utak nten or frm d feelingz we hve in our heart… they say tht LOVE CONQUERS ALL....ye right!!!  mnsan, n-fe-feel nyo pa yng tipong may mahal k, pero mern nmn syng iba, or u fell 4ur friend but ur too afraid 2let it show coz ur fearing of rejection? dialogue @d movie My Best Friend's Wedding which Rupert Everett said... "If you love someone, say it...u say it right then...out LOUD… or the moment just...passes you by..."  meron nmn yng situation na, tipong threz sum1 in ur lyf N u cld say n hez/shez 'd one' at mssbe mo rn n mahal na mahal mo sha...but then, uve lost ur trust on him/her...yng tipong bngay mo n lhat ng trust mo nun una, tpos nwla lhat kc nlman mong hez/shez cheatin on ya? dba mskit??! SOBRA!!! shempre u cnt help 2thnk tht he/she myt d0 dz 2u again, aftr uv gven him/her a chnce? N now, telln u dz promises tht uve heard a million tymz b4... but then...what IF he/she broke dz promises in dz 2nd tym arnd? ewan ko nlang... ---

19,August,2004


	 
      ampotah ang saya saya last night. i was w/ my frends. nanood kmi ng concert nng  bamboo ...amg ganda ang saya slaman 2 the max...ganun pala un! harhar.....hehehe....gwapo ni  bamboo,  suplado ni  aira ,  aztig drummer nila cute ung isa (di ko lam name eh...hwehehehe)...grabee na ito! next tym  ROCKISTA  naman sa  ultra !...kita kits! 
     

    


19,August,2004


	 
      y do we love b? so we can have somebody to talk 2? someone who can be der pag gus2 natin gumala? a person na pwedeng manlibre satiin? taong magbibitbit ng gamit mo? alalay for short! eh panu kung di ka nya mahal would u still love him/her? would you still continue 2 care 4 dat person? bakit naman endeeee? u didnt love love dat person para magkaroon ka ng alalay, magkaroon ka ng instant meal dahil libre, taong gagawa ng assignments mo or projects, or taong mihihila mo if u want to go out... if dats wat u think about love well sori ang babaw mo, loving a person doesnt nid 2 hav a criteria na dapat maganda o guwapo, dapat mabait or understanding, kc once u fall inlove u take the risk of accepting dat person kahit maingay sya ma2log, ung hilik ng hilik kahit matakaw sya o sobrang fat na indi kau kaysa pag puno ang jeeep! kahit sobrang moody nya na kulang nalang ay sapakin mo sa inis! ung sobrang selosa na pati barkada pinagseselosan bad3p dbah? and ung napaka-arte OA kung baga! o kahit anu png things dat would turn u off... hirap tlaga magmahal trying 2 be perfect kc gus2 mong magtagal pero endi un ang sagot sa lahat... ACCEPTING da real person fully kc if u said na mahal mo sya u dont nid 2find answers kung y mo sya love... kc lahat ng tao nagbabago but if u accept dat person magbago man sya in da middle of ur relationship endi ka masasaktan kc u know dat darating din un.. tsaka tanggap mo sya ng buo... mahirap gawin pero masarap subukan dahil wala ng sasaya pa if u let one person feel na MAHAL NA MAHAL mo sya without asking 4 any return... den u can say wow un pla ang LOVE! 
     

    


15,August,2004


	 
       Sabi nila... 

15,August,2004


	 
        Lahat ng tao ay may pakiramdam. Kahit sabihin mo pa na manhid sya may pakiramdam pa rin. Kaso may mga tao na nagpapanggap. Para hindi malaman ng iba kung ano ang tunay na nararamdaman. Sa pagkukunwaring yun parepareho lang nahihirapan.Kung ayaw mo sa tao. Sbhin mo ang totoong nararamdaman mo. Wag mo syang pahirapan pa. Masakit man ang katotohanan at least d na sya umaasa pa. Pareho lang kayo mahihirapan. Makukulitan ka sa kanya at maari ka pang magalit sa kanya. Aasa sya at pag nawalan ng pagasa magagalit pa sayo. Hindi dahilan ang hiya para hindi mo i-turn down mo ang manliligaw po. Saktan mo sya habang mas maaga dahil pag tumagal pa mahihirapan na sya lumimot.Kung mahal mo naman ang isang tao. Sabihin mo sa kanya. Malay mo mahal ka rin nya. Kasi habang tinatago mo ang nararamdaman mo para sa kanya ikaw rin ang mahihirapan. At kung mahal ka rin nya sya rin ay mahihirapan dahil aakalhin nya na ayaw mo sa kanya. Diba nagsayang ka ng pagkakataon.    
     

    


12,August,2004


	 
      My Confession   My love for you is  Fake it was never  True and I promise not to  Love and care for you again. I’ll  Suspend all the love I’m offering.  I also want to tell you that  The last time we met and spoke was  Really making me feel disgusted it’s  Really planted in my heart and brain. I  Hate to remember it, I’ll never ever  Miss your company and I would love to  See you jump off a sky caper, I hate to  Be with you again, one more thing is  The caring I’ve showed you is nothing and that  I hate to see you  Not for another chance and I really don’t  Cry whenever you’re down or misunderstood  I hate also you’re company that  Sometimes I’d rather be  In school because I’m really bored when I’m  With you and I wish that we will be  Enemies forever, I don’t want us to be  Together again and never ever again  Cross each others path. I long  That we will be apart, because life with  You is hell on earth, being without  You is pure happiness and there will be  Supreme you and there will be  No loneliness, I hope we will  Forget one another and never  Meet again at any place and time because  I can’t really bear to see you  Just to see you one more time  Coz that could make me vomit, I know you  Will give me enough feeling of  Nausea that will never again would have the  Strength to continue living  And your memory will irritate me  For the rest of my life, I  Long to tell you this – I don’t  LOVE YOU!  Goodbye.   (Read it again skipping in lines) 
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
      Travel more then one (1) hour out of town together.  Dance with or without music. (Always ask first, not only with words). Be a prince to her parents. (Brownie points) Share a plate of spaghetti. (Ever see Lady and the Tramp?) Give her roses or wildflowers. For no reason, often. Do the little things. (I.E., Pull out chairs, open doors, Notice when she does the little things. Never, ever forget  urlLink holidays ! (Take him/her somewhere!) Girls like guys who will listen to sappy love songs. (When she's around, and without groaning) Always ask them how their day was...and listen! Tell her you love her only when you mean it and make sure she knows you mean it.  Write poetry/songs for her Sing or play a musical instrument. (If you can) Draw. (If you can) Be nice to her friends, but not too nice. Call from your vacation spot just to say hi. Go 30 minutes out of your way just spend a few hours with her. Do things you have never done before with her. DON'T make her do anything she doesn't want to. Be there for the good and the bad times. Walk her to her door. Don't just tell her you love her, show her. Spend all day with her doing nothing. Go home and call her to talk about nothing. Find out her favorite flower and give it to her for her birthday. (No matter how difficult it is to find) Know her favorite flower, color, number, animal, song (or band) and movie. Treat her the way she wants to be treated, not the way other girls want to be treated. When you say I'm sorry look them in the eyes. Remember that silence is sometimes the best answer. Staring is rude Share your deep dark secrets with each other. Tell them your fantasies. Make them feel important. Have your picture taken together.Eat ice cream together. Send a silly/sappy card just because you were thinking about them. Carve your names into a tree/table.I f you cannot feel their heartbeat, you are not close enough. Everyone deserves a second chance. (Or third...) When people put them down, defend them. ALWAYS be honest with them. (Even you know it's gonna hurt it'll hurt more if you lie.) Give them stuffed animals Treat her like a princess Keep him company when he's outside 
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       naniniwala k ba na ang mundo ay bilog?   ako? ewan ko? pero naniniwala   aq na damn maliit lng itong mundong ating ginagalawan! hehehe   la lng! nakita ko pala c ate kat na ex   ni melvin na kapatid ni melody na nagaaral s CEU ... na schoolmate ni maica. tapos kahapon nakita ko c mark na kapatid ni marxis   na kakilala ni joel na pinsan ni jolo na kabanda ni sammy.   ngaung umaga pumunta ako s internet lab at nakita ko cla dhane na kasama c gr ace  na bestfrend ni majoe na pinsn ni jozelle na classmate ng utol ko! sa lrt naman nakasabay ko   c michael masa na skulmate dati ni rommel na classmate ni jazelle na nag aaral s feu na skulmate   ni julius na boyfrend steph!...hay mundo ! 
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       I feel  like a song without the wordsA man without a soulA bird without its wingsA heart without a homeI feel  like a knight       without a swordThe sky without the suncos you are the oneI feel like a ship beneath the wavesA child that lost its wayA  door without a keyA face without  a nameI feel like a breath without the airAnd  every day's the  samesince you've gone awayI gotta have a reason to wake up in the morningYou used to be the one  that put a smile on my faceThere are no words that could  describe how I miss youand I miss you everydayyeahand    I'm never gonna leave your sideand I'm never gonna leave your side againstill holding on girlI won't let you gocos when I'm lying in your armsI know  I'm homeThey tell  me that a man can lose his mindLiving in the painThe call in times gone byThe crying in the rainYou know I've  wasted half the timeAnd I'm on my knees again'till you come to meyeahI gotta have a reason to wake up  in the morningYou used to be the  one that put a smile on my faceThere    are no words that could describe how I miss youand I miss you everydayyeahand I'm never gonna leave your sideand I'm never   gonna leave your side againstill  holding on girlI won't let you goI lay my head against your heartI know I'm homeI know I'm homeI know I'm  homeand I'm never gonna leave your sideand I'm never gonna leave your side againstill holding on girlI won't let you gocos when I'm lying in your armsI know I'm home    
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       last week...birthday ni papa eugene,    nagkayayaan, xempre ano pa...kundi INUMAN...hapi! naka isang case din ata kmi nun hehehe...lasinggera ko noh  ... ako tanggera! nauna ako at c diane pumnta s bahay nila halatang exited!   sumunod naman c    nick    na ang suot ay puruntong! how nice!   ampotah ang tagal nung iba! maya maya dumating ni c tandog at c dabe w/ jolo na aztig kumanta! sobrang inip    na lumabas na kmi at nagcmula na! maya maya may dumating naka kotseng pula aba c papa mark daryll pal  a! sabi  nia di daw cia iinom kc may dala ciang sasakyan!  saws muta nia ! maya maya may dumating di ko nga  nakita eh ex ko pala may kasamang magandang  maputing nilalang na c melody! at at at the rest is history di ko n alam sunod may tama na ko eh!..... hahahahha.... 
     

    



