
22,August,2004


     
      rax! malapit ka na dating! im so happy! at last i have someone to talk with. nakakapagod din kung sa keyboard parati nailalabas ang lahat ng sama ng loob. =) ei! i'll tour you here in dubai basta don't 4get the pasalubong ha. =) 
     
    


15,August,2004


     
      waaah! its 11pm and im still in the office WORKING! =( damn that "final design" submission! its really diffcult to be an OFW. its much more difficult to be a hero! hehe! crap kasi economy sa pinas e. if only our wages in the philippines can support our family we wouldn't be working our ass here and be so far away from home... i miss home =( huhu! i miss my family and my friends. =( i miss the rain! gusto ko ng baha! =) shawie! kat! pumunta na kayo dito! iwan nyo muna mga bf nyo at sumapi kayo sa akin! =)
     
    


14,August,2004


     
      ey! i did not get fat. the camera adds 4 lbs. ok? =) i miss ou guys! we'll be home (hopefully) by end of december. we would still have to send a request form. we'll c u soon! mwah!
     
    


11,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Tina, Claire, Emar & me =P&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
      after half a year of not being able to watch a filipino tv show at last we have TFC! last week lang po kaya mejo excited! =). so....ok! testing...scan (boring..) scan (boring...) scan... wha!!!! hua ze lei!??? where is the rest of F4? bakit puro pinoy mga kasama niya? SCQ reload? a ok.. look alike lang pala ni Vic Zhou. anyways... napatigil ako dahil akala ko nga F4. dunno why pero natapos ko yung show and until now after work i make sure that we're home by 930pm just to watch SCQ! haha! puro kababawan lang naman yung mga stories nila pero siguro mababaw din ako dati kaya gets ko sila =). ito ang mga ka-boringan ko sa buhay. sleep--

10,August,2004


     
      If you yelled for 8 years, 7 months and 6 days you would have produced enough sound energy to heat one cup of coffee . ---

10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    me and my friends.. kash, shheryl (my sister), kat d brat, rhacksz, cherl, rina, abbie and shawie =)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    me texting!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
      testing..testing... i'll write something next time. =) im still in the office. nagpapakaalila! and its already 730pm! we have a submission this weekend so have to work double time ( e ano itong ginagawa ko???) haha! ok CYA! testing...testing... 
     
    



