
18,August,2004


    
       
      Ya know, here lately I have noticed alot of shit n oddly, I have seen others vent so I havent.  But I am gonna say my piece to now.  A few things that piss me off..  No matter what u do, u cant win.  People either use who you date or dont date, you issues with people they are friends with or petty shit that really doesnt even affect their daily life.  Now, why the fuck am I going to go out of my way to tell someone stupid shit about THEIR choices, when it doesnt even remotely affect me.  Coming to me n asking will get u my opinion voluntarily, but other then that...I dont give two shits.   Over the past few weeks I have come to find out about certain cunts on yahoo that shouldnt even be allowed computer access.  They need to log off their comps n preferably, while still plugged in, take a bath with them.  As some of u know, my ex I used to live with up north, proposed to me not too long ago.  I accepted, it isnt often u can say you're with your first love, on both people's parts.  Now of course, little cunts are coming out of the wood work.  They feel the need to mention about how he was while we was broke up.  HELLO, we was broke up, why does it matter to me?  Obviously, anyone who knows him knows he talks alot of shit to females but its very RARE he does anything about it.  And the whole time, tellin certain people he wanted us back together but had too much pride.  Now, you would think that "friends" would be happy for u when things go good in your life.  But no, instead they decide to act jealous n make comments thinkin it will phase u or maybe affect your relationship in some way.  Heres a reality check, I know fantasy can be fun, but reality will kick your ass in the end, n I wanna be there to laugh.  Making the comments n acting like we are still in high school only makes u look jealous.  Quite frankly, it gives us all a good laugh.   So keep it up, b/c for some of u fucks in 1, I KNOW your life aint fuckin GRAND CENTRAL, so keep up.....least we have already grown up n done what we need to do to get our life straight.  If you arent happy for me, ill stamp I CARE on my ass n u can stare at it while I hand u a spork to eat my ass with, your opinion matters please insert here ~~

15,August,2004


    
       
      ok so I thought I would give this a try...I already have a journal at livejournal.com/gods_tiny_joke....but hey...guess this one wouldnt hurt either since everyone knows that link.  Its all nikke's fault tho....lol.  Anyway...um I dunno what to say since I already did my other journal today.  So um yeah...have I ever told people how much I hate them?  I recently found out about someone who was supposed to be my friend...sticking a few knives through my back...that rocked!  She didnt like it too much tho when I busted her out on it n embarassed her in front of everyone.  But thats what she gets, screw me over n screw u over twice as much.  Ok well um thats all for now:D 
      



