

24,April,2003



       
      This is testing Blogger's  new  Dano stuff.
     

    


09,June,2003



       
      yo
     

    


28,May,2004



       
       urlLink stock.xchng - the leading free stock photo site 
     

    


26,May,2004



       
       urlLink UNH Biodiesel Group : "Widescale Biodiesel Production from Algae"
     

    


25,May,2004



       
       urlLink Linux High Availability Firewall  uses shoreline and heartbeat (Linux HA) stuff.
     

    


23,May,2004



       
       urlLink Rita Di Ghent.com  Toronto Based jazz singer.
     

    


22,May,2004



       
       urlLink IWILL Creative Form Factor  Dual Opteron in small form factor for $500??
     

    


21,May,2004



       
       urlLink Fast Ferry Toronto Rochester  $28 walk on (no car) takes 2hr 15 minutes.
     

    


20,May,2004



       
       urlLink Writing Scalable Applications with PHP 
     

    


19,May,2004



       
       urlLink Designs for Working       Who, after all, has a direct interest in creating diverse, vital spaces that foster creativity and serendipity? Employers do. On the fortieth anniversary of its publication, "Death and Life" has been reborn as a primer on workplace design.      
     

    


19,May,2004



       
       urlLink my furl page 
     

    


19,May,2004



       
      Testing why it doesn't show up as a recent post.
     

    


19,May,2004



       
       urlLink Let Windows Grep do the searching - ZDNet UK Insight 
     

    


18,May,2004



       
      If your getting this error message: "Could not open the requested SVN filesystem" then you probably have a permissions issue. Or your SVNPath is wrong.
     

    


17,May,2004



       
       urlLink The Webby Awards: 2004 Nominees & Winners 
     

    


17,May,2004



       
      Music - Kellers Cellar - Birds of a feather on  urlLink Gone Phishin 
     

    


11,May,2004



       
      Music - Kellers Cellar -  urlLink The Slip  - album does - so dope
     

    


11,May,2004



       
       urlLink Stats about all US cities - maps, race, income, education, crime, weather, area codes, zip codes, similar cities 
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink iStockphoto.com - royalty free stock photography community 
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink Benchmarking Filesystems on Linux    For those of you still reading, congrats! The conclusion is obvious by the "Total Time For All Benchmarks Test." The best journaling file system to choose based upon these results would be: JFS, ReiserFS or XFS depending on your needs and what types of files you are dealing with. I was quite surprised how slow ext3 was overall, as many distributions use this file system as their default file system.  
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink 300 Images From 1800 Sites   Icons from 1800 sites compared: Arrows, Posts, Mail, Comments, Bullets, Print, and shopping carts. 
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink Migrating from PHP 4 to PHP 5 
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink High Peaks Venture Partners 
     

    


10,May,2004



       
       urlLink Linux on Linksys 
     

    


09,May,2004



       
       urlLink Performance Tuning with Jfluid 
     

    


05,May,2004



       
       urlLink evhead 
     

    


04,May,2004



       
       urlLink magic bike :: wireless internet 
     

    


04,May,2004



       
       urlLink O'Reilly Network: The Fuss About Gmail and Privacy: Nine Reasons Why It's Bogus [Apr. 18, 2004] 
     

    


04,May,2004



       
      Got the new template now.
     

    


04,May,2004



       
      Need a bunch of posts here to fully test it.
     

    


04,May,2004



       
      This is a link to  urlLink petefreitag.com 
     

    


04,May,2004



       
      Keep on testing the posts.
     

    


04,May,2004



       
      Adding another post.
     

    


14,June,2004



       
       urlLink listen to live shows bonaroo, etc. 
     

    


09,June,2004



       
       urlLink Linux commands 
     

    


06,June,2004



       
       urlLink Firewalling with netfilter/iptables LG #103 
     

    


02,June,2004



       
       urlLink ieCapture - the PC cousin of iCapture  Browser snapshots for windows browsers.
     

    


08,July,2004



       
       urlLink SmartStart Venture Forum 
     

    



