









11,September,2002



           
      

10,September,2002



           
      As well, please enjoy the great feeling of stating your own opinion without feeling that you are being watched...there is good security in this.
     

        


10,September,2002



           
      This is a Blog for the Green Family to keep in communication with each other. Please use the site for communication in the family.   9/10/2002 6:45:46 PM | Stephen Olson] Well today I was at Dr. Dwyer's and managed to do some real good work with feeling accomplished. Also Richard from the CCA took me to Granville Street and Broadway to try to get into the new course through the Vancouver School Board. This is to complete the grade 11 math that I have to complete and it's better to do this in a structured setting. All I really need is to get a transcript from the Counselling office and then mange to give this to the 41st and Fraser location the John Oliver school location.   Things that are not right for me:   1. I sometimes have difficulty with defensiveness.   2. I do have trouble with relationships that are close to me, intimacy.   3. I have trouble with working with people who are close to me intimatly.   4. I have trouble with personal awareness many times.   5. I feel that I have to ask questions to feel at ease with others so that they will accept me and so that I will stay in their boundries.   6. Taking risks is difficult for me sometimes.   7. Feeling comfortable with others has always been a challange, and sometimes doing the basic requirements of life is difficult for me.   8. Sometimes I have trouble with procrastination with things that I don't want to do.   9. Budgeting and future planning is a challange for me.   10. Organizing is fine if I have the tools to do so, and time planning usually is the most difficult because it takes the most time to do.   11. I have difficulty using the telephone correctly sometimes esp. when it comes to personal converstaions with family.   12. I find myself being very able to handle a restricted lifestyle, but when it comes to a more complexities I tend to run into problems.   13. I find knowing and using skills that I have already quite enjoyable but learning new skills seem to take time developing, especially person to person skills.   I have to say to Mom that, I need to claim my independence of family even though I am almost 40 years of age at the moment.  Mom, you have done this yourself, and have continued to do this over time. I on the other hand have a non-grown child inside of me that is not fully a developed child.   My child's development has been stiffled by the fact that I have been put in a protected environment, and the outside world has not had any way of getting to me for a long time. So obviously I could not learn about this world since I was apart from it.  My difficulty now is that I need to know more about this world and understand more fully what this world means to me personally.   Inside my confidence has not grown in the world, since I was not in the world but kept apart from the world. You, Mom, have claimed your independence, and are a fully developed adult, and I need the chance to become one myself. I am just now comming to the point where I am comming out of the house emotionally as an adolecent.   This is a very crutial point.   I can feel shure and say that I feel reall good that this time has come. I now have to learn about the world around me much more than  others who are already fully developed adults.   Yes, I have asked for help from you, Mom, and asked you to be my coach, but you have to understand something. A child does whine, and cry when they are not feeling safe and a teenager does go against the wishes of their parents. I never really rebeled, I never really stated my independence from you.   I feel that I need to claim this independence, and state my position and claim my individualness as every adult has done.  I understand that nobody really rebells outrightly most of the time but they do claim their space and their own area of personal development.  You already know that I am very independent, and have always been independent and have had a hard time being together with another person because of my need for freedom.  This need for freedom, is very important for me.  I need to feel free enough to be able to state myself, and be free thinking.  As well as this motion is very important to me.  I need to be able to get away from things physically, and exert energy to this end.    I also need to have home as a place of rest and relaxation, and a place to get away from the world and escape into my own reality.  I ask for your help, and for Ron's, but I need this in moderation.  The problem for me is figuring out what moderation is.  What I need help with is finding out the middle ground, and the moderate.  I tend to do the extream thing whatever it may be. I tend to go beyond what is normal, and I don't do enough of what is within the boundries of normal.  The idea here generally is that I need to be moderated, but in a way that is not so direct maybe.         
     

        


12,November,2003



           
       urlLink Vancouver Community College - News & Events 
     

        



