

29,May,2004


	 
      right. so title is so correct.    so rebecca was like she no want to talk to you so i blogged and got all angry  and charlene apparently read it. and emailed me saying she'll talk to me she just needs space and to give her a week and how she still wants to be friends. see rebecca? i win!But not really. im sorry. v_v but anger loses! cause it didnt help really. so im actually im pretty okay. well. i watched the ziggy + max video with mary. and cried the whole time with my mary.  and also im confused by charlenes info.... but i dont think im going to talk about charlene for a week. and i think im just going to hang out the mac lab. or something. END TRANSMISSION  o also i dont think im going to be updating normal blog taht much
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
      guh. hatred well no not hatred just wallowing in sadness. as much as you may want to save me. i dont want to drag you into it. its not a "save yourself! forget about me!"and really i want you to be there. it's just a im in pain and not much you can say can change it unless you change other people. so im trying to sleep. and all i can think of  are horrible things. that's why I hate high school drama.Because its over active enough and then my mind makes it worse. Like imaging charlene getting shot and me not being able to say goodbye. even though i know its not true it still makes my eyes tear and worsens my mood. my dear that charlene and noah are secretly sending emails about how good last night was. not true but it still makes me hate everyone. just all this crap that i dont need.at all. It's really hard to forgive and remeber compassion. i think ill distract my self
     

    


25,May,2004


	 
      so all i did today was listen to the beatles and try to rember what i was going to say. and i forgot and it was in front of noah. and i fucking hate this.; how she cares and then she doesnt make up your mind. good christ it may not mean anything to you but if im going to move on i need closure. and if you dont want me to tell me. christ......
     

    


25,May,2004


	 
      wow. a title that makes sense. So yeah. charlene obviously did not want me there at all. and her mom got angry at her.for pouting. and was upset that we weren't talking. and she tried including charlene in the conversation. and asked me if charlene was hurting me and i said no and that she was treating me okay. regardless of truth i didnt want her yelled at. so her mom was nice. and charlene was there i guess just to because her mom told her to be. Anita joked about how there'd be a slap fight once i left.... i laughed politely but was scared inside. so then i left kinda. or said i was leaving and then evan distracted me and we talked about magic the gathering.and then charlene and her mom came out and charlene was really sad.they went into the van to go to scotties.Evan talked about how lame it was the she cried about her friends problems.... This is all so confusing but i think brad might know how to reach someone in the victim mode. .......so my ex's family likes me.but my ex doesn't.her mom is a bit mean to her but im not with them so i cant really judge.but her brother just sees it as crazy girls and not kindness and caring. i think i might know whats wrong.or at least why she goes with noah.This is just a guess.Her family likes me.and chooses me.And they don't know about noah.So in rebellion in love life? no idea.I need to know what she's so scared about and why she's hurt so much.
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
      another thing is this supposed jealosouy she has. im unsure wheter the turn the other cheek and not do what she's doing by not flirting with rebecca in front of her. or by playing it up so much that she thinks me and rebecca are married.   i don't even know how she got that. me and rebecca rarely even hug. Charlene on the other hand jumps on guys. actually the most physical activity between me and rebecca involves rebecca hitting me. which isn't that romantic.and rebeccas weak so she hurts herself. cause her bones are made of ash and mine are made of titaanium becuse i am so strong and i work out daily.All the time.  ....sarcasm....i just take karate. which i probaly wont take this week because the sun hates my flesh. I dont get tan. I get pain. guh SELF_DESTRUCT
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
      I'm so confused about everything. and because im not balanced my diet is not balanced. I want to eat. but all the food at school disgusts me. and water in the morning upsets my stomach. and of course theres an urge to vomit. my brain feels....oiled, greased, unhealthy.i need to get it out. also theres this happiness i can't get rid of. I think because im unbalanced my emotions are going crazy. either that or im bi polar. but i wasnt bi-polar before. and hence the happiness isn't true. it's just a fake euphoria. guh. i really don't want to go crazy. because im liking charlene but i don't know what we would talk about. If i found out what she was afraid of i could try to fix it or least ask brad and he could help me.*poof*
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
      im pretty sure im going insane. because im liking charlene again  audience of rebecca and maddi:NO!!! idiot 

23,May,2004


	 
      I feel better. I found this one song that is like my entire childhood.I love it. Plus i think charlene might like me. I know i know. why would i go back with someone that stabs me in the stomach multiple times. it's the only relationship i've ever wanted to have back again. I mean you know look at brenna.She and david love each other dearly and they have really emotional breakups.I actually dont want to have a breakup every weekend.It's just everything was so great with her.just being with her. plus if we got back together we could be stronger than ever. o well. whatever happens.
     

    


23,May,2004


	 
      i feel so much better one getting all of that out and then calming down. i listend to songs from my childhood. not lulabies just the 90s love music. what my mom and dad listened to. and i talked to charlenes mom and im going to get homeopathic remedies. ill probaly worry about it tommorow because ill have to be with her and i want to give her space. but ill be able to endure hooray for euphoria guh so much crap and its gone. life you never cease to amaze me. thank you
     

    


20,May,2004


	 
      all im in is a world full of hate and depression. i dont know anything anymore she doesnt care about me  I'M IN GOD DAMN PAIN DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT! but that's selfish when i told her i was cutting  she said it was okay just make sure i didnt get addicted ITS NOT OKAY IM NOT LIKE THIS I DONT DO THIS DONT YOU SEE WHAT HAS HAPPENED why do i go to ex-girlfriends swim parties all it is is them showing me (physically) that they dont need me they hug every guy but me they go everyone but me they conect with everyone but me and they care about everyone but me so im just left trying to feel good with the other people. but its never enough. its not ever anything. its just her and some guy. and in this case its noah and charlene flirting and playing together. and me just standing there hoping she'll notice me. why can't you just try to get along with me why do you have to be like this. i dont think i can go on youthquest. im too depressed and id probaly die. god i just want her to call me or talk to me just ask are you okay? instead she just flirts with everyone else. and everyone says, "oh you dont deserve her, shes  nothing , its just a high school relationship, shes just being a bitch, why would you want to be with someone who hurts you?" and then after talking about how much of a horrible person she is, go over and make jokes and hug her adn laugh with her. and thats why its so hard to take anyone seriously i try hiding as far away as possible. hoping someone will find me. but no one looks. no one cares. and thats the worst feeling anyone can have everyone says wait shell come to you so i just wait. and she doesnt move towards me just away. I dont think im going to school tommorow. or tuesday. so ill probaly see you wedendsday. or ill wake up forget about the intensity of suffering and go to school tommorow adn then go through another self-hating day.then say the same thing. *sigh* I hate my life I hate her I hate all the happy times we had. I hate rembering her laugh I hate trying to hold a space in my heart in case she wants to be with me I hate hurting cause she's with someone else. I hate hurting because she just moves away from me I hate her ignoring me all the time. I hate how whenever i try to talk to her anymore nothing happens. I hate wanting to kill myself. I hate how everytime i cry i want to go to her and show her im crying. I hate every song that i've heard that has to do with love is just fucking pain I hater her so much for all of this. im sick of trying not to blame her. she gets pissed and rants why can't i? I hate every fucking thing thats ever existed. im just sunburned and spazzing. and she probaly is just htinking of noah she says she doesnt know anyone. maybe its because she doesnt want to listen. If only i could stab myself then i would be so free. of all this bullshit I hurt and she just smiles and hugs noah. then only reason she cared about why i was hurting  was she doesnt want to be hated. I hate how i ask her, how are you? just silently hoping she'll care enough to ask how i am. why cant you help attain closure? are you too busy flirting with noah? or do you give everyone as much love as possible just to make sure i dont get any? It doesnt matter what you did! these dont make you what you are! you are who you are by interacting with people!! why does it matter how things started? the past is dead. you cant do anythinig about it. why does it matter? The only reasons i hate you is because i love you do you understand how much it hurts? to have someone you cherish so much , reject you? how they give you so many promises, only to really be lieing about them. "all i want for my birthday is you" thas probaly the most painful one. that and  "i love you" how can you lie to someone like that? what gives you the right to lie to someone? to say here is love and then just take it awawy im going to stop. because otherwise ill just repeat myself. ..
     

    


20,May,2004


	 
      I don't know her anymore. IN my regular blog i said she didnt chagne. but now realizing it, she has. she no longer cares. thats probaly it  shes not trying to make this easy. shes not trying at all! if you want to be my friend, include me! instead of listing everyone but me! ..... I think one of the reasons i want her is that i know her. And now that i dont know her. im just in hell. shes not helping to try to patch things. shes just hugging noah and flirting with him. and when maddi breaks up with him it'll just be them admitting how they've felt this way for a long time. It's either karma or ironic. her breaking up with noah made me and her go out and her breaking up with max, is probaly causing charlene and noah to go out. If only she cared...
     

    


20,May,2004


	 
      ....... guh. everything was okay. nothing serious happend its just that i walked home from northgate and retraced what happened on certain days guh just a tad bit sad./obsessive iunno.i didnt really mean to be. its just hard memories to get out. i dont know if im ever going to show her this blog.....
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      I dont know whats going to happen toda but it feels like something might.i hope thats the right speling.my stomach is a negative empty pain void again. i dont even know if i can go out with her anymore.I 've moved so far that it'l probaly take some time before I could go out with her., assuming this soehow happened.The best route is probaly her friend because itll be a lot easier to make desions.or something.i dont know.
     

    


18,May,2004


	 
      So today was an emotional day. I felt really empty in first I mean actual physical pain empty. So then for break I couldn’t find Rebecca. Or mary. So I went and blogged earlier. So with my arm  quite literally“under wraps” I looked a while and then found her. We went to THE BENCH And I couldn’t speak So instead I pantomimed while hyper ventilating. And then once I get the point across Charlene comes. It was so random And she starts touching me and my head buzzes And my arms I try pushing her away. I really couldn’t have her touching me  It hurt so much So then I went to stroeh with Rebecca. And I couldn’t talk about it either. So I just stood there and cried. And Rebecca told/pantomimed. So then stroeh let us go into a practice room. And I couldn’t feel my legs And my head was still buzzing. My legs actually scared me Cause I couldn’t feel them. But  I felt this huge amount of pressure building on them. As if I was on an airplane. And my feet started twitching. So then I talked and then Rebecca led me through a Guided Meditation. Oh my god. There was one point. I couldn’t control my body. I was shaking so hard. Because we got to a part Where she talked about my brother. And having a conversation with him And I did And I cried and my mouth wouldn’t stop shaking and neither did my body. I swear to god it was the first time  I ever thought to him And she said how he came down And and how we all go through this just to come together to be united. But when I talked to him It was him I felt it. So we almost had complete cleanseing but then my cell phone rang and then the office came in cause I ha to go for the Kaiser appointment.kinda. Cause they caught me an hour before I had to go So I requested a empty room and I wanted Rebecca to be with me So I got into a room and played stepmania on the laptop. Then Rebecca came in and we talked and I showed her my arm. Which was grossified.cause there was blood mixing with the dressing. So then we talked about stuff and Rebecca made the best hat ever.and I love it and cherish even now.And it looked cute on Rebecca.She looked like a mouse captain. And then we talked about private stuff.  And then we just happened to hear how bill Higgins got an in house suspension. And nodded and laughed about what he did. Like how he was in a food fight. It was fun and I smiled. I love that hat. So then I walked to my therapist meeting and talked bout everything and had to re-adjust my transparent bandage.Then I went to the mall and got Thai food.SOUP and sticky rice. Good stuffs. Then told Garcia that I couldn’t do cpr. I looked around and found baby manacins.I got out of there as fast as I could and started to write this! And now I just heard how Charlene is somehow taking offense about me not being able to receive her care.i just don’t know anymore. She walked right past me at the end of school and then had a conversation with her mom in the car, and then sat in the back so she “wouldn’t be seen” (I guess) in the car. Its not an insult.its not revenge.  i dont know what to do or say anymore
     

    


17,May,2004


	 
      Im panicing i cant find mary or rebecca andi dont want to ask rebecca  or really tell rebecca cause then she'll think im selfish im so stupid this didnt make anything better andi get the blood out of my mind. fuck I cant do anything right
     

    


17,May,2004


	 
      I cant beleive myself it was over something stupid too i just looked at it. adn just shredded my skin. and i couldnt  control myself and i just saw so much blood. and i tried to wash it  and it just stung and burned. it hurt so much and my mom came in. it was over something stupid and she saw it and cried and i said its not a big deal! it small cuts theyre just bleeding a lot and she says,"max they're fucking bleeding" and i don't know  it was just how i felt it wasnt a big deal It wasnt anything so then through much crying we got it cleaned up and i am now the proud owner of three band aids and i dont even feel that  bad at all i dont even feel sad but to those who read this DON'T TELL CHARLENE at all cause otherwise she ll just guilt trip and what not and its honestly not her fault. I feel almost giddy maybe im just high after pain i mean i just am looking around and i think suicide is funny its quite an interesting expiarnce actually 
     

    


16,May,2004


	 
      i read through charlenes old blogs just ot build some self hate. i dont know how she doesnt care. why would she do this?   
     

    


16,May,2004


	 
      i think i know why charlene mattered  i didnt do anything without her. not like we did everything together but like i do nothing now that shes not there i keep opening and closing internet explorer obsessively updating and checking my mail evrey ten seconds and looking at my cell phone to make sure i didnt miss any calls.  i dont have a life.
     

    


16,May,2004


	 
      ........... I think i always thought she felt the exact same way. so it hurts so much. to have her not care at all about me. i no one knows why she did it but her and if i talk to her about it itll cause another argument 
     

    


16,May,2004


	 
      beh...sad  I think i know what made me so obsessed with charlene i have an obsessive personality there has to be something that i need to obsesse about last year it was ddr summer and this was magic and this time its charlene i check her blog everyday to wonder if she typed anything i check my email to see if she sent me anything and i make sure i didnt miss a call from her but shes more than even that. she everything i've wanted. the unfortuante thing is shes not like me in that way she just wants to be with everyone not stay with one person. god i love her
     

    


14,May,2004


	 
      so this is the more emotional one that not many people will ever see this one makes me feel better this happened sometime ago by the way. charlygrl666 (7:07:53 PM): what do you mean a hint?  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Auto response from maxownsworld (7:07:53 PM): stuffas  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  charlygrl666 (7:08:09 PM): i talked about that so that you would just shut up about being so confused as to what love is charlygrl666 (7:08:17 PM): everything's relative!!! charlygrl666 (7:08:22 PM): there is no definition!! charlygrl666 (7:08:45 PM): everyone has different reasons for loving someone, therefore their experience of love will always vary charlygrl666 (7:09:08 PM): aaaahhhrthghghahkadshfl;kahsdf what did you mean a hint please do not tell me that you thought i was hinting at another relationship charlygrl666 (7:11:01 PM): max that was two years ago charlygrl666 (7:11:22 PM): if it scarred you so much, why try to start another relationship charlygrl666 is away at 8:35:16 PM.  maxownsworld (9:46:24 PM): what  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Auto response from charlygrl666 (9:46:24 PM): brb call if u wanna talk 479-4791  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  maxownsworld (9:46:30 PM): no not hint like that maxownsworld (9:46:42 PM): hint as in this is what you probaly did maxownsworld (9:46:56 PM): its not really scarring maxownsworld (9:47:09 PM): its like...failsafes maxownsworld (9:47:33 PM): word meaning ..well an example would be a backup kind of maxownsworld (9:47:41 PM): a failsafe to make sure this doesn't happen maxownsworld (9:47:59 PM): mergancy fire etuingeshers ......i can spell maxownsworld (9:49:09 PM): maybe its "not i love you beacause of this this this" kiond of thing(just as an example of what your saying how love is different for everything maxownsworld (9:49:12 PM): *ecveryone maxownsworld (9:49:41 PM): **everyone maxownsworld (9:50:36 PM): its more maxownsworld (9:50:57 PM): i want to be with this one person every single heartbeat of the world ever has maxownsworld (9:51:48 PM): its ..trying to join maxownsworld (9:51:58 PM): at least i think maxownsworld (9:52:06 PM): hence the idea of yin and yang maxownsworld (9:52:25 PM): and how all sexual acts are trying to connect the bodies physically maxownsworld (9:52:46 PM): and be one maxownsworld (10:01:07 PM): look i'm sorry for making you feel depresed maxownsworld (10:01:15 PM): and sorry for making sorry worthless maxownsworld (10:04:36 PM): i think i have two minds  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Auto response from charlygrl666 (10:04:37 PM): brb call if u wanna talk 479-4791  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  maxownsworld (10:04:46 PM): because they keep saying diffrent things maxownsworld (10:09:49 PM): i am unsure wheter or not to call.. maxownsworld (10:48:25 PM): you ever coming back?  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Auto response from charlygrl666 (10:48:25 PM): brb call if u wanna talk 479-4791  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  maxownsworld (10:48:33 PM): cause im pretty sure its too late too call maxownsworld (10:49:28 PM): meowwwwwwwww maxownsworld (10:49:37 PM): comeone  maxownsworld (10:49:40 PM): *on maxownsworld (10:49:46 PM): 

14,May,2004


	 
      This blog is just for me and a select few, hence the name.I want to , bitch at the world so to speak.Really its just a way to describe everything i want to without being criticized.I spell good.  so first me and charlene have conversation. like 2 seconds. i try to say i am hurt she takes it as you bitch you hurt me or something of the sort. she redirects that the times i broke up with her hurt her. i dont know why she's angry with me. it's said that people think about sex every ten seconds when i do that reminds me of charlene and hence a feeling of pain its not even that graphioc its not even graphic at all. its just pain. having to sneak behind her in the play hurt but i was able to get through it. seeing her skipping with noah after made me shout out in pain. i think about what i'll do next.all the time.what im going to say if this happens, etc. i hate the fire alarm on the stage. seeing make me fear ill pull it. i always have a fear i'll do something wrong. drop the coffin, trip, start swearing, it doesnt matter its just always there. fear.im ranting. whatever   so all the way back to charlene after school conversation. her excuse of why im hurting is because shes hurting because i hurt her.  it wasn't what i expected at all it wasn't what i thought would happen. it was in the end too much. i go slowly then fastly to jenny and with pure anger in my heart and then just breakdown. i cried. jenny walks with me to the kaiser i push her away when she tries to hug me not forcefully, just enouygh to move her. dj drives by with mary. asks if we want a ride. as im still crying,me and jenny cross the street and get in the car. i cant speak, it gets hard to breathe and i get fidgety with my seatbelt.i couldnt get it on my hands didnt stop shaking until 20 minutes after i got home. on the way to my house my lip starts to bleed. i clutch marys hand as we go by charlene's house. i try to get the mucous out of my throat but this just makes me want to vomit. once dj drops me off mary walks me in and i go to my bed and cry into my pillow i just kept saying why wont you listen. i didnt even mean to say it it was just coming out when i was resting on my bed i just wished charlene was there i dont think i could have managed if she was it would probably have made it worse. but it didnt matter to me apparently i even called her but i couldnt look at the screen because i had preset it to say charlene the sexiest girl in the world i typed that all without looking at the screen .. i really dont want to see it at all her brother answered so i hung up so then i call rebecca i couldn't talk so i imed her while she spoke to me on the phone my hands shook the entire time it was hard to write making out after 20 minutes of this i was able to talk to her on the phone her as in rebecca and then i calmed down. if she was physically there i wouldnt have been able to talk. why is she angry at me? i didnt do anyting she wants to be friends why does she hate me? because it hurts her? probaly. cant she understand that when your hurt you say things that when your mad at someone you dont say kind things and she still insists that i am going around her back spreading rumors i .. i give her space i go out of my way to go out of hers i don't let her see me cry and scream "this is all your fault!" i dont spread rumors about her i dont call her a whore i dont call her a bitch i dont call her anything   and the thing i didnt tell anyone once i got out of dj's car, i was going to slit my wrists end everything ive never had so strong an urging. i cant even touch the nail clipper. i wish this was over so i can just stop thinking about it i just want the pain to end
     

    


24,June,2004


	 
      so in my attempts to get -------- out of my mind, i'm not looking at her blog becaues that's pretty much is just...uncomfortable.It's weird and it's her talking about how much better of a life she is having and whatever. Anyways. I play dela which used to calm me down.And it brings back a lot of sealed wounds, which open up and blood sprays everywhere where stiches once were.Metaphorically speaking.I have never gotten stitches in my life nad my cuts are healing pretty good.Eh.Just thought i'd complain 
     

    


21,June,2004


	 
      eh i just looked at charlene's blog and yeah she has changed....*sigh* i need this poison out of my veins. oh well..,..
     

    


20,June,2004


	 
      this whole thing is driving me into memory fantasies.Simply put i remember nearly everything that happened all four times.From how her shirt fellt to what she said. As sexually appealing as this is it;s not good because i keep thinking that person is the same charlene as she is now.and maybe she is.*sigh* who knows  okay done complaining.  so how are you?
     

    


20,June,2004


	 
      brennamonkey (2:37:07 AM): hey, you there? charlygrl666 returned at 2:37:32 AM.  charlygrl666 is away at 2:37:49 AM.  brennamonkey (2:37:57 AM): ... um ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Auto response from charlygrl666 (2:37:58 AM): i most certainly like your pants around your feet.  ------------------------------------------------------------------------  charlygrl666 (2:38:23 AM): its' a song and i don't know you  charlygrl666 returned at 2:38:23 AM.  charlygrl666 (2:38:26 AM): goodbye brennamonkey (2:38:30 AM): i'm brenna brennamonkey (2:38:37 AM): a friend of max. charlygrl666 (2:38:46 AM): oh the one he cheated on vicki with charlygrl666 (2:38:46 AM): hi brennamonkey (2:38:51 AM): yeah, hi charlygrl666 (2:38:58 AM): nice to meet you charlygrl666 (2:39:02 AM): max told me a lot about you charlygrl666 (2:39:04 AM): but i g2g now brennamonkey (2:39:12 AM): the pleasure's all in this state brennamonkey (2:39:18 AM): no, i need to ask you something really quick brennamonkey (2:39:25 AM): it's been itching at the back of my brain charlygrl666 (2:39:28 AM): k  charlygrl666 (2:39:29 AM): go brennamonkey (2:39:36 AM): do you still care for max? charlygrl666 (2:39:41 AM): as a friend brennamonkey (2:39:44 AM): nothing more? charlygrl666 (2:39:46 AM): nothing more charlygrl666 (2:39:48 AM): middle man charlygrl666 (2:39:49 AM): bye brennamonkey (2:39:52 AM): ha brennamonkey (2:39:54 AM): fuck you too. charlygrl666 is away at 2:39:58 AM.  brennamonkey (2:40:08 AM): he's an emotional train wreck because of you ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Auto response from charlygrl666 (2:40:08 AM): i most certainly like your pants around your feet.  ------------------------------------------------------------------------  brennamonkey (2:40:10 AM): and you insult me brennamonkey (2:40:14 AM): you're a wonderful person.    so yeah....i didnt put brenna up to this and i told her to be agressive.but hey brenna is an independant person.
     

    


19,June,2004


	 
      so yeah im glad charlene didnt come that wouldnt have helped and seeing her hit on ryan would have sucked. and seeing other people join with charlene hitting on ryan with her would suck *cough "rebecca!"*   eh no you have more respect for people.you probaly wouldnt do that. i guess.i feel wasted right now so it;s good to ignore what i say ... gight
     

    


19,June,2004


	 
       My Horoscope Capricorn You may look like you have a tough exterior, but underneath it all, you can be as fluffy and sweet as a marshmallow. Don't be afraid to expose your soft side once in a while. You will get an opportunity to show your true feelings to someone whom you care about. If you take advantage of it, the moment will be treasured. Take the time to enjoy where you are right now, instead of focusing on where you want to be in the future. Don't wish your life away. Remember, tomorrow is always a d  i for some reason missed copying the rest which makes this anti climactic. but the middle part is good.specailly cause movie party tonight and bridget and maddi today! what an omazing coincedence. also im pushing charlene out of my mind.and all of that stuff.and all expectations.eempty empty, happy happy  and i'm lisetning to eric clapton and bob dylan
     

    


18,June,2004


	 
      i need to get drunk this summer.SO drunk i dont think about anything.But i'll need people around me to make sure i dont hurt myself or anyone.  Someone to make sure i dont die. because if the alcohol didn't kill me I .... i know.. i dont want to die. i just dont want to be here 
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
      So I want charlene. but i don't know what would happen It's knowing that the stuff that i need is poison. so i don't really know if i want charlene. because it hurts talking/thinking/seeing her.Mere mentions cause shortness of breath, increased blood pressure, and a faster heartbeat. so what do i want?   the person I love is the person i hate is the person i want is the person that hurts is the person that helps if you knew how much you meant to me maybe you'd understand
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
      yay fetal position!!! ffhiegrgjnrgl
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
      guh. so give up everything to the divine. give all suffering and pain and charlene scenario. all the stuff i can't handle. give it all to the divine. and i felt great. I no longer had the responsibilities or the pressure. just me   i look at charlene's blog, see the word "him" and freak out... everything comes crashing back. over something that isn't even used ina provactive sentence. fuck....
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
      from maddi's blog  "If there is one person you can't stop thinking about, post this same exact sentence in your journal." 
     

    


12,June,2004


	 
      You want her You need her And yet you don't believe her When she says her love is dead You think she needs you  And in her eyes, you see nothing No sign of love behind the tears. Cried for no one A love that should have lasted years   i found it in a friends info.i relate to it and it scares me that it was just there.... speaking of scared i figured out 98% of why relationship broke up. So it's like this two different sources of fear starting from the same thing: her being with me and me taking too much of her time. or something along those lines.  another thing was i was talking with my therapist and he says what happens is people think that these are cause by the relationship but usually thsese things were already in their mind but the relationship just brought them up.  so the two "seperate" fears:  1)she feels that she is forgetting herself.  2)she is scared because she's paranoid about people who obsess over her.  so these two interact with each other. 1 could have to do with that fact that she spent so much time with me and therefore feels she is neglecting her life and what she's going to do or something like that. or it could be just transition into herself, known as being a teenager. But this would explain her need for maine cause apparently according to caitlin this is where she was born. SO she's retracing her memories.  so 2nd stems from same thing of attention and whatnot.essentially self-explanatory. W/e. i'm going too much into this.at least i didn't look at her house today.I don't know why i do that......  I'm just confused about this.which is a main excuse for not looking at the truth.
     

    


11,June,2004


	 
      stuff that i didn't say: so reason akward was i expected ptak to be in his class.So i go there and it's charlene's brother evan,chelsey, and charlene. Seeing them i back out and put my finger to my lips to imply evan to shut up.Evan apparently never learned this as he yelled "max!!! what are you doing here" so i left immediatly.and evan came after yelling some more and chelsey followed and together we shut evan up. christ. and evan kept saying how he didn't understand why she hates me.i didnt know that she hated me...he could have misinterpeted. anyways. i wrote insanely in my journal at silberman's. 8 pages of logic and philosophy.i'll show "you" sometime.Just because i need a sanity check. it's....all i've learned about right speech and a computation of what went wrong which i've got mostly figured out.a few more pieces and i could solve it.
     

    


10,June,2004


	 
      So when i come crying out of the drama room rebecca and claire come in.And claire talks to me about how I really matter in her life and how i made some of her crappy days a lot better.I didn't really know what to say. Her voice got near crying so i didn't know what to do really, so I hugged her. I'm kinda confused about it...  There's other stuff but i'd rather tell it someone in person.But only if it rises up cause it's charlene stuff and i don't want to keep mentioning it ovr and over.
     

    


06,June,2004


	 
      so i have my sudden burst of confidence and i want to be friends with charlene. im going to say one thing in person. and then we'll see what happens. hopefully we'll become friends
     

    


05,June,2004


	 
      Im letting go. i just keep drawing back whenever theres anything to do with her. I dont know if we can be friends. your not the person i once knew.  i can't get you out of my head.  I feel so empty.  i have hope we could be friends charlygrl666 (9:35:26 AM): max people break up all the time and you can get over it charlygrl666 (9:35:51 AM): you don't need to do count-downs, tell other people, write obsessively in your blog and such  so this is her caring.....i guess.. i dont know. i dont know how we could become friends if it hurts to be around her. but it hurt to be around brenna.and now it doesnt.   i could see us become friends.But then i cant nothing would be the same. she would never trust to be alone with me but she could if i let go or could she?   its not my fault. i can let go
     

    


05,June,2004


	 
      all i'm left with is self-loathing and loathing for her. she makes this big deal of why. and then its the simplest and yet most complex thing in the world I know that she cares i guess.
     

    


05,June,2004


	 
      because all of the anger is prety much gone. and my insanity went away. see ive been plotting and trying to predict what will happen and create responses all this week.But theyre always wrong. So i was trying desperatley to get my mind to not think about it so more options will be open. so that's gone. but somethinbg is weird. my neck feels like im being strangled. Ijust awoke and the thought was the in the dream i had to scratch my neck and i think i did that while i was dreaming. But it's still weird. The air isn't getting in the same way. It's like its going through a hidden tunnel. I cant feel the place of where its going. It just goes straight to my lungs.IM not even getting enough air.or at least thats what it feels like.I'm actually happy right bnow but i dont know why.I really hope im not bi-polar.
     

    


05,June,2004


	 
      IF you read charlenes xanga you'll notice that its mainly directed at one person.  You'll also notice the emphasis on I DONT LOVE ANYONE.  You'll also notice me bitching and complaining monday            how could such a being of pain feel love? I had such high hopes. I thought that people could get along.I thought that giving her a week like she asked would enable her to say what she had to say to me to end all of this suffering.Instead she just throws a dirty sentence my way.Wow. I'm glad you care about people.   What did i do to deserve this? Oh that's right I loved you.I put all my heart towards making you feel loved and making your life better.I was the only one besides your dad that came to your play.And for this i am rewarded with crap. With your amazing display of imaturity towards other people. Are you hating me just so you don't have to feel bad when were not longer friends? just making up crap so that when i retaliate you can say " my god look at what a bitch he is! can you believe he did that?"  Thank you for lisning to my rant that will  never!!  be heard by the person it was supposed to.  I will not play this game no longer. Im not going to retaliate
     

    


04,June,2004


	 
      Oh christ.... christ christ christ so much pain so much pain....... it just doesnt end. why? so much pain.............. http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=charlybob  can she not even talk to me that she has to just say that ive been waiting. im not even iming her about this. In all of my planning and expectancies this never came up.. trying to calm down with a dagger in my heart.....  i still love you......If i let go my suffering ends but im  afraid of losing her forever. if i hold on, shes going to run away.  
     

    


04,June,2004


	 
      Oh christ.... christ christ christ so much pain so much pain....... it just doesnt end. why? so much pain.............. http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=charlybob  can she not even talk to me that she has to just say that ive been waiting. im not even iming her about this. In all of my planning and expectancies this never came up.. trying to calm down with a dagger in my heart.....  i still love you......If i let go my suffering ends but im  afraid of losing her forever. if i hold on, shes going to run away.  
     

    


04,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Its me and my mary!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


04,June,2004


	 
      she didnt talk to me. I cant tell whats realy anymore. Because i think o ill see the charlene i love tommorow, the charlene that loves me and we'll be happy and everyone else will be happy and if it takes years even, we'll work this out.  adn then once i get there she doesnt say anything.She doesnt even eat lunc hin the same place.I dont even know what to do.I know its not about me and i know shes going through stuff that i have no idea about.im not trying to judge her.Im not trying to ruin her life.Without the proper information, there is no way for me to act properly. exhale pain, inhale life
     

    


02,June,2004


	 
      so yeah and charlenes info says thursday is official ask someone out day.  hooray for me..    and i was feeling so good too. i talked and therapy and everything. iunno because i thought, the exact quote of this thought was  "no matter of boyfriends i'll still love you." irony is still existant in the world
     

    


01,June,2004


	 
      i cant wait for this week to be over my crappy drama final and then charlene will finally talk to me and peace will resolve. just two more days left. and then i can get on with life or mope less whatever it will be better. I need her. dont think of it as selfish. its just i need to know who she is again. i dont know her anymore i just havea ll of the times when i knew her. but shes changed. she no longer hugs me every day and every day we go closer and closer to kissing. she's no longer the charlene i knew. and that is why im scared.....
     

    


01,June,2004


	 
      This weeks lesson is patience. patience about charlene and what nots patience about fears patience about reacting patience before i turn my head.  too many fears about the future and charlene. we'll find out what happens when we do... we as in me.... cause everyone else will probaly know by the time i do. ..
     

    



