
01,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm a little tea pot, short and stout, here is my handle, here is my spout...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    *sighs* Sephi's so pretty and graceful... I wish I was just like him... He has pretty, long hair, too...  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    



30,June,2004



       
      Abunai: *huggles Legato-chan*  Legato: Let me go! *struggles*  Abunai: No! I own you! Besides, you'd get killed out there...! *points to rabid fangirls throwing themselves against a barrier*  Legato: *gulp* I think I'll just....stay here...  Abunai: Good boy!  Legato: -_-'  posted by Abunai at 12:33 AM  Legato: *sitting on the floor* That's it! Where's my trenchcoat!? Give it back!  Abunai: No, it's too spiky and stuff, besides, I like what you're wearing now.  Legato: B-but! Trenchcoats are cool! I want mine back!  Abunai: You're right, they are cool. *hands him a trenchcoat* There you go!  Legato: This is not mine, it's dark forest green.  Abunai: So? I like it, and it's not spiky or...um, skull-ish. And it matches your dark blue shirt and your brown pants.  Legato: It does? *looks in full-length mirror that...appeared* Hmm... I guess it's ok.  Abunai: Yay! *huggles* You look great! *squeezes and lets go, then skips off into a field of flowers that...appeared...(hmmm, I see a connection)*  Legato: O.o *sigh* Never...  posted by Abunai at 12:37 AM  Abunai: Legato-chan, what'cha doing?  Legato: *twitches at the pet name* Eating...  Abunai: Oh... What'cha eating?  Legato: -_-' Hotdogs...  Abunai: Really? Yum! *grabs a hotdog, tries to run away with it, but is tackled by non-other than Legato himself*  Legato: *snarls* It's mine!  Abunai: o.o Ok ok...sheesh, here... *hands it back*  Legato: ^-^ Yay! *eats it*  Abunai: O.o  posted by Abunai at 12:38 AM  Abunai was bored. She decided to sing a song.  Crawling in my skin,  These wounds,  They will not heal,  Fear is how I fall,  Confusing what is real...   There's something inside me that pulls beneath the surface,  Consuming,  Confusing,  This lack of self-control I fear is never-ending,  Controlling,  I can't seem,  To find myself again,  My walls are closing in,  (Not a sense of confidence,  I'm convinced that there's just too much pressure to take)  I've felt this way before,  So insecure...   Crawling in my skin,  These wounds,  They will not heal,  Fear is how I fall,  Confusing what is real...   This comfort endlessly has pulled itself upon me,  Distracting,  Reacting,  Against my will I stand beside my own reflection,  It's haunting,  How I can't seem,  To find myself again,  My walls are closing in,  (Not a sense of confidence,  I'm convinced that there's just too much pressure to take)  I've felt this way before,  So insecure...   Crawling in my skin,  These wounds,  They will not heal,  Fear is how I fall,  Confusing what is real...   There's something inside me that pulls beneath the surface,  Consuming,  (Confusing what is real...)  This lack of self-control I fear is never-ending,  Controlling,  (Confusing what is real...)  posted by Abunai at 12:39 AM  Legato: Why did you sing that song?  Abunai: 'Cuz, I felt like it. Duh.  Legato: I see. And what connection does this song have to your pathetic excuse for a life?  Abunai: ... *bursts out crying* You insensitive jerk! *runs off*  Legato: O_O' Wha... What'd I do?! *chases after her*  posted by Abunai at 12:40 AM  (After running awhile, Legato comes upon Abunai in a tree overlooking a meadow.)  Legato: Oi, get down here!  Abunai: *shakes head*  Legato: Fine, I'll make you. *uses his telekinesis*  Abunai: *just sits there*  Legato: o_o' 'I can't control her? Impossible! Yet... Oh no... This is quite a confusing matter, how shall I get her down?'  (unbeknownst to Legato, Abunai is watching him intently.)  Abunai: 'Hmm... He looks quite perplexed. *smile* I should just go down there.' *appears behind him and sits there*  (Legato had no idea of what just happened, and sits down in front of Abunai, unknowingly, of course.)  Legato: *sighs as he looks into the tree, only to discover that Abunai no longer occupies the tree's branches* 'Where'd she go?' Abunai?  Abunai: *stifles a laugh as she sits there* 'I know what I'll do! *grin*'  (Legato is glomped from behind, startling him.)  Legato: *oof* Ahhh! 'No! It seems that I cannot move, though it is probably just her.' *sigh*  Abunai: *giggle* Je t'adore, aussi, Legato. ^-^  Legato: 'What did she say...' O.o Um, ok...  Abunai: *squeal*  Legato: 


17,July,2004


						
						      I'm sorry for the following expletiveness of this, but I’m pretty fucking mad.  Oh...My...God... Ok... It is 6:24 AM... I have not slept. I could not sleep. And guess what happens when my mother finds this out? Well, it's the summer, so I don't really have to go to sleep, so she doesn't get angry if I'm awake. But lately, she's in a really pissy mood. I think it's because of my room... *screams* DAMN HER! *another frustrated scream* As soon as she finds out I'm awake, she calls me. And what does she call me for? To find a hair tie. A...fucking...hair...tie... And she can't just have one of the hair ties I find for her, oh no, oh GOD no, you see, that's blasphemic. She makes me turn over the fucking couches, crawl on my knees, and look for a SPECIFIC hair tie. As she put it, 'My black hair tie that the fuckin' cat had! I put it on the table, and now it's gone!' And, of course, she can't look for it herself, oh no. She makes me do it. Answer me this, mother: You know the cat likes to play with the hair ties, why the HELL did you leave it out on the table!? HUH?! *screams again* So I find it for her. It was in her shoe. Then she has to smile and act all innocent like, as if she wasn't just yelling and screaming her head off at me, saying that it was my fault that it was missing. Nay, I say, it's her fault. She says that it's my fault, because it's my cat. But she's the one who left the hair tie out in the first place. ... Oh great, now she's yelling because I slammed the door. That was not slamming. That was angrily pushing it closed, but not slamming. If you want slamming, I'll make the house shake. I've done it before, I'll do it again. God, I hate her, I really, really do. Yet again I wonder why she has friends at all. Supposedly, she's all fun when she's out with them, but I, oh, I dunno, embarrass her because I am who I am, or something completely idiotic like that. Before, I was glad that she was already gone when I left for school, because she couldn't stop me from wearing what I wanted to, but I noticed that when I was going to summer school, and she had to take me with her to work first, it was always 'Take off your chains, why are you wearing those straps, can't you wear something besides black all the time?' Schließen Sie Ihr Gesicht, Dirne! And now, she's yelling at me again. She asked why I 'slammed' my door. I said because. 'Because? I'll show you BECAUSE! If your room is not clean when I get home, I'm turning off your fuckin' internet BECAUSE! If it's not clean, I'm sending you down to your dad's for the rest of the summer, BECAUSE!' Sie ist solch ein Weibchen. Ich hasse sie. Ich HASSE sie. People probably wonder how I could hate her, oh, it's easy. Très, très facile. You can ask my friends who have met her. Met her, met her, because if they've talked to her on the phone, then she's nice, and even funny, then. Mary knows. Apparently, laughing is forbidden when she sleeps. So, if only once our laughter would get a little loud, she'd storm into my room and yell/growl/speak, 'If you don't be quiet, I'm going to send Mary home...' 'But it's 1 AM, you can't...' 'Oh, believe me, I can, and I will...' Then she storms off and goes back into her room. The same room that she always compares to mine, somewhat. 'If I can keep my room clean, so can you.' Oh really? And she spends, what, maybe 3 hours tops in there awake, and the other time in there is when she's asleep, or laying on her bed. I, on the other hand, spend all of my day in my room. All of it. I leave to get food and use the bathroom, or sometimes I even go out with my friends, when my room is clean. And that's like... Once or twice a month. On average... Probably about once... So, of course it's going to get messy. Also, she won't get another phone. Another PORTABLE phone. I try to explain that I have a busy schedule, and I have more than one person to talk to, and usually, that involves the computer and phone at the same time. Therefore, I cannot be in the kitchen to talk to my friends. Plus, if one of my rare TV shows is on, I'll have to watch it, too. But she's usually on the couch, watching some stupid Law &amp; Order episode that I've seen twice, and I know she's seen because she made me watch them with her. But she can't let me change the channel, because she is ABSOLUTELY sure that she hasn't seen it, then I'll tell her the outcome, and she'll say 'oh yeah...' and change it to another station with the same exact show on it. If she's asleep, I can't change it, because she's either laying on the remote, or she'll magically wake up say scream 'I was watching that!' Tch. *yet another frustrated scream* I just don't understand why my room has to be clean! She's shown everyone the house, and she's always like 'Oh, you don't want to see in there, it's a disaster area...' ...You know what? It's just like the other room. Go straight down the hall, take a right at the very end and boom. You're at my room's theoretical clone. Theoretical because it doesn't have the same furnishings, and it smells like an old person's house in there because no one ever goes in there, and mother keeps her jars and crap like that in there. Plus, I have a bathroom to take care of. It's MY bathroom, supposedly, but everyone uses it. And no one puts the lid down, and mother cuts her bangs in there, and she brushes her hair, and primps, and yada yada yada, even though she has her own bathroom in her room to do all that crap in. I tell her that she's going to die sooner than most people, and yeah, I'll probably be sad and stuff. Whenever I tell her that she's going to die soon, she gives me this nasty look and I'm like, 'Hey, it's your fault and I was only trying to help you' because I usually say stuff like that after I talk about her smoking. I know that it's sounds like I hate her, and I do, don't get me wrong, but I'm only trying to protect her and myself from lung cancer. My friends who have heard me sing say that I have a good voice, but after I sing for like... Thirty minutes, my voice starts to die because I feel as if I have phlegm and crap in my lungs, because both her and my father have smoked all of my life. That's also another reason why I stay in my room. It's smells better, though she always has to comment on the way it smells. Well, it smells better than outside, because it smells like cigarettes, and crappy perfume, and aerosol air fresheners that make me want to hurl. I don't know why, but unnatural scents and smells usually make me want to vomit, and they nearly always give me a headache. *sighs* I have to go clean my room, or I won't have any contact to the outside world for the rest of the summer if I do not. *turns music up loud and begins to work*  Well, I think i shall write a lot today, for I have not written in...forever... I don't see the use of short posts... Anyway, so, I was supposed to go see Spiderman 2 today with everyone, but, alas, my room is not in top condition, I have no money, and no one was around to get money from. Also, I'm just lazy. On a brighter note... I drew Malcom, a character from one of my friends. He's a kitty-person!    urlLink   www.abunai-updates.blogspot.com      He's the kitty guy with bubbles surrounding him... Yeah, so... So... I also updated A Perfect Night's Dream, though, on which day I have no clue. As I said, the days just blend together. I was sure that I had updated here not just a day ago, but I come to find that it has been 4... It's sad how my brain doesn't work, isn't it? I still have made no progress on my room, and I was distracted yesterday by my old school papers, mostly from art class. As I was looking through those, I realized something: Wow, I really am better at drawing anime/manga things than I am at real stuff... 'Real stuff' does not exist to me. Well, maybe a little, but not in my art area. The more I look at the picture of Malcom, the more I get the impression that he's...high, or something... Or on an acid trip, but let us not get into that, shall we? U'n... As much as people say that I can draw well, I still see that I...can't... That's also sad. I wish I could improve, maybe go to a school, but I don't think that any of my art teachers have ever thought of Anime and Manga as art... Blasphemic fools that they are. I always see what I want to draw so clearly in my mind, but it never turns out the way that I want it. A while ago, I realized that my imagination was seemingly deterioratiing, and it kinda scared me that it would happen so soon. So, in order to grow up and continue to have my imagination, I think I've strayed a lot from TV. The only time I ever watch it is when [Adult Swim] is on, and sometimes when some show happens to catch my eye. Though I don't watch TV often, I still listen to music, and sometimes it inspires me... I guess... Ew... The Justice League is on... Stupid Marvel... *scowls* Give me anime, sheesh! I want to get Anime Network so very, very badly that it's not funny. *sighs and yawns* U'n... Anyway, today is [Adult Swim] Comedy! Yay! I wish they'd put Space Ghost Coast to Coast back on, but they cancelled it! Cancelled, after a ten year run. Damn them... I loved that show... It was so stupid and funny. And the Brak Show can't exactly fill in for it. More often than not, Brak is more stupid than funny. Aqua Teen Hunger Force is always classic. Baby Blues... No, I would gladly say goodbye to it. Mission Hill... Is okay... Well, it's 10 'o clock... Do you know where your brain is? I don't... Yay, Family Guy! I'm never tired of it... The fat kid episode. Heh. Lol. Damn you, Mop and Glo! Yay. Anyway, again. I'm kinda bored... Maybe I should draw? Damn you, ice cream! Come to my mouth... How dare you disobey me? *snore* Ah ha... Yeah. Maybe I should get into a rant. Those are always fun, right? So desu ne... Alright. What shall I rant about? What makes me angry... Suprisingly, nothing has really gotten on my nerves today... I want a guitar. Or a keyboard. I like music, so I want to make it... *sighs* Beethoven's Moonlight Sonata is so pretty... So very, very pretty... But,- OMG, did they just say that Harvey Birdman was CANCELLED?! WTF MAN!? Ok, ok! Now I have something to rant about! They keep cancelling all my favorite shows! It's stupid and blasphemic to me! Heh, emu... HA HA HA! Off-topic. I love Sea Lab 2021! Ha ha ha ha! I'ma go, Shay's on the phone and we're watching [Adult Swim]... Bye!  Well, I think I might turn the TV off and listen to some music. Du Hasst again... Hmm... Yeah... Let's see... I think I'll put my CDs on shuffle, but I'll take out Evanescence first... German should go with German, yes. So, E Nomine and Rammstein it is. Hmmm... Summer will soon be over... Kind of sucks, though... I hate school. But I love it too, it's a dilemma. *sighs* You know what? I should draw, or write, or do something productive with my life. Yet, as soon as I feel like I want to do something, I think to myself 'Naw, I'll just sit here and do nothing...' I have quite a pitiful life... Oh well... I want to clean my room as well... I actually started to clean yesterday... Or someday that was before today... I'm not sure anymore. I have a weird schedule, so things kind of run together. I'll find myself waking up at 3 PM or so, and going to bed at obscenely early hours... Or I'll actually go to bed at a decent time and wake up early, or late... Depends on my dream. If it's good, then hell, why not finish it? I'm starting to regret the whole 'phone in my room' thing. It's really annoying. I hate the phone. Hate it hate it hate it. It's one of the most annoying creations ever, however useful it may be. If it had a more soothing, less irritating sound to it, I might like it. But when your day consists of sleep, you don't like to hear 'BRING BRING BRING' an hour before you wake. Or at 2:32 AM. It makes me furious and I want to kill people for calling at such obscene hours. I mean, really. I have no choice but to sleep. Sleep is good for you. Sleep is bad for you, too. It's just like breathing. You have to do it, it's just not always healthy. I can't wait until my mother gets off her vacation. Get her out of the freaking house. Just because it's her vacation doesn't mean she has to do anything improving around the house. It's her choice, just as it is my choice to sleep the day away. It's my vacation, and, no, mother, I'm not going to spend it doing housework. Sleeping, eating, talking to my friends, and being on my computer are my 'vacation time' options. Stop making me do things for you. Ha ha, look at me, I sound so very cynical. Oh well... Though I suppose I should do something... useful... I don't have any kids to babysit, therefore no cash flow... And therefore nothing new to speak of. I think I'll take out my mangara, set them on the floor, and stare at them a while. Just for the hell of it. Because I'm bored, or something. I wish I could find that book that I've been looking for. It's annoying the crap out of me. I borrowed it from someone for so long that they just gave it to me, and now I can't find it... *sighs* I also wish that I could find Fruits Basket vol. 2... I have no idea where it went, and it makes me angry. Angry. Roar. I wish everyone would just get along. It makes me just... Furious... I wish that I could learn every language in the world so that I could understand everyones' side. Our society isn't as perfect as most perceive it to be, and other societies aren't as bad as everyone in our society sees them as. *sigh* I'm sick and tired of hearing such hate in the media, too. A song entitled 'This Is War' was playing the other day on my station on LAUNCHcast, and I thought that it sounded good. I was liking it until I heard 'I'll knock your door down and blow your fuckin' head in for my country'... It appalls me. And that jackass, what's his face country singer, 'We'll put a boot in yer ass.' Oh, go to hell, you chauvinistic pig. Really. I think it was Allan Jackson. Or whatever. And I think a Dixie Chick made fun of his song, and so he went around and bantered (though it wasn't the friendly type of bantering) her about as a bad person. Oh, come on now! If you sing a song about 'putting a boot up someone's ass', do think you'll not get a little disagreement from people about it? Huh? I'm sure that the song will give our country a good name. 'Oh, sure, sure! Everyone's free here, but if you question us, we'll shove our foots up your ass.' Hate... humans... they... should... die... (especially over-patriotic ones)  I swear, lights are playing tricks on me. I think that there are little...things...crawling around me... But it's just the sun... Damn you sun! Well, I'm out of school as of... Friday, the second of July... I passed my test in Summer school... Man, I should fail my classes more, John was right, that was fun! Now, I'm sitting in the middle of my floor, where the mess has spread from this central point like a viral infection in one who has a weak immune system. Papers are littering my floor, with empty coke bottles strewn about, along with bowls, chopsticks, and assorted types of pencils. And I can only think one thought; Ah, this is truly life. Though, my mom is pestering me about cleaning it. Hey, it's my room, and I live in it, so leave me alone. Jeeze. Anyway, my mom seems to like to take things that I don't 'use' anymore and give them to her friends... Man, she annoys me... And I, of course, don't have a lock on my door, so she thinks that she can just come in here and take whatever she pleases and rummage through all my things looking for 'something' that I have no clue of its whereabouts. So she makes me find it for her. A few weeks ago, I got a new internet (which sucks, it took three weeks just to set it up right), thus rendering my old modem useless. And so, she wants to take my old modem and give it to her friends. My response: Why can't they just buy their own damn modem, huh?! So I have to search my room, which is a disaster, for a freaking CD and a tiny little freaking book/guide thing! Urh! And she yells at me about it, of course. God, I just don't see why she has friends in the first place, or maybe they're all just idiots like her. I know Suzy is. I want to kill that woman. What my mother doesn't seem to understand is this; when she's old and decrepit, I'm the one who's going to take care of her. And guess what? Old folks home. Screw her. Just screw her. ... Oh great. Now she comes in and asks for masking tape. *twitches* Does she have to be such an idiot? I have no idea where I get my 'smart' genes from, because it's not from the person who fried his brain with meth or the one who joys in spending her time tormenting me. But I know that my life's not that bad, and I loath pity parties. So... So...  



01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink Who's Your Anime Girlfriend?    Tell me again why I took this...?
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Magical Girl Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What .hack//SIGN Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Legend Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Art Style Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Mech Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Type Are You?    Yay?
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Stereotype Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Anime Vampire Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Berserk Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Cosplay Type Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What DragonBall Girl Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What DragonBall Guy Are You?    -__-'
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Forest Creature Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Gundam Wing Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What NERV Child Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Outlaw Star Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What San-X Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Shirow Girl Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Vandread Character Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink What Inuyasha Villain Are You?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
           urlLink Who's Your Anime Boyfriend?        urlLink Who's Your Anime Boyfriend?  
    


01,January,2004


	 
        Riku    urlLink   Which Kingdom Hearts Character are You Most Like?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
    


28,February,2004


	 
        You are a  PHOENIX  in your soul and your wings make a statement. Huge and born of flame, they burn with light and power and rebirth. Ashes fall from your wingtips. You are an amazingly strong person. You survive, even flourish in adversity and hardship. A firm believer in the phrase, 'Whatever doesn't kill you only makes you stronger,' you rarely fear failure. You know that any mistake you make will teach you more about yourself and allow you to 'rise from the ashes' as a still greater being. Because of this, you rarely make the same mistake twice, and are not among the most forgiving people. You're extremely powerful and wise, and are capable of fierce pride, passion, and anger. Perhaps you're this way because you were forced to survive a rough childhood. Or maybe you just have a strong grasp on reality and know that life is tough and the world is cruel, and it takes strength and independence to survive it. And independence is your strongest point - you may care for others, and even depend on them...but when it comes right down to it, the only one you need is yourself. Thus you trust your own intuition, and rely on a mind almost as brilliant as the fire of your wings to guide you.You are eternal and because you have a strong sense of who and what you are, no one can control your heart or mind, or even really influence your thinking. A symbol of rebirth and renewal, you tend to be a very spiritual person with a serious mind - never acting immature and harboring a superior disgust of those who do. Likewise, humanity's stupidity and tendency to want others to solve their problems for them frustrates you endlessly. Though you can be stubborn, outspoken, and haughty, I admire you greatly.    urlLink   *~*~*Claim Your Wings - Pics and Long Answers*~*~*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
    


05,February,2004


	 
       My #1 result for the SelectSmart.com selector,  urlLink  What Fruit Basket Character are you?  , is  Haru  
    


05,February,2004


	 
         urlLink     urlLink Omae wa dochira  juunishi  no MEMBAA desu ka?   urlLink [koyasunomiko.com]       urlLink     urlLink Omae wa dochira  juunishi  no MEMBAA desu ka?   urlLink [koyasunomiko.com]  
    


26,March,2004


	 
               cellspacing="2" cellpadding="0" bgcolor="#000000"          height="200" bordercolor="#FF0000"

13,March,2004


	 
       urlLink       urlLink theOtaku.com: What Anime Clover Are You?  
    


13,March,2004


	 
       urlLink       urlLink theOtaku.com: What is Your Outlaw Star Personality Disorder?  
    


22,April,2004


	 
        urlLink       AH! urlLink What anime cliche are you?  The Second time around.   urlLink   
    


15,April,2004


	 
        urlLink       I've come to take you.  urlLink What character from a creepy anime are you?   urlLink   
    


15,April,2004


	 
        urlLink         Nuts-O Angel   urlLink Find out what anime villan  you are.   urlLink   
    


15,April,2004


	 
           Become a God or Goddess. by zerogirl      Name:           God/Goddess of    The Moon      Element:    Fire      Animal Companion:    White tiger      Weak against    Polka music      Weapon:    Partisan             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


15,April,2004


	 
        You're a Psycho! 
    


12,July,2004


	 
        Vampire: Vampires are dead human beings who walk the earth. They are often characterized by fanged teeth pale skin and unearthly eyes. You have a short fuse. You know what you want and you will use almost any means to get there. However, you probably have a soft spot when it comes to the one you love. You tend to be possesive of those you love and they will never escape you.    urlLink  What Mythological Creature Are You (Many Results and Beautiful Pics)    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    


06,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Your dashing good looks      Your Favorite Target:    Inanimate objects      Your Kill Count:    1,702,221,433      Your Battle Cry:    "Allow me to molest your face with this rod!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    43      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $151,822,029,817,384        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 55%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Your own bare hands      Your Favorite Target:    High School Freshmen      Your Kill Count:    1,832,040,581      Your Battle Cry:    "Mutha fuckaaaaaaas!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    36      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $294,442,555,214,427        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 95%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Flamethrower      Your Favorite Target:    Zealots      Your Kill Count:    519,251,762      Your Battle Cry:    "Who let the dogs out?"      Years You Spend in Jail:    8      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $117,025,917,417,077        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 50%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Machete      Your Favorite Target:    Zealots      Your Kill Count:    1,546,426,605      Your Battle Cry:    "Who put the bomp in the bomp-a-bomp-a-bomp?"      Years You Spend in Jail:    26      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $213,766,921,481,737        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 70%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Desert Eagle .50      Your Favorite Target:    Mall employees      Your Kill Count:    1,334,205,221      Your Battle Cry:    "Allow me to molest your face with this rod!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    34      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $94,135,662,940,922        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 66%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Agent Orange      Your Favorite Target:    Women      Your Kill Count:    1,470,957,143      Your Battle Cry:    "Who put the bomp in the bomp-a-bomp-a-bomp?"      Years You Spend in Jail:    18      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $264,628,404,214,012        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 69%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    Desert Eagle .50      Your Favorite Target:    Pedophiles      Your Kill Count:    663,960,078      Your Battle Cry:    "My kidneys tingle with pleasure!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    8      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $51,020,525,724,980        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 12%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Your Homicidal Rampage! by  urlLink  crash_and_burn        Your name:           Weapon of Choice:    A muppet      Your Favorite Target:    Elderly men      Your Kill Count:    347,193,061      Your Battle Cry:    "Yo mama!"      Years You Spend in Jail:    21      How Much Money In Damages You Cause:    $148,932,760,854,557        Your Homocidal Insanity Level:: 88%                                                                                             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    


05,July,2004


	 
           Who will you be stuck with at end of time? by  urlLink  chi_a_baidh        Your name is           Your sex is      Male Female Undecided       Your favorite color is      Red Orange Yellow Green Blue Purple Black White Other       You are stuck there because    you escaped a nuclear war      For _____  years    72      With     urlLink  Jackie Chan. Click for pic.       He/She will think you are    God      You will    run far, far away             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !     
    



29,June,2004


	 
      Abunai fidgeted underneath Legato's piercing gaze. He had quickly lost his look of shock and surprise, and was not about to skirt around the subject at hand; how Abunai already knew his name.  "I will ask you again," he said in a terse voice. "How do you you know who I am? I have never even met you before, and not too long ago, I was labeled as dead. Answer." Legato's tone was starting to wear at Abunai's nerves. 'Who does he think he is?' She thought angrily, 'And I saved him, too!'  ~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~  'And I saved him, too!'  The thought rang through Legato's mind. She saved him? Why though? Examining her mind yielded no answers; her mind was one of the most guarded that he'd ever seen. It was almost as if she had prepared herself for circumstances such as this... He turned away from his musings to stare into her eyes. He didn't need to be a mind reader to know when someone was lying...  "Ok!" Abunai said in an exasperated voice. "Let's play twenty questions, alright?" "Twenty questions?" Legato asked, confused. He wasn't sure if he was on the same planet anymore... "Yeah, twenty questions. I ask you a question, then you ask me a question, and continue until we've each had ten questions each. But I think I will shorten it to Ten Questions... Understand?" Legato scoffed. "Of course I understand, I'm not a child." Abunai looked at him with a small frown adorning her face. "Do you want to go first?" Maybe if he was allowed to ask the first question, he would relax, Abunai mused. Legato looked down his nose at her for a moment before nodding.   "Fine. First question: Where are we?"  "Simple," Abunai stated. "We are on Earth."   Legato looked stunned. "Earth? We cannot be on Earth. It was abandon-"  "Now, now, it's my turn. Further questions will be allowed afterwards." The teen chided. "Okay, my turn," she stated softly. "Um..." Abunai's eyes wandered around, searching for a question. "How long did you work for Knives?"  Her question floated through the silence. 'So she knows about that too...' He thought suspiciously. Nevertheless, he would answer. "Most of my life, I suppose. As soon as it was found that I had powers, he came to me and asked for my services. Not that he would have let me refuse." Abunai's mouth formed a small 'o'. She had always wondered about that. She also knew what her next question would be.  Legato shifted slightly on his mat and once again looked Abunai in the eyes as he asked his question. "Why is Earth so...inhabitable? I thought that the humans had overtaxed it?"  "Hmmm..." She looked thoughtful for a moment before her expression brightened. "Well, I think that the entire SEEDS ordeal is actually in this Earth's future. On the other hand, it could be an Earth from an alternate reality. Though... If the humans don't realize that they are harming the planet, SEEDS could possibly be a not so far away future..." Her expression saddened once more. "I see..." Legato stated simply. "Your turn." Abunai nodded and proceeded to ask her question.  "You said that you have worked for Knives for most of your life, correct?" Legato nodded and she continued, "I'm assuming that it was most likely a long time... I assume that because of the left arm you now possess. I also know that arm once belonged to Vash. Yet, what I want to know is this: Is it prolonging your life?"  Legato remained silent. This girl knew more than she should... He was starting to feel like his life was some show to her. Though, in order for his questions to be answered, he had to answer hers. "In a way, I would say that it does allow me to live longer than other, normal people. Now, my turn." Legato smiled as he sat in a cross legged position and propped his elbow onto his knee so that he could rest his head on his hand. He was beginning to feel tired again. "How do you know so much about me?"  "Ah, so we come to that question at last. Truthfully, Legato-chan, um... I've been stalking you?" She grinned as she sensed his distrust. "You're lying," Legato stated in a firm tone. Abunai raised her hands in mock surrender. "Oh no, you've found me out!" She giggled slightly when he raised an eyebrow at her antics. "Ok, ok... Well, I guess it's the dreams..."  "Dreams?" He questioned. "Yeah... It's like some kind of movie that goes on in my head at random. I was confused at first, I mean, I can have some very farfetched dreams, but never without me in them." Abunai grinned as she looked up at him. "I must say, you've done some twisted things, mister." She laughed softly. "But I digress... I began to 'follow' you around in the dreams. You were intriguing, so I would often be around you whenever you traveled. You couldn't see me though... So, that's how I know so much about you."  "I see..." He mused thoughtfully. He hadn't heard of having a dream of someone's life before... Much less living some of it with them... "Your turn," he remarked offhandedly, too engrossed with the information he had just received. "Aha!" Abunai said cheerfully. "What to ask, what to ask..." She placed a finger to her chin in a thoughtful manner. "Oh yes... Was Knives the one who put you up to making Vash kill you?" She asked with a slightly vehement tone. Legato snapped out of his reverie and looked at her. "Yes, he asked me to do it... Yet, I was the one who came up with the idea." His eyes shifted as he began to think of other things, thinking that she had accepted his answer. Now he needed to think of a question of his own.  "Why...?" Abunai asked in a soft voice. "Why what?" Legato sounded slightly perturbed because of the interruption. "Why did you come up with that idea? You knew it would result in you death, didn't you?" Her voice was barely above a whisper, but he had no problem making out her words. "I was tired..." He shrugged it off as if it were nothing. "I wanted to rest, to not hear voices, just to sleep..." Abunai looked saddened at his words. "And you would go so far as to kill yourself?" After a pause, Legato nodded. "Oh, it is my turn, is it not?" He asked, seemingly unfazed by Abunai's now gloomy expression. "I've been meaning to ask you, why am I alive? I know that Vash killed me, so why am I here?"  Abunai looked at him before standing and kneeling next to him. Even though she seemed depressed by his thoughts of ending his life, she exuded a feeling of peacefulness that he was comforted by. "You're here... You're alive because..." Her face was covered in shadow despite the sun's attempt to spread light upon it from the window. "I didn't want my dream to end, either." Abunai leaned against him in a tired manner and closed her eyes. Legato was stunned yet again, and silence reigned throughout the house.
    


29,June,2004


	 
      Legato smiled as he stared down the barrel of Vash's gun, waiting for him to pull the trigger... Telling Vash to pull the trigger... Legato knew that he would, for Vash's precious companions were being threatened. Or would Vash sacrifice their lives so that he could keep his so called 'clean' slate spot-free...?   Vash was a fool, bantering on and on about never killing a soul, when he was indeed at fault. He may not have killed anyone intentionally, but after every city he destroyed, people were left homeless and devoid of food, of shelter, of peace. Filled with madness they would kill each other off, fighting for scraps like stray dogs in an alley.  How Legato hated this wretched planet.  So here he was, commanding Vash to pull the trigger on his gun. Vash's trigger finger twitched as one of his companions screamed, and Legato could see tears welling up in Vash's aquamarine eyes.  'Fool,' Legato prodded into Vash's mind. 'Why don't you just kill me and end this? You know you want to...' Vash made a small noise as another cry of pain came from his friends. Legato could see his resilience slipping every second. 'Yes, that's it Vash. You want them to live, don't you? Come on... It's not so bad, killing someone...' Vash's mind rang with Legato's laughter and he snapped. "NO!" He cried just as his finger slipped and the gun rang out.  Legato's last thought lingered on in Vash's mind...  'I'm finally free of them...'  Legato's lifeless body slumped to the ground as tears fell from Vash's eyes...   ~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~   'I feel so warm...' Legato thought sleepily. It was not often that he had the chance to sleep, and to sleep so blissfully was a rare occurrence indeed. He stretched and yawned as he rubbed his eyes. Suddenly, he froze.  'Why... Why am I alive?!' His mind was panicking. He had failed his mission! Vash must have had the will to move the gun, and it must have only grazed him... Maybe he had just been knocked out... No... It wasn't so... It couldn't be... He had felt the bullet hit him, had saw it coming... Time had slowed, he was sure of it...  Then, why was he here, alive?  Light flashed into his eyes from an open window, and he shielded them from its brilliance. Having two suns really was annoying sometimes... Yet, this light was not as intense as he had imagined it, and why was it so... green, outside? Legato stood and realized that he was previously laying on a bed. 'I must have been too shocked to realize it,' he deduced. 'It's been a while since I have slept in a bed.'  Legato yawned as he shuffled over to the open window. A gentle breeze blew by and lifted the curtains, the newly revealed view they concealed astonishing him. Plants... He leaned against the sill and looked all about him. 'There are plants everywhere...' He had never before seen the like. He knew that there were Geo Plants scattered over Gunsmoke, but none as large as this one. It seemed to never end...  He could hear the birds chirping and see other creatures he had never laid eyes upon scurrying about. Three large trees lay before the window, covering the ground and Legato in greens and whites that danced about in the breeze. Legato's only thought was, 'Beautiful.' He smiled as the soft beams hit his face. He closed his eyes and basked in the light, being for once in his life at peace with his surroundings.  "Ah... So you're awake at last. I thought I heard you earlier," said a soft voice from the door. Legato pivoted around wildly to see who had disturbed him. 'No,' he thought. 'I don't want this dream to end...' He rarely had such peaceful moments, and he didn't quite want this one to cease yet. His eyes widened at the sight before him.  A young girl stood, leaning against the door's frame. She carried a tray in her hands that had an assortment of food upon it. Her blue-green eyes sparkled and danced with slight amusement as he studied her. Light blonde hair was pulled back in a loose ponytail that was resting over her shoulder in a careless way. If she were not leaning against the frame, the top of her head would have reached just past his chin, and she looked for all the world to be sixteen or seventeen years of age. She laughed softly as she sat the tray on a low table to the side of room.  "I made you breakfast... I hope you're hungry, I prepared a lot. It was just too fun to cook for more than just me for a change, I guess." She smiled and scratched the back of her neck in a slightly embarrassed way. "Anyway... Good morning." Smiling brightly, she sat the table as Legato looked on.  She didn't seem worried in the least that he was there, in fact, she had made a meal for him. 'I might as well make the best of this situation...' he thought idly. 'She may even be able to answer my questions, she seems nice enough to help... I am kind of hungry, too...' Legato smiled as he kneeled next to the short table. There were no chairs, so he took his place upon a soft mat in front of it. The girl sat across from him on a similar mat. 'I wonder who she is...'  "Oh my!" she suddenly exclaimed. "You don't know who I am, do you?" She beamed him a bright smile and gave a short bow. "I'm very pleased to meet you, my name is Abunai Mori." She held out her hand, which he gingerly took. "It is also nice to meet you as well, Abunai. I am-"  "Legato Bluesummers, I know!" She grinned slightly and gave his hand a nice shake. "I know all about you, Legato-chan, and believe it or not, I've been waiting..."  The fork he was holding in his other hand clattered to the plate where his now forgotten food lay.  "How did you..." His words ceased as a wave of confusion overwhelmed him. "How..."  "Let's just say that it's for me to know and for you to find out, Legato-chan." Abunai smiled brightly once again as Legato faced her happy visage with confusion and shock written over his own. 
    


09,July,2004


	 
      Legato sat in silence, with Abunai leaned against him. She must have been asleep. His mind was once again dwelling over all that had happened in the short span of time since he had awoken.   'She didn't want her dream to end?' Legato was confused. Those words were nearly his own, he had thought the same thing when he first heard Abunai walk into the room. 'If I had died... Her dream would have ended as well... Maybe...' No, that was preposterous. He couldn't be dreaming her up, he was dead. Or he was alive. Either way, it was not plausible.  The figure beside him stirred a bit, and he was drawn out of his musings. "Le...Legato? Where are you?" Her mind must have still been clouded with sleep, for he was right there. "You weren't in my dream... Vash shot you..." Her voice sounded tearful, so he spoke up. "Abunai, I'm right here. You are not sleeping any longer." Abunai turned towards him and her eyes widened. "Legato-chan!" Legato almost jumped when she attached herself to his arm, acting as a child would to a favorite stuffed animal. "Uh..." Legato said in a very uneloquent manner. "What are you doing?"   Abunai looked up at him, and said in a small voice, "Oops... I'm sorry, it's just that..." She stopped and moved away from him slightly. "Nevermind, it's not important." Moving to stand up, she was stopped by his hand on her arm. "It's just what, Abunai?" She looked at him in a strange way, but sat back down. "When I sleep, you are always there, you know? Yet, when I was asleep just a minute ago... You were not there, and it...it frightened me... When I awoke, I saw you and... I just had to..." Abunai sighed and looked away. "Like I said, it's not important."  A voice floated in from just outside the room. "Kei-san! Did you fall back to sleep? You know that sleeping during the middle of the day is bad for you!" Abunai groaned and covered her face with her hands. "I hope he's wearing something...normal, this time..." Legato looked toward the door with a slightly puzzled expression on his face.  A young man with light brown hair and ice blue eyes walked through the door, carrying another tray of food. "Kei-san, I made brownies! I thought maybe you'd like some..." He seemed to spy Legato at that moment. "Well, you're a new face!" He smiled happily and offered the tray to Legato. "Brownie?" Abunai sighed in exasperation. "Val... What the heck are you wearing?" Val smiled again. "It's an apron! It's to keep food from getting on your clothes when you cook. Do you like it?" "Val... That was a somewhat rhetorical question... I know what it is, but why are you wearing it?" He looked unabashed as he said, "I was cooking! Would you like a brownie?" Val seemed almost anxious for one of them to eat his creation.  "Um... Sure, Val..." Abunai tentatively picked up a brownie as Val fervently looked on. She took a bite and smiled, "It's good, Val." He looked overjoyed. "Would you like one as well... Um... What is your name?" Val gestured towards Legato with an oven-mitt clad hand while Legato looked at him. "I am known as Legato Bluesummers, and I suppose you go by Val, correct?" Val grinned, "Yes! Also by Nox, I don't know why, though..." "I see..." Legato said quietly. "And why did you call Abunai 'Kei-san'?" Val looked thoughtful. "Oh, I dunno... Everyone else does for some reason, so I just did too..." He shrugged and walked away.  "Well..." Abunai said with a sigh. "I guess I'll show you around the house..." Legato nodded, it sounded like a good idea. He stood and looked down. Abunai did not move, and she was staring out the window. The bright light that once filtered through was now a hazy orange color, though. "Abunai..." Legato said softly. Still, she did not stir. 'Lost in her own reverie, I assume...' He thought. 'I think I'll try something different this time.' He smiled and tapped her shoulder. "Kei-san, you were going to show me around, right?" Abunai's head snapped up and she looked at him. "I suppose, alright then." Legato reached down a hand, intending for her to take it. She smiled and gently put her hand in his. "Thanks, you're a lot nicer than some of the others around here." Legato lifted her to her feet. "Others?" He questioned. "Oh, yes, of course! There are a lot of people here, most of them are off doing their own thing, though." "Ah..." Legato intoned and wondered how many other people there were.  "Oh, I lost count long ago!" Abunai smiled and pulled Legato out of the room. He was bewildered yet again.
    


03,August,2004


	 
      Legato followed Abunai out of the door. Rather, he was pulled slightly. Going down the corridor, they would often pass people at random intervals. Each passerby would greet Abunai in a cheerful manner, but some wouldn't, and only afford to her a look. Some ignored them completely.  Arriving in what looked to be the main room in Abunai's home, Legato saw a few people lounging on the couches, or laying on what seemed to be very squishy bags in front of an arrangement of lost technology. Two of which seemed to be fervently punching buttons on some sort of hand held devices that were connected to another piece of technology. Their eyes were glued to the screen and what looked to be a battle was playing on it.  Abunai smiled as she let go of Legato's hand and sat down on one of the couches. The young man whom she sat next to moved over slightly to give her room. Abunai grinned as she said, "What's up, Sieg-chan!" The person now identified as Sieg inclined his head to the pair that were on the floor in front of the TV. "Oh, nothing much, Kei-san. I'm just watching those two idiots play their games."  "I see..." She stated slowly. "Kyo-kun, Yuki-kun! Who's winning?" The seemingly infuriated red-head yelled back at her, "The damn mouse, of course!" Kyo growled lowly, "But he's cheating!" The lavender haired other did not seemed fazed as he quipped, "I'm not cheating, you stupid cat, you just suck at this game." His blase attitude only added fuel to Kyo's fire, and the angry cat jumped up without warning. "Let's take this outside, kuso nezumi!" Kyo shouted at the seated Yuki.  The mouse did not look up at him, instead he stated calmly, "I win." Kyo whipped his head toward the screen that was flashing Winner! 2P! Kyo dropped back into the bean bag defeatedly. "Best two out of three?" Yuki offered. Kyo snatched up the controller. "You're on!" He challenged, and the two began another game.  "Well..." Legato said slowly, "This is a very lively place." He watched as two more of the house's occupants passed him, talking about 'alchemy'. Strange, though. One was wearing a suit of armor, while the other was very short.  "Don't let him hear that." Legato jumped slightly from his reclined position against the wall. "Ke-Kei-san! I didn't hear you walk over. Ah... What was that?" Slightly flustered, Legato inquired as to what she meant. "The one who just walked by, you know..." She leaned in conspiratorially. "Don't let him hear you call him short."  "WHAT WAS THAT!?" A voice shouted from where the two had left. "Oh, no..." Abunai covered her face with her hand, "How does he hear so well?" Another frantic voice shouted to the accompaniment of angry feet running over the floor. "Nii-san! Wait! You know she didn't mean it!" The young blonde rushed in, and almost into Abunai. "WHO'S TINY AS A GRAIN OF SAND AND YOU NEED A MICROSCOPE TO SEE?!" Abunai put her hands up in a disarming manner.  "Edo, Edo! Calm down! I was just warning our new guest about not saying..." She looked at Edward's fuming face. "Well, you know..." Edward growled lowly and nodded. 'Oh, great. He's a beanpole...' He thought, looking at Legato. Huffing, he asked, "Who's he?" He glared at Legato.  Abunai smiled in an attempt to cool off Edward's hot head. "He's Legato. He arrived Earlier today, Edo-kun. Legato, this is Edward and Alphonse Elric." Edward eyed Legato warily. "Is he staying?" "Nii-san! Don't be rude!" Alphonse interjected. Abunai smiled and looked thoughtful. "It's ok, Aru-chan. He can ask, but..." Abunai hummed. "I do not know. That's up to Legato." She said.  Legato looked at the three of them and shrugged in a neutral way. "It doesn't matter. I'm dead, anyway." He looked outside of the glass double doors to a flowering tree. "I can't go back..." A lone pink blossom floated from the tree and softly hit the ground. 'There's no way I could go back, the dead do not walk among the living...' At this thought, he felt very lonely, but he thought, idly, that maybe, just maybe, here... He would find a place to be.  As the two Elric brothers walked away, Edward muttering something about 'research' before leaving, Abunai again took Legato's hand. Leading him away to a door, she opened it and they walked outside. The sun had just set, and there was a pinkish glow over the horizon. She lead him down a path, and into the middle of the three trees that he had seen earlier.  "I noticed how you were staring at the trees..." She looked up at him. "Gunsmoke was very barren, so they surprised you, yes?" Legato nodded. "It was very beautiful to see." He stated as he watched Abunai walk over to a tree and sit against it. Looking to his left, he decided to do the same. Settling down, he noted that it was quite comfortable. In the past, he never had time to relax like this. It was a nice feeling.  "The stars are coming out..." Abunai said as she looked to the sky, "The moon, too. It's full." Legato looked at said moon. "You only have one moon?" Abunai nodded. "Yes. There is only one sun, as well." Legato's eyes continued to scan the heavens. They sat in silence. "It's nice here." "Yes, it is."  "Indeed." Abunai's head snapped up to look into her tree's branches. "Dae! What are you doing up there?" She smiled as she said this. 'Dae?' Thought Legato.  A shadowy figure dropped from the tree, landing in a swirl of black cloth and... 'Wings?' Legato's mind questioned. "It is always pleasant to see new faces here." The stranger named Dae intoned. "Well, then..." He bowed slightly to Legato. "I am Daemeon Rothchilde the Third. It is a genuine pleasure to meet you..." Daemeon held out his hand to Legato. Taking the offered hand, Legato answered, "I am Legato Bluesummers. It is also nice to meet you, Daemeon."  Abunai clapped her hands together. "Now that everyone is introduced, shall we go inside?" Her ever present smile was back in place. "I'm sure you are tired from your latest journey, Dae-chan." Dae gave a small smirk in return to her smile. "Assuredly, Kei-san." He stretched his arms, and his vast wings moved with them. "It's always nice to rest at home after a hunt."  "Hunt?" Legato inquired. "Oh, yes." Dae answered. "I-" Abunai gave him a pointed look. "I'll tell you later..." He said sheepishly. Walking to the door, Abunai opened it and allowed them inside before walking in herself, and shutting the door behind her. 
    



27,July,2004


     
       urlLink    I do not like how this turned out... Basically, I was feeling crappy so I drew something... On second thought, I usually don't like how my pictures turn out...  urlLink   
     
    


25,July,2004


     
                      kimi ga tabidatsu hi wa  


24,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Ichi ^_^&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


18,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Awww... Cute...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


11,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Zorn! WAHAHAHAHA!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


11,July,2004


     
       urlLink    blinded&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


11,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Krytos, awwww... It sucks! Yay! ...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


11,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Malcom! =^-^=&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


08,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Ivves in color! *huggles Ivves*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Ruhe Der Ewigkeit&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Yay! Not inversed!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Never, EVER piss off a vampire...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Nar-chan!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,July,2004


     
       urlLink    Kura-chan! ^_^&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Dark... In color ^_^&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


08,August,2004


     
       urlLink    ^_^ Awww...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


06,August,2004


     
       urlLink    AH HA HA HA HA! Isn't it funny looking! ^_^ I was bored! Ah, Legolas, Child of My Boredom!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


03,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Ai&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,August,2004


     
       urlLink    I love this picture! It's Gaara-kun from Naruto... I've never seen Naruto... I've read like 5 pages of the manga... But anyway... He looks older... I always make them look older...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


02,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Ahmonra ^_^&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    



