
01,August,2004


	 
      It's a good question, and one that many people  should  be asking.  However, because a low percentage of poeple actually own an XBox, but love Halo, it's a fairly popular game.  I'm the only one aside from Antilles that actually owns the game, so I thought I'd take the time to post my position on the PC version.  1)   Halo was not designed to be a PC game.   If you take a look at many of the weapons, most of them were designed with the thought of a controller in mind.  For example, the plasma pistol.  If you're got a good trigger finger, it can fire pretty darn fast, and becomes a good mid/low-range weapon and a better resort to combat vehicles.  Place that into a PC, with a mouse.  Now just about anyone can fire it that fast - and it can now be pushed to just about a solid stream of blasts.  That unbalanced the weapons.  More importantly, let's look at the pistol.  Probably the best weapon in the game.  What happens when you add a mouse to the mix?  It becomes disgustingly cheap.  Where a three-shot-head-kill was once a feat, it's now standard. Let's also look at the plasma weapons (pistol, rifle, and ghost).  The most important aspect of these weapons is that they slow your turn/movement speed.   That's what makes them effective.  You can't turn to fight the enemy, and you die.  However, place this in PC, with a mouse.  Oh no!  You are suddenly assailed!  What do you do?  Move the mouse faster.  This becomes especially important in the Ghost vs. Tank scenario.  Where in Xbox, Ghost 

01,August,2004


	 
      We've had a few matches today, and the results have been quite interesting.  I forgot to record deaths, but the kills matter most anyways, right?  We discussed the possibility of a "lag meter" in which we try and estime the lag time, and we'll now include information on who hosted each game.  Below games hosted by:  Tol Erressea  Battle Creek Slayer:  Rendar: 25  TBone: 23  Finwe: 18  MR M: 10  BG Snipers:  Rendar: 15  Mr M: 10  TBone: 9  Finwe: 6  Wizard Shotguns:  Rendar: 50  TBone: 38  Finwe: 32  Mr M: 28  Note:  Finwe plays an excellent shotguns game.  I'd send the honorable mention his way for his outstanding display of skill with a shotgun!  Damnation Oddball was player afterwards.  I don't particularly like Oddball, so I sat that one out.  Any further games were halted by the massive lag on XBC.  We tried hosting from all boxes, it didn't work.  Good games, though!  I realized I can just take screenshots of the scoreboard, so from here on out I can provide much more detailed results.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Well, last night my bro (Antilles) and I played a 1v1 wizard game (typical game with pistol and assault rifle). We agreed not to use powerups and though both of us were trying slightly new tactics he beat me 50-37. While not a  huge  victory, that much of a lead on me in that kind of a game is quite impressive. We've come to the conclusion that what he's really good at is killing me, heh. We'll have to take a screenshot of him standing over my corpse... lol, that'd be the perfect bio avatar.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      We played over XBC last night, not compeltely seriously, but we had 400% (with shields) on, I think, normal for two or three matches, in Chill Out and Wizard.  We also played some 100% health / no shields Sniper on Rat Race, Wizard, Chiron, and Chill Out.  Scores were inconclusive due to the fact that everyone just used snipers.  It's hard!  Good matches though.  [danielreid edit] The 400% games were a variation by brother calls Ironhide (though this time with teams). The teams were myself and spoo vs Antilles and Tbone. In Chill Out we won it by a small margin and in wizard they won by a bit more. I think fun was had by all...  Honorable mention goes to Spoo (his bio will be up soon) for an amazing show of plasma grenade sticking skill. "Betcha can't stick it" was proven wrong a zillion times over and he impressed all of us. [/danielreid edit]
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Got it fixed... as you can see I've given a demo of what the avatar thingy might look like. Nifty eh? :D
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Ok, so I was trying to set up a bunch of divs (one for each bio) and stack them on top of each other, as you can see it messed up royally (though in the preview thingy it looked and still looks perfect). I'll try to fix it...
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      We're now working on getting pictures for each player's bio.  I finally got my video capture working (and my audio, so I can now play on my moniter instead of the TV).  I record the shots (some of these are gonna be difficult, like getting a shot of me firing a rocket on Wizard), and Daniel edits them.  I'm really excited about this - I can record my games and clear out the fluff (me dying repeatedly) and make it look cool.  Hopefully we can get the avatars up soon.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      As you can see, we've added a player bio section. This is not an exhaustive list and it doesn't include everyone yet... that'll take quite a while. Give us a little more time and I'll post a link on the HBO forums and see what people think.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      | Maybe he'll send you an invite | depending on how much we like you | and whether or not you can be trusted | not to post worthless junk. | | | V
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Now that we've endured some major appearance overhaul (and I think it's starting to look semi decent) I'll add ze link to my blog. Maybe a few people will check it out. Heh.   BTW - The purpose of this blog was to report on halo playing in our area (LAN parties, XBC matches, etc)... so if you know me and have a blogger account send me an email and I'll invite you so you can post here too.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Hmmm. Benjamin really needs to give me admin privilages so I can sprucen this site up a bit.  Apparently he's going to and then I'll add a few images and such things.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Why?  Because of counter-strike.  That one game destroys anything good about the original.  Why is CS a game only for 12 year-old script kiddies?  Because of the massive ammounts of hacking, the lame graphics, and most of all the players, who cannot do anything except hack and cuss eachother out, accusing eachother of hacking.  It's retarded.  Why is Halo good?  Well, why is Halo not good?  Hmm?  Sure, the single-player is a bit lame, but it's kinda fun anyway.  The real place Halo shines is multiplayer.  It is so much better than CS.  First of all, there is no hacking.  Second, most of the time you cannot talk to your opponents, so there is no complaining about hacking and type-killing.  Oh, the one bad thing about Halo:  WHY COULDN'T THEY FIGURE OUT HOW TO MAKE PEOPLE NOT SPAWN IN THE SAME FREAKIN PLACE OVER AND OVER?   
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      [update 6/30/04] updated the player list [/update]  Ok Tim, so I probably should have been the one to post that seeing as I'm setting it up and know everything, but that's ok. You were probably just bored and felt like posting *grin*  We plan to have people show up between 11-12noon on saturday and we'll play till things wind down, people get bored, and parents want to pick people up (I seriously doubt we'll go till 10pm, simply cause my mother would get rather irked).  Currently the player list is:  Me Ben Benjamin Nolan Tim Jesse Weilin Carter Dad Than Paul Josh Mark Jordan Peter  If anybody knows anyone else gimme a call to check and make sure we still have open slots and then bring them along.  equipment list:  Us - 2 Xboxes, 2 TVs, 8 controllers Tim - 1 xbox, 1 TV, 4 controllers Carter - 1 Xbox, 1 TV, 4 controllers Benjamin - 1 Xbox, 2 controllers
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      So far things are looking solid.  We're hoping for at least 10 people this time, and might have 4 boxes there this time.  It will be this Saturday, probably starting in the afternoon until 10:00 PM, I'd say.  This isn't a definite, but please bring at least 3 or 4 dollars in case we get some pizza.  I'll try and provide the coke (for you Northerners, that's soda - coke variants, dr pepper, sprite, root beer, nothing random or nasty, 2 liters are good as well), at best I can only bring 3 packs (my estimate is two), so maybe a few people could bring one too?  Mostly just throwing out ideas here, but definately bring a little cash on hand.  Correct me if I'm mistaken, but the definates for those playing this Saturday are...  Stuff-people-zorz: Rendar, Antilles, DrBithead - 2 boxes, 2 TVs TBone - 1 box, 1 TV, coke Mr M, NCM - possibly 1 box RoniN - possibly 1 box, possibly TV  Players: Jesse Carter Weilin  Unfortunately Spoo is out of town, but we should have at least one more before the end of summer.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Ok, currently the plan (and I've got lots of work to do regarding this) is to try for a halo party this saturday, the 28th. I'll be calling around once I get the day confirmed to invite everyone.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Decided not to do it this weekend because Tbone will be out of town... unless he wants to lend us his controllers that is, and maybe a TV :P We'll probably try sometime during the beginning of next week though.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      I just want to say that though there haven't been any posts for a while, we aren't inactive. I've just been taking a little break from Halo recently... I know I'll get back into it soon.  Speaking of which, we're hoping to have a LAN party this saturday at my house... haven't worked out all the details but I'll be calling around sometime soon to work it out with people.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      [Neo] Woah! [/Neo]   EDIT: Stupid blogger doesn't edit out HTML tags.  Can I use 'em?             'parently so.  Cool.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      Added Spoo to the list...
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      So on saturday, the 3rd of July, we got 16 people together and hooked up the xboxes. Halo was the game and fun-to-be-had-by-all was the goal... ACk! AErrhgh HWGFAHKgwafg  Whew! Boy, that was starting to sound all weird and everything. Ok so yeah, we got a TON of people together and the only bloopers to be had was a small transportation/permission issue in the morning about getting Tim here. Unfortunately the way to solve it was that I had to drive over and pick him up, thereby leaving my team during a Blood Gulch CTF match which we MIGHT have won. Apparently as soon as I left the defense started to crumble and by the time I returned with Tim it was almost over. Anyway, that was just one of many games we played.  We tried just about everything in the arsenal of gametypes (not rally though, bleh), including a new addition that I actually really enjoyed (though it might need a bit of tweaking). It's called wargames and it's fashioned after a tactical squad-based idea. You leave shields on, knock the health to 150% and put it on "No Sniping" weaponset. We left it with just warthogs. It's based on the CTF gamemode, though with the assault variation added in. Only one flag, so each team takes turns trying to take their flag into the enemy base. I thought it worked better when we had a 4v4 going then when we had 8v8. For some reason all those people had a tendency to actually make things just way too difficult (at least not without seriously increasing the respawn time).  Ok, so we played rockets, shotguns, classic FFA and TS, CTF, Assault, Team Shotguns, Oddball,  Goldengun, Team IronHide, and a few others I can't remember. One of the most memorable was when Tbone challenged everyone else to take him on by himself. We chose a shotguns game in wizard to try it and he basically owned because he had so many targets. The second time, and this time we were determined to beat him, we played ironhide in prisonor (sp?) and it quickly deteriorated (sp?) into a game of who could betray the most of their own teammates *laugh*  My brother and I also took on eight or so people and came out on top (I think) for most of the few games we played like that.  We never did get around to trying the Bug vs Marine idea with 16 people... it just didn't last. Speaking of not lasting, we also got to play Ultimate frisbee (about 8 of us) partway through the day. Honestly most of us just needed a quick break... so we went down to ACS and played some fribsy (Ben C, Aaron, Jordan, and Carter vs myself, Ben A, Ben P, and Jesse). I'd say it was an awesome game basically because I'm not used to playing it with all people who know how to run and play.  Than left somewhat early (he was really tired), and Peter was only here for a few hours (I barely remember seeing him) but I think they both had a good time. We ordered pizza around 5:30 and consumed ALL of it (not hard when you have 16 hungry boys there)... and also consumed ALL of tim's soda (3 12 packs I think).  I would be much amiss if I neglected to mention the playing of a surprise 1337 gamer. Aaron (also known ingame as AFLO and Lil Jon) was certainly good enough to gain the "Legendary" skill ranking I think and even gave me and my bro a run for our money a few times. I'd actually known him through the BG (not blood gulch you g33ks...) youth group, so it was cool to run into him again. Also impressive was Carter's playing skills after having only owned an xbox and halo for about 2 weeks. He must just be another natural. *grin*  As for my own playing, I'd say that I played about normal about during the middle of the day and got better as I went (meanwhile everyone else seemed to be playing better than I'm used to). As a result, I didn't do well during the start but sorta picked up towards the end. During the huge CTF games one  might  say that I was the MVP for my team, simply because whenever I left it went downhill almost immediately (really, just ask). For the FFA and TS I think Antilles (my bro) really shined the brightest. He cleaned up for the whole beginning of the day and pretty much kept up the momentum throughout the day. Tbone (though much ridiculed throughout the day, sorry tim!) I think also really shined brighter than ussual. He beat me quite a few times and I don't think unfairly, so perhaps he is finally moving himself out of the "3rd place" position.  In regard to the MVP of the entire day I'd hope that everyone will agree when I award it to my brother. I honestly think he played the best of all of us, even if he slowed down a tad at the end.  Here's the end player list for who was there:  Daniel Ben C Ben M Ben A Ben P Tim Nolan Weilin Paul Than Aaron Dad Peter Carter Mark Jordan Jesse  You'll note that there we 17 names on that list, though we never did have more than 16 (than left and peter showed up). I would personally like to give a special thanks to everyone who brought equipment and helped chip in for the pizza.  Stats: Most kills - Rendar - 138 frags in a targetted killing game Most deaths - Don't remember this one... though it was definitely over 100 MVP - Antilles Most surprising player - AFLO Most improved player - NCM (he's been promoted to the heroic rating by the way...)  I can't think of anything else, so... adios.
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
      I believe we can add yet another player to that list - Paul.  Isn't a regular Halo player, but the more the merrier.  Might be able to get another friend.  [danielreid update] and another... Peter looks like he's gonna show up later in the day afterall, w00t [/update]
     
    




