
30,September,2003


    
       
      Last night and Today was fun ^^  Last night we (Jyan, Eden, Takao, and I) went to the new Starbucks and we got to sit on 'our couch' (haha!! Eden ! You are crazy ~~ hey! Maybe one day we will have our own Starbucks and it will be so crazy ^___^ hehehe~)  Today was good! This morning, while walking to Art class, I seen one of my HK friends.. Jyan says I should ask him to go to Starbucks with me and he did say he wants to  do something with me this school year ... so ^O^ I think maybe it is good.. ^^ My first class was funny when Rinn got some paint on her ear! Haha!! Then it was my Engrish class 

29,September,2003


    
       
      WOW!!! Today was fun ^o^v I think the most at lunch break when me and Mako were dancing Para Para :P O! But also it was great in my CAPP class ~~ hehehe ( Mako! it was scary but good!! Twice today in the same class !! ^.^b ) Hehehe.. that international student from HK is good ^O^/ Cute ! ^___________^V  YES ! The new Starbucks is open by my house now ~ So much people to go in there 

28,September,2003


    
       
      Sundays are evil !!! I swear ! 

21,October,2003


    
       
      ^^' Sorry all my fans that I didn't write lately ~ (Haha~ I think my only fan is Naoki ! :P Thanks Naoki!) Anyways, lots of stuff happened during the time I didn't write ... (when was that anyways?! O.o Thursday or something ??) On Friday I went to the mall with Jyan, Eden, Rinn (Well she ditched us on the way there ! that meat bun 

16,October,2003


    
       
      Yesterday was my play !! ^O^ It was AWESOME! My HK friend is soooo cute when he acts ! ^^v I loved the part when he said 'Alei... don't go' KAWAII !!!!! ^_______^ For the first kiss he put the paper infront of us and I am not sure how close he was to my face but it sounded close. Then the second one he put the paper infront again but this time made a slurping sound ! O_O wowowowowowo~  Anyways, our play went as we wanted it to and everyone liked it ^^  After our play I became sick X_X So, when I got home I wrote an e-mail to my HK friend about some things and congradulated him on his good work on the play ~ When I checked my mail today he wrote to me and hoped that I was better and so on ... but he also asked me if I liked him with or without his glasses (o^-^o) hmmm~  Well I am still a bit sick so I will rest now ^^ - alei ^^  (song) *Ai no Uta* by : Psycho le cemu  Ai no Uta  There will be hope ! There will be hope !   Chiheisen ni ukabu kumo yuruyakana oka wo koeru sugita hi no omoide ni saiai wo sagasu tabi  Kodoku to kunou no hibi mo subete asu no tameni aru to yume ni made mita futari wo tsuyoku shinji tsuzukeru kara  Ai no uta wo ima [KIMI] ni tsutaeyou to tenshi no [KIRAMEKI] afureru keshiki wo kakenukeru taoneru made Let's fly again  Sono mune ni tsuzuku kono tairiku wo wataru tame  Kyuuyakuseisho mo sutete michi wo terasu taiyou ni nari tengoku no na wo seotte nagai tabiji wo hajitteyaru  Ai no uta de [KIMI] wo tsutsumeru no naraba kotoba ga todoku sono maeni kokoro wo kureteyaru kowareru made Let's fly again  Ai no uta wa kaze ni fukare naiteiru koboreta namida kawaku kara sekai ni hibikasete  Ai no uta wo ima [KIMI] ni tsutaeyou to tenchi mo ugokanu shizuka na keshiki wo kakenukeru ai no uta de subete tsutsumeru no naraba kotoba ga todoku sono maeni kokoro de fureteyaru taoreru made Let's fly again  And if you can do that then there will be hope.. And If you can do that then there will be hope !  
       
    
    


14,October,2003


    
       
      Today was great ^O^ I got to meet 2 of my sisters penpals (well one is mine aswell ) they came from Japan and the one who is mine and my sisters penpal brought us Japanese mag's with Psycho le cemu , KinKi Kids, Gackt, Dir en grey and so on~ It is very lovely ! ^O^ I love to look at the Koichi part the best ^.- haha ~~ I am also interested in some other J-Pop stars now ^^'' I think one guy is from Flame ~ But it is the newest mag's (October and November 2003) The new look of Aya is scray ! But I still think he is cool ^^ And of course I still like Daishi (o^.^o) This morning in Art me and Rinn were working on my picture and she just put her fingers in the paint and then put it on my painting ~ haha ! It was funny :P I seen my HK friend today and he wasn't wearing glasses !! WOW! He looks ... well ... good ^^' haha ~  O!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I have the play with him tomorrow ~ ^___^ I am really looking forward to it since I get to act with him ^.^ But I wish that it is not only kiss on the cheeck 

08,October,2003


    
       
      Hump Day! O Hump day ! ^^; haha  Wow ! I didn't write for a few days ~ Yesterday I couldn't cause my stupid computer was being a queer 

05,October,2003


    
       
      Good morning ! (yawns) Last night was good! I was playing Dynasty Warriors 3 in the day ^O^ Zhou Yu ! He is a very good Juunanagou ~~ ^^v Anyways,  I went to Eden's house with Jyan and Raz and then Rinn came after ~ We watched a movie and when I came home and checked my mail I got a letter from the international student !!!! \^o^/ I think we will become good freinds (heh heh heh :P) Lately I have been kind of pissed off aswell.. I don't know I am just getting sick of everyone always asking me to do something for them 

03,October,2003


    
       
      WOW!!! TODAY WAS SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO GOOD !!!  This morning I was walking to CAPP and I seen the international HK student and talked to him :P It was good and he is so cute !!!!! XD hehehehe~~~ Anyways in my CAPP class we had the same group so in the group for our play I have to be the girlfriend and he has to be the boyfriend!! ^O^ SO GOOD (does 'the hands' ) I guess all my friends will hear about this later ^^' hehe hope they don't mind ~ I think Eden will say 'GOOD!' then do some kind of 'hands' with me :P hehe. Also during my CAPP class we exchanged e-mail and talked ^^ WOWOWOWOWOWOWOWO~~~ (seems like I say that alot now o.O) At lunch I seen him again and when he seen me he looked so happy and said ' HI! ' (ugh!!! it is so good \^.^/) Well now my Japanese friend will come to my house so I will write later ~~  - alei ^^  Ok ! I am back! Tonight was geat ! Eden is so crazy with 'the shtink' and how it barfs out tar XDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD  Anyways, me and my friends (Jyan, Eden, Rinn, Naoki, and Raz) went to play pool! I thought I will beat Jyan because she says she sucks, but she beat me !! :'( whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa ~~~ haha It's ok though ^^' When I got home and all of us walked Naoki and then Rinn home Eden, Raz and me all feel asleep on the couch 

02,October,2003


    
       
      Today was alright I guess.. haha I can't believe I didn't fall asleep in my class :P hehehe ~~  This morning was a bit strange... my HK friend I see all the time when I walk to Art class looked so happy when I waved at him XD hahaha ~~ I am a bit confused now .. hmmm... o.O I still need to ask him about the Starbucks thingy 

01,October,2003


    
       
      O! It is the holy hump day !! ^.^/ ( WOW! Now that I think about it, it is really is a hump day since CAPP class 

30,November,2003


    
       
      为这Blog 我认为它非常重要我的梦想人读整件事甚而歌曲为日本和英国抒情诗   *has a very angry look on her face* `' 

29,November,2003


    
       
      AAHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! I am so mad 

26,November,2003


    
       
      WOW ! Today is so cold out ! *falls over frozen* Shit ! I think maybe the weather is .. 1 degrees or something .. but maybe with the wind chill it is -1 or maybe even -2 .. (great XD I sound like a weather reporter now ~) " This just in .. tonight there will be high winds of 80 km/h causing blackouts across B.C. " Ok ok ... I am a dork 

24,November,2003


    
       
      Today I feel.. maybe depressed .. (see Eden you were a bit right ~ /;_;\)  Well.. first, at school I was a bit mad cause of the international student from HK ~ Well not him ... but that stupid girl in my class (Mako ! lets go kill her ok ? ^.- ) haha!! But after school I got really scared .. cause I thought I seen someone I know standing at the bus stop .. When I seen them I got so scared that I think maybe my heart almost stopped.. I wanted to cross the street but the light had changed _-_ FRUCK!  Mako had said the guy had cool hair XD hehehe ~ But, for some reason this time .. I was really sure it was him ... Gosh .. I am really stupid .. 我是爱有病？! *hit selfs head on the computer desk* Hmmmm... YUK ! I just a pic of a frucking hotdog in my head ~ 感谢罗杰 (u.u); Well thinks I will get off here soon ~  See ya  - alei ^^/"  (song) * The Domestic Fucker Family* by: Dir en grey  Mr. Fucker Show  Fucker Fucker Radical Fucker Trans Psycho Pleasure Fucker Fucker Radical Fucker Trans Psycho Pleasure  Fucker Fucker Japanese Fucker Thrash Psycho Family Fucker Fucker Japanese Fucker Thrash Psycho Family  Fucker Fucker Domestic Fucker Human Psycho Passion Fucker Fucker Domestic Fucker Human Psycho Passion  System M -SEXIST-  suriruna geemu wo hajimeyou ka Mr. Fucker M yaritai houdai dokuzetsu mankai Mr. Fucker M housou kinshi no riaru aidoru Mr. Fucker M kamiteki sonzai STALINIT no Mr. Fucker M  Radical Fucker Japanese Fucker Domestic Fucker Family 
       
    
    


22,November,2003


    
       
      Last night was my party ^-^  It was fun ... but.. my wish didn't come true ... I had a feeling it wouldn't come true .. I mean.. never mind ~  Anyways, I got lots of good stuff and I really enjoy my Manga Peach girl. ^^  My parents keep bugging me now because it is a Romance Manga 

15,November,2003


    
       
      HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO ME ~ ^o^ Just now Rinn said ' Happy Birthday Alei ! WOW! the big 16 huh ? ' haha ^^ Thanks Rinn ^^v I wanna dance and then watch my KinKi Kids VCD !!!!! \^o^/ MO FO WA !!!!!!!!!!!!  Well time to do thoes things :P haha ~ Just hope I won't wake my parents ^^" *Laughs nervously* heh heh heh ~  - alei ^^   (4:03pm)  Today's sleep was horrible :'( I was caughing all night ~ Frucking cold/flu (who knows what it is ~) Now I just woke up from nap ^^: I must be sick to want to sleep all day .. Wait never mind .. I ALWAYS WANT TO SLEEP XD haha! Anyways, this morning I got my gift from my parents ^^ Final Fantasy X ( ok ok I know it is a bit old .. but everytime I wanted to buy I forgot 

14,November,2003


    
       
      5 more hours!!! ^.- haha ~ ( man I am stupid XD )  Tomorrow I will open the present from my parents *wonders what it is*  Hmm... *listens to Jyan's convo on the phone* ^o^  Well I guess I will be going to Starbucks later on ~ ^^v  *sings* kururi, furari, fuwari, kurari kururi, furari, fuwari, kurakurari kururi, furari, fuwari, kurari kururi, furari, sawagu!!!   Shit ! Why I am so hyper?? 

13,November,2003


    
       
      Alright ~  the last few days have been very stressful but good (how that works I have no Idea ~ ^^")  Well I will write later cause I have to get ready for school 

09,November,2003


    
       
      Today.. Today was .. I am not sure how to explain today o.O  It was a bit interesting but I wish Eden would have talked to me about this certain thing ~ But .. doesn't matter 

06,November,2003


    
       
      Today I am so happy !! v^..^v When I got home from school my Mom handed me a package from Hong Kong. First I was really shocked because there wasn't a name on it so I wondered who it was from. Jyan joked about it being a bomb, but I still opened it ~  When I did it was a birthday present from Sam ^^/ KinKi Kids CD !! The newest one ^o^ Koichi looks so good on it !! *looks at CD and drools* haha XD Yesterday was such a tired day ! I cleaned my whole room out so the stupid painters can go there today 

04,November,2003


    
       
      Wow! Didn't write for so long ~  Some new stuff had happened .. so I will start about Halloween ~  Halloween night was fun ^o^ I went out with Rinn and Raz ~ It was sooo  cold ... I think maybe -2c or -3c 

25,December,2003


    
       
      MERRY CHRISTMAS EVERYONE !!!!! \^______^/
       
    
    


23,December,2003


    
       
      I am just writing to say I will write all of what happened after my Winter Holiday ^^  See you all then ^^/"  - alei ^^ 
       
    
    


16,December,2003


    
       
      

13,December,2003


    
       
      星期五- 星期六 ( writen at about 1:30 am but transfered to here now )   At the morning of Friday I had got up and did all my morning routine ~ I had checked my mail to see who wrote when I had remember I had to put some clothes in the dryer -o- When I came to my PC my dream guy had popped a message up on my MSN window..  He told me he got my letter and blah blah blah ~ But I am happy ^^ ( The Blah Blah Blah doesn't mean he said something bad..)   Well I have to clean my house and so on.. so I will write another day ~  See ya ^^/" - alei  (song) *Tokimeki Nagara For You* by : Wedding Peach   ganbari ya de irare nakute tsurai toki arun desu hare nochi ame nochi kumori Automatic * amedasu  chiisaku maenarae shiteru yowai toko aru kedodemo ne minna koi wo suru to  tsuyoku narechau no  Ground kakenuketeku mabushii Shooting Star me wo tojite shinkokyuu hora kaze ni naru yo  kizukanakute kamawanai yume wo oikakeru senaka mamotte miseru wasurerarete kamawanai kokoro dake soba ni itakute tokimeki nagara For You  torekaketa mune no botan tsukete agetai n desu kaban no naka katakata to setsunaku naru sewing case  minna to nara wari to heiki me ippai sawaijau dakedo yada na futari kiri ja nani mo ienakute  akogare wa tooi kedo dare ni mo yuzurenai suki tte iu kimochi wa nani ka fushigi ne  kizukanakute kamawanai ai de shika dekinai hodo tsutsunde ageru wasurerarete kamawanai tenshi no kokoro itsudemo tokimeki nagara For You kizukanakute kamawanai yume wo oikakeru senaka mamotte miseru wasurerarete kamawanai kokoro dake soba ni itakute tokimeki nagara For You 
       
    
    


10,December,2003


    
       
      Seems these last few days I am really nervous .. could it be about my dream guy ? O_O Of course !!! 

04,December,2003


    
       
      I was getting some stationary for my letter last night.. ^^; The only one I could find was Sailor Moon ones XD haha ~ Eh------h! *falls over* I also found this really old picture of the real Juunanagou that I drew in grade 8 ! Wow ~ That was 4 years ago ! ^-^ Haha ~ I remember one girl I used to be friends with, her mom had seen the picture and said it was really good and then the girl became angry at me ;_; I told the mom that it was a stupid drawing.. but she still was mad 

02,December,2003


    
       
      As I sat on my bed awake in the late our of lastnight, gave me time to think of some improtant things to me ~  Some were of the past and some were of the present. I often wishes that I could have the summer back. Those were good times ^^ Haha~ Always having parties and playing DDR ^_^ Also, there is always the times when I didn't sleep until early morning ~ 5 am, 6am and sometimes 7 am ! Hard to believe that this was my everyday routine practically. My day was usually one of these 2 things :   1) - has gone to bed at 6 am so wakes up at 2 pm     - does " morning " routine  ( washing, eating, dressing and so on )      - calls friends to make planes for the day (if not have spent the night from tiredness of the previous night)     - checks e-mail and chats untill friends arrive (if friends have splet over then rest untill other friends arrive)     - when friends arrive cook for them XD or give them something to eat ( I am usually like a cook or chef for them ^^' ) * gets frying pan out * " food anyone ? "      - Play DDR !!! (Top thing to do ! You can get fit and have fun at the same time XDDD)      - Dinner~      -  After dinner is usually to go out and cause trouble ?! " I'm a good girl .. maybe ^.^' "      - When the sun goes down ... P-A-R-T-Y !!!! *gets strobe light and glow sticks out*      - Sleep _o_ zZzZzZzZzZzZz ...   2) - goes to bed about 6 am and wakes up at 10 am ! ( O_O I need more sleep ~ )      - gets ready for the day ( same as #1)      - checks mail and chats to family, friends and others     - calls friends to make plans for after dinner ( Seems as though "taking it is easy" is important for these kind of days )      - Dinner ~      - after dinner go out to friend but doesn't " P-A-R-T-Y " ( Seems everyone is a bit tired today )      - go home about 2 am to check mail before resting      - chat to friends and others      - sleep ...   But now it makes me sad a bit.. wanting the Summer and 我的夏天希望 .  But then again, Christmas is comming soon. 23 more days I believe...Thinking of Christmas makes me always want to go iceskating. Going with my friends is fun and an option, but I would really want to go with my " dream guy " . Remembering parts in Manga and so on makes me want this even more ! 多么浪漫!  *blushes* If I do fall (which I usually don't) he will bend down and offer me his hand *laughs* When he does help me up maybe I will push him then ~ Haha! Am I really this crule ? " If you push me I will push you back..."  Now I want to go to Downtown! ^ ^ Everytime at Christmas they put Christmas lights in the trees ^_^ It's a nice view and enjoyable to walk there. Even more enjoyable with my " dream guy " ~ Maybe he will think it is quite chilly weather since he is from another part of the world.. even to chilly to walk in the city streets (more if it snows~)  Hey ! I know he loves the snow so he won't mind if it does. Yet again it's my chance to snuggle him. A kiss should surely warm us. Just hope he won't burn up ~ ohoho ^o^ For some reason I can see how he would dress for this weather...*giggles* It's so cute! *wishes he was here to hug and never let go* And seems he is always wearing some kind of baggy pants which is a great match for his large/ baggy shirt. Don't know about the jacket though .. never seen him wear a winter jacket. I will have to ask him.  Gosh.. all these thoughts are silly to some people. I just hope I can have these experiences with him one day~  我非常想念他   Well I will go now .. so see ya ^^/" - alei  (song) *Love* by : Escaflowne  If you find a way to love Can you see and stay to love        In a sign called countlessness       Sketch the keys to you       Reaching for a post       Where one loves the most        As we learn in different ways       Free so dreams come true       Searching for a style       Care without denial        What we say despite of love       Collide into self-retreat       Can't we see that love can be       Something so precious       To cherish and hold and then  In so many ways to love If we realize its love In so many ways to love If we realize its love         If you see ignite in love       So far to reach above       Can't you see that love can be       Something so precious       To cherish and hold and then       (...something so precious       to cherish and hold and then)  All so many ways of love Can we compromise true love It's those funny things in love In our only way we love      * Our love so precious       True love is to cherish       Our love so precious       True love is to cherish      * repeat   
       
    
    


01,December,2003


    
       
      我是很愚笨

17,February,2004


    
       
      Hello Everyone ! Sorry I haven't wrote what happened in the winter break yet but I will do that on my next blog ^^:  Anyways, I have been doing well these last few weeks~ But, I have been feeling sickly (is that even a word ?!) Well I have this feeling due to this stupid ugly guy 

26,March,2004


    
       
      This is the site to go to my "Comment Box" ~ ^___^ http://www.geocities.com/alei_blog/alei_blog_comment_box.html I will be going out soon so see ya ^^/"  - alei ^^                        ( I will be posting my site after entry from now on so you don't have to go to this stop and find it ~ )
       
    
    


25,March,2004


    
       
      Hiya ^^  I just wanted to let everyone now that I have a Comment Box! ^O^/ ~~  It is a guestbook but for the time being it will work as comments. *waves fist in rage at the PC screen* Stupid Blogger ~ They should really get a Comment Box on the blogs -o-; Well I am out for now cause I gtg to Jyan's~  c ya  - alei ^^  I'll give the site later ~  
       
    
    


21,March,2004


    
       
      Hello all ^O^/ ~~  Lately I have been ok ~ But I was a bit angry at some days ( You all know why -o-' )  Also, on Tuesday 2 things happened.. one scary and one really good! Hehehe~ I really liked the good thing ^^  Friday was a bit strange.. I think I am really turning into a wuss.. *blushes* I mean, I was watching my Korean Drama and I started to cry so much.. *hits self head on computer desk* G-R-E-A-T ~ But, It was kind of a good thing because then I was getting ideas for my Romance manga ^.-v hehe ~ I think it will also be in a Winter type setting ~  Last night was my last night of freedom 

14,March,2004


    
       
      Happy White Day♪ ^_^ Today is the day ( that's not all that famous in many parts of the world, but is in Japan) when men return the gift of giri-choco or honmei-choco to women who gave them choco on Valentines day~ Hehehe ~ 私はバレンタインデーに特別な誰かにhonmei のchoco を送った ^O^ I know soon the same for me ^.^v hehehe~  Recently I have been watching this Korean drama. It is called "Winter Love Song" It is a nice drama! ^_^ I think many should watch this!  Well I have many things to do today so I must go now~  See ya ^^/"  - alei ^^ (song) *Winter Wish* by: Love Hina   chiisana shiawase o  daiji ni atatameteta nee, omou to mune no oku  konna ni itaku naru no  anata no me  anata no koe  subete itoshikute...  konayuki ga hoho ni maiori  namida ni kawatta itsu made mo soba ni ite  kono te o hanasanai de fuyu no sora  kirameku hoshi wa futari o tsutsunda shiroi kata  shiroi iki  anata to kanjiteru WINTER WISH  yorisoi aruita  umizoi no yuuenchi nee, kanransha ni notte  hikari no machi miyou yo  tooku naru umi to awai kiss ga setsunakute...      hajimari wa konayuki no IVU  chiisana SUTORI dare yori mo aishiteru  kono te o hanasanai de arukidasu futari no mirai  naranda ashiato nukumori mo yasashisa mo  anata to dakishimeru WINTER WISH  konayuki ga hoho ni maiori  namida ni kawatta itsu made mo soba ni ite  kono te o hanasanai de fuyu no sora  kirameku hoshi wa futari o tsutsunda shiroi kata  shiroi iki  anata to kanjiteru WINTER WISH     
       
    
    


11,March,2004


    
       
       Tasukete! 

10,March,2004


    
       
      Well this is it ~   ^_^ First things first. My Winter Break was the best EVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  (Dec.19, 2003) The beginning of my winter break! Me and Rinn rushed home because we had to go shopping for Christmas still ^^: haha~ When I arrived home I met my guest who was staying for the break~ He is my sister and mines Pen pal ^_^ So anyways, I was introduced to him and then I rushed out to shop 

05,March,2004


    
       
      Ok oK .. I know I said I would write about Winter Holiday on this one but I promise next time ~  Anyways, last night was so scary for me !!! O_O I was feeling kind of sick so I decided to sleep a bit early.( about 10:30 pm ) ~ I only slept about an hour or so before I woke up feeling worse ! 

27,April,2004


    
       
      Wow ~ I haven't wrote in this thing for a long time now.... I am always so busy with school work and projects ~ 

11,April,2004


    
       
      Well I'm better from this cold now.. almost I guess ~  Have drank a coffee with the Irish Cream ... feeling tired? Yes... very much.... but waiting for something and doesn't know what ~ Crazy ?!?!?! Yes ! ^^: Eh heh heh ~  等待的。酒醉男孩在領域在花 ~ haha ~ This is not making sense ga ~ 

01,April,2004


    
       
      *cough cough* This Freakin Cold SUCKS ASS! 

25,May,2004


    
       
      Hiya all !!   

13,May,2004


    
       
      WOW! When I 1st came to Blogger yesterday I was surprised that the site had a whole new layout ! *_*  Anyways, next week will go to the Buddy club with my friend ~~ 乘坐腳踏車! 乘坐腳踏車! ^o^ The same week.. think the day after Buddy club is my other friends birthday ^_^ He will be 18 ~  Today played "Little Fighter" with my friend Tommy o^_^o It was nice to actually spend time together again.  Well need to sleep soon for school ~~  See ya ^^/"" - alei ^^  
       
    
    


01,May,2004


    
       
      Yesterday was a great day ^_^ I got to have Chinese Hot Pot! YUM !!!! ^.^ It was really great with the Chinese meat balls and beef ~ Lately the weather has been getting hotter and hotter 

13,June,2004


    
       
      4 more days !!!!! then I can scream "Yatta!" just to realize I still have to complete one more year of school.. (NO! this doesn't mean I failed 

03,June,2004


    
       
      Whoa ~ It's June already .. Soon will start the final exams.. scared so much la ~~ I don't wanna do SS one ... 

29,July,2004


    
       
        Arrived home about 1 hour ago and my eyes are beginning to feel tired (=_=)     Today was kind of a crazy day 

27,July,2004


    
       
       我有頭疼並且我的面孔感覺如我有熱病 ~~ 需要按摩在我的後面!     Now is 1:26 am ... have talked to my new friend for a long time today ^^    I have not really been doing much lately, but on Wednesday will go to see fireworks! (^o^)    It is from China ! I am excited for it ^^&nbsp; Love fireworks so much! But, will be going to the beach that will be packed so much! (X_x)'' Will take us&nbsp;1 - 2 hours to get out of the crowd!    *feels dizzy* ...yoooosssshhhhh 

22,July,2004


    
       
        ** 我將設法我最佳獲得我的目標! ** 


18,July,2004


    
       
      *Drinks the COFFEE*&nbsp;... 

03,July,2004


    
       
      Hehehe ^^ Now in Summer break (about 16 days) So far it is fun ^^ Have to go to the beach soon though ~ Hope I don't get burnt 

11,August,2004


    
       
        Went to the fireworks on the 7th .... (=___________=);;  


05,August,2004


    
       
        WAIII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ^_^ 


03,August,2004


    
       
       Nothing much to say today ... so if u feel bored u can take these quizzes ~~~      Did Someone Say "Hip-Hop"?--I'm Gackt's Poofy Paparapa Pants! He really only used me for the crazy concert, but even still I'm an easy cosplay and no one will hit you if you wear me at night. Cool, eh?   urlLink  Which type of Gackt pants are you?      brought to you by  urlLink     

02,August,2004


    
       
        WAIIII!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  



