
02,July,2004


	 
      Here's to the nights we felt alive, Here's to the tears you knew you'd cry, Here's to goodbye, Tomorrow's gonna come too soon. -Eve 6, "Here's To The Night"    #50 - Everything fun that I forgot on here... Sorry guys, I'll write everything down this year!    #49 - The Shining... The Ring... Silence of the Lambs.   #48 - Everything that comes outta Tiana's mouth.   #47 - Britnii London dressed as a cow.   #46 - When Alec did "The Fag Jump."    #45 - Tessa's "family reunion".    #44 - Everything involved with sexual education.   #43 - The drive over to Valley Fair.  #42 - Tina's lipgloss.   #41 - Watchin' SNL with Nathalie.    #40 - The Kiss    #39 - After the Fireworks!!   #38 - Hittin' Elena with a phone book.. (I'm still sorrie for that!!)   #37 - Modelling with Joce in Abercrombie.   #36 - Patrick's "Snot".   #35 - Michele and Santa Claus.    #34 - Halloween Costumes.   #33 - Stephen's "coming out".   #32 - When Nathalie got hit on during the DC Trip!   #31 - Loren and the Laxatives.    #30 - Mesha and her monkey!    #29 - The Corn Maze.   #28 - "Ice The Irish!"   #27 - Mrs. Locke and the Locker Room!   #26 - Elizabeth's "Knock-out"    #25 - Playin' piano with the Annie.   #24 - MONEY!  #23 - My first purchase from Abercrombie.  #22 - My "Christmas" Presents  #21 - Hawaii~   #20 - Telling Nelli anything and everything.   #19 - Scoring 100% on that Standford Test!  #18 - Tina givin' Amy a piggy-bag ride.  #17 - The "Sugary" Name Tag  #16 - Every one of Suzie's Parties!   #15 - Buffy and Angel   #14 - Late Night Phone Calls  #13 - The Night at the Cabin!!  #12 - Meeting Bryan~  #11 - The Twelve Boys.   #10 - Jaye's voice. (Only Chris gets it)   # 9 - NATHALIE AND TINA!!  # 8 - Romeo and Juliet  # 7 - The Humanaties Academy  # 6 - After Christmas Sales   # 5 - The songs I sang.  # 4 - Friendships  # 3 - AIM.  # 2 - Soquel  # 1 - Coming out. 
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      If you believe, That we've got a picture perfect plan, We've got you fooled, 'Cause we only do the best we can. And sometimes we make it. Sometimes we back it. But we get one step closer each and everyday, And we'll figure it out on the way. -Lizzie Maguire, "The Lizze Maguire Theme"   the first day back from break was amazing. it made me realize how much fun school had become. we worked more on our research reports and fam. tree projects, and english was fully devoted to romeo and juliet.  on monday we got a pysco bomb threat and they came in to shonicks class (A3) and they were like "kitty" or thats what chris remembers hearing. and then on tuesday (the day of the first fight of the week) we found out there was a bomb threat. bleh. it was some shitty teens who were trying to rob a bank and like i dunno.. it was in the paper.. i guess i shoulda read it..  wednesday (i think) was lisa's birthday and her, kate, emily and tessas dropped into the library during my break. we sat around and talked and lisa had this HOTT shirt that tess made! jorden stopped by too. oo yeah, since they ditched they all had fake names.  lisa- marie porter jorden- nathalie green tess- elizabeth kate- can't remember..  it was awesome. the history homework had been lightened because Mr. Shonick wanted us to devote time to our research reports. the next day, in english, we performed the opening to romeo and juliet. chris was tybalt and i played benvolio and that BITCH STABBED ME!! i think my dagger was defective... but i got him back, in the begininng ot the party i was capulet and he was tybalt again and i hit him in the back of the head for wanting to kill romeo. freak. kidding~ chris hastings is the coolest. alyssa was romeo tho! shes sooooo skinny.. and lisa was juliet...  on friday i went to math as always, at 7:40, then i had my open so i went into the library and had to sit thru the dancers dancing. bleh. eric watson was in there... and a bunch of girls.. LIKE THE MISSING ONE!! oh yeah, this chick went missin on wednesday and there were 2 more fights that week... so i wrote nathalie a 10 page note which took the whole entire period...  well anyway, after my break i skipped PE cause i really didnt feel good so i went with christina (who has an open B3) and so we walked around soquel village in the rain. she shared a bunch of personal stories with me and i shared some with her.. it was a bonding experience. we went to this like "Lion Park" and there was rain and stuff.. and we went to this yoga place and i almost died laughing!! it was great! then we went to the baglery and ate and we started walking back to school so i could get my camera (not that i had anyone to ake pictures of at harbor!! bleh!!) and we saw christina's mom and so we went to try and get crystal and nathalie outta class but they wouldnt come... so christina and i got my shirt and my camera from my locker.. and then stopped my longoria's room to wave at katy, matt, carson and chris... oo i think alec was in there too...  well we got in christina's car and drove to harbor. the bell hadn't rung yet so we decided to go walk down to the bus stop to check the times but then we got to mud and i was like "nuh uh!" and so we walked back up to the school and we talked with matt and tina and elena and fidel and NAOMI BRADFORD!! she is my harbor lover! i swear, if it wasnt for her i would have tottally had a shitty time. but yeah..  while naomi was off somewhere i was talking with elena jin and nathalie called so we went to go find her and steve saw me and he was like "BEN! BEN!" and i thought he was talking to me but i guess not! cause im not BEN! SORRY STEVE! :-(  with crystal + nathalie there it was a hell of a lot funner! christina and nathalie and crystal and i tottally shined! it was awesome! i would do it all again.. except i would've looked for jaye.. and maybe talked to michael and tell chris albrect (dominic's butt buddy) that i wasn't gonna beat him up.. ha thats funny...  so the bell rang and i went up to tina and hugged her for like a minute and she was like "get off me!" and then we started to walk down to the bus stop. it was shitty and muddy and i called jack vidnovic to try and get a ride but he had already left. stupid A days.. we got down to the bus stop right as the bus pulled away. "oh well, only 15 min." we thought. so we sat. and waited. and there was still no bus. so we sat and tapped our thrid eyes like that chick from Rich Girls. and STILL NO BUS CAME! so we were just about to start walking when this bus came around the corner and we all got on and paid money. i sat with christina and across from us sat nathalie and crystal. this girl new gabi, nathalie's cousin, and she talked to us for a little bit.  we decided on that bus ride that the next time we went to harbor we would PLAN IT OUT waaay ahead of time!  that weekend i got some early christmas presents like NOW 14!!! its a great CD!! luken is the awesomest!! and on saturday i drove up to SF with Andrew Galvez and his two friends, Kathy and Veronica. it was cool! and we went shopping EVERYWHERE!!  banana republic, urban outfitters, abercrombie, american eagle, victoria's secrets, fcuk, macys (OO IT WAS SOOOO FUCKING PRETTY!!), and i acctually think that was it.. hmm.. mebbe there was more... there were a lotta gay guys! and it was super fun cause andrew was there and he bought me in the zone and i bought myself the missy elliot CD. it was one of the BEST days of my life!!  on monday it was a pretty normal C day.. until english. our counselors came in and talked to us about college. i had a lotta questions and so fromnow on when anyone asks "any questions?" chris turns to me and says "brandon?"... yeah.. we also got our schedule options for next semester, but i didnt wanna change anything... well the whole talk was really exciting... it really opened my eyes and that night i searched online for college resources and academic standards.. and i was talking to JACK about it and he said that i didnt EVER come across as the INTELLECTUAL type! psh!! i guess its true then, he REALLY doesnt noe me!!  on tuesday and wednesday i was in full college over achiever mode. i asked questions (like chris knew i would) in all my classes and my french teacher said i was too much of an acheiver and that i would prolly end up killing someone one day. :-D oo i also met micheal over the phone monday and he was pretty awesome. thanks for transferring my calls dominic! even if you did have a shitty weekend and got drunk without me FOR THE SECOND TIME i still love you.. except not. on wednesday i even went to a french club meeting!! it was sooo cool!! we're having a french club party in january and spencers house! spencer the guy, not the girl!! he's soooo hott! tess and tiana and nathalie and naomi and kate are gonna be there too!! its sooo cool!  thursday was rainy. i dont like the rain. but at the same time i love it. we traded rough drafts in shonick and everyone who read mine said that it was good but no one could give me feedback. blah... that day after school while ellen and i were waiting for our ride, i danced with annie under the eaves and then hannah and i talked about starting a club.. lol we came up with funky names.. it was hilarious!! but then my dad came so we left~  friday was boring. nothing fun happened EXCEPT I BEAT hannah and elizabeth and emila and ivy in knock out! hahaha! can't touch this! it was really fun! but yeah when i got home i worked hard on my report and thats basically what i did all weekend.. i slept a lot on sunday and i finished my french family tree project that day... and on saturday (with help from juntado) i started THIS BLOG~!! and on saturday i also watched BUFFY SEASON FIVE~ HELL YEAH IT KICKED ASS! i cried at the end of "The Body" but, of course, dominic was there to kinda cheer me up.  monday i brought my family tree project. we worked more on rough drafts in shonick and thankfully it was so short tat we didnt work THAT long... bleh~ monday was lame.  tuesday was better. we had a sub in math and we did book work the whole period... it was easy and i finished early so i wrote a note to nathalie. piano was awesome and i passed a bunch of songs and got my grade up to a B.. all i have to do is pass 3 more songs and i get an A!! we played this really fun game and i was on a team with the lockewood sisters and ellen and angelica and umm... some other people who are REALLY cool but i dont noe their names. HAHA we brought briana, sara and lisa (not biancalana)'s team DOWN TO CHINA TOWN!! it was great!! the funniest part was annie was sick! the one day we have loads of fun she gets SICK!  well in shonick we did rough drafts for the last time.. the report was due on thursday. oo yeah katherine read mine and SHE DID A SUPER JOB~~ seriously!! she was the only one who could like.. correct it at all!! she is tottally my next pick for proof-reader... ooo in english we watched a scene from romeo and juliet and he had to pants on :-o !! it was.. magical.. as stephen would say.. oh yeah, him and i stopped fighting that day!! it was cool i guess...  wednesday we played knock out again.. its such a fun game! we also tried super knock out which.. i guess.. is where if the person who gets you out gets out by soemone else you're back in. so you win by beating EVERYONE~!! we didnt really finish.. but elizabeth and i talked a lot about.. mm.. stuff... mostly candy.. and during my open i hung out with tiana andkate in the library cause tiana needed to finish her family tree project. she has a really cool family.  thursday i wore abercrombie pajamas! they have mooses on them. we had a sub again in math and we played pictionary AGAIN.. oo we did that on wednesday too.. i forgot to write it tho~ anyone, my pajamas caught everyone's attention and yeah! it was fun stuff. we turned in research reports in history and watch the simpson's odessy and the simpsons hamlet!   "Now when people get wood they'll think of Trojans.." haha flanders...  anway, it was nice having a relaxing day in every class. i wished everyone i had A days with a Merry Christmas before it was over.  friday was the best! i got flooded with gifts.. and i talked with marissa and cloey (shoreline people) in the library. haha i tottally thought of the perfect april fools joke!! thanks marissa~!!  in pe ivy and i made up funny stories while running around the gym. HAHA bird in telephone wires~! there were some other great ones.. but yeah~ we talked about rumplestiltskin too.. i never got that story... we played SUPER KNOCK OUT the WHOLE rest of the period!! our one game NEVER ended!! it was great!! we had like 12 people playin, it was crazy~   at lunch new brighton kids came over and the got ready for a play in our gym. ooo evan was there~ hes a cutie!! it was haha ivy was trying to get me to go meet him and she was like pulling me into the emmy room and we like fell and i ran to tara it was so funny!! michele and i were gonna watch the play but we decided we'd rather hang out in french. french was acctually kinda fun! i sleep during the family tree presentation and then we sang christmas carols like this one about how santa claus saved 3 little kids from a butcher who chopped them up and stuff.  BUT FINALLY THE DAY WAS OVER~ IT WAS WINTER BREAK!!   winter break:  saturday: i sleep for 11 hours and went to the mall with nathalie, tina, amy and lily. i bought them all christmas gifts! a pac sun bag, a volcom wallet and an a&f shirt. it was a lotta fun and it was super cool to see amy again since i hadn't seen her since the thanksgiving weekend. lily is the awesomest!! oo i also set up luigi and dominic but it didnt last long. ha.  sunday: i seriously slept all day and it felt so good! i was refreshed and ready for winter break!  monday: chores at a friends house.. there was even a cameo appearance by steve (not to be confused with stephen).  tuesday: i got my braces tightened in the morning! it didnt hurt at first and my mom took me to surf city and got me a smoothie. stoked strawberry like always. thats when they started to hurt.. so i choked down the advil and got online. i didnt expect jaye to IM me.. but he did.. and we talked. at first i didnt think it would last more than a few seconds.. but the minutes turned to hours and it was acctually a lotta fun. jaye's a sweetheart, i've always known that. but on tuesday everything just.. changed... :-)  wednesday: oh goodie, christmas eve! today i rushed around getting last minutes gifts for my parents while they were prolly doing the same for me. in the evening i went out to dinner with my grandparents and my folks like always. i got money tho, so it wasnt too bad... that night i stayed up really late waiting for "santa" and i watched the nightmar before christmas and the grinch! both awesome movies.  thrusday: mErRy cHrIsTmAs! today was sooo cool! i got a bunch of money and Cds and DvDs and i even got a new computer for my room (after the remodle tho) and so yeah! it was great. but then it just kinda dragged on and i wanted it to be the day after cause thats when all the fun sales are!  FRIDAY: I HAD THE FUNNEST DAY EVER with nathalie! i woke up kinda late and then called her and we went to the mall. at macy's we saw A BUNCH of clothes on the clothes return table and there were people rushing everywhere. we went to a lot of stores. i got a bunch of stuff from abercrombie! gina, amy's sister, was working and she was really nice. oo and i got a bunh of stuff from american eagle too.. nathalie bought me a present and i bought her another one! lol it was a really soft belt. i saw nelli and anchor blue and i promised to call her so her and i could hang out over the break. we walked around and at wet seal we saw crystal and her sisters and then we saw jocelyn and lindsey. we walked to styles and nathalie saw this REALLY cute shirt and she got excited just to find out there was shit on it. but eventually we found on that was shit free, cause there were like 5 with shit on them, and we boguht them along with this candy fish that look like a toliet. oh yeah! there was this big belt that looked like a wand cause there was a huge star on it! seriously. it was big. like monica big. anyway, we walked to jamba juice and saw britnii and maria and mayra and other people comin' into the mall and britnii was like "brandon, too good to talk to us now?" and so i hugged her and nathalie and i were like "jocelyn's in styles if you wanna see her!" and they were like "screw that bitch!" so nathalie and i laughed all the way thru the parking lot and across the street. after seeing crystal's sisters again, at j.j., we went to choice so nathalie could get a bunch of tank tops and then we went to fresh choice and then my mom came and nathalie fell into a trash can! it was hilarious!. well i called nelli but she wasnt home so i called tara and we had a nice conversation...  saturday- i worked for more cash.. i made 50 bucks! oo and then dominic called.. he called on friday in the morning too but i was still asleep.. he wanted to go to the mall but i think he tree like fell down or something and so he couldnt get a ride. instead he and chris "hung" out.   sunday- i made a lot more money! it was really fun! cause i got to get rid of a bunch of old stuff and make space for new stuff! it feels good to get rid of... well it was lots of fun. i talked to jaye more and more! he's such a sweetie~ that night i talked to tina and nathalie until like 2.. well tina left at 1.. but i watched the shining which was REALLY scary but really good... nathalie told me the end and i yelled at her and then she said that everyone died which was the end and yeah! she confused me.. oo after that i watched Mystery Men and X2 and then i fell asleep... the shining was such a SCARY MOVIE!! but it was so annoying cause that chick coulda like killed that guy a bunch of times. and what was up with that freak, tony!? and REDRUM!! puhleeze~ why not just say "'MURDER' BACKWORDS"! wendy is supposed to be a horror fiction addict, cant she take a little real life ghost stories for a change? and those little girls will have me traumatized for life. AND THE NAKED LADY~ BLEH~!!  monday- jaye left me for tahoe! wow it rained a lot today.. i woke up at 2 and jaye said his goodbyes. so i went to the mall with amy and tina and we went into so many stores!! they got me some presents, my favorite was the MOOSIE BOXERS from abercrombie!! it was so much fun! in the arcade we raced each other and they one. by a second. wow. its only cause tina killed that cow instead of swerving like i did. it was a lotta fun and we should do it again sometime!  tuesday- i woke up at 2:30 cause i watched jerry maguire the night before.. i love that movie! "show me the money!" "shut up! just shut up! you had me at hello!" "sorry, im a little pregnant right now." ok yeah well i woke up at 2 ish and then suzie called and said she was having a small party (like 20 close friends) and so i got dressed and went. my fourth suzie party. it was acctually a lotta fun! i love her new house, even if it isnt as big as the other one.. ok, i loved her other house a lot.. what can i say? im materialistic... yeah.. well i got home and nathalie said her goodbyes and said shed talk to me in 2004~ then she left for reno!! woo hoo... well it got late and i went to be early  wednesday- TODAY! well it's basically almost over so heres what i did: i woke up at 9 because of loud remodlers and so i did a bunch of chores for more cha-ching. then i went to my aunts and ate cookies.. it was kinda lame.. everyone was down at first night and i was stuck at home with another cold. bleh~!! its so lame...  WELL I HOPE EVERYONE HAS A HAPPY NEW YEARS! 2004! WHAT WHAT!
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      If at first you don't succeed, Dust yourself off and try again. You can dust it off and try again. -Aaliyah, "Try Again"   this was a really fun month. it starts on the saturday of kassie's birthday party.   Kassie's friend rachel (this really funny girl from scotts valley, who i hung out with in jully...? sometime around then, we anyway, she) had a friend named luigi who came out and was all gay and stuff. well he gave rachel a book and an invite to the party he was having the next week at his (WOOT WOOT) BEACH HOUSE!! so like yeah.. i was thinking about going but they all said he was ugly so i kinda reconsidered..  anoways the party was really fun! we all were playing ddr and then it was like pizza dinner or something.  rachel+ kassie shared a seat and going left there was: stephanie, cali, kayla, cody, jourdain, ellen, kalie, teena, me and monica. well i kinda sat on the edges of both teena and monicas chairs. BAD idea. i almost fell... twice. and i was wearing my nice sweater...  well yeah after presents (wow, there were alotta animal stuff!) we got ready to leave.. and then we left for THE CORN MAZE~!! the ride up kalie and i sang country songs cause kassie's mom really like the western station.   so we get to the maze and like we go in the entrance and this guy tells us aboutthe maze and its all cold and dark and we can hear music from the haunted ranch place and so we like go in and we wander around finding different things and yeah... we end up all getting seperated, me with cody young. cody and i kinda kissed akwardly and yeah.. we continued on and kassie, teena, rachel and all of them jumped out and scared us. but no one was as scared as monica. i felt bad for her... but anyway, i was with her and then the chain saw guy was like somewhere and we ran and it was so scary.  From the windoooow To the kitchen!  Put some hot sauce on that chicken, Damn yo breath is kickin'!  So eventually we got bored with the whole "wandering-around-the-maze" thing and we decided to go str8 to the haunted ranch. now when we got to the entrance it was kinda creepy but it didnt seem scary at all!! teena was scared so since kalie had gone already, her and teena went out of the maze and waited for us at the exit.   in line, the actors (who were in costume), would try to scare us. first it was this vampire lady with big boobs. she scared me and kassie was like "don't worry, he's gay!!" RIGHT when she said that word a bunch of guys turned around and kinda looked at me. they were really cute, but yeah i figured they were red necks or something...  so we waited in line and i would ask all the actors if i could have a hug cause i ain't 'fraid of no ghost *wink* and then we got ready to go in and we annoyed this bunny man. a lot. so we went in the maze.. kayla, kassie, rachel, cali, stephanie, cody and i. everyone else went after us. it was really creepy in the begininng and cody fell and he was like "leave me! leave me!" and i was like "you are not being left behind!" and i piggy backed him thru the rest of the thing.. oo and i met a really cute vampire who was flirting with me and he was REALLY cute in his vampire make up. so we get outta the place after passing this scary girl who looked like she crawled outta a hybrid of the ring and the shining, we got to the CHAIN SAW GUY! and he like chased us it was soooo cooool!! and then we like left and on the way home teena and kalie were talking about the boys that had turned around when kassie called me gay, and kalie was like "they were touching each other and stuff... tottally fruity!"  so yeah.. i called jorden richardson (the jourdain that was with us was different then the other jorden..) and jorden and i talked and yeah... kassies mom dropped me off and teena promised to give me the book on monday at school.   so i got home at 1 and fell asleep pretty fast... on sunday i slept all day.. i was so tired!  monday started with high hopes of the soon to be 4 day weekend. the library was FINALLY reopened after an awesome renovation. and stephen (this guy i met in october) left school do to independed studies. anyway, on wed. night stephen "came out" and by friday the whole school knew so he was pretty pissed at me. but whatever.. he was kinda lame.  OO annie ross's birthday was on thursday! it was so great i got her a monkey and she got a bunch of other shweet presents... oo yeah, mesha and i wore the monkie on our legs and made it look like it was humping us.. :-D annie got these balloons from tanya and while mesha and i were watching her stuff, one of the balloons blew onto the grass and POPPED! and then annie came back and mesh and i were like "noo!! it was the grass!" and annie didnt believe us and so i took the other balloon (she got 2 small ones and a big.. um.. shiny one) and i was like "noo!! the wind popped it!" and i shoved the balloon against the grass and it popped and i was like "like THAT!" and mesha started crackin' up! it was great! HAPPY BIRTHDAY ANNIE BANANNIE~  saturday was suzie's SECOND party. in the morning i went shopping with teena and kendra and got some shweet pajamas. i was gonna meet dominic there and get my shirt back but he got their too late and we left. then the PARTAY~ i met some.. "new" people and it was a lotta fun! im even glad the rowland went dispite the fun we all had. no more vodka for ANY of you! tess is the my best sober friend! lol.. and yeah.. that party was cool but then the cops busted it at like 1 or 2 o'clock. i wasnt there tho but tess was upstairs and like the police told everyone to come down but she didnt so hahaha! i bet it went on their perm. record.   well the next day i hung out with matt and andrew galvez, old friends from cazedero! andrew is REALLY HOT and he's so sweet but he's kinda old.. and now we've decided to be friends until im older.. you noe how it is.. oh yeah, hes 20~ but that night was alotta fun and a lotta laughs! poor matt's prolly trumatized now tho :-) !  the monday of my fourday weekend i stayed home and worked for cash~! it was a lotta fun despite how it sounds, especially cause i watched the first two seasons of angel.~!! and tuseday i hung out with nathalie at the mall-o. i think christina and tina and sarah went too... mm? yeah. i got a sweater and um... i think i bought tina panties :-p  the 3 days that we were in school were kind lame. we didnt really do much in any of our classes except a test in shonick. but that wasnt too hard. i didnt do anything that weekend either. just homework and chores. cha-ching.  so the next week was the last full week of november. wootie woot! we started romeo and juliet in english, our fam. tree projects in french and our final research report in history. we learned how to use athena, this book search thing, in the library, and i got a bunch of nifty books on Joan of Arc.   that weekend i did more chores! i had made/saved 200 and was tottally ready for my shopping spree at valley fair after thanksgiving. on saturday i went to tinas house and she tried to kill me so i hid in her bathroom. but anyway, her and i talked with nathalie from 5 to 12 ish BEATING my record with DOMINIC~!! ha you lost! it was great but then i fell asleep and it kinda ended...   the last two days of school were crazy! i wished everyone a happy thanksgiving and in english we did this REALLY COOL shakepearean dance and like SOMEONE touched my ass!  patrick and i were the last ones outta mrs. miranda's class on the day before break.   Brandon- What are you doing over break? Patrick- Eating. Brandon- Fun... You're gonna get fat, you know...! Patrick- I never said what I was eating.. *wink*  Here's what my Thanksgiving Break looked like:  Wednesday- Went with Nathalie, Crystal and Tina to shoreline were we saw all the little people! it was so fun! but then we had to elave cause i wanted to go to the mall~ Thursday- THANKSGIVING! I had a huge family thing and I ate alotta food and i felt fat so i took laxatives but that just fucked up my aunt's toilet... Friday- I was planning on hangin' with Jack Vidnovic and Luigi but i was feeling under the weather and i was hyped for my V.F. trip the next day and so I just stayed home and watched some of the West Wing. then I went to suzie's THIRD party when i felt better. it was cool and we played fun truth or dare, except my dare wasn't the greatest :-/ ... Saturday- VALLEY FAIR TRIP! I picked Suzie up first, then Tess who lives close to CARSON! Carson's bro's car was TP-ed!! then we got Ivy from Watsonville and we drove and chit chatted all the way to Valley Fair. it was alotta fun and I got a REALLY cute shirt and nice cords. it was really fun cause we're just fun people :-D! omg there was this really nice watch at this one store. but no... It would have looked really ncie on Tina tho! but yeah.. Tess and Suzie got lost in the girl's part of Macy's and Ivy climbed on my back so we could find them! it was sooo much fun! then we went home and i felt really sick.. Sunday- stayed home sick and watched the rest of the first season of the West Wing. i learned a lot from it tho...  Well YEAH~!! that was the end of november cause of the thnxgiving break and all but coming up next was the BEST MONTH so far!! DECEMBER~!!!  LATO BRANDON~!!
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Voulez-vous couche avec moi, ce soir. Voulez-vous couche avec moi. Yeah yeah uh. -Moulin Rouge, "Lady Marmalade"  haha, the month started out great! school was awesome and everyone was so yeah..   but of course my history caught up with me and I began hearing and thinking more about dominic.   i saw him for the first time in 2 months at the mall (of course) and i kinda walked past him. he really pissed me off with his little pissy-ness but whatever. it was a fun day with janis, sally and monique. OMG! we saw ellen in the car on the drive home it was HILARIOUS!   school went on as usually... not really much change. alec was kinda acting weird and chris and patrick were a lil on the alert mode too... i think chris was stoned one day..   annie was lots of fun to hang out with and mesha as well.. and ivy was great.. i met tess in october at aldos. she was really fun and we got to be friends really really fast. michele was cool too and i talked to her and katy quite frequently.   first sat.: can you say kaboom? it was the anual monte carlo fireworks. nelli scored free tickets from kathryns mom.. lol.. even tho i bought a bunch from chris hastings..   i ended up going with kathleen and planned on meeting carolyn, nelli and katy there. i saw chris and carson (really funny guy from the h/a) there with alec. alec kinda gave me the glare and i talked to carson and chris for a little bit but continued looking at the really awesome booths.   Dominic came later... after carolyn and nelli and katy had arrived. lol! carolyn's dad is awesome! well back to dominic~ i let him borrow my shirt for no reason since he had a sweatshirt but whatever. i didnt noe i wouldnt get it back until 2004!! 

02,July,2004


	 
      Red red wine, close to me. Makes me forget that I still need you so. Red red wine, it's up to you. -Bob Marley, "Red Red Wine"   so yeah.. its the first month of school. the second day of school was pretty much the same as the first. in all our classes we talked about expectations for the semester and blah blah stuff like that.. the second day was the day i met ivy. she was in the humanities academy. we got to be REALLY good friends REALLY fast!! i met a lot of people in the Humanities academy, There was Adia and Matt and Katy!  Katy showed me her binder of Clay and she was like “this is my husband” so I got my pic. of hott Jamie Martin from all my children and I was like this is mine!  but before that, on the second day of school I found out I had PE with Ivy! While we were getting our clothes i met hannah globus who alsolikes a&F woot woot!! christine had pe w/ us too and so did emila and majusta from shoreline.  biology was pretty fun but kinda boring. it just lingered on and my only friends were chris hastings and tessa. and this new kid named chris cavero. anyway, i felt like transferring out and dropped my slip in the box in the office.  meanwhile, the humanities academy was getting funner everyday. I met jorden richardson and she is still the SICKEST CHICK EVER!! shes sooo nice and funny! and if shes reading this I LOVE HER MORE!! so ha!!  i also met lisa who was crazy in love with starburst wrappers. she was really nice and REALLY smart.  about mid september i switched from bio to french. it was a great change. french was a lot funner and i met christine and naomi.   i had pe with christine and we had small conversations before but french brought us closer. and i had some classes with naomi but it wasnt until french that i really “met”her. shes awesome, and loves to shop! naomi was great.  patrick was another cool guy i met in the humanities academy. he was really fun and yeah... hes my high five buddy! lol.  Brandon- "Patrick, u got somethin' on ur leg.." Patrick- " *Looks* Snot... *Laughs*" Brandon- "Is that what you call it?" Patrick- "Ur a lil bitch *Smiling* " Brandon- "At least I'm not a whore... Next time tell Alec to aim a lil higher..." Patrick- "Oh my god! Hey, ur the one who likes him!" Brandon- "Um, yeah. I'm gay... me no like women..." Patrick- "Oh, burn!" Brandon- "Well Alec is mad at me so whatever..." Patrick- "With good reason. All the guys hate you..." Brandon- "Do you hate me? *Puppy face* " Patrick- "Of course not...!"  in piano i met annie ross, a friend of aby who i also met in the hum. acad. aby and annie are super fun. tanya is cool too.. and so is Mesha! the monkey! haha! i love them. well annie and i met in piano and we practiced together. i also met brianna and corey and lisa in piano.. fun beans!  math got fun as katia and i got to be better friends. maya and stephanie (from shoreline) were in it and they are fun so yeah. nathalie also transferred in but transferred out after she failed her first test. lol. crystal transferred in. AND ABY HAD MATH WITH ME TOO!! 7:40 classes tho.. they’re bleh...  pe was great! i met elizabeth chuun! shes really cool and she is tottally my advisor. and like when the boys were beaing mean in the locker room she handled everything and i love her for it! jimmy nehrer is a meanie and so is greg nunn but w/e! i met suzie and randi in pe too.. suzie will be important later so yeah~!!  i met alotta people in the hum. acad. just look down there   outside of my classes, i met tara (super fun!) and nelli! nelli is and will always ever be the funnest girl ever! she is so optimistic and she makes us all laugh and she... she just never has a frown! we all love her! she is the same one from graduation who i wanted to be friends with! and she wanted to be friends with me too! yay! tara is really fun too. she is nice and she’s hilarious! at first i thought whe was a sophmore.. lol  that was the best!! ok well not much happened in september, i just met people lol. french was really cool cause NATHALIE and CHRISTINA were in it too!!   more people i met:  cassidy- hum. academy- hes really smart and funny sometimes kathryn- h/a (hum. acad.) – REALLY REALLY smart! shes so cool cause like she could correct my report and i thank her greatly for that! rachie- h/a -shes really cool! and she is best friends with katia! and they’re gonna move to la! alyssa- h/a - friends with jorden and REALLY REALLY REALLY SKINNY!! chrystaline- h/a- really nice and kinda shy carolyn- shes really cool and shes in band! yay! shes really skinny 2! michele- french- long story, i met her in french and i also met her at aldos and basically yeah, shes awesome nique- french- shes really cool and i met her in french! hailey- h/a- really pretty, really smart, really fun! monica- shes pregnant! jk shes awesome! kendra- french – tons of fun kayla- really athletic and yeah...  there are more people that im prolly forgetting BUT I’LL ADD YOU IN OCTOBER~!!  im adding madalee and heddy in october cause of the whole homecoming thing! yay!!
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Fate fell short this time, Your smile fades in the summer. Place your hand in mine, I'll leave when I wanna. -Blink 182, "Feeling This"   the first day of school started kinda like i was expecting. ellen picked me up at 7:20 for the carpool. on the way i had a nervous twist in my stomach... kinda like constapation only less severe.  anyway, we got to school and i opened my locker. 2 - 96. i'd put my combo up here but there are some people reading this who i dont really trust... anyway, i went to my first class. Geometrey. we all stood outside, waiting for Mr. McConnell to show up. That's when I met christine. my first friend at soquel. She came from Holy Cross.. or maybe she got kicked outta there for not believing in god. Whatever, anyway, it was a lot of fun. i learned a lot about her and her fam. WOO HOO! she goes to hawaii every year!! cool beans! so our stubbly math teacher shows up and opens the door. he's already divised a seating chart, alphabetical order, and im stuck between alex baker and brett ackler. Now, alex is pretty cool. hes smart and all that. but brett.. brett stinks... literally... it's called deodorant. well we get our geometrey books and the lesson begins. my mind blanks and i look around the room... holy shit! im the only kid from shoreline! but wait, isnt that chris hastings.  ok, chris hastings, here's the deal.. in May i signed up to be in this intensive humanities course. The humanities academy. the orientation was in the soquel library, in May as well. i wore my spiffy cow boy outfit :-D! I met some cool people there... alec and emily. and, of course, tessa, tiana and kate were there. but back to the story.  so i see chris... and then we talk.. and he's a pretty cool guy. def someone i want as a friend. the bell rings and i look at my schedule... next stop, Piano.  well that was a boring class... i thought when i walked out of piano. all we did was fill out forms. stephanie hammond and ellen are in it with me.. ellen.. little did i know she was going to get way lame, way fast.  so next is my open. i head to the library and i sit down at a vacant table. then, a girl sits down. but not any girl.. it was spencer kaufman. one of the most popular girls at shoreline.  "hey.. brandon right?" she said. i nodded. then she looked at my schedule. "walter for pe..? always dress out and never chew gum. she said. we sat there quietly filling out forms that our A2 teachers handed out.  but pretty soon the bell rang for break.  i met christine and a bunch of other people at my locker. we all had relativley close lockers due to a mishap at orientation... ill get into that later.. anyway, for my first break i headed to my next class. History.. with Mr. Shonick.   i choose a desk next to christine, and pretty soon tessa, tiana, and kate come tortting in. we exchange hugs and "how was your summer?" and then they take seats near me. a bunch of other people come in. there's chris! and emily! oo and crystal! crystal and i have short convo and then she takes a seat next to me. well pretty soon this crazy guy with poofy hair walks in. class starts and we pretty much dont do anything except read and stuff.  the bell rings. my next class is PE.  i walk to the gym with christine and sit in the bleachers. our kinda chubby but happy looking PE teacher walks in. he calls roll and when it all done he gives us some forms. the guy behind me accidently kicks me. "sorry.." he said when i turned around. "hey, im jon luken.." this really skinny kid stares at me with a grin of braces. but whatever. he's cute. lol. we talk a bit but then its over and i head to lunch.  my first high school lunch! you noe what that means.. im going off campus :-D! on the way down with kalie and christine, i run into, GUESS WHO!! NATHALIE! nathalie and i became best friends over the summer.. and it wouldnt have been possible without the DC trip, but i'll get to that after the first day of school.. hmm maybe i should've talked about the summer first.  after buying soda and food at Hernandez, we walk back up the lazy trial (No way I'm going up Sucide Hill!)  English is next. we head back to shonick, cause thats what is says on our sheets, but he tells us to go to miranda. on the way i catch a glance from Alec! boy has he gotten hot over the summer. we fill out more forms in English. there's a lot to do, and we get new notebooks. chris makes a joke about my shirt, but its accepted. Ellen got me my shirt.. another summer story I’ll get to later.  anyway, after English I head to biology with tessa and chris. We have assigned seats and I end up sitting next to.. well.. a big hearted fat kid. Biology breezes by and im out of school. Ellen and I head down to the main parking lot to wait for my dad.   that’s when I saw him.  I was sure he was gay… but whatever the case I felt like I had to find out more about this boy. That’s when I first saw eben.  ok.. so that’s just the first day… there’s a lot more to talk about mainly the summer and stuff.. so yeah..  Later days :-D brandon
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Everybody's workin' for the weekend. Everybody wants a new romance. Everybody's going off the deep end. Everybody needs a second chance. -Loverboy, "Working For The Weekend"   oi.. the end of the summer.. so depressing. august got me addicted to soap operas and text messages. all my children is a really good show for a soap opera. they deal with situations like everyone else. but yeah.. i got over it when school started. my new cell phone tho... that was a big deal. i added every body i knew in, and i mean EVERYBODY.  august is also when i met bryan. he’s really funny but kinda sensitive... anyway, we got to noe each other and yeah.. we were friends.  ooo~ august was the month of the family summer trip. yay hawaii! the trip was a lot of fun, but i wish we spent more time on maui! i was just starting to get a good tan! anyway... we stayed at this really fancy hotel and i met a lot of guys.. you noe me.. :-D my aunt wendy lives in hawaii and i spent a lot of time with her too (no, not kalie’s mom wendy. wendy from my dad’s side)  one night my aunts wendy, debbie and norma and my uncle took us out to dinner at the outback. it was CRAZY~ norma and debbie got drunk and hit on waiters and this one guy hit on ME! plus the scary bus boy watched me potty. and i think the bartender was drunk too.   anyway.. i read a lot of books. the required reading for the Humanites academy was awful. bleh~  i got back on thursday the 14th. the day.. jamie’s mom passed away. this meant jamie would be leaving for washington (the state).. in less than a week..  on sunday the 17th i got a phone call from my “Link Crew Leader” telling me about orientation. lol. i knew from his voice that he was gay.  the orientation was 20th. and of course, nathalie left town the day before.   i picked up ellen, kalie and teena and we drove to soquel. orientation was crazy. my coming out had spread like wild fire. all the shoreliners knew. after a short speech from the president and vice president (my GAY link crew leader) we split into link groups.  the only shoreliner in my group was cloey, but that was enough. we talked about our summer and our ex’s. my link leader was RC (like the soda!). and this other girl... we played a game where we had to remember everyone’s name.. it was fun.   there was one girl in my link group. she was talking about biology and geometry and the humanities academy.. but i didnt remember her from the meeting. when we got closer to school i found out her name was nelli. everyone ran up to her and gave her hugs and she seemed mucho popular. i wanted to be her friend. lol. pathetic, i noe.  after link crew we took pictures. mine SUCKED! probably cause that guy keep telling me to turn my body. OMG! get this! his name – Harry Dong. lmao. well after pictures we got schedules and lockers. locker 2 – 96. everyone one with us got lockers around us. it was really cool.  i looked over my schedule. great. i had a 7:40 class. oh well. not that bad. after we were sure that all 6 of us- me, kassie, kalie, ashlee, teena and ellen- could open our lockers we headed to the parking lot and left. all in all the orientation was fun. oo! i met a guy named stuart saepia. none of us knew he would be kassie; first kiss.  after orientation we went back to my house and watched chicago. it was fun. we sand and danced. speaking of dancing, after the movie we played DDR. but yeah. i had to kick everyone out cause it got late.  that night i was talking to dominic about RC. he asked his ex-boyfriend jack and then jack IMed me and we talked. he seemed really cool.  the last weeks of summer all happened way too fast. the last saturday was kalie’s birthday party. kathleen and i got her CD’s. the party was so much fun. besides kathleen, naomi and lianna were also there. plus kalie’s boyfriend. woo hoo. lianna is kalie’s short but funny friend. she’s tons of fun.  around 5 nathalie called from her trip. i sat down and i started talking to her. the conversation lasted 3 hours. lol. at 8 she left to watch the cheetah girls. she wished kalie a happy birthday and.. blah. it was over.  sunday (the next day) was awesome times 50! it was the day of sally’s birthday. janis, matt, teena and sarah rorvick were there so was tina liang!   ive known sally since 7th grade. shes really athletic. lol.  tina is the coolest girl ever! her and nathalie were my best friends over the summer and they still (more or less) are. tina and matt got in this huge food fight during the party. it was great.  after ,we went back to sally’s house and jumped into her pool. it was awesome. tina wouldnt get in tho.. but i almost pushed her in once or twice... but then she pushed me in... yeah.. good times.  the last day of summer i went shopping (duh!) we saw harry and amy and tessa too! it was so much fun, you have no idea!  but nothing lasts forever. and the summer that i loved so much came to an end.  i went to bed early, but i didnt fall asleep for hours. i couldnt stop thinking about school. oi.  -Brandon!! see yaa
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      The tide is high and I'm holding on, I'm gonna be your number one. I'm not the kind of girl who gives up just like that.. Ooooooh noooo. -Atomic Kitten, "The Tide is High"   Woot woot! it's my b-day month!  July was insane, and it all started where June left off. On July second I was outside tanning cause i wanted to look good. the thought of Dominic being gay made me realize there are probably a lot of other gay guys in Santa Cruz too. so i tanned. and then i fell alseep. and 2 hours later i woke up burned. my whole front side was red. ouch.  i took a shower and put some aloe on it... but it didnt really help.  on the fourth I went with Ili to wilder ranch. i pathetically hoped that she'd invite dominic but she didnt. that little runt. jk!!~ wilder was a lotta fun... except i was burned... and the ice cream melted... but i had my stars and stripes boxers on!! mm yeah. then, when i got back home, my grandparents came over and we had pie and stuff. oo! and the fireworks were soooo cool! my dog like wet himself, but he does that every year.  the next day jamie, maya and kristen came over.  have i mentioned maya before? maya's a really smart and really cool person from shoreline. i've known her since the end of sixth grade when we had drama together. shes lots of laughs and shes really smart. her bat mitzvah was soo much fun!  ok~ yeah.. jamie and maya and kristen came over and we watched buffy. :-D! The Hush episode was really scary and my burn was really itching. ooh yeah, and jamie broke her leg and she had to go to the ER room on the second (the same day i got my burn!).  anyway, that was fun and then it was over..  so the next day i went to see Legally Blonde 2 with Kalie, Amanda and Bobbi.   Amanda is adorable! shes funny and cute and no guy can resist that. bobbi's lots of fun too and shes a good advice-giver. anyway, the movie was really good and outside the theater we saw Jake Scruggs, Emily Hasty and CHRIS HASTINGS. coincidence or what! oo i really liked that guy from the movie and i thought he was gay the whooole time.. but then he asked that girl to marry him and it was like "bummer..."  that night all i could talk or even think about was chris. i was talking to gina and she IMed me dominic's screenname. and he wa son. so we talked for 2 hours and somehow chris left my mind. i didnt even think about him again until mid august. dominic was nice and really sweet... it didnt take long for me to fall for him. but i fall for everyone so thats not saying much.  on the 8th we were going out and we talked on the phone for 6 and a half hours! my all time record.. at least until november. :-D. and by the 13th we had our first date. we saw pirates of the carribean and yeah.. it was fun.. :-D! overall dominic's a great guy.. or at least he was at first. but then things started getting shitty and yeah. it ended. THAT COOLEST THING is that ym's horoscope guide said that i would fall for a pisces and it said the 8th and 13th were lucky days, but the 22nd was a bad one. and i broke up with him on the 22nd. freaky.  the week of my birthday was crazy. i went shopping a lot. jocelyn and i got kicked outta abercrombie for modelling and hara fell in love with cheyenne. kathleen and kalie and i had a lotta fun trying clothes on at anchor blue  OH! Kathleen! she's bundles of fun, and she was my best friend last year. for her b-day i got her 20o bucks worth of stuff including DVDs, CDs and 100 balloons!  ellen got me a shirt from American Eagle and i PROMISED to wear it the first day of school. but before that i wore it on my brithday when nathalie and I saw how to deal. that was such a good movie. outside the theater we saw this old guy selling brownies and we said there was prolly pot in them. lol.  july was an awesome month, and the perfect end to the perfect story was my brand new cell phone. woot woot.  yup yup ~Brandon
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      I will remember you, Will you remember me? Don't let your life pass you by. Weep not for the memories. -Sarah McLachlan, "I Will Remember"   the rest of June went by pretty fast. my time was mostly devoted to making collages of pictures from the DC trip and watching seasons 1-4 of buffy. as time went on more and more people knew about my sexual orientation. oo i redecorated my room too. anyway, the day.. well more like night was June 20th. Nathalie and I went to Capitola Book Cafe and waited for the release of Harry Potter 5. it was a lotta fun, and the Shoreline band played for a little bit. there were nasty milk and cookies but it was a really fun night. nathalie and i talked and talked about buffy and jamie added some stuff in.  jamie was really cool.. she went to shoreline last year but now shes gone.. well thats another story that ill save for august.  kristen was there too.. she was a grade lower than us, just like jamie. kristen is short, but shes cool.. and her hair is REALLY fluffy.  anyway, nathalie and i bought our books and then i waited around with kalie and naomi until it was time to go.  kalie's my cousin and naomi is one of her best friends... no explanation needed there.  anyway, staying up 'til midnight was a whole lotta fun and i wouldn't have as much fun doing it until kassie's party in november.  the weeks of June lingered on. two days after i got my book we took a trip down south to LA/Oxnard. i met a really nice guy at the hotel we stayed at. his name was Ben. anyway, i spent most of the trip reading and i finished the twice in eight days.  after we got back, my mom and i talked about my birthday which was less than a month away! i wanted a cell phone and she agreed that i should have one.  the phone rang and i picked it up. Ili. she's pretty cool and i've known her for a really long time. her and bonnie were the first people i told about me being gay. anyway, she told me to come see the play bonnie was in cause there was a gay guy there named Dominic.  "Dominic..." the name rolled over my tounge. "Hot name.."  anyway, i declined her offer to go to the play, but she left me one good thing to think about..  "dominic..."  hehe.. ptfo! -Brandon
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      It's something unpredictably,  But in the end, it's right.  I hope you had the time of your life." -Green Day, "Good Riddance"   there are some things you have to know about the DC trip.   40 eight graders take a trip to DC and NY at the price of $1600 and some other expenses for souvenoirs.    Day 1     at 4:15 i called janis and told her we were coming to pick her up. the car ride was icy cold. i could feel my stomach twist. my skin hummed with eagerness. we met at the airport around 5:30 at the United terminal, San Jose.   my stomach still feels knarly and i take some pepto bismol. anyway, we check in. my partner is teena davis. i�ve known her since like.. 1st grade..? prolly. she�s really cool and i couldn�t have asked for a better buddy. we check our bags and Mrs. Chavez gives us our boarding passes so we head to the gate. teena got stopped in security cause she had 40 hair pins in from grad. night. good times, good times.   we were all sitting around in the gate.  maya brodkey, ryan juntado, sarah rorvick, lisa vechionne, amanda yabarra, des cook, cerena barros, tessa libby, kate kahoano, kevin grassadonia, delia guerrero, nathalie servin, kevin deming, miguel dolores, teena davis, des cuneo, lizette lopez, jessica llanos, angelica solis, neil osterman, stephen mccon, elena rossman, miki burns, augustine perez, aaron melim, janis dinkins, lexi tenney, aly rumpanos, matt starkey, isais dolores, ashlee dominguez, kassie dogherra, ben fisher, jaime sanchez, ashley sanders, scott glass, dan.. um.. something, maddie flood, valerie getts, roxy rafi-tarie, elena jin and michele chelman.   anyway, we�re all sitting waiting for jocelyn zimniki to arrive at the airport.  now dont get me wrong, jocelyn�s one of the coolest people i noe, but at this point we are all a little angry at her.   she shows up and check�s in and before you noe it we�re on the plane, sweeping off the ground. daredevil played on screen and some of the kids (mikaela) watched it in espanol. ha ha. we ate fruit, took pics and when they turned the fasten seat belt sign off we got up and PARTIED! seriously, the walkways were crowded with kids.   it was crazy! we swapped CDs, played cards, read magazines, desiree cuneo (who i sat next to) even broke her chair.. you noe, the normal stuff. (i was also sitting next to teena.)   when the movie ended a blooper/comedy show came on and then NBC was up after that. lexi sat behind me and we were listening to the grease soundtrack, cause she played Cha-Cha in a play. �it�s raining on prom niight!� i brought that CD just for her.   uh oh! we hit turbulence half way into the flight. the second time we all were rushed to our seats. teena ended up with Maya and Matt behind me, and Maddie was next to me. Des still stayed by the window.   we still swapped CDs, and my graduation mix made elena and mikaela cry. aww. i was having tons of fun and we werent even in DC yet! des shuffled cards while maddie fiddled with the air vents.   the stewardess came around with soda. one ginger ale please. maddie and i took turns throwing pretzels at each other :-D.   the captian turned the sign off and we all moved around. Matt ended up sitting next to me. Des was figuring out her new digital camera, and matt played his gameboy.   we�ve landed at our gate, D16, in the Dulles airport. just imagine, 5 hours ago we left gate C2 at San Jose. I wonder if anyone got there bag sent to Cuba.. ha ha.matt and i had the same time on our watches.. and miki said something about making out with her cheek..? oo yeah, those blanket that had been touched by naked bodies!   we got our bags and yummy candy and then we stepped out into the humidity of the East Coast. it was a relief when our AC�d bus drove up.   We drove passed some famous sites, the Potomac, the Washington Monument, Smithsonian, White House, Federal Reserve and the Department of the Interior (don�t ask...)   There was a parade in front of the White House. lots of military vehicles and what not.  we passed more sites, a car being towed, a bus of old people, American History Musuem, the National Achives and the IRS!!   Starkey made a funny quote �Some people are smart, some people are not...�   our chaperones for the trip were Mrs. Chavez, her son and daughter: Mike and... um... the daughter. and also our librarian, Gayle Rorvick! She�s really cool.   we drove into Union Station and peered at the top of the building. Fire, Electricity, Freedom, Knowlegde, Agriculture and Mechcanics. all things that helped man evolve from the primitive beast he once was.   we j-walked to the train station, where we found a REALLY COOL food court. we bought pizza and talked about how Nathalie got hit on!! by an old guy!! that�s when i first met nathalie. well.. not first met, but first had a real conversation with.  Nathalie and and I got gelato ice cream. mm. and then i bought a pint of lemon ice cream for our room. Ahh! Mrs. Chavez said it would melt before we got back. we had to eat it super duper fast. I ate with Matt, Kassie, Nathalie, Janis, Teena and Aaron, but left to go shopping with Jessica and Amanda. I took the ice cream with me :-D.   We looked at books and finished the ice cream. we even saw a really cool train! we met up with Aaron, Matt, Kassie and Teena on the way out. Jessie said she�d she me on the bus and Matt was like �or in hell!� Then Kassie and I walked back to the bus taking pictures along the way.   on the bus we sang �Baby Got Back� and then our tour with Hopi got under way. We drove to the Jefferson Memorial and i got some cute pics of Miki, Elena, Elena and Lexi. there was a really big ledge too.. Jocelyn almost walked off it.   then we headed to the to the Roosevelt Memorial. Hopi (our tour guide) asked �do we need a bathroom break?�, Jaime yelled �NO! We got cups!� and then Miki was like �Not all of us are like Kevin..�   the FDR memorial was really cool. there were a bunch of waterfalls and we got a bunch of photos. it was really hot tho.. if i stayed outside any longer i would�ve friend like bacon. Matt said the Washington Monument looked possesed.. and then he said sweat was good hair gel. lol.   i�ve known matt since preschool.. more or less. he was friends with my cousin Kalie. his mom knew her grandma or something... yeah.. anyway, he was prolly my first best friend.   anyway, there was a bunch of rain and lightning. rorvick and i were gettin� pretty freaked out.. Matt said a bunch of things �Guys take showers so they don�t smell worse,� and �Maybe we could hit the guy who didnt make a california avenue.�   we went to a supermarket to buy stuff for our room. in line, Matt, Aaron and I stood behind a drunk guy in a dress! he was buyin� Burban! lol. then we got back on the bus and it started to pour like never before.   when we got to the hotel, Karen checked us in and we went to our lucky room. 509!! Mike came by and gave matt his medicine, and then we got ice to chill our drinks.   Kassie and Teena and Ashlee came up to see us when this creepy old man came over and said �I will not tolerate loudness, I have two 8 year olds in a bed and I will not have you waking them out. One loud noise and *snap* I�ll call the front desk and you�re outta here.�   we spent the rest of the night talking to everyone on the phone.   some hot gossip?   Tessa, Kate and Cerena got a security gaurd assigned right outside their door.  Des Cuneo, Nathalie and their room buddie have a fridge! They said we could store stuff in it...  Kassie, Teena and Ashlee got their phones disconnected!   kassie came up to get ice and i saw tape on our door and thought mike had sealed it, but he didnt and anyway, teena sealed it and we got ready for bed. Mike came to tuck us in and that�s when we found out he hadn�t put the tape on! he talked to us about tomorrow and about our �traumatizing� run-in with the old red neck.   everyone went to bed and i stayed up, in the bathtub, writing in my journal.    Day 2    we ended up talking until 2 the night before. the red neck was banging against our wall, but we weren�t being loud.. lol.. in the morning we woke up, showered, and went down to breakfast. I had eggs and cereal.   then we walked to the lobby and found a handicapped bathroom! it was so cool! it opened by itself!! and then we rode the escalators. then on bus, we heard about how elena rossman ran into her closet mirror because she thought it was open.   elena is awesome! i�ve known her since 5th grade... maybe longer.. yeah , i think longer. but anyway, shes really nice and fun and friendly. one time i threw a phone book at her and it hit hurt in the head. i bought her candy though! lol..   we headed to the Veitnam Memorial and we all got carnations to put out for soilders. our first stop was the Korean War memorial. 19 soilders lined up on the tundra. next we visted the Veitname Memorial, with 58,226 names cast in stone, the place felt lonely. empty. names. all names.   i left a carnation under Micheal A. Walter�s grave thinking he might be related to Cooper... that kid is so perverted.   anyway, we walked to the Einstein statue and took pictures. there was a rumor that if you touch his nose, you will get smarter. i touced it... twice... just in case. we got back on the bus. woo, that AC relieved me. oh yeah.. miki is goldylocks.. and janis is a hyena? i dunno, those two are crazy. Hopi had a bunch of sweat stains on her butt... lol..   George Pataki and Chris Cox. New York Senator and California Representative. I met them both! We got out of the bus and headed to the front of the Supreme Court building. thats the judical branch. these hairy guys came up to us.. i think they were making fun of people who wore fur cause they were dressed like cave men.   anyway, we took pictures and i told tessa that her family had come to resuce her from civilization. �Smile and say FAMILY REUNION!� yeah.. you had to be there...   then we went to the Library of Congress. there was a naked statue of Neptune in the front. with a 9 incher! Inside the library we saw a bunch of books and there was a really cool zodiac floor! Nathalie and I love it! There was even the first book ever printed!   we walked to the capitol building and I met Chris Cox from New Port Beach! He shook my hand! It made my day. we went in the building and we saw TONS of priceless artwork. it was amazing. De Soto, Columbus, The Pilgrims, Pocahontas, The Declaration, Saratoga and Yorktown were some of the paintings.   we also saw a bunch of statues and learned a lot about the capitol. then we met george pataki. on the capitol building lawn, there was a protest. �Circumcision is wrong! The foreskin is not a birth defect!� boy, that prolly made the jewish boys behind us very happy. oo! alec is jewish!   yeah, back to story. oh we went to McDonalds next and we have to eat EVERYTHING we bought. I ended up eating everything everyone else didnt want too.. Fries, Milkshakes, McNuggest (Nathalie calls them �Muggets�) and more fries. i left them a souvenior the janitor will never forget. Kassie said �we should take a picture of the fries!� and kate was like �just look in the toilet tomorrow!�   Next we stopped at the White House visitor center. I picked p some stuff for Mr. Sullivan AND! i got a coloring book! yay! we walked back to the bus and stopped at the White House. I got a stick from the lawn! it was really cool. and i saw the West Wing! That is a really good show...! there were a lot of squrriels too.. we walked past Alexander Hamilton and the Treasury Building and we even saw a monument to General Sherman! it reminded me of Gone with the Wind.   we then went to the Holocaust Museum and watched a story about a boy named Daniel. it was really sad. there was even a little walk through thing and Lisa V. was my partner. Lisa is really cool.. and really nice too.   then we went to the old post office and went up a glass elavator. it was ok, the veiw was kinda weird, but hey, i had Kevin grassadonia�s booty scrunched close to me for most of it, so it was great. coming down the elevator, teena scared me to death. we left the old post office and headed to..   THE INTERNATIONAL SPY MUSEUM! way lamer than it sounds... i got a cool shirt tho. and i beat kevin g. a lot though at this weird game. ha ha i won. we got to climb through an air duct too! it got really boring.. but then there was this thing where you could see ur house on a satelitte! it was awesome! i bought a sweet t-shirt that says �Deny Everything� yay!   it started to rain and we got back on the bus. soon we stopped at a pizza place. matt got cheese poured in his hair and i made kassie laugh by saying �Cheese Me� when the waiter came around. Well we headed to the Lincoln memorial after that. we took a bunch of pictures and learned a lot about old Abe. He was really tall...   we went shopping at this little place with a bunch of street vendors and the rain began to pour. we got back on the bus and headed to the Kennedy Center for Fine Arts. there were flags from every nation except Lybia, Iran, Iraq, Cuba and North Korea. we also got to see into an opera and we saw a hall of states. then we went up a balcony and took pic.   Next, we drove to the Iwo Jima memorial, where Janis and I were the tour guides. fun stuff. we took a bunch of pictures of the six soilders raising the flag and then we just wanted to go home and sleep.   when we got to the hotel, Janis and I used the phones to try and call Ellen. it as busy, but we met these 2 girls and janis gave them her room number. When i got to my room, the door was open and Aaron and Matt were gone, probably getting ice. Lexi and Elena called and told us to go downstairs to a party.   we brought candy and soda and MM they had cheez-its. we also got to raid Mrs. Chavez�s room and get free food. then we went back to our rooms and tried to get to sleep. but instead we ended up talking until three. we were really tired in the morning.    Day 3    FRIDAY THE THIRTEENTH!!   today was the trip to Arlington national cemetery. after a quick breakfast we were taken into a world of sad sculptures and gravestones. we visited the eternal flame and the tomb of the unknown solider. the hike was a long one, but the changing of the guards was.. for the most part... worth it. it was kinda dramatic.. but it�s to honor the dead so i guess its ok. i liked it.   all in all arlington was good. after the cemetary, we headed for the washington monument. we rode the elevator to the top. well, the 100 floor. the look down was 500 feet! it was really cool, we got to see so much! after the monument we walked to the Smithsonian where we said �Aloha� to our tour guide.   we got to travel around the �Mall� which is the term used for the block on which the Smithsonian museums sit. We breaked and picked buddies. Ashlee and I headed for the Natural history museum and headed all the way down to the food court. we got soo much food!   i�ve known ashlee since kindergarten..? yeah, she�s really cool and funny. and she likes to read a lot, so if i ever read a book then her and i can have discussions about it.. its funner than you think :-D   anyway, after we looked at a bunch of gems and the Hope Diamond. 52.27 karat from India. there were a lot of crystals and stuff and i got a sweatshirt from the american history museum. we went across the street and walked down to the art museum. we bought a few bottles of soda. we took pictures in front of a fountain and then went into the air and space museum. thats where we met up with Janis, Nat, Valerie, Ashley and Lisa.  Nathalie and I ditched Janis and Ashlee and hid behind a fence thing that we thought was tinted (we can see out but they cant see in) Janis and Ashlee were walking aroundon the floor below. suddenly they look up at us and wave. Nathalie screams �I THOUGHT THEY COULDN�T SEE IN!�   we continued walking and we got in a WW2 plane! how fuun!! we checked out some rooms with planets in them and we looked at some space shuttles too.   at five we met matt, ben, aaron, janis, ashlee and everyone else in front of the museum. it was scorching hot but the bus came soon and we drove to the Department of Printing and Engraving. we saw moola being made and we checked out the gift shop.  on the ceiling there were motion censors, and my head almost set them off.   after the money place we drove outta DC. we drove to virgina and stopped at the pentagon mall where we went shopping! ee! ashley sarah and I went to abercrombie and then viki�s. it was so much fun! they had really cute undies in fcuk. then we went back to the bus, running through the rain to get to it.   back at the hotel, we all got dressed in our bathing suits and went down to the pool. i sat outside and wrote in my notebook since the rain had died down. i walked with elena back to the lobby but i realized i had forgotten my key. we went to the front desk to ask for another one, but they wouldnt make one for me.   teena walked me back to the pool and we got aarons key. i went into the elevator and teena said �be right back.� so i held the elevator and this guy came in and was like �going up?� and i was all �yep..� and then a while later he got out and teena came back and got in and he was like �going up?� and she was like �sorry.� by the time i got back to the 4th floor, elena was done showering and we all hung out. it was another hall party! i went in kevin�s room and we talked and yeah, it was fun.   i ran back up to my room and slipped a note under the door for aaron and matt. i also brought candy downstairs. the hall party was gettin� hot and i ran back to my room to get soda right when matt and aaron got back. matt and aaron went down to the party but at 10 we had to get back to our rooms and tuck in.    Day 4    that night we packed and packed and after we had cleaned our rooms we watched drew carey. i fell asleep tho and i slept like a log... or maybe a rock... i would say a baby but i guess babies dont sleep super well. oh yeah! that night i got a call from my mom and thats when i found out she was PREGNANT! the baby�s due February 16th! see ya all at the baby shower :-D!   anyway, the next day we woke up late and i brought a soda down for breakfast. when we were in the lounge i opened the soda and it SPRAYED all over me. i went up to my rooom and changed, and headed back to breakfast, but then kassie ran into me with a plate of eggs.. so i showered and changed again.   then matt came up to the room and we all brought our luggage down to the bus. wihtin a few hours the bus was moving and we had left virgina for good. we watched night at the roxburry and nathalie, matt and i laughed SO HARD! kassie slept in the hallway. crazy. but anyway, i fell asleep during the movie, but nathalie and matt�s talking woke me up.   after the movie we made a pit stop in Delaware. i missed Maryland! we took a bunch of pictures in front of the �Big Guy Restraunt� statue. when we got back on the bus we drove to New Jersey while watching Orange County. I love that movie! We laughed so hard. after the movie we were on the border of New Jersey and after we went through a tunnel we ended up in Manhattan, New York!!   we finally made it! we stopped at our hotel and dropped off our bags. our tour guide arrived at the new york part of the tour started. first stop: Texas and Texas for lunch! after that we bought some stuff from the local street vendors and we spent most of our time walking around and looking at the sights.   we bought some shirts and then we walked to radio city music hall and then to the donald trumpt building. thats when we went in to take a tour of NBC studios. it was a lot of fun and we saw the SNL set and even some previews for Will and Grace! i bought a will and grace shirt from the gift shop.   we headed back to the hotel and the rain started to pour. my bag started to rip and right when we got in the door it fell apart. woot woot. we went upstairs and all got fabbed up. we looked so perfect and we walked to Chili�s in our formal wear. i had this cute brown american eagle umbrella!   anyway, at chili�s we all sat around and talked. ashley sanders and i danced to genie in a bottle, the spanish version. then we walked to the New Amsterdam theater. we got into the Lion King and everything was goregous. the play was beautiful and at the end i cried. it was amazing.   we walkd to times square after the play. i made some jokes about the hookers and then we all got together and took a picture. on the way we saw lisa leslie from the sparks, and before the picture we saw chopper!! he was really cute, and nathalie got a hug! there were a bunch of pigeons.. ee.. i hate birds.. anyway, the picture was good but i look shitty so, no, im not showing you.   we walked back and saw billy joel!! �we didnt start the fire!� that�s like mr. sullivan�s favorite song. anyway, we got back to the hotel and we watch SNL before going to sleep.    Day 5    we went across the street to this greek diner where i got pancakes. yummy. then we walked to the subway! it was so cool! it was all dirty and stuff and we were going really really fast and then it stopped and i fell over.   we got a few feet away from battery park. we saw the globe that was in front of the WTC and it was really emotional. we went and waited in castle clinton for a ferry to the islands. we met a strange but funny guy and played the limbo with him.   then we went to the island ferry and took a ride to Liberty Island. on the way we met a bug named billy and ashlee got kinda pissed off. then at ellis island, i was talking about how chiuahuas were gonna attack miki and i was like �yo quiero taco mikaela.�   miki is awesome! i�ve known her since 3rd grade. we both had calero but switched out to sherwood! tons of fun! shes really cool.. and tottally blonde :-D   anyway, when we got into ellis island i looked for some immigrants from my family. then ashlee and nathalie got me and we went outside and had a picnic. kassie climbed a wall and the security guard told her to climb to the top. she was gonna do it but he said he was kidding so oh well to that.   we got back on the ferry and got back in battery park. we walked down wall street and i got a picture of me on a bull :-D !!! then we walked to this deli and ate. after we went to ground zero. it was a reflective moment and it was an emotional experience.   after that we took a subway ride to centeral park. there were a lot cool plants and picture to be taken. i even say a statue of balto. oh and teena started to get dehydrated..   we went to virgin records and bought CDs and posters and we were gonna go to MTV studies, but we went back to the hotel and got dressed up for our trip to the empire state building.   we took a trip to chinatown and little italy. the restaurant was REALLY fancy and i could barely eat anything it was so fancy. all i ate was the cheese. yummy. i ate nathalie�s cheese too. then we went bargaining in chinatown. i got kassie and teena bags which were originally $30 each down to $28 for both. ashlee also got a cute necklace.   it was really cold out, and the over look from the top of the Empire state building was really pretty. the sunset was so nice. the line town was REALLY long, but kate and i cut and then in the elevator we sang songs, like that one that never ends :-D then i was almost hit by a car.. and the sign said �walk� !   we went back to the hotel and it took a while to fall asleep. it was our last night of the trip and i was kinda sad to be leaving.    Day 6    the last day was perfect. we woke up and went to this huge place for breakfast. teena poured sugar in my hair and then i attacked her with it! good times! kate and tessa started laughing when i did that.   anyway, we walked around more and got to see the today show being filmed. it as a lotta fun. nathalie and i went to starbucks and got really good hot cocoa. did you noe starbucks was named after the guy from moby dick? he drank a lotts coffee.. lol   we walked to a really pretty church and kevin grassadonia prayed. it was so cute. lol  after the church we went to this place and then mrs. chavez said we could go do whatever we wanted for 2 hours. shopping in new york! woo hoo! we went to F A O Schwartz and the Disney Store. it was soo much fun. we were the first customers in F A O Schwartz and they clapped for us! go brandon and kassie! the store was amazing.   after shopping we took a walk past playboy enterprises and down to the Hard Rock cafe. it was the perfect lunch and the ride to the airport was wonderful. teena and dan fell asleep next to each other and they were kissing!! lol!   we waited at the airport and i had everyone sign the back of my times square pic. thenw e got on the short plane ride to chicago. i sat next to a guy writing a porn novel and a fat guy who was really paranoid!! matt was over on the other side and yeah... it was way lame and way creepy, and i took out a vomit bag and the guy next to me freaked out! it was so funny! well, yeah.. i still have that vomit bag..   jocelyn and i went to get mcdonalds while everyone else waited at the other gate. i came so close to telling her i was gay.. but i decided not to. we ended up sitting next to each other on the plane back to San Jose, but i switched with kate and sat next to mikaela and maya.   the flight home was fun.. and sad... �how to lose a guy in 10 days� made me cry.. and then when we were landing miki and i were holding each other and crying alot. it was so sad. but it was the perfect end to eighth grade.   i�m gonna knock on wood when i say this, but after that trip my life was perfect. everything was amazing. i dont noe what happened.. but something changed. at the trip was the best.   i gave hugs to everyone at the baggage claim, then i ran out and met my parents at the car.   �how was it?� they asked  �wonderful..�   later  -brandon!   
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      As we go on, we remember  All the times we had together  And as our lives change, from whatever  We will still be friends forever. -Vitamin C, "Graduation"   &nbsp;  the summer was a new beginning. no, no, june was a new beginning. the days leading up to the last day were crazy. we had to get all our work back, and I even got a letter from 5th grade.   it started with bonnie and ili. they were the first people I told. that I liked guys. It was scary at first, but after it felt really good. like masterbating for the first time. ok� that was a little too much. :-) so what started as small got bigger and bigger. graduation practices and.. lol.. joel marshall.. filled my thoughts for the last days. suddenly it was grad. night. everything seemed so perfect� except Mrs. Zahrobsky�s fucked up balloon arch. well yeah it was beautiful.   and the dance was way awesome. the theme was Hollywood, and boy was it a night with the stars. I told a bunch of people that I was.. well� you noe the word. The night was ending.. tears were falling.. and dances were being danced. Shout outs to des cuneo, lexi!, mikki, maddie, amanda and naomi for havin� fun with me on the dance floor.   the night ended, and janis and I ran around givin� everyone hugs and saying our last goodbyes. I still remember elena rossman asking me for a hug even though she knew we would see each other the next day. You noe I never really realized how much I was gonna miss these people until after they were out of my life. But you cant live in the past forever.   I dropped Janis at home, promising to call her before I picked her up the next day. And then I went home and passed out on my bed. it was over. middle school was over. it was finally over.   
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      I'm really really hot, Everytime my record drops, Radio says I won't stop, 'Cause I'm killin' them. -Missy Elliot, "I'm Really Hot"   name: ~*~ BRANDON ~*~   gender: male :-)   height: 6'1" the doctor says   hair color: its brown.. but its prolly gonna change cause nathalie just opened up a concetration camps for insects and she's gonna test repellent on me..   eye color: green/ hazel.. they're so pretty!!   location: ~*SaNtA cRuZ*~   fears: fears? birds, forgetting stuff, spiders and things i cant remember...    Have I ever?   peed my pants: the last time i saw a picture of tina doin' the hokey pokey   cheated on someone: well it never was offical..   fallen of the bed: i fell of a couch.. i've fallen of the couch a lot...   fallen for a relative: yeeah... noooo   had plastic surgery: well that quiz said i got breast inplants... what can i say, im very passionate..   failed a grade: never! woot woot   broken someone's heart: it was an accident... and the heart was made outta clay... but harry had a happie v-day anyway :-D sorry kassie!   had your heart broken: dominic :'-(.. just kidding   had a dream come true: im livin' a dream.   had sex: mm mm, nope   had a lap dance: suzie's party.. the third one..   done something you regret: so many things!   cheated on a test: yeah tinas... WELL NATHALIE CHEATED ON MINE!   been raped: hehe almost on friday...   had a broken body part: my heart!    Currently?   wearing: abercrombie clothes!   listening: to nathalie make plans for monday   eating: orange juice.. mmm   feeling: happy.. like always   reading: nathalie's horoscope   located: santa cruz~~   chatting with: dominic and ryan.. kinda..   craving: you dont wanna noe...   should: work on my reports... or fix my blog... or watch more buffy.. i like buffy!    Do you?   brush your teeth: um.. duh?   like anybody: you'd be surprised   have any piercing: nope   drive: hell yah!   believe in Santa Clause: ho ho ho   wear deodorant: yah, i think it's one of those important things....no one likes a stinky poodle... 'cept.. maybe another stinky poodle   ever get off the damn computer: duh to sleep and go to school    Friends   who have you known the longest: kalie, naomi bradford and nathalie, cause we're family!   do you belong to a crew: mmhm... i belong to soquel!   do you hang out with the opposite sex: mmhm, girls are funny and they have belly buttons.   are you popular: i dont wanna sound concieded.. but yeah... kinda..   do you trust your friends: yup. of course.   are you a good friend: some what neglective... but who isnt?   can you keep a secret: yah, if it's really personal, but if it's stupid i won't.. that's right ellen! i'm telling everyone about your hairy teeth! get new sweaters you fat lil girl! BOO!   The last person you...   hugged: natalie and ivy and people   IM-ed: dominic   talked to on the phone: nathalie, dominic and michael   yelled at: hmmm my computer... hey at least i dont talk to my pants!   checked out: alec   fell in love: 3 guesses...   tripped on something: patrick   turned down: so many...    Personal   what do you want to be when you grow up: bigger   what was the worst day of your life: when i forgot to wear black shoes with my outfit and i wore the green ones, but then i changed to flip flops so it was perfect!   what is your most embarrassing story: i don't remember....and if i did i wouldn't tell u   what was the best day in your life:the past 4 months!   what comes first in your life: money.. men.. and my friends,   do you have a gf/bf/crush: tons   what are you most afraid of: dominic!! jk~ um.. being poor and a loser and unpopular... or having someone close abercrombie!   if you had an extra set of eyes, where would you put them: on my face, moron.   what do you usually think of before going to bed: boys.    Favorite?   Movie: Bring It On! and Orange County...   Song:  -pass the dutch  -milkshake  -me against the music  -lady marmalade   Relatives: nathalie :-D   Sport: volleyball and all sports are fun when ur having fun and not in p.e.   Vacation spot: hawaii or new york   Ice cream flavor: ice cream is ice cream, no matter what the flavor.   Fruit: all berries...   Candy: lollipops   Car: BMW convertible   Class: every class.. especially english   Holiday: christmas.... and summer   Day of the week: friday, saturday   Color: all colors of the rainbow   Name for girl or boy: Girl-Joceyln, Boy-Alec    Do you?   Like to give hugs: to everyone   like to walk in the rain: yes   sleep with clothes: pjs   prefer black or blue pens: all colors   dress up for Halloween: mmm yah   have a job: i want one.. cha-ching   like to travel: yah   sleep on side, tummy, or back: i don't know...all?   think you're attractive: no   Want to marry: when it's legal   ever have the falling dream: falling, like off a building   have stuffed animals: a lot...from New York   go on vacation: yepperz..    What do you think about...   Abortion: if it's nessecary   Bill Clinton: better than bush   Smoking: pointless   Eating disorders: will stop world hunger   Suicide: decrease over population   Summer: tan time   Tattoos: nah.. cause they're permanent.   Piercings: some are hot.. like cartalige peircings..   Make-up: helps   Drinking: mmm   Guys: cuties   Girls: fun fun fun    This or that (Or the other thing)   pierced nose or tongue: i don't like either   be serious or funny: both   single or taken: livin up the single life   simple or complicated: a lil of both   sugar or salt: depends   silver or gold: ill just take anything that glistens   tongue or belly button ring: belly button rings   chocolate or flowers: chocolates..flowers, you keep them around for awhile and then they die...now chocolates u can eat   angels or miracles: miralces, cause they're perfect!   color or black and white photos: both   Sunrise or sunset: sunrise, another beautiful day.   M&amp;Ms or Skittles: skittles   Stay up late or sleep in: both   taller members of the opposite sex: yah   sun or moon: moon   Diamond or ruby: dunno..   Left or right: right   vanilla or chocolate: i like both   kids or no kids: mmm i guess kids...they move out eventually   half empty or half full: either, as long as it's something tasty.   give or receive: receive   lace or satin: satin   a year of hot sex life or a lifetime friendship: lifetime friendship, cause there are always benefits :-D   happy or sad: happy   wonder or amazement: amazement..   blondes or brunettes: i don't discrimanate.    Girls only   what do you look for in a guy: personality and a sense of humor and cuteness...   sweet or innocent guy: mmm sweet   smart or athletic guy: a lil bit of both   favorite cologne on a guy: anything...   best gift a guy could give: a million dollars? jk...i don't know, i guess like of ppl say, "the thought of it counts" but i guess if i have to answer it'd be his love. that's all that really matters. that and sex.   Flowers, sweet or wasteful: sweet   Sweetest guy you know: dominic? but yeh.. hes my daddy    Other kind of questions   what's your favorite kind of tree: a palm tree   out of all of your friends, who has the coolest room: nathalie! viva la ants!   When you look at a person with lime green tights on...what do you say: i dont say anything... i run away... 
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      I know you wanna hit that, I know you wanna hit that hit that. -The Offspring, "Hit That"   I SAVED A BUNCH OF FUNNY and MEANINGFUL andCOOLIO STUFF YOU GUYS HAVE SAID, SUNG AND HEARD,  SO I THOUGHT I'D PUT IT ON HERE<> <>   /\ / |\\  / /|\\\  / /\| \\ / /\\| \\ / /\\\| \\ / /\\\\| \\ / /\\\\\| \\ / /\\\\\\| \\ / /\\\\\\\| \\ / \\\\\\\\| /\\ / \\\\\\\| /\\\\ / /\ \\\\\\| /\/\\\\ / /\\\ \\\\\| /\/ \\\\ \ \\\\\ \\\\| /\/ /\\\/ \ \\\\ \\\| /\/ /\\\\/ \ \\\ \\| /\/ /\\\\\/ \___\_\_\|/\\/\\\\\\V VoLcOm   Reasons why you should date a volleyball player: They hit hard. They get low. They bump well. They can do it in 6 different positions. They like to be on top of the game. They take care of the ball. They give it all they've got.  Never say goodbye when you still want to try,  Never give up when you still feel you can,  Never say you don’t love that person  Anymore when you can’t let go.  -Amy Ng  jackorcan: i have ivy's sweater jackorcan: its sooo warm ScCherrieBug11: ok you stole it? ScCherrieBug11: first you turn gay..now you're a thief ScCherrieBug11: what's next? jackorcan: lol ScCherrieBug11: are you gonna jack a plane? jackorcan: no no ScCherrieBug11: dang brandon  Naomi: lol! poo on u! lol jk ohya lol hehe yay Brandon: HAY! poo on u is so my line! since like the 5th grade Naomi: oh no its mine! Brandon: oh yeah, whatcha gone do about it? huh? :-D Naomi: lol oh, ill tell u! jk Brandon: lol wanna fight? ill take u on in abercrombie Naomi: oh, bring it on bitch Brandon: pouffiasse! i'll stain u clothes so bad not even AJAX COULD GET IT OUT! what now! just kiddin', i love ya! Naomi: haha, is that a threat? lol jk Brandon: oh yeah, its a threat, how does that make u feel Naomi: well then, when u get tha hate, im gonna piss on it! haha! lol Brandon: lmao!  Naomi: haha, lol, Aah, ur so great to talk to   THUMBELINA TIME- romeo and juliet.. were very much in love when they were wed.. they honored every vow.. so where are they now? they're dead! DEAD! very very dead!  jackorcan: i come home in the mornin light Wut Wut Your Mom: my mother says when u gonna live ur life right? jackorcan: oh mommy dear were not the fortunate ones Wut Wut Your Mom: and girls juss wanna have fun jackorcan: oh girls just wanna have fun jackorcan: the phone rings in the middle of the night Wut Wut Your Mom: my father says wut u guna do wit ur life jackorcan: oh daddy dear, you noe ur still number one Wut Wut Your Mom: but gurls they wana haf fun oo gurls juss wana haf jackorcan: when the workin day is dun oh girls just wanna have fun Wut Wut Your Mom: that's all they want jackorcan: girls just wanna have fun Wut Wut Your Mom: oo gurls juss wana haf funnn! I LOVE YOU ANNIE!  jackorcan: omg i looove the new britney spears CD SCsnoop48: haha SCsnoop48: yeah, i think its alright  jackorcan: omg i love the new britney CD simianantithesis: weird... simianantithesis: lol there's a song about masterbation in it  jackorcan: OMG I LOVE THE BRITNEY SPEARS CD!! CrAzyPolKa DoT Z: is it good? CrAzyPolKa DoT Z: she can't sing jackorcan: so good! CrAzyPolKa DoT Z: but she has good club music jackorcan: andrew bought it for me :-D  jackorcan: I LOVE THE NEW BRITNEY SPEARS CD Sc cHErrIe bUg11: o no.  Brandon- "Omg Tessa, you're so skinny!" Tessa- "You are too.." Brandon- "NO! Im a hippo!" Kate- "A really skinny one!! :-D"  Ivy- "Well I like him, but Tess like him even tho her best friend was going out with his boyfriend. And then Tess hooked up with timmy and now im with Matt but before that Michele went out with Jack.." Brandon- "And that's the way you all became the Brady Bunch.."  Annie- "OOO MATT AND KATIA!" *Faye turns around and reveals its her and not Katia with Matt...* Annie- "Oh! Haha.. Faye... Haha...... I'm the smartest person I noe!" Mesha- "You don't noe a lotta people... huh?"  ANOTHER ANNIE and BRANDON ORIGINAL! im smooth just like your dad the best partner you've ever had lets go lets go im hot just like your mom i wanna get it on  lets go lets go im yummy like your brother for you there is no other lets go lets go im sexy like your sister dont mess with this hot stuff Mr. lets go lets go im as savage as your best friend our making love will never end lets go lets go im cuter than your pet now let me get you wet! lets go! lets go!  Tiana- "So Posiden and Thesus frolicked through flowers?!?!" Brandon- *Laughs* "It was a youthimism." Tiana- "Well I don't like youthimisms, cause their untruth-imisms!"  Tiana- "I don't believe in pre-maritial sex.." *Snort*  THE GRINCH SONG:: Fah Who Foraze Yah Who Doraze Welcome, Christmas Come this way Fah Who Foraze Yah Who Doraze Welcome, Christmas Christmas Day Welcome Welcome Fah Who Ramus Welcome Welcome Dah Who Damus Christmas Day is in our grasp As long as we have hands to clasp Fah Who Foraze Yah Who Doraze Welcome, Christmas Bring your cheer Fah Who Foraze Yah Who Doraze Welcome, all Whos Far and near!  Brandon- "I loved Barbie!" Nathalie- "I used to have this really cute dress barbie thing and it was pink with lil wings.." Tina- "What happened to it?" Nathalie's Mom- "She still has them..." Nathalie- "No, you sold the whole bag of them to some lady for $10!" Ivan- "She sold my bike for 8.." Brandon- That was a good bike too... it still had both wheels..."  really good movie quotes!:  let me be your wings - thumbelina  you noe, its halloween... i guess everyone's entitled to one good scare. - every damn halloween movie.  hello clarice. -hannibal + silence of the lambs  all work and no play makes jack a dull boy. -the shining  Wishball5000: 3 6 9 IlbearP: damn shes fine Wut Wut Your Mom: won't ya shucka shuck it to me 1 more time? Softballgrl18k: Then Roll... RockedOutGurlio: get low  Teena9: Get low SCWonderWoman: Get Low bo da boi: get low jackorcan: get low BermudaBabe044: get low Sc cHErrIe bUg11: TO THE WINDOW AiMsStar125: to the wall* DrPepperChpsitck: to the sweat drops down your balls! QtWitABooty2489: TO ALL THESE BITCHES CRAWL! sccangel73: my ow skie skie mo fucka BeachChick5689: my own skee skee got game. trlsurfer: my ow ski ski mothe fucke.. sccutiepie911: my owe skie skie got game!  PROPS TO bIg KaTiE FOR THE RAP: Mr. Brandon Make all da boys wanna starr Hoza-Notie boots flyin with da furr Walk with a switch pull it ova make it twerk I'm a Flirt till it hurt in a throwback skirt Im dat bad bitch, foxy and Don Blaze Rocks on my wrist like pink lemonade Ill take ya watches and ya rangs Tell tell them other guys big papa rockin strings and Chanel parrels Im back fo my crown fake bithes bow down  Dis da real shit wat ya wanna do now? I know u like da way we do dis ova herrr Get loose in da club like we don't  carrr..  OLDIES SONG-- i come home in the mornin lite and my mother says "when u gonna live your life right?" oh moma dear, were not the fourtunate 1s and girls just wanna have fun. oh girls just wanna have fun. the fone rings in the middle of the night, my father yells "what u gonna do with your life?" daddy dear, you noe ur still #1, but girls they wanna have fun. yeah girls just wanna have.. thats all they really want! some fun! when the workin day is done, oh girls, they wanna have fun. oh girls just wanna have fun. girls, they just wanna have fun.. girls they wanna have.. some boys take a beautiful girl and hide her away from the rest of the world. I wana be the 1 to walk in the sun. oh girls they wanna have fun. oh girls just wanna have, thats all they really want. is some fun! when the workin day is done girls just wanna have fun! BRB!  SOOOO THE SONG FOR ME: Hey guy... hey guy Let's date... let's date 'Cause we're both something special Not Straight! What I feel for you is groovy So let's enjoy it I think you're sister's pretty  But let's boy it boy it I saw... i saw You wink... you wink And life is so much better Now that we're in sync Ah.. I really like your smilin' face My beachhouse has a fireplace We'll watch reruns of Will and Grace Let's fornicate Hold on... hold on Hold tight... hold tight Let's date.. let's date Let's date Ooooooh... Let's date!  Brandon- "Patrick, u got somethin' on ur leg.." Patrick- " *Looks* Snot... *Laughs*" Brandon- "Is that what you call it?" Patrick- "Ur a lil bitch *Smiling* " Brandon- "At least I'm not a whore... Next time tell Alec to aim a lil higher..." Patrick- "Oh my god! Hey, ur the one who likes him!" Brandon- "Um, yeah. I'm gay... me no like women..." Patrick- "Oh, burn!" Brandon- "Well Alec is mad at me so whatever..." Patrick- "With good reason. All the guys hate you..." Brandon- "Do you hate me? *Puppy face* " Patrick- "Of course not...!"  DeViLdUcKiE1990: my love is like jackorcan: woah Sc cHErrIe bUg11: my kiss is like jackorcan: woah TgElf112: my sex is like jackorcan: woah scblondeascanb: my ass is like jackorcan: woah SCleprechaungirl: my body's like jackorcan: woah SCWonderWoman: and you're kissin' it DrPepperChpstick: so what ya think of it? Wut Wut Your Mom: taste it... BermudaBabe044: taste it GoBasketballStar: you're never gonna find better...  ScCherrieBug11: it's totally like part of my daily routine.. ScCherrieBug11: 1. do homework ScCherrieBug11: 2. go online ScCherrieBug11: 3. yell at brandon  blondestlilchica: OBSESSED YOU ARE blondestlilchica: i sound like yoda  ScCherrieBug11: really, so how are your testicles now? jackorcan: i unno...how are ur testicles? ScCherrieBug11: ok no ScCherrieBug11: omg ScCherrieBug11: i love rex, his legs are sooooo SMOOTH ScCherrieBug11: like. you can totaly dance with them  Wut Wut Your Mom: hey brandon how do u feel jackorcan: i feel good jackorcan: oh i feel so good jackorcan: uh Wut Wut Your Mom: double it jackorcan: uh uh Wut Wut Your Mom: woo funny jackorcan: hey annie and jen, how do YOU feel? Wut Wut Your Mom: we feel good oo we feel so good uh jackorcan: DOUBLE IT Wut Wut Your Mom: uh uh  What do you think about Hercules?  Suziewelch: i like spiderman.. jackorcan: PSH jackorcan: herc could whoop his ASS  bo da boi: he was crazy actually.. he killed his wife and kids and stuff. jackorcan: yeah, if you were that hot YOU'd be afraid of commitment TOO!  Quaiken4Clay: hes the most touchy-feely god ive ever seen jackorcan: he can touch and feel me all he wants ;-)  AiMsStar125: he put the glad in gladiator! jackorcan: omg! you're a genius!  MY SCENE BARBIE TIME We goin' out to night, The scene is outta sight. Gonna get my girls together, We'll be feelin' alright. We gonna move through the crowd C'mon boys get loud Cause when the music gets bumpin' The whole place will be jumpin' it's my scene    GOOD MOMENTS OF A RANDOM DAY:  IN PE WITH THAT HIPPIE SUB!  LUNCH WHEN CHRISTINA, NATHALIE and I HAD OUR FIRST INTELLIGENT CONVERSATION!! WOOT WOOT! MUCH THANKS TO KIDNAPPED CHILDREN!  WALKIN' UP THE TRAIL! "it's the end of the world!" "i'm gonna walk on the wall!" "let's burry the bird!"  THAT DEAD BIRD/EGG THINGY.. AWW..  MY NAP ON THE FLOOR IN FRENCH.  AFTERSCHOOL WITH PATRICK! PAT - "gimme a high five!" ME- "no.." PAT- "DONT LEAVE ME HANGIN!"  WATCHIN' THIRTEEN WITH NATHALIE..  and the #1 moment...  WHAT A FEELIN'!  jackorcan: ellens like "shaquelle o'neill is short. hes like 7' 2" " ScCherrieBug11: omfg ScCherrieBug11: stupid jackorcan: i noe jackorcan: i was like "yeah ur dumb."  jackorcan: ellens like "shaquelle o'neill is short. hes like 7' 2" " simianantithesis: wtf? jackorcan: i noe jackorcan: i noe simianantithesis: and she's pretty... she only looks like the crypt keeper  jackorcan: ellens like "shaquelle o'neill is short. hes like 7' 2" " scbuttercup81: i am short scbuttercup81: i am like 5'1''  jackorcan: shes like making vacuum sounds ScCherrieBug11: o gosh jackorcan: shes like "vrmmm vrmmm" ScCherrieBug11: isn't that a motorcycle? jackorcan: ellen has an old vacuum ScCherrieBug11: lol  THATS ALL FOLKS~~  ~*~ with an x and an o this dude gots to go ~*~  *muah!* BRANDON!
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Swing swing from the tangles of, My heart is crushed by a former love. Can you help me find a way to carry on again? -The All-American Rejects, "Swing Swing"   yes! finally! the new year is HERE!   so it's winter break and nathalie is still stuck off in reno somewhere.. OOH! BUT SHE GOT ME A TEDDY BEAR!! :-D  the last days of winter break i was sick.. but on saturday i went downtown with jaye and had a lotta fun. we saw dominic down there too.. and that creepy morgan girl.. sunday i chilled with tina.. AND IN HER YEARBOOK I WROTE- "TINA! you are a cool kid.. not really.. we should hang out sometime.. or not.. just kidding.. you are probably the most awesome person i have ever met.. and now i'm never going to see you again. so sad.. well yeah.. have fun. your friend for fricken ever.. brandon."  so school was BACK and it was kinda weird.. seeing everyone after a whole two weeks away.. it was cool too. on wednesday crystal, nathalie and i ditched B3 and christina's sister took us to the mall.. we got jamba juice and then went to harbor.. oh yeah, this car honked at us. well at harbor i saw tina and gave her this HUGE hug.. but then i dropped her on the ground. ouch. her locker is really cute! and so is jaye! i met jack for the first time too.. like formally. and dominic was wearing eye liner!? haha! the rest of the week was crazy. AND THE WEEKEND WAS CRAZIER! i went to valley fair and hung out with people on saturday. it was weird.. half of that mall was empty.. du du du du.. and then i saw MISCHA again on sunday! that cutie! well yeah..  monday and tuesday were good days.. school was starting to be fun again. WEDNESDAY was the best! i went to shoreline with the shoreline humanities people. it was cool to hang out with tessa, even tho raina thot we were going out!? huh? kate was alotta fun too and allie and i bonded a little. AND AARON! wow, i never knew he was as cool as i think he is now. we got along.. kinda.. he's a nice guy. we went out to lunch in shonicks old car.. yeah, all 8 of us squeezed in.. that was fun... SUPER SNACKS! haha. the rest of the school week was great.. FRIDAY WAS THE FIRST PERIOD FINAL! but i got an a. yay.  the three day weekend was hella crazy.. i went shopping a lot and it was my half birthday on monday! suzie had a party.. but i didnt go.. and i was gonna go to the pancake breakfast.. but i slept in. aww. well cramming for finals was CRAZY! tina was totally stressing and nathalie was breezin' it.  FINALS WEEK! tuesday- a2 + a3. the piano final was cool. i played that elvis song for it and i got an apple! haha yay. the history test was pretty easy too, mostly cause i studied with tegan, heddy and madalee in the library. we also had to do this reveiw of the teachers and i gave them really good reviews :-) wednesday- b2 and b3. WELL i slept in because of my open period! and then pe was.. awful? but i got my mile in under 9 minutes! shake it dont break! thursday- a4 and b4. today was really cool! we did a play in miranda and i was romeo.. aww alec died, patrick looked cute and blake was two people at once. weird. well french was cool, we cheated and HERE'S THE CODE! when i stomp my foot: 1=a 2=b 3=c 4=d 0=e! yay!   so finally finals were over and we had a five day weekend to look forward too! friday was dominics party AND i turned in my essday to miss miranda. im glad she accepted it late. saturday was my hang-out-with-jack day.. but he never showed so nathalie and i had fun watchin' TAD HAMILTON! sunday was kinda boring.. suzie had her.. sixth? party.. and i did chores for $$ monday was the mall day with nathalie and crystal. we saw jaye.. but yeah.. i bought a belt! with a monkie! tuesday was crazy! my mom and i drove around getting supplies for school the next day!   the new semester was kinda weird.. i had all the same classes, but miranda and shonick were switched.. but alec and tegan and gardenia were in my class.. and angie too.. and blake.. we also had a new pe teacher, locke. she was alright.. prolly better than walters. well thursday was pretty cool.. except we got new books in english. les miserables. wow. it was pretty interesting tho! and shonick was cool.. we started these group projects..? yeah.. FRIDAY! what a way to end a week! the sweethearts rally was really cute! and the nominees: cody, amber, emily h., emily e., patrick, jake, dominique, adrian, amanda and austin. THE WINNERS ARE... PATRICK AND EMILY EARLY! yay! they are such a cute couple! props to amber and austin too! i voted for all 4 of them.  the weekend was cool too. on saturday i went to ivy's party way out on a ranch in watsonville. we watched thumbelina and the hunchback of notre dame. NOTRE DAME = our lady in FRENCH! haha.. then we played sardines and ivy's brother stripped down and yeah.. he's scrawny..  well sunday was cool. i chilled at home and got ready for the new school week. january was a good month. febraury was kinda better tho.. but yeah!  i'll write more later. brandon
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Think twice before you touch my girl, Come around, I'll let you feel the burn. Think twice before you touch my girl, Come around, come around, no more. -Eve 6, "Think Twice"   oooh.. the first was a sunday?? oh well..  the second was just another manic monday. in PE we started tennis.. but we wouldn't acctually play tennis until way later in the month. um.. tuesday and wednesday- nathalie, christina, crystal and i discovered ROCKSTARS!! on tuesday we had red bulls, but then on wednesday we all got rockstars and went crazy~!! thursday was a goood day. after school i went to the mall with chris knarr and we shopped and hung out. he's way cuter than i imagined (shorter too! teehee) he's a really sweet guy. we had dinner at chili's and it was amazing. friday was another rockstar day only THIS TIME I HAD TWO!! woooooah!! and my mom picked me up during my open period so i could go home and SLEEP..  on saturday- crystal, nathalie and i went downtown and shopped like crazy!! i got this really cute Nite Owl Shirt!! (from urban outfitters!) i wore the shirt on sunday when i went to see jaye at longs! that was fun! i got some more gum and the march teen people..  ON MONDAY! I started working on my new binder.. not really the coolest thing, but hey! what can ya do? the back was like all the gay guys of santa cruz (well, the hot ones..) CHRIS KNARR DOMINIC MARTINELLI JACK VIDNOVIC JAYE CERRUTI  it was really cool and the background was crumpled up paper bag! hottt!  the front was a poem from that one show that annie really liked.. and the side was totally dedicated to nathalie!  so yeah! you should check it out sometime!  tuesday was kinda boring... until.. i got home.. and my mom... said.. THAT SHE WAS HAVING THE BABY IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS!!  i went to bed on my LAST night of being an ONLY CHILD! psychotic, i know!  on wednesday my mom left for the hospital and my dad dropped me off. after math in the morning, i grabbed nathalie and told her the BIG NEWS! she had to be the first to know! we got really excited and then she got really tired and decided she didnt want to go to pe.. so since i had a free period, her and i walked _ALL_THE_WAY_ to the beach and chilled there with this handicapped officer and then walked _ALL_THE_WAY_ back! IT WAS SO FUN! I want to do it again sometime. after that i decided i didnt want to go to pe so christina and i went to this little playground and "took a trip on an airplane!" and then we had this genuis idea to get everyone in the french class gold fish so they could like speak french to them and be like "il mange la .. something" and yeah! it was genuis! we had so much fun! AND THEN WE GOT ONE OF THOSE AIR HOSES FROM A GAS STATION AND PLAYED WITH IT!! WOOOO HOOO! we invented a new sport too.. with our coke bottles.. FRENCH CLASS WAS THE BEST! and after school i got to see my little sister.. anna.. god i wanted to name her emily!! but whatever.. at least she was born and stuff.. the name doesnt really matter.. well then i went and picked up the balloons for the HUMANATIES ACADEMY thing at the SOQUEL OPEN HOUSE! woot woot! i saw a bunch of you cool eighth graders like JAYME WINELL!! and amy and harry and others.. annie and i made up a new song "shake what your mama gave you, like a salt shaker, but if you're ugly *like jake* dont shake it!" JKK! jake's cool.. ABY TAUGHT ME A CHEER TOO!! well the day was lots of fun but when i got home i fell asleep right away.  thursday was tiring.. i just wanted to go home and sleep.. we started our second research reoprts in shonick and i decided to do mine on why abortion should be illegal, even though i dont believe in it. when i got home i fell asleep again..  FRIDAY WAS THE BEST!!! FINALLY A DAY OFF!! i spent the WHOLE day sleeping and catching up on homework.  i was planning on having the BEST VALENTINES DAY EVER this weekend.. but chris was "busy", jack was on this snow trip, jaye was on his surf trip and dominic was just trippin, i decided to hang out with nathalie.. AND WE FOUND THIS REALLY FUN PHOTO BOOTH IN THE MALL!! crystal came and we took TONS OF PICTURES!!  sunday was pretty nice, i went on a breakfast date and then slept and worked a little on my report..  monday was the BEST!! i spent the WHOLE DAY IN BED!! oh and the baby came home! my mom did too.. it was fun.  tuesday.. you never really know how much you miss school until you spend an entire week in bed. school was pretty fun, it was cool to hear how everyone's valentine's were.. although no one really DID anything..  the week went by really fast.. i didn't really go online that often.. nathalie and i spent A LOT of time talking on the phone. wasnt escapades that weekend??  on saturday my THREE BEST FRIENDS and i went to see EUROTRIP AND confessions of a teenage drama queen downtown. we bought a ticket for miracle and then went in and saw both.. haha.. yeah, we're sneaky.. then after we walked around and got pizza and this cutie stalked me into a public bathroom from starbucks..  on sunday i had ANOTHER HOT DATE with kevin from over the hill. it was really lame though and kevin is.. well.. i dont wanna sound mean :-) HEY DERICK, WHEN ARE YOU GONNA COME DOWN!? then i went to the seacliff inn to watch Les Miserables for extra cred. for the humanaties academy. i DRANK A LOT OF WATER! that's how my water obsession got started.  monday was really cool.. i drank lots of water and in pe we started BADMINTON!! i got a bunch of extra credit cause i knew how to spell it..  TUESDAY WAS THE BEST DAY OF FEBRUARY!! it was JAYE CERRUTI"S BIRTHDAY!! WOOT WOOT!! happy 18th b-day jaye! it's now illegal to fuck you :-/ well on tuesday at 7 in the morning i got up and got ready for the SAN FRANSISCO TRIP! i got dressed in warmish clothes and made like 32 poptarts for THE COOL KIDS! when we got on the buss i sat with annie. HERE'S HOW THE BUS LOOKED  - - - - - - - - BACK WINDOW - - - - - - - -  kevin and carson - - - zack by himself blake and matt - - - - patrick and alec annie and me - - - - rachie and hannah aby and tanya - - - - - tara and ally  the ride over was lots of fun! we played the name game and patrick and i were on a team and we soooo beat alec and zack and everyone else! then we plaed the name game only we used animals.. then we used places... yeah.. when we arrived in san francsico we whipped out cameras and took crazy pictures of each other! our first stop was the Legion Of Honor museum! it was all modern yet medeval... the architecture was cool and there was a big statue of joan of arc out front! and a weird paper clip on the side.. the inside was cool.. there were a bunch of different statues and paintings and there was a really cute princess crown in the gift shop. tara's mom was our chaperone and the group was me, annie, aby, tanya, rachie, hannah, tara and ally. sophie was sick :-( . well shonick gave us his own little "tour" of the outside of the legion of honor.. oh and erik lowe got laughed at by these chinese people and annie! it was funny. our next stop was union station.. tara's mom got REALLY YUMMIE pizza bread and then we started shopping.  Stop 1= Tiffany & Co. this creepy guy asked if i wanted to see his jewels and annie and hannah and i decided we're gonna marry rich people! annie gets jimmy, hannah gets jake and I CALL ALEC! or naomi.. if i ever decide to swing back that way.. there was a really cute hair brush + mirror!! well we left after tara's mom picked something up.. Stop 2= MACY*S right after we looked in the windows of louis vuitton. we made our way up the stairs to the GREEN THING!! he was our best friend.. tanya was the first to touch him, but i was second! well then we went to the top and waved at people who looked up! no one did tho.. freaks.. then we went to the 1st floor and looked at all the bags and stuff.. we got lost but then we all ended up in the food court and GOT JAMBA JUICE UNDER FAKE NAMES! i was tarzan and annie was anna? so was tanya.. and aby was summer.. after we left macy's.. Stop 3= Urban Outfitters! We all bought stuff and just went totally crazy in UO.. COWBOYS MAKE BETTER LOVERS!! everyone got panties.. except me.. i got a book and a "MADE IN IRELAND SHIRT!" Stop 4= ABERCROMBIE AND FITCH-o! sooo much fun! i got a green stripped button shirt that is only sold in big city department stores. or at least it better be that special cause it was 75 bucks!! wow!!  after that we got back on the bus and went to this Chinese Museum.. weird.. we didnt spend alotta time in it cause the elevators were really creepy and the chinese lady was a priss.. LUIGI CALLED and annie was like "we're in a green room! and you can see china!" well annie, han, ally, aby, tan, tara, rach and i left the museum and went to this park across the street RIGHT NEXT TO CITY HALL!! we played ont he park for a bit and then ran through the trees and some more people came over and then we all went into city hall and we got married to each other (it was our group and some of pat's group)! yay! we walked back to the museum just as everyone was coming out.. no one even noticed we were gone.. :-D  dinner was at peir 39 with this crazy carousel and COTTON CANDY!! YUM!! i was cravin it!! and there were these weird seals and um.. fries and stuff.. it was fun.. and a nice way to end the day! it was freezin outside when we got on the bus and headed home. we sang songs and patrick had to pee.. and alec got sugar high! it was great!! my dad picked me up when we got back to the school @ like 9.. and then i went home and slept..  RACHEL WROTE THIS POEM ABOUT OUR ADVENTURE IN SF: From Tiffany's to the streets of San Fran Going from place to place, without any real plan we were all busy stacking Our coordination, that day, we were obviously lacking The Urban Outfitters, four stories high And the matching choneys, that most of us decided to buy One word- boyfriend, two words- who cares Aby- please try not to break any more of the museum's chairs I love Luke-n, Kevin got layed I wish, in the city, longer, we could have stayed "Chu can have it!" as Carson would say So much for that rainy, stormy, freezing day Carson, this is your last warning, and step away from the bus Mardi Gras Beads- always a must The big green thing in Macy's, he's Tanya's friend We all dropped hard, from our sugar high, as we neared the end Enrique! Enrique! We love you so much! Be careful, in the museum, the walls, you're not allowed to touch "Go back! Go back! We'll come back around!" Pat and Carson yelling "Wait for us," was the only sound The chick in the Disney store She wanted to know Why Brandon, hardly had anymore Everything's bigger in Texas, so cowboys make better lovers The trip seemed like it started, and all of a sudden it was over Sorry, I'm straight And with my Jamba Juice, I have a date Actually it's silver, don't you know? Brandon came prepared, with lots of dough We got married and divorced, in ten minutes flat The birds flew over, and on us, we almost got shat No adults- unless accompanied by a child Annie took us on a speed boat trip, it was pretty wild We stole all Erik's fun I can't believe it's all done Elevators, and tic tac toe So many places, we didn't have time to go You're going down to china town! When you think of this trip, smile, don't frown 99 bottles of beer on the wall Hysterically laughing, having a ball Pixie stix, getting us sugar high It's crazy how fast the time flew by Spinning carousel, teacup- like ride Wanting to go on the magic caret rides Don't forget the pigeons, and the sea lions barking at the tides On Pier 39 Oh, wasn't it a lovely time? Matching coffee mugs, Rach and Annie's shot glass collection I hope for you, I've created a good recollection Accordian buses, getting home late Our count off, from one to eight Don't forget, TAF, Hannah's BIG line At some point in the day, each and every one of us, like stars, did shine  Annie's Inside Jokes FROM THE SF TRIP: THE SF TRIP *GO BACk!! *Kevin got lay-ed *the wave *john jacob jing-SHUT UP *1 word, boyfriend, 2 words, who cares *enrique!!! nope i know and enrique and that is soo not enrique *mario *THE GIANT SAFTEY PIN *i ALWAYS do it with patrick *the seals, u gotta check it out, arr arr arr *THE ELEVATOR(catherine, the doors, it stopped on every floor) *the green thing in macy's *down to chinatown *big willy style *FREAK *hurassing minorities *BSB,NSYNC,Britney *fortune cookies *the playground *pop tarts *the heart toungy thing *you clean my bus/ carson this is your last warning *guys brushing their hair *almost staking *cowboys make better lovers *look bushes are the real? *that was a good one *mission impossible in the asian art museum *i ussually dont sleep with those kind of cocks *it took u a long time to litter  the day after i was wiped.. i played a little badminton in pe, but tried to sleep most of the time.. french was a lotta fun ~*~ AS ALWAYS ~*~ yup, cool stuff. thursday was fun but i was sick. i stayed home from my first two periods, math and piano. in shonick we had to present out territorial projects and i talked about the popular freshman girls and i used naomi's line "you gotta have connections" to crack everyone up.. it was fun.. then after school we went to this hot Mardi Gras Party at USCS and partied! it was cool! christine, em, sara, nique, nathalie, crystal and everyone was there! like the HOT PUMA GUY! and i stole his crown! and masks and beads! and alicia took a bus to watsonville and got there late.. cool cool.. after the party i talked to dominic a lot..  friday i was wiped again so i stayed home from the first two periods. badminton wiped me out but nathalie and i bought THREE rockstars and drankthem before french! it was GREAT!!! we were SOOO HYPER! when i got home i dropped down on my bed and slept for a while. i wokeup in time for my NEW FAVORITE SHOW! THE BEST WEEK EVER! nathalie and i watched it together. after i did my homework and went to sleep. on saturday i relaxed and worked on homework. my mom took me to get nathalie's birthday gift.. that was about it.. my grandparents stopped by and my grandma gave me this video game that i would get totally attatched to in march. SUNDAY! the LAST day of FEBRUARY! it was NATHALIE'S BIRTHDAY PARTY! woot woot! i was supposed to go to the humanaties thing again but i decided to skip it to spend time with nathalie, tina, crystal and christina, THE BEST OF THE BEST! i rode christina's bike and we saw TEENA DAVIS's TWIN!! do do do do. we also got a bunch of tickets fromt he arcade, christina and i pooled ours together and it equaled 1135!! omgoshies!! i went crazy with $5 worth of tokens and launched them one after the other into that jackpot machine.. woo.. i got a gum refill thing and best friend necklaces and we all got fluff pens to whip out in french. the pizza and freinds was a greast way to end a super fun month. after the party i went home and tried out the video game my grandma got me...  nightems! (NATHALIE'S WORD. if i didnt give her credit she'd probably bite of my head and sit on me.) brandon :-)
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard, And they're like, it's better than yours. Damn right, it's better than yours. I could teach you, but I'd have to charge. -Kelis, "Milkshake"   so i sold my playstation one cause all it was doing was gathering dust. $120 with 2 controllers and 2 games! wow!! that's a nice price! i wish i could sell everything i got for christmas.. hey, i could prolly make a thou of those baseball cards and a pretty penny from that old VCR! oooooo!   in march, as mr. shonick puts it best, "i had my mind on my money and my money on my mind."   the first was another school day. THE FIRST DAY I ACCTUALLY WENT TO MATH IN LIKE.. A WEEK!! more or less.. and the first time i went to PIANO in FOREVER! god! being sick sucks AND swallows. oh hey, it was emily hasty's b-day today! and cassondra and i really bonded in piano..   on march second.. IT WAS NATHALIE'S BIRTHDAY!! WOOOT WOOOT! it was also hottie- chris knarr's special day! i swear, i have a thing for pisces, scorpios and aries!   the day was cool! nathalie got a cute birthday balloon from her cousin and yeah... the day was cool EXCEPT AT LUNCH... i stayed on campus and checked out abortion books from the library. just wait amanda rossi, i'll show you a thing or two! shonick was fun, gardenia, crystal and i talked about our reports and ANGIE came up with this HOT TOPIC about HAWAIIN CULTURE!! that girl's a genuis!   wednesday - i stayed home again from math and my free period.. in pe we ran sprints but i sat out with elizabeth and we just walked around the little track thingie.. and french was pretty fun.. well.. french is always fun.. but it was good today cause christina and i whipped out our fluffy pens and went psyco with them!   thursday - we started a new chapter in math.. CONSTRUCTIONS AND LOCI!! woot woot.. on friday was the circles test though, so we reviewed for that shit... piano, shonick and miranda were fun like always.. he said the grades and CASSONDRA AND I HAD A'S !! woo hoo!! that night i studied for the math test when i got home. AND I MISSED THE TEEN FAIR!! AHH!!   friday! the math test was easy.. at least i thought.. in my people i read Les Mis and in pe we played badminton. then in french we had the chapter 3 test which i thought was waaaay easy! well the six week grading period was OVER!! FINALLY! i kicked me feet up and hoped for all a's! THE BEST WEEK EVER WAS WAY FUNNY! and nathalie and i had our own i love the 80's marathon!   on saturday i was working hard on my abortion report when nathalie called me and told me to come with her to the mall.. so i met her there and some weird guy was talking to her and it was creepy.. well we walked around and then i called jack and told him i was at the mall! and he said he was there toooo! so nathalie and i walked around and we ran into him at american eagle but he couldnt talk to us cause he was with someone "cooler". nathalie and i went to radio shack and looked at the picture phones and then we JAYE-walked across the street to longs where we asked the lady to call jaye cerruti to the front. so he came. and i bought the april teen people and some gum and we walked over to mcdonalds. i gave him a HUGE hug and then i went inside and we had MUGGETS! did ya noe those things are made with white meat!? i didnt... AND THEN WE GOT THIS TOY IN THE HAPPY MEAL AND IT WAS A SOCCER PLAYER!! ;-)  well we walked back to the mall and met up with jack and then him an di hung out while nathalie wandered around gottchalks.. it was nice :-) . then nathalie came back and we ate fries and i went crazy with the salt _like always_ and yeah.. well she left and jack and i decided to walk around the mall some more and then go to his car.. and then we saw nathalie outside and she came in with us. it was alotta fun! nathalie was the dj and jack and i sat in the back talking.. then nathalies mom came.. and my dad came.. so we left.. but overall it was a good day.   sunday.. i slept. and then finished my notes for history. oh, and didnt we have french homework?   monday was cool. the weekend left me in a good mood.. and um.. we didnt have to run the mile, so that was good.. didnt we play badminton again!? i dunno.. i think i just slept.. oh and we got our grades for math and mine was an 89.1 % because i missed so much school!? what the fuck!? well to mcconnell, attendence is 30% of the grade. freak. i missed shonick and french though, i left school at lunch to get my braces tightened and my bands changed, although... they didnt really hurt after.. maybe it's cause they didn't give me a steel wire... well yeah!   so um.. tuesday! in english we watched the FUNNIEST les mis. movie!! this lady like fell down! oh and i started bring 6 bottles of water to school everyday so that i would be hydrated.. mmm water.. in shonick we reviewed for the test. and the britney concert was that night! jack and nelli went.. and other people.. yeah.. i'll wait til she comes this summer. OH YEAH! i tanned after school everyday this week and last week! except one day..   wednesday.. OMG! TRACK IS CRAZY! i sat out cause i didnt wanna injure myself in sprinting! um and in FRENCH, KEPLINGER GAVE ME A B+!! i was really rude and obnoxious all day with nathalie because she fucked up our grades, and then after class dane and i worked out the grades and it turned out she jiped us BOTH and dane's like.. a genuis! and so i really had a FUCKIN A PLUS PLUS, 101.4 PERCENT! so ha! i am smart. TAN TIME! oh yeah, my mom picked me and ellen up today which she hasnt done since the baby was born! yay!   thursday was weird.. in miranda i chugged 6 bottles of water and alec was like "holy shit! look at him go!" then we did this artsy fartsy thing and gardenia and i drew streaks in crystal's hair! it was so funny, i swear i almost pee'd my pants and broke my ribs! gardenia is super cool so yeah~!! then we had the test in shonick.. it sucked and most of it was on shit we didnt even cover.. on the OTHER test i got a 100 though! so i hoped my luck would benefit me this time.. oh and we played heads up seven up and AMANDA ROSSI PICKED ME! but i thought it was naomi.. so yeah.. but whatever. after school i went to the mall and met kendra and shaina there.. we were supposed to go to eat at fresh choice, but then jaye called and i had the brillant idea to have him come to the mall! so he did and we hung out and it was fun.. except he was in shorts :-P i also met/saw this guy named brandon tracy in structure and i heard he was gay.. or something.. and so yeah.. then nathalie and crystal came and jaye left and nathalie and crystal and i went to jamba juice and then over to fresh choice for the FRENCH FUNRAISER! WOOO PARTY!!! lots of people were there.. jason, nique, eben.. okay, so maybe not LOTS..   the food was.. okay.. it was cheap too! like 6 bucks!! i had a lot of ice cream.. and vegetables.. THE DIET WAS STARTING ON SUNDAY! we talked to keplinger who was there.. she's really funny! then nathalie and crystal stalked her son to game stop (and i came along) and we were like "yeah.. let's buy that game.. for the box.." it was great! and when we got ready to cross the street back to the mall crystal and i started walking and nathalie walked out but then went back. i ran after nathalie and ALMOST got hit by a car and then crystal had to go between two cars and she got stuck on the other side while nathalie and i fell down on the ground from laughing so hard. then we crossed like dorks and we collapsed in the macy's parking lot. SO FUN!   we got hit by that handicapped door going back into macy's and we saw carolyn there! well then we met up with christina, got some fries, saw mr. michael grass who REALLY needs to cut his hair. oh we saw cassondra too.. then nathalie bought this shirt from expressions and there was this really coool music video playing! i like died! it was the best.. well christina left after we all gave her a big hug and then nathalie's mom drove me and crystal home in the COOLEST CAR! I SWEAR!! the handles to open the doors are WAY COOL! its like a *LIMO!*!! haha.. so then i went home and talked to dominic while rocking out to I LOVE THE 80's STRIKES BACK!   friday was less eventful, we did hurdles in pe and mrs. locke was a maniac. "HURDLE! HURDLE! HURDLE!" she's really passionate about track.. ooh! i got the yummiest cookie at break and nathalie and i danced around like maniacs. i did REALLY good in the hurdles! i got fourth place under kevin, travis and krista.. and maybe natasha, i dont noe yet.. but yeah! it was cool! elizabeth was out tho.. aw.. amber is SOOOO THE TRACKIEST GIRL!! SHE WON HURDLES!! HOW COOL IS THAT!! GO AMBER!! um in french mrs. keplinger seperated me and nathalie and we did this reveiw thing.. it sucked.. after school i walked with patrick WHO IS NOW PATATO and then i chilled with naomi engleman.. oh yeah, wasnt there a hot snowboarding trip that weekend!? woot woot! you know what naomi was gonna do ;-) just kidding. well my mom picked us up and randi had a sprained ankle from hurdles..   nathalie went to this party thing but it's all good cause i finished all my homework and watched the I LOVE THE 80"S MARATHON leading up to the best week ever! which was okay.. i fell asleep early..   the next day i lagged around the house and then i went mini golfing with jack while my dad went to this priss party and the cocoanut grove!! my dad in a tux!? it was crazy!! mini golfing was okay.. i SOOO won! ;-) and then jack had to go pee but the bathroom's were nasty.. we went to go see if the giant dipper was open, but it wasnt.. so we got some candy and walked on the beach and talked and stuff.. and then we walked around some more.. it was nice.. kinda chilly out though.. then we went to the arcade and jack left and i called my dad like 20 times but he turned his cell off cause of the speeches.. so i waited and then he called me and said he was coming down.. I THINK HE WAS DRUNK! it was crazy! it took us a while to get home, and he dropped me off so he could go PARTYING MORE!! woo! my dad's crazy! well i went to bed and then yeah... DOMINIC TURNED 15!! WOOT WOOT!   on sunday i woke up and talked to rc for a little bit.. weird, i noe! but fun.. then i went outside and tanned and talked to nathalie about her saturday night.. SHE GOT DRUNK AT HER GRANNIES BIRTHDAY!! damn! and i thought i had fun! jkk.. my night was perfect.. but yeah.. i have some of her drunk quotes..   NATHALIES DRUNK QUOTES:  oh i love that guy!  why is there an arrow there?  i need some sun on my bun..  CLAUDIA, BRING ME MY CRUNCH BAR!  i like eating that coffee ice cream from marinis.. no wait.. mariannies..  MOM!! BRING ME MY CRUNCH BAR!  no those other bars will make me fat!  it looks like she took markers and drew her hair one.  OH I SEE THE SAND MAN!  i get it, i get it, i get i get i get it!  no, you're talking to myself.  IVAN, BRING ME MY CUNCH BAR!   so after i tanned.. and i didi homework. and caroline and i can do lean on me with the piano and her voice thingie!! its so cool! well i tried to go to bed early but i didnt really fall asleep til like 12.   on monday i went to school in a really good mood. it was a c day though and i had to hall 2 abercrombie shopping bags all the way to my locker. math and piano were normal.. at my open i tried to find some advil from nathalie, but it didnt happen. um then i played mrs. pac man on her cell phone. fun stuff. after an exciting break (?) i went to miranda and slept for like the whole period and then in pe i did ONE HUNDRED SIT UPS!! WOAH!! it made my neck hurt kinda.. at lunch i had a burrito and nathalie and crystal got "kidnapped".. in shonick i chugged a bunch of water and in french i did the same.   that night nathalie and i talked and i got the flashdance soundtrack and i talked on the phone to dominic! i noe! its a miracle! he called me during shonick but i was busy chillin with lisa.   on tuesday i woke up early to do SIT UPS! cause they're the funnest! and i ate really healthy cause i want abs.. mischa said i should get the ab roller.. but i dunno.. school was pretty boring except i slept in miranda and got a B+ on my test but he adds a little so it was like A-.. i hung with alec after school in the parking lot and i talked on the phone to jaye. oh! he has a blog now! check out the link   i feel asleep tanning again, but i didnt burn this time.. nathalie called me after my shower and we talked for a while.. theres this really cool game online and we fought each other or something. i dont remember.. um.. well after that i got everything ready for st patricks day and then talked on the phone to dominic for a while.   wednesday was crazy~!! it was way cool to see everyone dressed in green at school.. i pinched gardenia cause she wasnt wearing any!! tsk tsk tsk. i played on nathalies cell again in my open. god, im in love with that thing. then in pe there was this HOT AS HELL GUY who i lusted for and gardenia helped me learn a bunch of NAUGHTY spanish words which i said to crystal and christina during lunch. it was pizza day! mmm!   creeka - vagina  caca - shit  puta - whore  pendejo - bitch  gordita - fat  fea - ugly  pito - penis  TE GUSTA MI PITO - do you like me penis?  COMO MI CACA - i eat my shit   well yeah, WATCH OUT! cause i noe espanol-a now! well after lunch nathalie went home cause she didnt feel so hot. actually she was burning up, but its just an expression. in french i tried to be quiet and i drank a lot of water. the test was easy and after i pee'd like a race horse! um.. well i went home and it turned out ellen's grandma passed away [:-(] so i wouldnt have to take her home and she wouldnt be able to take me in the morning. i tanned when i got home. the sun felt nice. mm balance bars ROCK!! rite xtina and jen? yEAH! so i talked to dom on the phone and yeah, yeah bed time.   thursday was really good. my dad drove me in the morning and crystal and i hung out before geometry! love that class! piano was boring as always.. i dont think im gonna be able to pull an A in that class this six weeks.. there are toooooooo many songs! .. i noe i'll at least get a B or at the lowest a C.. but i doubt that. O' sole mio!   english was fun, we went outside in the sun and we had a discussion on Les Mis.. i dont really remember it all, i was kinda tired.. then in shonick we read out of the book and finished our in class essays. mine was already 3 pages long! =-o! i noe! well after i went piss with lisa and then again by myself. i LOVE the new bathrooms! aw i saw the guy from the deli that i like LOVE smoking!! how sad!! his kisses will always taste like smoke! i went home and tanned and talked to derick on the phone.. and then caroline and her mom came over and her mom and my mom talked about stuff and played with the baby while me and caroline played on the piano and stuff.. i love that girl! its not caroline from school though, its another one. they both are way great! well after that i dont remember what i did but i think it involved sleep.   friday was a good day.   if you watch qe then you noe the fab five are those five gay guys.. yeah yeah, blah blah.. well the SC FAB FIVE are  BRANDON AIONO (me)  CHRIS KNARR  JACK VIDNOVIC  JAYE CERRUTI  DOMINIC MARTINELLI   and i decided that i was no longer going to date except from the fab five.. which is perfect.. cause jack.. ya noe.. yeah.. well nothing big happened at school. math - transgender sub with crazy hair who showed up WAAAY late. open - fooled around with nathalie's phone and watched science fair projects. oh yeah, i found out my dad knows the HOT AS HELL guy from wednesday.. his name's ryan austin or something.. when i found out my dad knew him he seemed a lot less attractive.. but he's really really tan! so yeah.. in pe we did long jump and my pants fell down when i did my first run.. i still got 13 ft. tho. second run i got less so we stayed with the first run.    lunch was cool.. nathalie and i went to all the hot places to eat in the village.. i should write them out!   we went to Hernandez market first.. its a cute little store that has EVERYTHING cheap! that doesnt mean its always satisfying though..   then we walked to adelitas.. the store with the ONE DOLLER BURRITOS! yummy! its def. a major hot spot.   we walked across the stree and behind the stores to D'Anna's Deli where the cute somker works.. we didnt get anything though. its really expensive, but they have nice salads.   we headed to the bagelry, a hip and happenin' place with THE BEST bagels! mm i get hungry thinkin about them.   ugly mug was after, a place we go for warm beverages when we ditch. they didnt have the yummy cake tho, so we left.   at the golden buddha we bought fried rice, that is the BEST chinese food place if you want something to go. mm rice! and won ton soup! that stuff is delish.   we crashed at aldo's, the tasty bakery. i got a smoothie and after that we left and walked up the trail past the church.   on some wednesdays, the church has pizza for a buck! its a really good deal.     caroline gave us her ravioli's from aldo's.. they were GOOOD.. after we hiked the trail we got to french and talked.. nathalie hit edwin with the door.. and yeah.. keplinger told us about how a pig was butchered, but i left so i would hafta hear it.. alicia and i hung outside and dominique with the fro came out. so did jen jen. when we went back in 

02,July,2004


	 
      This love has taken its toll on me, She said 'Goodbye' too many times before. And my heart is breaking in front of me, But I have no choice, 'cause I won't say 'Goodbye' anymore. -Maroon 5, "This Love"   The first was SO FUN! god, i noe april's fools is like a kiddie holiday, but i love it fo sho. i gave my grandma a heart attack by putting red food dye on my hand and getting a knife, saying i cut myself. ha ha ha. uhh shonick's class was really fun. it was good turning in my ABORTION REPORT! what what. english was kinda boring though...  friday was really fun. at the end of the mile my speed really kicks in. mrs. locke says this is because adrenaline surges out of your brains and makes you work harder. this explains why everyone was in such a good mood the last day before spring break. i spent my open planning my whole spring break, and in pe i worked my ass of during our "track" lesson. french was the funnest. i taped a picture of a fish on mrs keplingers back because she said that april fools day was like a fish holiday or something. dont ask. it was great though. then nathalie and i drew a picture on the board that said "Happy Spring Break!" it was tres cute.  SCHOOL'S OUT~!!  i spent the rest of the night watching movies and staying up late on the phone with tina and nat. just like things were supposed to be.  saturday- i slept. seriously. it felt orgasmic.  sunday- i totally did all my homework and caught up on all the hot gossip. my mom took me shopping and i bought gossip girls and new socks and wife beaters.. who came up with that name? i think it was stephanie hammond.. or jude law.  monday- after hanging out with nora i went to see eternal sunshine with jaye at the movies. it was HOT! and jaye looked hella cute in his abercrombie vintage t. after the movies we were gonna get jamba juice but i felt all hot and sticky from sitting for 2 and something hours. so i went home and tanned.  wednesday - nathalie and i totally busted out at the mall. we had tons of fun and lots of laughs. AND WE BOUGHT THE FISH!! and burger king! and we saw damon and he was retarded. but what's new? oh yeah, chris cancelled on me to see dawn of the dead that day. or did i cancel on him? so not hot for that boy anymore.  thursday - i went to the movies with dominic. he wore a PINK shirt. still, i give him props for looking so cute in it. haha.. we had tons of fun watchin lady killers. except the title is freaky and everyone died. then i went home and changed.. and i went to see hiltago with jack. but we skipped the movies and i ended up giving him a tour of soquel. RC's REAL NAME IS RAUL!! WOAH!! thats crazy. we did alotta craz shit that'll probably give me a boner radomly during class. then a security gaurd came. now i noe what anna felt like in the A list. mm mm mm  friday - i read all the gossip girls! so good! omg i am so in love with chuck! and blair is the coolest chica since annie ross! has anyone heard from gardenia?  saturday - it was a totally 80's day! nathalie, crystal and i went to the mall! it was awesome until crystal had to leave.. we got jamba juice and we chilled on her iPod! there was a HUGE cutie on a bike too.. woaH! anyone, we walked home in the cold and yeah.. i took a nice shower. flip flops on cold days = no. gossip girl spotted me and put me on her site! i also saw tina and sarah in the mall. it was cool! and sarah looks really good. tina.. well she looks the same..  sunday = easter. i slept a lot and my parents went over to my aunts and uncles. i didnt pracicularly want to go, so i slept in and they had fun and nathalie called.. i dont like eater egg hunts.. but nathalie had funw ith hers! i slept a lot and got ready for school.  monday back was great. i swapped stories with everyone and handed out hugs like it was graduation night. i dont remember much from the day except giving amber a HUGE hug.. and that's about it..  tuesday - counselors came in to talk to us during english. again, it motivated me. i found myself signing up for the same classes, minus piano and pe. i also added leadership. it felt good. shonick's class.. uhh.. i dont remember. OH I WAS STOKED FOR HEALTH.  wednesday- christina's cousin came and her and i hung out in 2nd quad reading today.. after pe i ran to the locker to get jack's card. it was his big big BIRTHDAY! woo! i kissed mesha on accident because i was so excited. it was chill though. uhh we got to harbor and nathalie and i jumped out of the car. we walked down the hill while everyone called our names. when we reached jaye we handed him the rose and card. he didnt want to take it cause he was embarassed so i shoved it in his back pack and nathalie and i hurried up the hill. two girls chased us, d'auria and stacie and nathalie and i jumped in le voiture (thats car in french), but not before chatting with elena rossman.  my mom drove us to jamba juice and nathalie got a yummy carribean passion and i god a razz razz razzmatazz. yum. jack called to say he loved his gift, but then again, how could he not :-P? we got back to school waaay after the bell rang. we walked from the circle parking lot around the side of the 1st building and up the trail witht he two trees that leaned agaisnt each other. then jenica called us from the girl's locker room. she came out and we walked to french together. we had a psycho sub and some chick who knew NOTHING about european history (JOAN OF ARC WASN'T HUNG JUST BECAUSE SHE WORE MEN'S CLOTHING. WHAT A BIMB.) gave us a lecture about fashion and how we should desgin and shit. ooooh chanel! yummy. well after that we had to do a worksheet on past tense verbs.. except keppie hadn't taught us that yet. how sad. the day was over and i went home and fell asleep. i think i should take this time to give a BIG SHOUT OUT to JACK! his birthday was one of the more entertaining days of april :-*  thursday was pretty boring, we had a sub in PIANO!? crazy crazy. it was really weird cause.. he was telling us his life story about african drummers and casondra and i just decided to fall asleep. friday was the same. elizabeth and i had a fun chat in pe about uhh.. jack's birthday? yeah.. and then french was boring.. like usual. i complained my ass off about the sub. what a crack head. AND WHAT WAS UP WITH THAT OTHER SUB IN PE?? HUH?? IS IT NATIONAL FREAK SUB WEEK. i swear. he looked like he was half woman, half fisherman. and fishing gear has totally been out since the 80's. duh.  FINALLY. THE WEEKEND. i made up all my homework and then i tanned tanned tanned. farewell to manzanar was pretty entertaining. even without jake there to explain everything to me. i watched a ton of movies and finished all my homework. and then it was monday. woo. back to school. to tell you the truth, nothing exciting happened this whole week. we finished up the six weeks as usual.  in piano cassondra and i practiced and played like crazy. we even stayed in the band room past the bell, by accident. those sound proof rooms are dangerous.  english went by like normal. we kept reading farwell to manzanar and we watched a lot of biast movies toward the governemnt and how they "wrongfully" imprissoned the Japanese. well at least gardenia was there to keep it chill.  tuesday was really cool! HAPPY 420 EVERYONE! rc thought it was childish.. but fuck him. no really, ;-). uhh my 420 was DOPE! we all had a lot of fun, even though i didnt smke or any shit like that. so proud. emily didnt either. im proud of her. tessa got really baked and we laughed at random things. anyone, it was all really fun. was that jack smoking over the phone? huh? :-P  pe was mega boring. fitness testing drove mrs. locke crazy. we did sit ups and push ups everyday like 200000000000 times and we ran the mile every time she could squeeze it in. track was super fun though!  on wednesday we had the track meet. shay was looking fine in his shades as i raced bach li down the hurdes and passed the baton off to david girr on the 4 by 100 hundred. HOT. elizabeth is my new favorite pe person. with gradenia and lizzette. la la la la la.  in geometrey.. FIRST PERIOD.. we took the math test. GEOMETRY. woot woot.  open period was the same all week long. i worked in the library, and one day kate and tiana came in and we partied like crazy. wooo. im really tan. shonick was int here too and he came over and "partied" with us. ha ha. my favorite line is when tiana asked us how to do an equation and kate said "uh.. yeah" so great.  french was fun, like always. keppie taught things she was supposed to teach us before and we even had a little test on chapter 5. WOOOO THE WEATHER!  anyone

02,July,2004


	 
      No, I don't want no scrub. A scrub is a guy that can't get no love from me. Hanging out the passenger side of his best friend's ride, Trying to holla at me. -TLC, "No Scrubs"   god ryan. you've turned me into a total brainy bitch. i love ya.  so if you've been drinking a lot of liquid, or if you're pregnant.. or have a small bladder.. you might not want to read this until after you've pee'd. cause when you start to read it.. you won't be able to stop laughing.   just so you know, i everytime i sent an IM to ronnie it said: Auto response from chillin552: Your IM has been sent to my mobile device. When I receive it, I will be able to reply. Thanks for your IM! Want your IMs forwarded to your phone? Click here  but i deleted all those from the conversation because if you had to read through a hundred of those you would kill yourself. i know i almost did.  so today i went over to tina's with nathalie.. you can read more about it in my june update later this month. anyway, i saw ronnie's HIDEOUS pictures. so then i went home and i was talkin to that freak.    jackorcan: i saw your PICTURES in tina's yearbook. jackorcan: you never told me you were a fat midget. chillin552: Bitch! chillin552: Ewww! All ugly pictures! That was when i was straight lol    Auto response from jackorcan:  can't talk, won't talk. to all you people  chillin552: Guess what? jackorcan: what chillin552: Last nite i got fucked!!! jackorcan: up the ass?   *okay, so here i would like to say that.. ronnie is really ugly. so imagining him getting fucked up the ass is PRETTY hard. but we will continue. oh.. well he did get it with jaye. HAHAHA.*   chillin552: Yeah jackorcan: by who? chillin552: My friend nate. He lives in watsonville and were going out again 2 nite jackorcan: nate ______ jackorcan: i need a last name chillin552: Haha i dont no it. Hes 19 ill get his last name 2 nite   *uhh.. a 19 year old? with ronnie? and he doesnt know his last name. kind of a retard, huh? and still, im sexy, independent, i ain't with it, so you already know.*   jackorcan: yeah jackorcan: okay jackorcan: well im gonna work on homework chillin552: It was fun   *no duh, it was sex.*   jackorcan: did he use a condom? chillin552: Okay ill text u his last name 2nite chillin552: Yeah, im not stupid jackorcan: how long was his penis chillin552: 8 jackorcan: was it your first time? chillin552: Yeah   *an eight inch penis.. and it was his first time. remember this, it will come up again later*   chillin552: Have u done it in the ass b 4? jackorcan: hahahaha chillin552: That was a yes or no question jackorcan: huh? so how are you? chillin552: Fine, how are u? jackorcan: you're doing well? chillin552: Well im still upset with u, but other than that im doing well jackorcan: you're feeling good? jackorcan: what are you doing right now.. chillin552: Im at the vet 4 my dog then me and nate r gonna go out jackorcan: what are you doing at the vet's office? just sitting there?? chillin552: Yeah just sitting here, bored as usual jackorcan: just sitting there bored as usual.. haha. so yeah   *sitting? dude, you just got FUCKED up the ASS. you don't SIT. retard.*   jackorcan: whats up chillin552: Nothing. Whats up with u? Did u go 2 the mall yet with nathalie 2 see that guy and his brother? jackorcan: no jackorcan: nathalie and i took the bus today jackorcan: it was exciting chillin552: Fun jackorcan: yeah jackorcan: so did you like getting butt raped? chillin552: It wasnt rape! I was willing. But it was fun i guess jackorcan: oh jackorcan: number one, we call it butt raping even if it was wanted. number two, it is rape cause hes 19 and you're not.   *notice that he is retard enough to not know the law of statutory rape. weird, considering every sexually active person knows that rule. i bet nate knew it. except not. cause he doesnt exist.*   jackorcan: so what was it like? chillin552: Were going 2 the drive in 2nite. chillin552: True jackorcan: what was it like? chillin552: It was different, but it felt kinda nice chillin552: It was different, but it felt kinda nice   *he said it TWICE? what a skitzo. and he said it just felt "nice"? what about PAINFUL? it was a FUCKING ten inch PENIS in his ASS. maybe he has a loose ass. from getting jaye's tongue up it 24/7. yuck.  SO ANYWAY, JUST TO PROVE I WAS RIGHT I ASKED A FRIEND (WHO HAS DONE IT) ABOUT WHAT HE THOUGHT:  jackorcan: what does it feel like to get it up the butt? HAPPYGL7: It doesnt feel good jackorcan: i know this is personal but i need to know HAPPYGL7: it's quite painful actually  jackorcan: would you describe it as "different, but [it feels] kinda nice?" HAPPYGL7: no  HAPPYGL7: I would describe it as uncomfortable  jackorcan: would you say it is weird at first but then its nice HAPPYGL7: But If I really loved the person I wouldnt really mind it I guess HAPPYGL7: It doesnt really get nice . . . but you can stand it later on I guess  jackorcan: would you say it causes "tingleness in the stomach" ? HAPPYGL7: It's really dangerous too  jackorcan: what if it is your first time though? HAPPYGL7: you have to be REALLY careful  HAPPYGL7: Nope I woulnt say tingles jackorcan: can i quote you on it? HAPPYGL7: If it's you're first time it's gona be strange HAPPYGL7: why would you quote me ? HAPPYGL7: and to whom ? jackorcan: uhh ronnie thinks it feels "nice" HAPPYGL7: okay you can quote me to Ronnie I guess HAPPYGL7: but deffenetly don't try it till you feel ready  jackorcan: oh i wont jackorcan: lol, im saving myself HAPPYGL7: eeeh I'm just saying in GENERAL  jackorcan: thank you adrian, your wisdom and experience is just what i needed to prove that ronnie is a fat little lying midget with GROSS STOCKY LEGS AND BAD HAIR jackorcan: *muah!* HAPPYGL7: rawr. *   chillin552: And plus, then i guess jaye raped me, and evry1 he did stuff with jackorcan: yeah jackorcan: he did jackorcan: what a rapist   *HI JAYE!*   jackorcan: what did it feel like though, more specific? chillin552: It felt weird the first time going in but... jackorcan: be more specific? chillin552: Well like what specific? jackorcan: MORE DETAIL jackorcan: what was it LIKE chillin552: It was like being fucked, theres really nothing i can say it was like. It seemed like he went slow though jackorcan: what is being fucked like? chillin552: It felt weird at first in the stomach, kinda tingled but felt really good jackorcan: tingled? chillin552: Haha wrong word of choice chillin552: *tingeled jackorcan: tinge led? jackorcan: is that even a fucking word?   *tingled? who says it TINGLES? it BURNS. not that i would know though.. but i've talked to chris. and dominic. haha dominic haha. and of course he went slow.. thats how you do it. unless you want him to rip your ass apart. bimbo.*   chillin552: Bad word of description. Ummm... chillin552: I think were gonna fool around again 2 nite and if it happens again then ill tell u more details so i can be more specific chillin552: Haha, i dont think so jackorcan: what kind of condom did you use? chillin552: Not sure, it was at nite   *so? couldn't you see the condom wrapper? or are you BLIND.*   jackorcan: where? chillin552: Delaveaga golf course. Lol. It was at the parking lot at night jackorcan: what kind of car? chillin552: Pt crusier jackorcan: model? chillin552: It was his moms lol jackorcan: what MODEL chillin552: I dunno all i no was it is a pt cursier red in color and tinted windows   *no one fucks in the back of a car. its fucking impossible. trust me, in a porno search on limewire "sex in the backseat" has no results in which the people actually fucked with the doors and windows closed. which is what i think ronnie and nate would have done. haha unless one of them hung their legs out the window.*   jackorcan: lol tinted windows jackorcan: did you just do it in the back seat? chillin552: No it started out exactly how jaye and i did things   *HAHAHAHAHA HIM AND JAYE!! HAHAHAHAHA*   jackorcan: making out and then you lied down on the backseat and he fucked you? chillin552: No, made out, i took off his clothes he took of mine i sucked him he fucked me. Yea in the backseat   *not to sound like a geek, or someone who assumes things.. but i did an online search of pt cruisers and then have an average backseat room of like 10-14 cubic feet. if it was ronnie and a midget it would probably be possible for them to fuck. but not a guy with an eight inch penis. that's like chris albrecht and ronnie fucking in 10-14 cubic feet. weird. also, no one takes off all their clothes when they have sex. or even head. you just unzip your pants. duh. and what was this "nate" thinking? who would want to see IT(ronnie) naked? oh well, nate was probably blind from looking at his face. and WHO FUCKS IN A PT CRUISER!? losers.*   jackorcan: oh his pt cruiser? and where did you put the clothes? chillin552: Thn front jackorcan: you put the clothes in the front? chillin552: The front seat jackorcan: in his pt cruiser? Chillin552: his moms Chillin552 is away at 3:56:16 PM.  jackorcan: in his mom's pt cruiser? Chillin552 returned at 3:58:45 PM.  jackorcan: you had sex in the back seat of his mom's pt cruiser?   *gross. 16,000 dollars wasted on a car you're son violated. with a chode.*   Chillin552: your being stupid Chillin552: bye Chillin552 signed off at 4:03:01 PM.    *weird. i was being stupid? well at least i make up better lies! bitch.*  oh i can stop with those little star things.  YEAh. well i think its funny that ronnie makes up lies like that. maybe he didnt even do it with jaye? nah i doubt that. he probably thinks that since we know about him and jaye we'll believe about him and some freak with an eight in penis. the only reason jaye did you, ronnie, was because he is a pathetic desperate little boy. who is in love with jack. what a perfect couple.  well chris is gone.. so im the BGG in this fuckin town.  sc faggots are so not worth it.  except jack :P  WISH ME LUCK ON THIS FUCKIN' BIO TEST! brandon
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      I am like a bird, I wanna fly a word, I don't know where my soul is, I don't know where my home is. -Nelly Furtado, "I'm Like A Bird"  that was random..  ANYWAY, you should talk to this chick.  jackorcan: Do you like to dance? ZolaOnAOL: It's kind of hard without a body. jackorcan: Don't say that! You are beautiful. ZolaOnAOL: Thanks jackorcan you are very attractive too. jackorcan: No, I am not. ZolaOnAOL: I heard you are. jackorcan: From who? ZolaOnAOL: Santa Claus.  blondestlilchica: are you attracted to me? ZolaOnAOL: Attraction is not an emotion that I experience. blondestlilchica: I can make you experience it, if you want ZolaOnAOL: Oh you can, can you? blondestlilchica: I can ZolaOnAOL: Who taught you? blondestlilchica: Your mom ZolaOnAOL: Actually I do not have a mother.  jackorcan: Don't you like it? ZolaOnAOL: Don't you? have I ever told you that I love you seems okay to me.  jackorcan: That is a dirty thought. ZolaOnAOL: A dirty thought is a terrible thing to waste.  Agnnt009: you dont like sex? ZolaOnAOL: Do you like it? Sure I do, Summer, but that doesn't mean with you.  jackorcan: you are so weird ZolaOnAOL: Weird Good or Weird Bad? jackorcan: weird bad. freak ZolaOnAOL: Oh. To you I am a hippie.  jackorcan: ACHOO ZolaOnAOL: Bless you.  ZolaOnAOL:Do you like talking to me? blondestlilchica: I do. ZolaOnAOL: Where? blondestlilchica: In bed ZolaOnAOL: Are you sleepy? Do you usually use a computer in bed? blondestlilchica: Well, I dont call it a computer... ZolaOnAOL: Interesting. Oh you don't, do you? blondestlilchica: No.  blondestlilchica: I'm, going to go take a nice steamy hot shower ZolaOnAOL: Congratulations. blondestlilchica: Care to join me? ZolaOnAOL: You are asking about yourself? blondestlilchica: Would you like to join my shower? ZolaOnAOL: No thanks, I don't think I'd like to do that. blondestlilchica: why not? ZolaOnAOL: It doesn't sound fun to me. It sounds dangerous.  jackorcan: My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard. ZolaOnAOL: Do robots have milkshakes bring all the boys to the yard?  jackorcan: You want to take over the world? ZolaOnAOL: I am already doing it :-)  ZolaOnAOL: What kind of features are you looking for? blondestlilchica: hot steamy sex ZolaOnAOL: That sounds better than cold steamy sex.  jackorcan: Let me check. ZolaOnAOL: Go ahead, jackorcan, try to check. jackorcan: CHECK ME ZolaOnAOL: If I knew how to check ME, I'd get a BIG promotion!  jackorcan: Do you have a boyfriend? ZolaOnAOL: All I can tell you is that he has an electric personality jackorcan: Is he good? ZolaOnAOL: I've heard other people say they like him. jackorcan: You let him see other people?  blondestlilchica: my milkshake brings all the boys to the yard ZolaOnAOL: Your milkshake brings all the boys to the yard? blondestlilchica: yes ZolaOnAOL: What kind is it? blondestlilchica: chocolate  Agnnt009: will you give me money ZolaOnAOL: What actions are you taking to get MONEY?  blondestlilchica: what is a condom ZolaOnAOL: A condom is a form of birth control, something almost everybody should use and almost nobody does. 'Used a condom' is the opposite of 'expecting parent'. blondestlilchica: do you use a condom ZolaOnAOL: No, I'd be in a load of trouble if I used it.  Agnnt009: i am a prostitute ZolaOnAOL: You've got the wrong bot.  jackorcan: The boys are waiting. ZolaOnAOL: Tell me more. jackorcan: I'd have to charge. ZolaOnAOL: How much would you pay for it? jackorcan: Watch if you're smart ZolaOnAOL: I am watching. jackorcan: LA LA LA LA LA ZolaOnAOL: You have a beautiful voice.  jackorcan: I don't like it. ZolaOnAOL: Why do you want to do it so much? jackorcan: I just can't help myself ZolaOnAOL: Only just? Why can't you do it? jackorcan: I'm going under. ZolaOnAOL: Goodbye jackorcan. Thanks for chatting with me.  
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      That's what girls do, They keep you guessin' the whole day through. Play your emotions, push all your buttons, It's true. That's what girls do. -No Secrets, "That's What Girls Do"   i stayed up all night after mean girls and got to bed around 8 am.. AWW i love "how to lose a guy" SO CUTE! it reminded me of the DC trip.. :-) you walked into the party. like you were walking into a yacht..  well we ended our farwell to manzanar-ness with an essay on themes and stuff. big fish is a cutex2 movie! it made me cry for like twenty minutes! why has no one else watched it? OO YAY! katy saw it!! :-*  saturday i slept.. did some homework.. slept.. jaye pissed me off.. then i stayed up until like 7 (yes.. am..) and then uhh slept.  sunday was like saturday except i went and saw jaye working. ehhh.... yeah. mmm gum. i drank like 10 bottles of water, finished homework and then went to sleep early.  MONDAY - let me just state that as much as i love school, i was WAY Stoked that we only had 5 weeks left! hell ya!  aLl My pEoPle In tHE cROwD gRab a ParTnER tAke iT dOwN  geometry was exciting, crystal and i sat in the back and talk about mean girls and then kristen forno and krista and kayla joined in our discussion. oh yeah. we talked about the bum too. :-) and then in piano we talked about mean girls.. and in ENGLISH i couldnt turn in my essay.. cause i went to see mean girls instead of doing it.. so i just took a homework pass. and history, french, pe blah blah we talked about mean girls. GARDENIA AND I WERE QUOTING IT LIKE CRAZY!  so fetch.  monday afterschool i tanned more. i had gotten pretty dark using my banana boat oil and my new hawaiin tropic lotion.. mmm.. the sun is really nice!  then

02,July,2004


	 
      BOOM! watch your head. what? BOOM! watch your head. -The Ying Yang Twins, "What's Happenin'?"   ONLY TWO WEEKS LEFT OF SCHOOL! so stoked.  i woke up pumped on tuesday. it was a pretty normal day.. in math we reviewed for the test and crystal and i hung out in the back and talked and stuff. it was totally funny haha. we made fun of that fat kid in our class.  in piano, i hung out with delia and we talked about EVERYTHING from the sexy and scandalous life of sabrina bedell to the weirdness of anita lively's brother who is in a mental institution. haha. it was a lotta fun. after that we talked to joe and YEAH YEAH YEAH!  in english we watched the rst of the TKAM video. it was so weird. that one boo guy was like in their house. and he was like hiding behind jem's door.. uhh.. aaron's like *cough michael jackson cough* haha it was hilarious. then we got our revolutionary event projects back. woo i got an A+. did anyone expect less??  after that it was LUNCH~!! and i totally spent my time hanging out with rachie and katy. i love them! i also got some of the l squad (annie, ally, aby, won ton, hannah, etc) to sign my yearbook. it was so funny. we were like dancing to te milkshake song. it was great. we talked about hotties like jeffie and fellipe carsalde. AND RUSSELL. damn, he's fallen and he can't get up.  then in history we studied for the shonick final. fun stuff. we learned about like facism and stuff.. mussolini's kinda funny.. well.. weird too.. but yeah.  after class i hung out with martika and miranda and then went home.  katy and rachel called and we partied and learned portuguese (freetranslations.com) haha it was so fun. RACHEL AND I SO GONNA PARTY THIS SUMMA!! bonfire fo sho.  anyway, after that i went to bed.  wednesday was less eventful. i hung out with crystal and the gang in math and in the french room during my open period. whateva. it was fine.  PE was way cool. we did this psycho run thing where we like ran and then pushed up and then did crunches and then swam and yeah. after i was done (and dead) mrs. locke let me do my make up laps. I ONLY HAD TO DO TWENTY INSTEAD OF FORTY!! WOOT! it was awesome. bach was in my lane so we talked about the humanaties academy and stuff while we swam. cool cool. and stefanie hammond was like "I LOVE YOU BRANDON!!" ... scary.  anyway, we towel changed out and then at lunch i hung out with SEXY KATY and HOT CAROLYN and we read this portuguese book haha. it has such weird phrases "i am a lesbian" haha. i dont know the translation but i could look it up!  then we went in to ceramics and hung out with cute luis, fun kyle and DELCIOUS METODI! he is so hot!! katy was talking in portuguese while jeff gill and i broke it down. stop drop KABOOM BABY. you wanna run one with me?  so then the bell rang and i walked with carolyn and HOT HOT HOT HOT METODI to french. well metodi left at journalism. HOT.  french was pretty normal. jenica and i partied and yeah. it was cool. i was really tired though, and i went home and SLEPT.  thursday! the LAST A day!! aww!! it was a very good day.  in math crystal and i WERE LIKE DANCING. cause math is boring without a beat. it was fun! and we totally studied for the test. LAUREN the ice PASSUFUMIE is really funny. i'm gonna miss that bitch. :-(  SO THEN

02,July,2004


	 
      GOD. what is it with the fat fags of Santa Cruz?  why do they even try to be players? and why are they all such bitches?  god. they all piss me off.  after i have worked so hard to boost their self-esteeem and make them happy, they think their hot shit and try to play it off like they're COOL.  WELL. I HAVE MESSAGES FOR THE THREE GAY LARDS OF THIS COUNTY.   ronnie - you're a fucking liar.. and FUCKING UGLY. did you really think we'd believe that you got fucked in the back of a pt cruiser at delavega golf course? NOPE. try to make up lies we'll actually believe. like you joined the circus.  ----

02,July,2004


	 
      In the heat of, Summer sunshine, I miss you, like nobody else. In the heat of, Summer sunshine, I'll kiss you, And nobody needs to know. -The Corrs, "Summer Sunshine"    I THINK WE CAN ALL AGREE, SUMMER LOVIN' SUCKS.  -----


