
09,March,2004


	 
      Argh, today and yesterday were hilarious and I can't remember a damn thing. All I can really do is complain my leg hurts and to recommend you to this site: www.redvsblue.com to download the Blood Gulch Chronicles. Download season one, they are hilarious, and very good topic starters. Usually. Calling someone a cock-biting fucktard isn't one that springs to mind, but still... download them.
     

    


07,March,2004


	 
      Well I was eating dinner tonight, and my grandma, who's visiting, had brought some buns from home. I'll describe them as my family does: "Nice and fluffy." Now why the hell would anyone want to eat fluffy rolls? Do you LIKE eating air, then burping it right back up? Give me a nice, dense, soggy, warm roll and call me happy. Same concept as muffins, cake, brownies; anything that could be fluffy or thick. Fluffy has no substance, no mass. As I've said before, it's like eating air. You don't get the full flavor of the article you are ingesting, and you have to eat about 15 of the damn things to even get half full. Mash potatoes too. Fluffy is crap. Pure crap. Do not feed anyone fluffy, even if they say they like it, because most of the time people don't know what's good for them.
     

    


07,March,2004


	 
      Yeah so I finally found something easier than that retarded subprofile. Hopefully this will work, otherwise it's back to the sub.
     

    


07,March,2004


	 
      If it doesn't, I'm going to smash something.
     

    


18,March,2004


	 
      

16,March,2004


	 
      Ah the night before bowling, and all through the house, not a creature was stirring, except for Tyler, Jeremy, Mike, and me. And Biscuit, the dog. Started the night well with pizza, 5 pieces fo me, and off we went to Halo, on two Tvs. Tyler brought his TV and Xbox, so cheating was at a minimum. Unfortunatly, Jeremy is the only one without Xbox, so whatever team he was on was, let's just say, OWNED. BADLY. Very frustrating, but fun nonetheless. I had 69 kills one game of Capture the Flag. I was proud. Then we got bored, and video taped me and Tyler and Mike taping up Jeremy and shoving him in a cage. Jeremy volunteered. Then we played more Halo, blew up some Coke cans, and went to sleep some time in the morning. We had to get up for bowling, you see, so atleast 2 hours of sleep, I think that's what it was, was sufficient in our minds. I got the couch anyways.  Bowling was entertaining. The farthest left pin in the back row was disfunctional, and sometimes others, so if you knocked down all but one pin, you would get a strike sometimes. Also worked with spares. It was awesome on the receiving end, but otherwise it sucked. I won two games, under the alias "Caboose." The others were "Shaq" (Alex), "Tucker" (Jeremy), "Church" (Tyler), "Donut" (Mike) and one player, played by all of us, "Doofus." It was an overall good time, finished off by a washed out badass lighting up a stogue in the entrance way to the lanes. I laughed at him when he left. 
     

    


23,March,2004


	 
      

03,April,2004


	 
      

24,April,2004


	 
      

22,April,2004


	 
      

18,April,2004


	 
      I'm in the process of redoing my color scheme, don't razz me for having bad colors, I'm new at this and not too good.
     

    


18,April,2004


	 
      

14,May,2004


	 
      Ran my previous job idea (janitor at elementary school) through my mom, and she says that's probably not too hot an idea, since it's most likely a union job, and obviously I'm not in a union. sob. I'm thirsty,  ---------  ~Chill~
     

    


10,May,2004


	 
      The bus has become my naptime in the afternoon. I sit down, and almost immediately, I get sleepy. So I put my head against the back of the seat in front of me, cuz I'm too tall to lean back (my neck would most likely snap if I tried it). So some people get off the bus, and Russ moves out of my seat, and I lay down and fall a sleep. So it was on Wed. or Tue., except I was rudely awakened by a kid named Cody, or however you spell it. He kept talking to me, when I was clearly asleep. I think Russ was laughing, so I open my eyes, and there Cody is, 2 feet away from my face babbling on and on. Just thought I'd share that little story with j00.  Babe Ruth starts Monday, 6pm. I'm happy. I really really want to play. Tomorrow is Saturday, and I plan to sleep in. That's it. Possibly play XBOX or wiffleball, but that would be the extent of my day. My hair has finally grown to barely acceptable lengths, but it's going to be a few weeks still before it's back up to par. Eh, that's what I get for cutting it. =/  ---------  ~Chill~
     

    


10,May,2004


	 
      Google has re-done the whole blog stuff. Leaving comments is a new feature. Be cool and do it.  ---------  ~Chill~
     

    


10,May,2004


	 
      This past Saturday, Tyler and I went on down to Russ's, and had a nice little war with our (semi)-trusty airsoft guns. All in all, it was pretty good. Outside is always fun, and during night wars I almost pissed myself after an encounter with Tyler from around the corner of the shed. The distances from outside started to get tediously long, so I (atleast I think it was me) had the bright idea of going down into the basement and setting up tables and stuff.     That turned out to be quite a harrowing experience in close-quarters warfare. Turning a corner equaled excruciating pain if shot on the flesh, and the floor soon became littered with billes (plastic BBs for all you non-cool people). I still have welts two days later, and I'm sure Russ was happy as a beaver who just got wood with the mess we left him. It was definitly exciting, atleast.   ---------  ~Chill~ 
     

    


23,May,2004


	 
      Summary: Campout and Vin's Bday  Campout: Pretty sweet. Left on friday, set up tents, and had a jolly old time. Mr. Ortiz locked his keys in his running car (REEEEtard!) and ruined one of Tyler's skewers while using it as a slim jim. For all you dummies who don't know what a slim jim is, go die. Then we slept. It was good. When we woke up, we made bagels for breakfast, and went shooting at the rifle range. It was comfortable, except instead of earplugs, we had cotton balls, which sucked ass. Mr. Shwart (I bet I spelled that wrong) had his lever action 30-30, which is a hell of a gun. Heh. Then we worked on a shelter which kicked ass, but we didn't finish it cuz everyone wanted to shoot the boomsticks. Wasn't great, then Mr. A pulled out the .44 Magnum Handgun, and that thing is a fuckin' BEAST. He bought heavy loads (more powder) and the first shot he took, the left lens of Jer's sunglasses POPPED OUT. He was standing atleast 10 ft away. That's how powerful that handgun is. The concussion of firing that weapon is so incredible, it actually makes your heart skip. No shit. So later that night, we made S'mores and told funny stories which I can't remember cuz I wasn't very "on the ball," as they say. So Mrs. Sardo brings out a cake cuz it's Shaq-fu's B-day, and everybody crowded around, going I'M FIRST MEMEMEMEMEME.   Around that time is where my brutal badness REALLY kicked in that night. It's terrible. I was trying to come up with something crafty, catchy, whatever you wish to call it, and I failed miserably. The blasphemous utterance of gross incompetance that spewed from my mouth went something like this: "Guys, it isn't like... this is the last... gold.. coin of the... 21st century." I studdered, and halted, TRYING to redeem myself, and I just dug in deeper. Yes, I'm a retard, and Tyler will harass me with this for a VERY LONG TIME.   After my bit of dumbness, we played capture the flag. Two experiences I will explain with stories from the dominion council: From Tyler, about me: As for CTF, due to the mega incompetence of his team he lose. Heh there was 3 of us on our team and 2 on their team standing on the neutral line. And we're just talking about the game since we really can't do anything. They're standing there so I go ten feet to the right of me into the woods, and they know perfectly well I'm there since I'm loud and still in sight. They say "I don't care about Tyler, he's not doing his job" So I jogged down to the flag (a flashlight) doing my best not to fall in the pitch blackness. I grab the flashlight, and start sprinting the 1000 feet or so back to my base, probably less but somewhere around there. I get back to the neutral line and the two guys on their team are still standing there. Alex sacraficed himself and tackled them both and just lied on them, I just sprinted all the way back and won:).   From me, about me: Yeah, GROSS incompetance.  Again, we were at the nuetral line, me, Jeremy, and another young kid, and against us were Tyler, Alex, and a young kid. So Alex is like, "I gotta take a piss!" so in the middle of the game, he goes into the woods and pisses. I'm like, "Jer, get ready." I tell Alex to move into the woods more, I don't want him pissing on me, so he DOES, and I'm like WOOOOO and run straight through the woods, almost getting decapitated (a branch took my hat) Tyler runs after me, and all that's guarded Jer is a bewildered youngun. So I get down to their flag, turn around, and Jeremy isn't there! and I'm like, JER! WHERE YOU AT YOU ASS! and I get caught. =/   So then we went to bed, and in the morning we were breaking camp. Everyone is up, and Mr. A decides to shoot his .44 MAGNUM IN THE CAMPSITE. He just loads it up, and shoots a tree! I almost crapped myself, the thing is so loud. Then he yells "You all are awake now I bet!" And then me and Tyler are like "Um, we were already awake." So that was the campout. It was fun.   Then was Vin's bday party @ battleground in Waterbury. That place is the shit! We played counter-stike and some WW2 games for three hours. It was great. Wow, that story sucked. Eh.   ---------  ~Chill~
     

    


03,June,2004


	 
      Registration is open for Dominion, Round 24. I highly suggest signing up and making an attempt to learn the rules/play. It's a good experience.
     

    


02,June,2004


	 
      School today was extremely boring, so I came up with an idea. I will write about all the stupid things that I remember, probably once a week. These will be the "Tales of the Stupid." And today is Entry 1. Ahem.  Tales of the Stupid: Day 1  US History is the site of today's tale. We were going over worksheets on pre-Civil War events, and a question came up that went something like this:  Congress tried to compromise to keep the Union together. What two things did this compromise include?   1) Congress would make slavery _________    2) Congress could not interfere with slavery.  Now, saying Congress would "not interfere" with slavery would imply that slavery would be ALLOWED, or PROTECTED, which were both correct answers. Nevertheless, some jackass had to open their mouth, without thinking, and say "PROHIBITED!" I knew it was coming, and almost immediatly after the words came out, I yelled a quick "NO!" I thoroughly enjoyed it, and I hope very much that the person mentioned felt heartily ashamed of their actions. I also highly doubt it.
     

    


30,May,2004


	 
      Life ticks on, and school only has 3 weeks left or something. All I know is IT'S GOING TO END SOON. Yeah, I'm sooo in the not-doing-any-school-work mood. So I didn't go to school friday. Yep. The greatest part is that when my mom woke me and my brother up, she asks "You wanna go to school today?" I'm like "Nope," and then I went back to sleep. When I woke up, it was two fried eggs and toast for breakfast. I prepared them myself, I thank you. Then XBOX WOOOOOO.    So onto less connected things.  On Thursday, the new edition of our school newspaper came out. Some crap about crap was in there, and some other crap, and then I came to two things that got me really worked up. First, was an article about the movie "Bowling for Columbine," which is about the Columbine shootings and stuff. The article really had no purpose, except, in my opinion, to support anti-gun sentiments. First of all, that movie is in NO WAY impartial, or unbiased. It is the work of a raving mad gun hater, bent on the destruction of firearm ownership and the NRA. That got me just a tad bit angry. So then I went on to read an article about how obesity (fatness) is a major problem in society. No shit Sherlock. Everywhere I go there's a fat person walkin' down the street. Now don't get me wrong; there is "large" fat, and then there is "so grossly obese it makes you want to gag" fat. I'm talking about the second choice. So I was reading it, and I get down to a paragraph that says something about people SUING MCDONALDS FOR MAKING THEM FAT!! That got me royally pissed off. How the HELL do you get off blaming SOMEONE ELSE for YOUR FATNESS. The pure idiocy in blaming a food company for making you fat astounds me! It's one thing to sue if you get food poisoning, or Hepatitis A, but fatness? IT'S NOT A GOD DAMN VIRUS. EXERCISE A BIT, YOU FAT, RETARDED FUCKS. People just don't want to take responsibilty these days. They always have to go and make an excuse for EVERYTHING. Even when it's not they aren't to blame.  For example: Someone breaks their toe on a chair that you were sitting in, and you automatically blame either the person who set up the tables/chairs, or you blame the victim. OR A hubcap on your car flies off while you're driving, and accidentally kills an old lady. Instead of saying "OH GOD I'M REALLY SORRY," you say "It wasn't me! It was the pothole's fault!" Not even their fault, but there is no way they're going to take the blame for it. Get some morals people! I could go ON and ON, but in the end, it all breaks down to BEING STUPID AND NOT THINKING. Unfortunately, no one is perfect. Everyone is stupid at one time or another. But there are a few things that can easily counter-act stupidness. They are: 1) Breathe. Taking breathes forces you to stop talking, and therefore plan your next move/words. 2) Plan/Organize. This forces you to think too, and when you're thinkin' you disappoint less people. This also allows you to have less stress, especially when coupled with more chillin' and less FREAKING OUT.  3) Don't be an ass. First think "How will this NOT HURT anyone else." THEN think "How will it help me." By making other people happy, in the end you yourself have less hassle, and therefore are more happy too. If you're an ass, all you'll get back is, you guessed it, SHIT.  If I come up with anything else, I'll put it in.  Some other stuff that really pisses me off to hell is that people will sue over any little thing. What happened to solving things so everyone is happy? Nope, all that counts is mememememememememememe! The world is full of selfish, stupid, unkind and unthinking BASTARDS! (insanity!) AND THERE'S NOTHING ANYONE CAN DO ABOUT IT, BECAUSE STUPID IS A RACE, AND GENOCIDE IS ILLLLEGAL!!!!!! GAAAAAAAAAAAAH. (end insanity!) ACH! There is NOTHING that I can type or say or do to EXPRESS my TOTAL frusTRATION except CAPitalize HALF of the WORDS I SAY.  ajlkdfjklaskdjlfklj;sdaklfasd;fam,sl/nfnlaskdhfjklkasdhkjfdanskhefntkrhdft  SO ANGRY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!1!1!111!!!!1shift!1!!!!!!1!!!!one!!!!....  ...  ... ... ... ... ... I wish I was God. And my one commandment would be: DON'T BE DUMB, OR I'LL SMITE YOU.    ...grumble...grumble...
     

    


13,June,2004


	 
      If you haven't read my old sub-profile, I suggest you read "I HATE TREEHUGGERS." Or whatever it's called.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ok. Today, I painted Tyler's house. Then I went home around 6:45. I get home, and my neighbor is talking to my dad. That's never good, because this is the tree hugger neighbor.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;To understand the situation, here's a summary of their past month's retardedness: My brother has a dirtbike. He likes to ride it. So he has many trails. The neighbors are obsessed with "protecting the environment," as they see it. I do not care about that. Unfortunately, they insist on invading our property with attempts to stop my brother. He goes around their blocks, thus creating more trails, and destroying more wildlife.   Are you seeing the stupidity yet?  Back to the story. They plant more shrubs, and they plant one in a blind corner, so my brother takes the turn, doesn't see it, and of course, runs over it. It is clearly not destroyed, but damaged. So they flip a shit, even though the land they planted it on isn't theirs. They CLAIM it is their, but it is not. It is an access road from the road, THROUGH someone else's land. By law, that 25ft strip of land cannot be owned by ANYONE. And they claim it belongs to them. Yeah fucking right. Bitches.
     

    


25,July,2004


	 
      Adding on to my previous posts about fat people, I would like to say that America is in for a hell of a ride if parents continue to fatten up their children like pigs going to slaughter.  &nbsp;During summer camp, some friends of mine made the observation that all the kids 12 and under in our troop are obese. By obese, I don't mean tubby, I mean "so fat that they have disgusting man boobs." Anyway, I looked around, and was unpleasantly surprised to find it true. I looked around the rest of camp, and found that all kids that looked 12 or under were either grossly obese, or extremely skinny (which is probably the reason that they aren't fat), and this observation made me VERY VERY ANGRY, and led me to thinking about the causes. I believe I have them. A children's parent's are there figureheads for growing up, and make them what they are. Sometimes kids are exactly like their parents, sometimes they aren't, but the main thing is that parents DO make their children who they are when they become adults. This being said, I look at fat kids, and I see parents who baby their children (which takes on the façade of caring too much), don't care about them, or pass on large genes to their unfortunate children, the latter not being addressed in this article. I will address the two evil-fat-children-creating tactics in two sections.  Parents who baby their children. For lack of a better set of terms.  Now, I have a prime example (sorry for those who don't know this impling): Alex Tonning. A short history on him: An 11 year old boy, son of a couple who were previously married, and each had children. His Dad is pretty cool, I don't know about his Mom, but it seems she is the dominating factor in his life. He is one of the fattest pieces of crap I've even seen. I believe this is because his mother let's him get away with everything, and makes him do nothing. From all the stories I've heard, this kid does absolutely no work, and never get's in trouble for anything, even if it's his fault. All this builds up, and from lack of anything requiring hardship, he becomes fat. This also causes the individual to be EXTREMELY ANNOYING, because he thinks the world revolves around him, and his sense of justice and right/wrong is extrememly skewed.  Negligent parents  Actually, now that I think about it, the reasons for fat are exactly the same, even though on opposite sides of the spectrum. Parents do not care, so they do not limit their kids: they eat everything and anything they want, and do no work. Argh.  So, what I'm getting to is that not only should you blame the fat children for being fat, but their parents for making them fat. Make sure you feed your children properly, and put them to work, even if it's cleaning the toilets or something, because every little bit helps. 
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
      ATTENTION! ACHTUNG! WE HAVE STOOPED TO A NEW LOW!  As I watched Dennis Miller, I learned of a terrible, terrible thing. I went online, only to find sources corroborating what he said. The horrible news: Krispy Kreme, to increase sales, has made a liquid donut. I repeat a LIQUID DONUT.  Not only are we a fat nation, we are EXTREMELY LAZY. Too lazy, in fact, to CHEW OUR FOOD. Holy Christ!!! I can't even put into words my disgust. This is SAD. ARGH.
     

    



