
17,March,2004


     
       Capital Punishment   Does any man have the right to sentence another to death? Even if the man is question has commited murders?
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       Too Far?   You tease someone, using some light-hearted comments about his family and or friends, and he does too.  He then decides to take this further, and spread a secret you told him in trust, did he go too far?
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       Karma   Does it exist?  You do something bad to someone else, does it come back to haunt you?  Or what about if you do something good, does something good equally happen?  What about the theory that if you are doing something good, someone else is recieving pain or something bad, or vice versa.
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       Do we have a stalker?  (Contributed By Jo)  How comes q is always followed by a u? Is it some sort a stalker?  We see u all over the place however q can barely move around without being beside u. Is u jelous? 
     
    


14,March,2004


     
        Completely Random Thought #1    I wonder what it's like to be friends with a lesbian
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       People In Relationships   How come some people in relationships, always seems prepared to take so much slack(hassle, trouble etc) from their other partner? Is it worth it?
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       The Speed of Light   Say, Technology improves, and travelling at the speed of light is possible.  You are on a train which is travelling at the speed of light, and you turn a torch on. What happens?
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       Train Travelling  (Contributed By Jo[Curly

14,March,2004


     
       The Rule of Like-Like?   You like someone, however you just know or having a feeling that they don't like you. However, you know that someone likes you, but theres just no way you could like them for whatever reason.  I've noticed this in a few relationships really, very...weird.
     
    


14,March,2004


     
       The Internet   Why's it got such a bad rep?  It's good to use for reference, but if you like it too much, or spend too much time on it it's bad?  It's ok to be online once in a while, but not on for more than 2 hours a day?
     
    


14,March,2004


     
      Welcome to the "Thoughts on my Mind" Blog, Home to some of random thoughts and questions to the world, feel free to comment on them!
     
    


01,April,2004


     
       APRIL FOOLS~!   MWHAHAHHAHAHAHAHHA  Tricked ya jo ;)
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       Fuck That Ruin My One Pleasure In Life   I dnt care! Percy Pigs ROCK and il stand by them as long as they r about drugs or not i love em **runs and protects percy pigs no one wil pass!!!!!!!!!!!! **SUPER JO**
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       Random But Makes Me Think Why?   WHY is it so wrong for a girl to ask a boy out? Thought we were all in the same boat now none of this man must do everythin shit, but this simple thing just seems so wrong for some strange reason, hmmm..... **im not a feminist btw**
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       Percy Pig's=Drug?   BBC reports on the latest news on the Marks and Spencers Brand of sweets known as Percy Pig(tm), it has been identifies that they contain a drug called tartine, information of which is below  TARTINE INFORMATION   Classification:  Central Nervous System Stimulant    How might the user feel?  Relaxed  Dizzy  Excited  Nauseated  Energetic  Tense    How might they look/act?  talkative  white lumps on lining of mouth (leukoplakia)  tooth loss    What are the after effects?  Irritability  Trembling  Anxiety  Weight gain  Insomnia  Depression  Restlessness    How does it affect the body?  weight loss  bad breath  shortness of breath  increases cavities/tooth decay  reduces sensitivity to pain/stress  constricts blood vessels  increases urine output  increases blood pressure  increases heart rate  chronic obstructive pulmonary disease  arteriosclerosis  physical/psychological addiction  lung, mouth, throat, esophageal, bladder, larynx cancer  stomach ulcers  hypertension (high blood pressure)  heart attacks  impairs sense of taste and smell  decreases physical stamina  emphysema  chronic bronchitis  heart disease  ages/wrinkles skin  gum disease  erosion of the teeth  mouth lesions (leukoplakia)  
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       England   Don’t predict bad weather it has a wonderful ability to prove you right!
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       April Fools   Pointless? Creates too much problems for the sake of "tradition"?  or, Good harmless fun?
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       Life   It just cant let you be happy has to knock u while ur happy, and if it can it will knock you when your down...... just the life we have to live.
     
    


30,March,2004


     
       Perm theory   People with perms find it impossible to put on hair spray.... i no random lol!
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Hair Mousse Friend Or Foe   its great makes ur hair its best, but then you cant seem to live without it your hair seems lifeless without it... its like a god damn drug...!
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Being Drunk   you do stupid things which you would never do when your sober but is that a good enough excuse?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Time   You leave somthing too long the other person cant remember what they used to feel......
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Is life purposefully Ironic?   Is it just me or can life turn out to be  so  unbelievablly Ironic?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       See Thru Tops...   Are they so wrong.... ive had about 4 guys point out the top from my screen pic is see thru, now id like to point out 4 GUYS, and so i answer my question they rock! lmao
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Right I Have A Really Dirty Mind And Im Gonna Say Sorry Now For Anything I Post In The Future   lets start off with a classic joke lol...  If your left leg is x mas and your right leg is easter can i visit you in-between the holidays?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Naked....hmmmm maybee   If a turtle doesn't have a shell, is it homeless or naked?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       SORRY   Id like to say sorry and correct my fishing vs guy hunting theory, maybe im just not that great at fishing??
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Gross Quote #1   "My dreams are like a tropical ocean...nice to be in, but too damn wet"
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Guys?????    Maybe finding a guy is like fishing, you go out, set the bait **lol** and fish sometimes you dont catch anything, somtimes you do but you put it right bk, and other times u find the perfect fish.....  OK i lie....  Perfect fish yes   Perfect guy.... Maybe not? 
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Come Again?   Totally random but can anyone say that without laughin? I know I cant!
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Rubber Humans Vs Rubber Chickens...   Do chickens find rubber humans funny?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Religion...and Alcohol...Co-Insidence?   "Alcohol is rather like religion, it is great but makes you do some silly things"  mmm, Good Point
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Sign Strikers   If sign makers go on strike do they have anything written on their signs, and lookin a bit deeper...... do they even have signs.... dont lie you are now all really wondering!
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Being Blonde   is it true we have more fun......, you see i wouldnt know ive never tried being anything else?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
        ID LIKE TO INTRODUCE TO YOU MY FRIEND CALLED FRED.......
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       Reality Vs Dreams   How can u prove your not dreaming that your reading this?
     
    


28,March,2004


     
       (We're) Back~!   After a short...(11 day) break, I'm back along with my lovely assistant Jo, who will be contributing to the site without the need of going through me, not that I dont mind her going through me....  So yes, get ready for some random-assed comments!
     
    


28,March,2004


     
      CHEESEEEEEEEEEEE!!
     
    


07,April,2004


     
       Things You Havnt Tried In Life   some seem appealin others not one always seems so akward..... Might as well just forget it
     
    


07,April,2004


     
       Money   WHY DOESNT IT GROW ON TREEESSS DAMN ITTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT!!
     
    


19,April,2004


     
       A Smile   A form of power.....? hmmm
     
    


19,April,2004


     
       A Smile   A form of power? hmmm......
     
    


12,May,2004


     
       The Beheading of the American Captive by Rebels in Iraq   Unbelievable.  Never have I, nor will I ever want to see such a sight as I witnessed. Completely Discussing.
     
    


11,May,2004


     
       The [Un]Classy Exam Revision Tip #1   Take A Revision Book With You Into The Toilet!
     
    


11,May,2004


     
       High School   finally over teeheee wow feels very weird... it's all down hil from here then lmaoooo
     
    


10,May,2004


     
       Speakin Of Tans   Why do i burn? i think this is very unfair lol! damn it i get the pale skin from my dan not the nice tanable *is that even a word?* skin from my mum *sad face*
     
    


10,May,2004


     
       Impossible Tan    How comes you cant get a tan on your palms?
     
    


10,May,2004


     
       Dan   LOVE UUUU YOUR ALWAYS THERE WEN I NEED U WIL NEVER EVER FORGET IT!!!!
     
    


10,May,2004


     
       Love   ..It taught me to cry....
     
    


10,May,2004


     
       Welcome Back!   After a Brief Spell, which includes several events in both mine and jo's lives (Not together 

21,May,2004


     
       Revision...    You really have to be in the mood for it
     
    


20,May,2004


     
       Me   If you dont like me for who i am then you dont like me for who i am and all your gonna get is who i am! *avril lavigne*
     
    


18,May,2004


     
       Relationships   should you be lookin out for somthin better? or completely focused on the one in hand *lmaoo in hand lol* *oh god sorry lol* hmmmmmmmm......
     
    


17,May,2004


     
       Trust   starting to believe it doesnt exist... well maybe not for me *sad face*
     
    


17,May,2004


     
       No Perfect Partner   I dont think there's such a thing as a 'perfect partner' while there are some good people out there, they'll just never be perfect, they'll always be something wrong...
     
    


30,May,2004


     
       The Truth Coin!   It never lies lol! woohoooo 
     
    


30,May,2004


     
       Relationships   haha cant resist!
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       LMAO   i is sittin here havin a gd old chuckle at the fact people r actually betting on how long i can last in my new relationship and i do realise my last two have been short and sweet but may i remind u all i went out with paddy for 9 months...... and i think things r lookin quite promisin for this one! bens sweet lovely and he makes me laugh.. its a gd mix..... and anyways its so lastin over 3 weeks to prove u all rong *pissin herself laughin* so thats 3 weeks 1/2 a day whey only kiddin... heres me hopein it lasts longer than that thanks!  well gcse's r goin as badly as they possibly can and the one subject COUGH sceince COUGH i thought i was any gd at had some arse uppers of an exam paper so meh and maths *just simply laughs*  MWAH 
     
    


08,June,2004


     
      ...the thick of exams have finally sourrounded all year eleven students in England and Wales. Almost Halfway through every major subject, things are looking sticky, and I'm not talking about the palm of jo's hand.  The lack of entries could be put down to revision, however that would be a tick of such great proportions, like a president not actually winning the election, but is president anyway...but that would never happen....  Not much has happened, I'm still lurking and Jo is on her fourth boyfriend of the year. While bets are on for the length of the relationship, the odds of Jo going out with two people at the same time during the year are at a good 10-1. ;)  Ah, gotta love Jo ^_^
     
    



