
28,March,2004


						
						     Hi my name is ??????????? you want to know my name so I give you some hints (Listen:I am a Korean person and I'm 14 years old and Grade 7 in NJIS.) Do you know my name now?? My name is KWang Wook,. And I can play golf so my golf scores are 95,and handicap 40. But next year I want to be golfer. and i will be better than Tiger Wood. He was famous at LPG golf competition. And next I like to play computer games too much. Because computer makes people happy and exciting. I can  play Clarinet because I like  urlLink music . Clarinet makes to good sounds and feels comfortable. my favorite subject is English and science. my e-mail was " urlLink skw92000@yahoo.co.kr "   urlLink   

						


28,March,2004


						
						   Hahahahahawhahahahahaha

25,April,2004


						
						   1. Do you feel this would be something you would like to use? =

15,April,2004


						
						   1. Do you feel this would be something you would like to use? =

15,April,2004


						
						   Hello Njis Students tomorrow we are going to YOGJAKARTA. So i think there was fun. I already have been YOGJAKARTA 1 times. There are so hot and so funny places.                                                   BY: Kwang Wook SHin.....    em

15,April,2004


						
						   Today I have swimming and I learned butterfly strog. at first we swimming 7 laps and then later playing "Tube WaterPolo." and I ride on the Tube and starting play. I like swimming at PE times.     

						


04,May,2004


						
						   1. How does the increasing use of cameras affect privacy? =It could affect us, people will watch us when we are sleep, eating, Running, talking or other else... 2. Where do you think it is fair to have cameras installed? Not fair? = I think, it is fair to have camaras installed in house or places because when we stay at home we can take a picture of family and it can show my house pictures. And when in other place we can use for important things.... 3. What is your opinion on this subject? =In this opinion i want to tell the technology was development with them... *^---^;*  4. If you feel that this is an invasion of privacy, how do you feel governments should help increase protection from the inclining terrorist threats? =????????????????????????????????????????????????  

						



