
11,May,2004


	 
      HEY,  I WILL TRY TO POST THE HOMEWORK EVERYNIGT  STARTING TOMARROW TO PLEASE CHECH AND I WILL LET ONLY SOME OF YOU POST ON THSI ONE BECAUSE IT IS SPECIAL AND IT IS NOT FOR FUN BUT IT IS FOR PROFIET
     
    



08,May,2004


     
      hey, you guys. It's me. People are swarming my house today. I'm not sure who all is coming, but it looks like Tim, Tina, Mellissa, and Katie Withrow. Just letting everyone know. Man, I just can't stop putting stuff into this blog. It are fun! Well, I'm being invaded right now, so I'll see you all later.       ~Phil
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      the time stamps are kina screwed up. we hope to get this fixed!
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      So ends my first day of true blogging. Going to bed... sigh... stayed up too late playing video games... well, good night all. Hope to maybe see some of you guys at my place in the morning (If i'm awake).       ~Phil
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      I am sleepy because I went to a track meet. I am going to bed . good night.~Daniel
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      I am in now, my name on the internet.... and I am an administrator woooohooooo! ~Daniel or SupaChicken
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      Daniel is now an admin. We run the site, you get to watch :-)
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      May be adding Dan to the bloggin team. That way we can both post stuf. If you're from inavale, and want to be on the team, email me at mr_mouthwash@comcast.net and I'll consider your request (I can't have 30 people running amuck on a blog!). Thanx, everyone! See you all later.  Over and Out.       ~Phil
     
    


07,May,2004


     
      Hi. This is my first post into my blog. Right now, I'm OK. Nothing to new. It's a weekend!! YAY! See you all soon! And hope to get to see some of you guys at the garage sale set-up!
     
    


14,May,2004


     
      Holy Crap!!        there u go 
     
    


13,May,2004


     
      Hey, all. This is Phil. Hi, Katie, BTW. Glad to have you on the team. So, not much to update today. People have been coming in and out of my garage dumping stuff off for the past few days. It's actually real annoying. I'm playing my  urlLink Ragnarok Online  when all of the sudden the doorbell rings and it's random people throwing stuff at me! and their all   WEAK  !!! They make me carry everything for them!   DO IT YOURSELF.  Well, not much else to report, besides this:   Dan:My cheek really hurts for no apperant reason. Maybe it is Philip's fault that it REALLY hurts for no reason I guess I am in the mood for blaming things on PHILIP.  Phil:i'd be happy to shoot you in the cheek with my AIRSOFT GUN whenever you want.     Well, cya all later!! ~Phil
     
    


12,May,2004


     
      Yeah, If i need you to do that I will know who to come too I found these pictures of Halo 2 and they are awesome. They sugest something even better about Halo2 and its Multiplayer mode I will talk to you at school I think Katie Withrow joined our team. Hope that is alright ~Daniel
     
    


12,May,2004


     
      i'd be happy to shoot you in the cheek with my  AIRSOFT GUN  whenever you want.
     
    


11,May,2004


     
      Hi every body. My cheek really hurts for no apperant reason. Maybe it is Philip's fault that it REALLY hurts for no reason I guess I am in the mood for blaming things on PHILIP Thanks Philip ~Daniel(ouch!)
     
    


11,May,2004


     
      this post is going to be  multi   colored.   i don't know why i do it like this, but it is FUN FUN    well, cya later!! 
     
    


11,May,2004


     
      Hey Everyone! I am in now! SUPER! Yea dis are funn! ~~~Luke~~~
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      love being administrator, it is fun.hehe hahahahah hahahahah ~Daniel
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      That one is better, tell me how you like it. ~Daniel
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      that works I want a different template, I will find a good one and you can tell me what you think of it ~Daniel
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      we have a new and good template now. it are fun and fun for you!!! hahahaha
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      hey,  my name is Tim,  i am not cool what-so-ever! don't mind me i will post with dan and phiip
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      Yay tim is on the team!! thats 3 so far. me and dan will still be admins, but tim can post freely. sorry that u are sick dan. yesterday was his birthday, btw
     
    


10,May,2004


     
      Wish I was too dead to cry My self-affliction fades Stones to throw at my creator Masochists to which I cater You don't need to bother; I don't need to be  I'll keep slipping farther But once I hold on, I won't let go 'til it bleeds  Wish I was too dead to care If indeed I cared at all Never had a voice to protest So you fed me shit to digest I wish I had a reason; my flaws are open season For this, I gave up trying One good turn deserves my dying  Wish I'd died instead of lived A zombie hides my face Shell forgotten with its memories Diaries left with cryptic entries  
     
    


09,May,2004


     
      I am at school right now. I probably shouldnt be posting, but it are fun to do! I'm in math class with mr. regan. Dan are sick :-( Luke says hi, btw. umm, not much to say. CRAP! G2G!!
     
    


09,May,2004


     
      Ahh... I got up late today :-) So, The garage sale setup went a lot better than I expected. We got everything setup and all we need now is actual stuff to sell. It's real exciting. Well, not musch else to say, but I hope to see you all later!!      ~Phil
     
    


09,May,2004


     
      Philip we need new bloggers Who? we can fix those pictures later, we need to get a better on of me sorry I was sick because I am really sick! I hope I get better soon. Lets change the adress and the template  ~Daniel
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      That is a great song and you should all listen to it. good, It is edited though                                             ~Daniel
     
    


19,May,2004


     
      Been a while sinse my last post. I can't seem to be able to wrtie anything, with daniel always posting pictures! whatever. it doesnt really matter, so I wont worry about it.  urlLink THIS IS A GOOD SONG AND U WILL DOWNLOAD IT  or death will engulf you in a roaring ball of demonic HECKFIRE!! AGH! cya later   TO DOWNLOAD RIGHT CLICK ON IT AND HIT SAVE TARGET AS    That is all          Phil 
     
    


19,May,2004


     
      hehe    haha    yeah....       why doesn't anyone else post anything?                                          ~Daniel
     
    


18,May,2004


     
         yeah but that isn't james bond goldeneye! HEY! ~Daniel 
     
    


17,May,2004


     
      now if we find some kind of bukeroo...   
     
    


17,May,2004


     
      I think I got it    that is right damn I am good ~daniel
     
    


17,May,2004


     
      I am going to try one more I think I got it.    
     
    


16,May,2004


     
      I figured this part out.     
     
    


16,May,2004


     
          
     
    


16,May,2004


     
      Hey guys. We have to do a Biophysical Foundations test on saturday morning. I'm not sure when... or where... well, for now i'm just going to have to leave you all with a picture... dont ask me what it says...    
     
    


16,May,2004


     
      haha, that ws really funny only you and I got it Philip. Thanks for the controller see you at school ~Daniel
     
    


26,May,2004


     
      We should have more people post things on it. Did you get the idea from the BnL blog? Tim has one, are you in it? Yeah, I get that...it looks fine but i am going to wait to play it with you                                                        ~Daniel 
     
    


25,May,2004


     
      nobody is posting... yargh. whatever! Hey all, i havent posted in a while. By the way, that Tales of Symphonia games is awesome. Gonnna buy it....
     
    


25,May,2004


     
          YAY, it worked. That looks cool                                                                                 ~Daniel
     
    


24,May,2004


     
         I look forward to fighting a formitable foe                              ~Daniel
     
    


23,May,2004


     
      me and my dad rode our bikes to staples and bought a wireless router, so I am tyrping this on a laptop that has no cords attatched!! :-O!! It are great. I can do everything that I could on our big computer on a laptop now :-D
     
    


17,June,2004


     
      How is everybody? i hope you all are having a good summer i sure am...  i love playing vidio games
     
    




