
19,May,2004


	 
      Post all of your comments and thoughts about my work here...  But PLEASE read the text before you say something about it!  *LOLZ*
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      This is the beginnings a fantasy-science fiction novel that I am working on.  If things get a little strange, please bear with me because I'm still a budding writer. (I guess)  

19,May,2004


	 
       **THIS CHAPTER WILL BE UPDATED WITH THE REWRITTEN VERSION IN A FEW DAYS**   

19,May,2004


	 
      **READ THIS ONLY IF YOU ARE ITCHING HORRIBLY TO KNOW WHAT THE REST OF THIS STORY IS ABOUT**  **NOTE THAT I AM REWRITING THE ENTIRE BOOK AND SEVERAL EVENTS THAT MAY OCCUR IN THIS ORIGINAL DRAFT MAY NOT EVEN BE A THOUGHT IN THE NEW ONE**  **ALSO, READ THIS AT YOUR OWN RISK: IT IS HORRIBLY UNORGANIZED IN MY OPINION**  **KEEP IN MIND THAT MY INSPIRATION FOR THIS WAS NOTHING BUT A DREAM AND THAT I HAD NO IDEA WHERE THE DRAFT WAS GOING UNTIL I FINISHED IT!**  **ONE LAST THING, THE PRIMARY REASON WHY I POSTED THIS IS SO THAT PEOPLE WOULD COME TO MY BLOG AND MAKE A MOCKERY OF MY FIRST DRAFT AND SEE HOW MUCH IMPROVEMENT I'VE MADE**  (Well, not entirely, but you get the idea)  **OH, AND IF YOU GET TIRED OF HAVING TO SCROLL DOWN PAST THIS, JUST CLICK THE PREVIOUS POSTS BUTTON PLEASE**  

19,May,2004


	 
      Please visit the other Blog that I've recently created.  It's at  ryu_endless_realm.blogspot.com  and it features polls posted every weekday and updated with your votes.  The subjects will range invariably but will focus mainly on some of my interests.  Please vote on these polls.  I would very much appreciate your input.  Thanks and I hope to have more writing up over the summer!
     

    



19,May,2004


	 
      I also know a choice few of you who play Phantasy Star Online.  No, this is not a net game.  It's for GameCube, XBox or Dreamcast.  (I think)  On this poll, you may vote three times, but only once in each area.   Do you have the game?   1A--"I've got it for GameCube." 0 votes (0%)  1B--"I've got it for XBox." 0 votes (0%)  1C--"No, you're not crazy.  They do have it for Dreamcast." 0 votes (0%)  1D--"Don't got it." 1 vote (100%)  1E--"What's that?" 0 votes (0%)  ----------------------------------   How's your character(s) doing?   2A--"I just started, so I'm a newbie.  (Lv 1-15)" 0 votes (0%)  2B--"I'm pretty rockin'...  (Lv 16-50)" 0 votes (0%)  2C--"I'm lovin' it!  (Lv 51-100)" 0 votes (0%)  2D--"I'll wipe all your @#%es!  (Lv 101-200)" 0 votes (0%)  2E--"I'll just whip out my Supreme Overlord!  ...Now what is this game about again?" 1 vote (100%)  ----------------------------------   How much do you like the game?   3A--"It's awesome!  I could play it forever!  Well, at least until I get to Level 200..." 0 votes (0%)  3B--"Eh, it's OK, but it gets boring after awhile." 0 votes (0%)  3C--"Ick; imitation Diablo..." 0 votes (0%)  3D--"What's it like?  I'll give it a try if it's any good." 1 vote (100%)  3E--"What in the #%@$ are you talking about?  What is all this @%#$?" 0 votes (0%)  Thank you for your votes.
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      Read the About Me portion of my profile and tell me what you think.  Post comments to vote.  A--"I don't mind a quiet, sentimental person...  Random, but quiet and sentimental." 2 votes (100%)  B--"You've got issues..." 0 votes (0%)  C--"Aww, you're such a cute little suck-up!" 0 votes (0%)  D--"You've got your problems, I've got mine.  I can accept that..." 0 votes (0%)  E--"I dare you to go parachuting or rock climbing!" 0 votes (0%)
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      School is out in Vancouver on June 23, 2004; today!  What are your plans for the summer?  Post comments to vote.  A--"I'm going somewhere far, far away where no one will ever find me.  See you next fall." 0 votes (0%)  B--"Yeah, I'm stuck here at home.  Somebody please give me something to do!" 0 votes (0%)  C--"Yeah, I'm going somewhere, but I'll still be Blogging!" 0 votes (0%)  D--"First, I'm gonna be a test pilot for that new SpaceShipOne thing, then...  Oh, yeah, I won't have any time for you guys this summer." 1 vote (100%)  E--"I've got no idea what I'm gonna do, 'cuz my friends are all gone.  So what are you doin' on the weekend?" 0 votes (0%)  Thank you for your votes.
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      I know a few of you that play RuneScape.  I was just wondering if there were any more.  Please post comments to vote on this poll.  A--"Yes, I play RuneScape.  It's great!" 0 votes (0%)  B--"Yeah, I play it.  It's OK." 0 votes (0%)  C--"Nah, it's not my type of game." 0 votes (0%)  D--"I'll try it.  How do I play?" 1 vote (50%)  E--"What the heck is RuneScape?" 1 vote (50%)  Thank you for voting.
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      I replaced my profile picture recently.  Post comments to vote which picture you like better.  A--"The white dragon one you had before." 0 votes (0%)  B--"This new green and blue, shiny one." 2 votes (100%)  C--"I never knew you had a profile picture." 0 votes (0%)  D--"I have no idea what the first picture looked like 'cuz I just now found you." 0 votes (0%)  E--"Don't know and/or don't care." 0 votes (0%)  I will update the poll as I get more votes, thanks.
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
      Post comments to vote when you think I'll FINALLY get that new first chapter posted!  A--"I know you can do it...  (1-2 days)" 0 votes (0%)  B--"I think it's gonna be awhile...  (3 days-1 week)" 0 votes (0%)  C--"I'm losin' a bit of faith here...  (1-2 weeks)" 0 votes (0%)  D--"Forget it!  You've had that message posted for almost a month!  (not before you die)" 0 votes (0%)  E--"No idea, honestly..." 0 votes (0%)  Thank you for your votes.
     

    



14,July,2004



       
       I was thinking, when this site has a few members, to suggest something to the Jagex staff. This suggestion has two parts: 1. The Runebag: This helps mages to store runes and saves inventory space. As arrows and bolts can be equiped, it's only fair. 2. Steeds: Everyone has only asked for horses so far. Why not mules, asses, mares, and stallions? That way, the poor players will have the ability for backup and speed.  If you agree with this, post your comment. Much appreciated!
     

    


14,July,2004



       
       Feel free to e-mail me if you wish to join. Currently,ALL 9 staff positions are open.  UPDATE: 8 staff positions. 2 filled. Me and Kooji
     

    


14,July,2004



       
       I would like to introduce meetings of members on this site and add eachother on RuneScape friends list. I would suggest leaving your usually visited world and your username.  I am:  Battlesuprme  World 17  Just leave your post in 'comments'. We should meet in world 17 when we reach 50 users and recruit users the entire day.
     

    


14,July,2004



       
      The triangle is composed of 3 battletypes:                   Archer,           Warrior,                                       Mage,  The type clockwise is the battletype's weakness. Eg. Warrior loses to Mage. Mage loses to Archer. Ect.  With multiple types of battle, you may be 'impure'. This means being two or three different types. You will still have the weakness of your highest skill, but you will infilct all weaknesses, depending on the weapon you currently weild.   I suggest that you keep all three weapon types: Staff, bow/crossbow/thowing knives/throwing axes, and sword/mace/battle hammer/ax. This way, you will have the apropriate tool to train ANY battle skill at ANY time.
     

    


14,July,2004



       
       This hint will make your playing experience on RuneScape a little cooler.   Become an Archer/Warrior. Have your sword or other warrior weapon out and keep bolts in your quiver. Join the pheonix gang in Varrock. Go to the weapons store and kill the weapons master(You must be lvl 20 or have mith/ammy/silverlight).  Then take the crossbows. You may wait for them to respawn and take more. Keep one and put the rest in the bank. Train your ranged to more than your attack skill if not already done.   With your sword out and leather armor, attack a mage in the wilderness or accept a challenge. Change your weapon to the crossbow(that's why your wearing leather). The mage will have an auto weakness to ranging. He will soon die.   Take the mage's items. Now, you are probably rich and strong. You will be immune to both warrior's and archer's weakness points. You now have only dragons to fear!
     

    


15,July,2004



       
       I am now able to post links! If you wish to be linked, place the URL of the link button and the site that is linked to me. If you link me and are NOT a porno site, I shall link you.
     

    


15,July,2004



       
       I, as trying to know my acquaintances better, would suggest leaving your skill lvls in the comments.
     

    


15,July,2004



       
       I am known on RuneScape in world 17. These are my names:  Battlesuprme(username)  The Traveller  The Asassin of Varrock  The Tramp(I hate this one) And I wish to be called: The ArchWarrior  You may speak of me as the Tramp. Though I would prefer the Traveller, thanks.
     

    


15,July,2004



       
       Mages are becoming ever popular, though Rangers are DESTROYING them. Here is a guide to stop that, and look good doing it....  First: All Mages MUST be able to Runecraft. Making your own runes take time but is worth it. Go to the Duke in Lumbridge Castle, second floor. Talk to him. Then, after excepting the quest, go to Draynor Village. You will find a southern path where you see a cement port. It is actually the way to the Wizard's Tower. Then, go through, talking to a bunch of NPC's to get quests. Then, back to the first floor. Use the trap door. Deliver the Talisman to the only talking NPC. Go into another room. You will see a skull. Pick it up, but be prepared: A skeleton will attack. It will disapear at 1/2 health. This is the skull from the Restless Ghost quest!First, go to the Rune shop in Varrock. Talk to the shop keeper. Give him the item. On your way to Draynor, stop by the Lumbridge Graveyard. Put the skull in the coffin to gain quest points. Then, go back to the Tower and talk to the Wizard again.   Second:Make sure you have a pick ax. And inventory space. Select teleport from either the Rune shop keeper or the Wizard. They will teleport you to where to mine.. Rune Essences!   Third:After filling up, use the portal. Then, use locate with the air talisman. It will bring you near Draynor if you follow the pull. Select 'use' when at the stones and boulders. Click on the big stone called 'Mysterious Runes'. With the talisman selected, it will teleport you to the Altar of Air.  Select to use the Essences with the Altar. All your essences will be turned into Air Runes. Congratulations! You crafted your first runes!  Fourth: At lvl 2 runecraft, kill imps. They will probably drop the Mind Talisman. Use locate and you will come to MORE mysterious runes. Select use and click on the big rock, as before. You may repeat this when your new lvl says you can craft the next type with the talisman and location of the next type.  Fifth: Now, with about 1000 runes of each type, as you may have unlimited completed runes, attack a Warrior in the wilderness. You will probably when, if it is within 10 lvls. Next, train defensively with your staff.  Sixth: Beat a Ranger repeatedly with your staff. It will count as warrior, the Ranger's weakness. You have beaten the Archer!
     

    


16,July,2004



       
      Hi y'all...  I'm KOOJI and I play runescape two... Don't  think I am good with runescape, but I'm gettin' better every day. My combat = 21  My runescape nickname is KOOJI_986  bye...  KOOJI
     

    


17,July,2004



       
      &nbsp;I haven't been on lately because my computer contracted 2 viruses. It's fixed now. I have some RuneScape playing to do! KOOJI, fill us in. Also, my ActiveX has been damned to damage, so it may be some time before I actually  do  play RuneScape. 
     

    


25,July,2004



       
      &nbsp;I am making a REAL website which I will introduce later.... The suspicion....... 
     

    


25,July,2004



       
      &nbsp;I know this is late for an update but I must tell you: Quest Journals! you now have info on what quest steps you have completed and where to start. And members: you now have hats to show how many Chompy Birds you killed! Cool, eh? 
     

    


30,July,2004



       
      These are my lvls.Keep in mind I am not a member: Attack:39 Hit Points:33 Mining:22 Strength:23 Smithing:14 Defence:22 Fishing:35 Ranged:25 Cooking:38 Prayer:22 Crafting:5 Firemaking:27 Magic:19 Woodcutting:27 RuneCrafting:8 
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      We have a logo!Just i don't know how to post it... 
     

    


03,August,2004



       
      Combat Lvl: 61 Attack Lvl: 58 Strength Lvl: 44 Defence Lvl: 44 Range Lvl: 40 Prayer Lvl: 34 Magic Lvl: 37 Runecrafting Lvl: 17 Hitpoints Lvl: 52 Agility Lvl: 06 Herlbore Lvl: 25 Thieving Lvl: 26 Crafting Lvl: 41 Fletching Lvl: 53 Mining Lvl: 49 Smithing Lvl: 44 Fishing Lvl: 37 Cooking Lvl: 39 Firemaking Lvl: 04 Woodcutting Lvl: 48  TOTAL LEVEL: 698 
     

    


03,August,2004



       
      The Logo is up!!!!!!!YES!!!!!! 
     

    


04,August,2004



       
      i need the cooking experience for "Heros Quest"  once in heros quest i will be able to get our runite ores and bars  --to get runite ores and bars i need to gain levels on mining and smithing too --this might take me a while 
     

    


04,August,2004



       
      get some limpwurt roots and give them to me... then, i will be able to make some strength potions through herblore...  -- this might be given to the pk squad -- depends on what battlesuprme says -- might take me a while to get the potions because i need the herbs for it 
     

    


05,August,2004



       
      I am currently looking for somone who knows graphics to make this site a Sword Cursor and place the code in the correct template spot 
     

    


05,August,2004



       
      Ghettosquirl, the Free Cooking and Strength potion posts belong in the clan blog. No problem, but they are better suited there. Also, please donate Bronze and Iron bars and maybe even Steel bars to Ghettosquirl. And donate logs, also. 
     

    



