
31,May,2004


     
       (Christian Milian - Thank You) I never thought these clouds would come along and bring me so much pain. When my world was upside down I didn't think that I could make it,  I reached out my hand for you and you were there to take it.  I wanna thank you for being my strength when I thought I couldn't go on.  And I wanna thank you for showing me right when my heart was leading me wrong  for all the times I was lost and my soul was blind.  I didn't know what to do.  Somehow you pulled me through -  and I wanna thank you.  When I was down and feelin' low, looked up and you were there - somehow you knew and found me.  You were the answer to my prayers.  You shined a light when it was dark.  And opened up my eyes.  You led the way when I was lost and you helped me realize.  I will never walk alone, cause you'll be by my side.  I don't know what I'd ever do without you in my life.  With every step I take you show me there's a way and in your hands, my heart  will never go astray. So each and every day I wanna thank you    Happy Birthday Mummy!! ^^  *yawns* really tired..been up since 5:30...making mums brekkie...heheh..really simple stuff...toast..jam...cuppa tea...didnt really wanna wake anyone up =/ more tears from both of us again =*) really shoulda got her something..but i think its the first time in a long long time since ive made her brekkie...and dad was in one of his moods =/  caught by sezza in hurrsie again..and stayed with her till 4:30 cos im 'sO nice' 

30,May,2004


     
       (ATB - 9PM [Till I Come])   happy 21st birthday benno!!   im 1 day old!! =D went to church alone today..mum went straight to aunt adas... first time i took notes in church..i figure it'll help me from falling asleep XD hehe..pastor ferguson was cool!! hmmm..applied to be a steward/deacon...hope i get it *fingers crossed* =) hafto be at church from 8-2:30 once a month though...no more sunday sleep ins 

29,May,2004


     
       (Westlife - Swear It Again) I'm never gonna say goodbye  cos I never wanna see you cry  I swore to you my love would remain  and I swear it all over again and I  I'm never gonna treat you bad  cos I never wanna see you sad  I swore to share your joy and your pain  and I swear it all over again  all over again    had the most wonderful...awesome...great...surreal...incredible... (run outta adjectives ^^;)...but most of all..blessed...day...my baptism day..was just like one huge birthday party =D  woke up with a sore throat...felt asif a hole was being burnt into the back of it =/ but things got ALOT better ^^  hadto go to tennis in the morning...it was freezing!! 

28,May,2004


     
       (Unknown Artist - Ain't Nothing Like Being With You)  listening to be bestttttttt song atm...dont know who sings it...so im naming it myself!! 'ain't nothing like being with you' it is =P theres a link on the side to d/l it hmmm...cant find anything on this song on the net...so...i wrote the lyrics up myself (very dodgily)   i like rolling with my girls, when when chilling on the late night scene out at four in the morning, yawning, but they ain't feeling me on my two way, you say you don't wanna be alone so i get dad to scrap and shake, and tell my girls im gone  (mumble jumble)  aint gonna keep you waiting all night see my friends they just dont get it, cos the club is packed and i aint withit dont wanna close the club no more, cos ive done it all before see ive been around the world, seen alot of things met the princesses, saw the kings and queens danced in france, had millions of fans but it aint nothing like being with you see i can ride all night in my droptop, nonstop beepbeep, speak when i see your cutie drop (holla holla hey) i dont wanna speak, cos it aint nothing like being with you  sometimes i wonder if you understand what you mean to me i gave you my heart right from the start, and boy you still hold the key aint no body who can take it make it, break it, fake it, duplicate it baby i made it, just for you, theres nothing they can do, this room was made for two  (mumble jumble)  aint gonna keep you waiting all night see my friends they just dont get it, cos the club is packed and i aint withit dont wanna close the club no more, because ive been through it all before see ive been around the world, seen alot of things met the princesses, saw the kings and queens danced in france, had millions of fans but it aint nothing like being with you see i can ride all night in my droptop, nonstop beepbeep, speak when i see your cutie drop (holla holla hey) i dont wanna speak, cos it aint nothing like being with you  i wanna rock with you, all night all night all night when i get home baby, im gonna treat you right see im never do you wrong, and this i know cos i could spend my lifetime, and never stop loving you (never stop never stop loving you)   jose got married yesterday...didnt tell me bout it...whatta rude boy =/ awww...all my cousins are getting married off 

27,May,2004


     
       (Brian McKnight - Every Beat Of My Heart) I want you to know  You take my breath away  And it's been that way right from the start  I didn't know how to tell you  That I want to love you  With every beat of my heart  (With every beat of my heart)    strike day!! =D got up even EARLIER than a school day 

26,May,2004


     
       (Sowelu - I Wanna Know)  gO the blues!! ripper of a game...9-8...bOOtiful 40m field goal in the 3min of extra time by Shaun Timmins..who got he man of the match..and yes...he plays for the dragons!! hornby had a great game as well =) abit sick atm...runny nose..argh!! so annoying 

25,May,2004


     
       (Color Me Badd - All For Love) I’m so glad you’re my girl I’ll do anything for you Call you every night And give you flowers to I thank the lord for you And think about you all the time I ask him everyday That you’ll for-ever be mine  I wanna hold your hand To show you I’ll be there I like to do the things That let you know I care I sing this lullaby ’cause girl you fill me full I look into your eyes You’re so beautiful  Oh girl I think I love ya I’m always thinkin’ of ya I want ch-ya to know I do all for love I love it when we’re together Girl I need you forever And want you to know I do it all for love  I will never leave you sugar This I guarantee I look in to the future I see you and me Knight in shining armor I will be your fairy tale I wanna take care of you Girl, I’ll serve you well.  I will be there for ya To catch you when you fall I’ll hold you in my arms That’s where you belong I sing this lullaby ’cause girl you fill me full I look in to your eyes You’re so beautiful...beautiful...yeah!  Oh girl I think I love ya I’m always thinkin’ of ya I want ch-ya to know I do all for love I love it when we’re together Girl I need you forever And want you to know I do it all for love  Yo-come here sweetheart I want you to know something all right See everyday in my life without you Is like a hundred years The distance between us An ocean of tears See all the things I do for you Are for love dig it  All for lovin’ (all for love) All for you (you) All for lovin’ you...you...you...you  Oh girl I think I love ya I’m always thinkin’ of ya I want ch-ya to know I do all for love I love it when we’re together Girl I need you forever And want you to know I do it all for love  Oh girl I think I love ya I’m always thinkin’ of ya I want ch-ya to know I do all for love I love it when we’re together Girl I need you forever And want you to know I do it all for love  the musics sO cheesy/happyhappy =/ but its still a nice song ^^   happy b'day Jack!!   rainy day today...its freezing 

24,May,2004


     
       (B2K - Everything)  free period first in the morning..yay for ms davis and her canberra excursion!! 8 hours sleep *droolZ* hehe..teacher strikes on this thursday and next wednesday...more sleep time XD  waaa!! its so weirD...first one of my cousins friends wanted to go out with me...and then i hear that another one thinks im hott..and now...one of the others had a dream bout me....UGH!! O.o  got caught by sezza today...was forced to spend time with her and lawren till she went tutor 

23,May,2004


     
       (The Diplomats feat. Juetz Santana & Toya - Hey Ma [Remix]) In a summer day, in the winter time When you breathe the heat, gotta make you mine And I'm liking all the things you do Can I get the chance to know you, so come on  I like it, you like it No need to front when I'm around I love it, you love it That's why you keep on starin' me down You want it, I gut it And I'm telling you that There's no need for you to be afraid I like it  Saw you walkin' by, again you caught my eye I knew right then you were the one I needed in my life    Happy Birthday Andy!!  nearly missed your surprise today in church today =P finished my baptism classes today..no need to hang round in church till 3 n THEN get lunch no more gonna 'chong lerng' next saturday...gonna be hard to get there on time cos of tennis 

22,May,2004


     
       (Brian McKnight - Someday, Someway, Somehow)  yay!! no one got angry cos i played tennis 

21,May,2004


     
       (Allure - You're The Only One For Me) I had to leave behind a dream that could be mine  I thought that I would never find  Someone who's heart could read my mind  Now I don't have to hide cause you are in my life  I promise you that love won't be easy  I promise you there'll be times apart (apart)  But I swear that it comes from my heart  When I promise you're the only one for me  (for me.. yeah)  awww =*)  crisis seems to be over?? ruth seems to like jason..according to sandii ^^ they talked on the phone till 2:30 last night..no wonder he was complaining bout being tired 

20,May,2004


     
       (Tamia feat. Talib Kweli - Officially Missing You [Remix])   NOW!!  =P hmmm..today was a date of updates updates and MORE updates here ^^ lets see what i did: - added my lil profile bit                      - added that lil imood thingo                      - added that lil coolies phoenix sig on the sidebar                      - changed the background colour of sidebar to match the phoenix sig                      - added the scrolling marquee for the time and date...i rorted it a li bit..see if you can notice =P learnt alot more bout html n javascript today ^^ at least ive done a li more work today i guess..still not very productive schoolwise 

19,May,2004


     
       (Monica - Angel Of Mine)   yay!! starting my blog!! ^^ hmm...im just using a default layout (THANKS douglas bowman!! ^^) atm...and prolly for a long long time...not my fault im not too busy (or issit not skilled enough?? =P) to do anything 

30,June,2004


     
       (Hikaru Utada - Close To You) Why do birds suddenly appear Everytime you are near Just like me They long to be Close to you  Why do stars fall down from the sky Everytime you walk by Just like me  They long to be Close to you  On the day that you were born The angels got together And decided to create a dream come true So they sprinkled moondust in your hair and golden starlight in your eyes so true  That is why all the girls in town Follow you all around Just like me They long to be  Close to you Just like me  They long to be  Close to you   a remake of the old carpenters song i think...heapsa people have done covers of this song =)  necks a lil sore..from trying to sleep in english ^^; never knew it was so hard to block the teachers view from seeing you AND to sleep XD ...was another one of those boring lessons...where she was just saying 'shoosh' every few mintues to keep us quiet while she marked her year 7 kids work...  eco pizza day =D mew can be sO weird at times 

29,June,2004


     
       (Chemistry - Point Of No Return)  its..rednose day today!! well..at our school anyways ^^;  omgosh!!!!!!!!! i aced the eco assessment =O first time ever been at the top of a subject in something as big as this...still in disbelief!! i knew i did aight in the test...but this was unexpected...especially with only doing 1 or 2 hours of study...oh well..guess actually doing the assignment helped heaps =D why are people meanieZ to the guy who flukes the test 

28,June,2004


     
       (B2K - Why I Love You) From day one you and I've been friends. Hangin out, havin fun, chillin. Now I know at times I got crazy, silly ways and actin shady. You peep things in me that no one sees. You hold it down fo shizzy. Now I have friends I thought were true but no one more true than you. So what am I gonna do. It took a while for me to see how special you treated me  Maybe thats the reason why I love you. You're my heart girl. And wit all the crazy things that I do, you're still here girl. Noone else can meka me feel like you do. You've shared my world. Baby thats the reason why I love you.  No other girl is quite like you. And noone has my back like you do. Girl you're one of a kind and you blow my mind. And I'm glad to say you're mine. Girl you're the one that changed me from a boy into a man.  It took a while for me to see how special you treated me. Maybe thats the reason why I love you. You're my heart girl. And wit all the crazy things that I do, you're still here girl. Noone else can make me feel like you do. You've shared my world. Baby thats the reason why I love you.  I Love You, maybe thats the reason why I love you.    had quite an alright day at school...very funny day!! =D  had this weirdish substitute...for the substitute thats taking over from xena?? lol...anyways..she was totally whacked up =/ first she struglles to put the tape thingo on...like 'aww...wheres the play button...theres only shapes...' kinda like every other english teacher..so we thought it was all normal... but she was like a total primary school teacher!! when she first sat down..she was like 'GOOD MORNING EVERYONE' in one of those loud and annoying voices 

27,June,2004


     
       (Lisa - So Beautiful)  woot!! 3 wins in a row for the saints!! 52-12..caned the rabbits...going great guns =D   relos coming and going today...they...look....really...old...lolz =P i think their son is at least 30something...so theyre entitled to be old =) dinner wasnt exactly the best..that restraunt down at punchbowl just keeps getting worse =/ at least aunt agnus said i had gotten 'thinner'..hahaha...im getting less obese!! hehe...caught up with some of the gossip going on in st george with wynnie...sharing gossip ^^ did get harrassed a lil though..oh well..at least shes gotten over the whole amy thing =/ lil wendie was freaking me out!! 

26,June,2004


     
       (Goo Goo Dolls - Iris) And I'd give up forever to touch you 'Cause I know that you feel me somehow You're the closest to heaven that I'll  ever be And I don't want to go home right now  And all I can taste is this moment And all I can breathe is your life 'Cause sooner or later it's over I just don't want to miss you tonight  And I don't want the world to see me 'Cause I don't think that they'd  understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am  And you can't fight the tears that ain't  coming Or the moment of truth in your lies When everything feels like the movies Yeah you bleed just to know you're alive   *yawnZ* tiredness...its not even 10 yeet as well!! the more sleep i get the more tireder i am?? =/  ahh..no tennis..today...or for the next 4 weeks!! =D well..no comp...still have training...hopefully the mornings arent gonna be too cold when i train in the holiz =/  mums biggest bro n his family are coming over from hk tomorrow...gonna have one big 5 family dinner somewhere tomorrow =D eep..that means im gonna be interrograted XD too 'bad' samuel and his gf audrey are going to china/hk =P meeting her folks...does that mean marriage is on the cards?? hehe  lol...grandmas memory is a lil fuddled up...thought my bday was on the 29th for some reason...apparently she always gets it mixed up?? =/ oh well...early bday presents are always welcome ^^  anyhoos...its 11 and im typin here...lol...taken me at least 2hrs to type this blog out =P so...hope you feel bettter sezza n danni =) 
     
    


25,June,2004


     
       (Emi Hinouchi - Magic)   something beautiful happened to me today =)


24,June,2004


     
       (J - Confession) when i look into your eyes and see  all i see is you and me  can't you see the want within my heart?  it's all about you   love to hear you voice at night  it softly calling out my name  boy you're sending chills straight down my spine  with your caresses   you got me fiening for you love  you know you're all i'm thinking of  baby never leave me  can't you see, you're all I want oh yeah  maybe, you were sent from up above  baby, know you're all I'm dreaming of   when i look into your eyes and see  all i see is you and me  can't you feel the love within my heart is all for you baby  if you hold me in your arms tonight  boy I'll make you feel just right  stay with me, you'll never need to find another lover   my reflection in you eyes  so softly takes my breath away  boy you fill me up with your sweet love  there is no other   yea recognize looking in your eyes i get butterflies us together brings an end to my lonely cries daydreams and smiles i feel your style i see our future as we headed for the extra mile treat me like a lady officially your baby keeping the brain hazy lovesick and crazy what you think honey, keep it going yo true confessions with the ladies  if you take me home with you tonight boy i'll make you feel just right baby stay with me you can trust me baby  ...maybe change 'boy' to 'girl'..hehe  omgosh!! dogged by cheungy!! 

23,June,2004


     
       (BoA - ID; Peace B)  she actually looks aight in this vid..although a lil retarded at the end =P  2 test back today...not so good =/ i knew i stuffed both the tests i had on the tuesday up badly... oh well...at least 2u was aight... failed 3u..and chem wasnt that good as well 

22,June,2004


     
       (Hikaru Utada - With Or Without You [MTV Unplugged]) See the stone set in your eyes See the thorn twist in your side I wait for you  Sleight of hand and twist of fate On a bed of nails she makes me wait And I wait without you  With or without you With or without you  Through the storm we reach the shore You give it all but I want more And I'm waiting for you  With or without you With or without you I can't live With or without you  And you give yourself away And you give yourself away And you give And you give And you give yourself away  My hands are tied My body bruised, she's got me with Nothing to win and Nothing left to lose   finished downloading the 'Making of Hikaru Utada unplugged'..and they were talking bout this song...added the morning before the first japanese MTV unplugged show was to start...so i went and found the clip of it i downloaded a while ago...its a cover of the U2 song... hmmm...you get to hear hikki talk a lil in english in the clip...shes got pretty good english...guess she hadto since she did graduate in the US...first english album should be out now...havent seen it for download =/  omgosh...damn alex 

21,June,2004


     
       (Do As Infinity - Field Of Dreams)  HAAAAAR!!!! go the saints!! kicked those hapless tigers 50-0!! bout the only piece of good news today...  ms abson was all down when she walked into class..which is really weird cos the dragons kicked ass =/ all 9 of us figured that her husbands best mate simon died...she told us a few months that he had been diagnosed with cancer...that had spread everywhere...after he was found driving out somewhere with no reason or idea why...he had scans done...and found that he had tumors all over his body... put a real dampener to the end of the day...guess cos its only a small class...and shes like the best teacher...we all feel more closer to her?? i think he died on...tuesday..or wassit friday arvo...not sure..found a tumor at the base of his brain early last week...and his body started to shut down soon after...its tragic...he was prolly only in his 30s...already a daughter whos 9..n a son whos 5...apparently david...her husband is still in disbelief...gotta hurt so bad at the funeral on wednesday...heh...at least he was catho =*) prayers go out to all...  stupid me stuffed up BAD today!! 

20,June,2004


     
       (Brian McKnight - Could) Lying alone in my room Don't know what I'm gonna do Trying to figure out If this is it this time Just can't stop thinking About the way you make me feel inside I just can't get you off my mind No matter how hard I try  Could you be the one for me Could we dance the night away I wanna give you everything Though I don't have much Could you fall in love with me Could you love me the rest of my life Could you forever be The one for me, this time   =S feeling sick...again!! i guess those late nights for assessment week werent all that healthy =/ got somethin swollen in my throat..so everytime i swallow something..it hurts real bad...cant eat that much no more!! 

19,June,2004


     
       (The Brilliant Green - Rainy Days Never Stays)  aww..morgans wrist is stuffed up..cant use his double hander 

18,June,2004


     
       (Daz Koz feat. Brian McKnight - Love Changes Everything) summer changes to fall winter into spring seasons come and go but love changes everything   its over!!!!!!!!!!! =D went to school for the 40min written test..hehe...went okay...3 n a quarter pages with my relativly small writing =) had a mental blank in the middle of it...missed out bout a paragraph of the stuff i prepared =/ oh well...at least its over...they gave us own draft trial timetables =/ sooOOOoooo gone 

17,June,2004


     
       (Fatboy Slim - Praise You)  its nearly over!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! one more day..one more test...bring it ON!! fully pumped!! =D maybe its the fact that i really want that arvo nap thats waiting for me tomorrow XD  today was..pretty fun!! well...at least assessment week has gotten better from killer tuesday 

16,June,2004


     
       (Usher - T.T.P.) Somebody tell me Why do people stay in situations that'll never work Thinkin' bout you wanna leave and  You can't wait to get even When deep inside it really hurts I never should of ever got in the mix You'll never understand till you go through it All the rights things to say Wrong things to do While you're out tryina pick and choose  You should be lookin' for a TTP Now that I know the difference That's all I'm tryna be with Somebody that keeps it all in together now I'm living better Since I found the total package  So many people think They got it - but they don't have a clue You gotta have more than just a body For me to be talkin' about you oh Take it from me when playin' the game you're day will come When you gotta stop what you do  and start lookin' for the one   hehe..im home already!! ^^ todays assessments went through alot more smoother than yesterdays =D was karking it for eco last night..cos i didnt study everything last night =/ lucky the test didnt specific the parts i didnt study =P so i managed to write about 3 pages..which is pretty good i guess...average wouldve been bout 3 and a half...i reckon i did pretty well..but some people sounded asif they really ripped it 

15,June,2004


     
       (Youjeen - Where Do I Go)  assessments were totally bad 

14,June,2004


     
       (Westlife - Close) Across the miles, it's funny to me How far you are but how near you seem to be I could talk all night just to hear you breath I could spend my life just living this dream You're all I'll ever need  You give me strength You give me hope You give me someone to love, someone to hold When I'm in your arms, I need you to know I've never been, never been This close  With all the loves I used to know I kept my distance, I never let go But in your arms I know I'm safe 'Cause I've never been held and I've never been kissed in this way You're all I'll ever need, you're all I'll ever need  Close enough to see it's true Close enough to trust in you Closer now than any words can say   hmm...i worked out how to do the wallpaper thingie so it wont take forever for 56k ppl to download XD ive just been using the same image and resizing it using html...but i figured that it would just be alot easier if i upped a smaller image just for the link ^^; so yea..thats the wallie im using atm..its very blue =)) and its got that coolies 3D crystalish kinda thingos =P ive also worked out (yes..2 brainwaves in one day!! XD) that by the time i leave the house tomorrow morning at round 9:15..i wouldve spent more than 113 hours at home!! HAHAHAHA....i have no life =(  R.I.P. dannis glasses =*( lolz...they were tragically crushed on saturday muimui?? you poor thing..maybe thats why you cant find a formal date..cant see them all..ahahaz *wonders how many more dirties youre gonna give out* =P   ive got chem and ext1 math exams tomorrow..thank God that chem is based on the assignment we've done...just gotta have a good read through it ive 'studied' bout 3/4s of the math thingo atm...really just going through the excerises in the textbooks doing a few questions here and there...im sO not ready for this assessment week..my marks are all gonna depend on the night before cram sessions 

13,June,2004


     
      hey justin readers! *waves* well after much whining justin being the nice person he is and all.. has given me a invite to his blog! *feels special*..  but now i have nothing to say..=( well ill like to wish the techies the best of luck on their assessments!! especially if they are doing the 'journey' in english like justin whose doing a flower!! hehe ok latahs!  
     
    


13,June,2004


     
       (Fragma - Everytime You Need Me)  hmm..we have a new guest...or maybe appropriately should be called a 'gate crasher' =P  hehehe danni...welcome!! lotsa huggz   EDIT: hmmm...i worked until 4...and im totally gooOOOooone atm... stupid word died on me at 10..and didnt autorecover my document =( took me 6 hrs to finish all the eco essay....and im supposta write it in an extra within 40mins 

12,June,2004


     
       (Aaliyah - Miss You) Now you’re gone and I’m lost without you here now  But I know I gotta live and make it somehow   Come back to me (to me) Can you hear me (Callin’)  Hear me callin’ for you (For you)  ‘Cause it’s   It’s been too long and I’m lost without you  What am I gonna do? Said I’ve been needin’ you, (said needin' you,wantin you) Wonderin’ if you’re the same and whose been with you  Is your heart still mine, I wanna cry sometimes I miss you  Now I’m sittin’ here thinkin’ ‘bout you  And the days we used to share  It’s drivin’ me crazy, I don’t know what to do  I’m just wonderin’ if you still care    i think dads gonna pull the phone cable out soon 

11,June,2004


     
       (Andy Hunter - The Wonders Of You)  my net got zapped!! 

10,June,2004


     
       (LL Cool J feat. Amerie - Paradise) If you need me baby i’m, for, real The rest of your life, I’ll take you to paradise.. If you want it baby just, be, real The rest of your life, I’ll take you to paradise I’m gonna give-a-you all my love, yeah  If you need me, just call me Said if you want me, just be for real And if you like me, come and talk to me And if you want me, tell me how you feel   lolZ @ allan...very wear a bra today XD hehehe...mightve been worth it for $50 i guess...especially when they paid for the bra =/ so...how does wearing a pink wonderbra feel like?? ;)  aww..the front of my 'neighbours' r34s kit got ripped off O.o mustve gone too fast over a speedhump...the middle part of its missing as well as the grill...poor thing... not even sure if its my neighbours car..i think it belongs to those gangsterish guys who sometimes live at my neighbours house =/ oh well..at least they still have a civic type r n paseo to fall back on  yayz..got tomorrow off =D good luck to all those peepz who have got legal...ext english...ipt and jap ext... sO lucky i got the day off...can hopefully finish assignments =D  grrr @ my dad atm... my coach dean is going away for the long weekend so hes gonna cancel tomorrows lesson...but dad still wants me to go have a hit tomorrow -.- seriously...ive already had a hit on tuesday...im not playing on saturday...and ive got assessments next week with no time to study cos i havent even finished any of my 3 assignments... friggen...yea...its only '1hr' of hitting...but usually with you it ends up to be 1.5hrs of useless hitting and not the mention the time its takes to go to and from the courts...thats like 2-2.5 hours -.-  O.o comp blacked out for a sec...and then my modem died...i think telstra got zapped XD hehe..i hope everyone doesnt hafto spend their night without electricity...especially all you dudes doing assessments tomorrow =) and..also to the scardy catz people who are afraid of lightnin and the dark =P hehe..*hugZ* you all..dont worries ^^
     
    


09,June,2004


     
       (Namie Amuro - Come)  just got back from the dentists..havent been there for awhile ^^; he found the lillest hole in my tooth...otherwise...ive got really nice n healthy teeth =P hehe...was kinda zoning out/half sleeping during the first bit =P but then he started to go crazy with the teeth cleaning thingo that felt asif it was stabbing my gums O.o and then there was the uber fast toothbrush thingo...and they he gave me more than enough fluoride...was like dumping heaps in and not spreading it out =X at least it tasted niceish..strawberry ^^  my elbow kills though...cant really bend it heaps =( hurt it yesterday at tennis...hope its not tennis elbow =/  thank God for skeg and karkass...now i have hope of finishing my assignments by the end of the week =) and my cough is almost gone..things are lookin up ^^
     
    


08,June,2004


     
       (Brian McKnight feat. Justin Timberlake - My Kinda Girl) When I was younger I never went too far hung my feelings I never even wanted to start til when I met you I didn’t know what you were gonna do with my heart  when you talk I hang on every word you say when you move its like the breeze on a summerday when you smile the sky turns from gray to blue that’s what you do and you' re the kinda of girl I think of and you're the kinda of girl I dream about my heart is telling me I need you in my world(in my world) cause your my kind of lady your my kind of girl  when i'm not with you wherever you are baby i'm counting the moments till im back in your arms all I want is to have you here with me every night every day   

07,June,2004


     
       (FC Kahuna - Glitterball)  i think my baybee danni muimui is doing work exp this week?? sorwiz..havent talked to you in ages =( aww..you get to go to uni even before me...esp to the gifted and talented faculty =P hehe...anyways..wishing have a great week!! =D  arrghh 

06,June,2004


     
       (Human Nature - When You Say You Love Me) Now youre moving closer to me  And our eyes have connected emotionally  Not looking for a one night stand  Or a place for a broken heart to mend   I know everybody here wants to hold you  I know what its like cause I feel the same  When you look in my eyes theres a part of me thats still afraid   And when you say you love me, do you mean it?  Baby when you hold me, do you feel it?  Should I believe the magic in your eyes?  I'll be waiting till the end of time To hear you say you love me, like you mean it  Baby when you hold me, make me feel it  All I wanna do is make you mine  I've been hurt way too many times   Again and again and again i've been hurt my friend till the end  And though i've been high i've been low i got no place left to go  Again and again and again when will this searching end  great song =D   Happy B'day Ken!! ^^   was puffing while walking/rushing to the train station in the morning..maybe i should go see a doctor =S  been looking through some of those university prospectus's...hmm..i kinda know what im kinda aiming for now...the UAC gives you 9 choices...so my 9 choices with their 2004 UAI cutoffs atm would be: 1. UNSW BA Commerce (96.00) 2. USYD BA Commerce (95.05) 3. UNSW BA Economics (93.00) 4. USYD BA Economics (91.05) 5. UNSW BA Information Systems (90.00) 6. USYD BA E-Commerce (87.95) 7. Macquarie Economics/Commerce Course (Somewhere in the 80s) 8. Macquarie Economics/Commerce Course (Somewhere in the 80s) 9. USYD or UTS or UNSW IT/Software course (Lower 80s)  hmmmz...theres a few more eco/commerce course for UNSW n USYD...cept that theyve got the same UAI cutoff as those ones...so theres really not that much point in putting them in... gawd...why issit sO hard to get into uni 

05,June,2004


     
       (Tom Novy feat. Lima - Without Your Love)  yay!! its my day off tennis!! and next week is the queens bday =D been sitting here writing up the chem summaries for that 10 page booklet they handed out on the solvay process...sulfur and soaps... its sO st00pid..its not even worth anything...i guess its just to make sure that we read the booklet..so they can test us and not hafto answer any complaints bout not reading the booklet or whatever and thats only half of the chem assignment...hafto find info on galvanic and silver cells or whatever...i think i lost my sheet 

04,June,2004


     
       (Goo Goo Dolls - Slide) Could you whisper in my ear  The things you want to feel  I'll give you anything  To feel it comin' Do you wake up on your own And wonder where you are  You live with all your faults  And I'll do anything you ever Dreamed to be complete Little pieces of the nothing that, fall Oh May put your arms around me What you feel is what you are And what you are is beautiful Oh May do you wanna get married Or run away   my school photos came back the other day 

03,June,2004


     
       (Hikaru Utada - Hikari)  hmm..this is the song she remade to do 'Simple And Clean'..the kingdom hearts theme ^^;  athletics carnival..woke up and it was raining...hoped sO badly it was on so i wouldnt hafto do that eco essay...and thank God the carnival went ahead =) track was still wet...and i nearly missed my 100m...was playing cards ^^; went down and luckily the 8th lane was open...mullholland misfired the starters gun 3 times -.- sO bloody nervous by the time he actually got it done...got off to a good start compared to the others...ronron was too fast for me all the way though...was haning onto 2nd till the last 20 or so when mark caught up 

02,June,2004


     
       (Jamelia - Thank You) The fights, those nights I tried to pretend it don't hurt The way, I prayed Someday that you would love me Really, completely Just how I wanted it to be But no, so wrong Can't believe I stayed with you so long  You hit, you spit, you split, ever-y bit of me, yeah You stole, you broke, you're cold You're such a joke to me, yeah  For every last bruise you gave me For every time I sat in tears For the million ways you hurt me I just wanna tell you this You broke my world, made me strong Thank you Messed up my dreams, made me strong Thank you  My head, near dead Just the way you wanted it My soul, stone cold Cos I was under you're control  So young, so dumb Knew just how to make me succumb But I un-derstand To make yourself feel like a man  You coulda had it all babe It coulda been so right I woulda given you everything Morning through night Yeah, you taught me some lessons Those are my blessings That won't happen again Thank you    same song title...so much more venom =/ still...nice song ^^  today was the second strike day...bah...totally wasted 

01,June,2004


     
       (Overseer - Supermoves)  first day of june...and its pretty cold 

31,July,2004


     
       (Aya Ueto - Tears)  been a lil moody today =S things havent turned out as planned i guess?? well..they never really do... well...i think tonights the night of amy lins bday party..down at ashfield or something for red...hehe..hope everyone stays safe..and takes it easy on the pills..booze n bongs =S  lost my singles today...taking it too easy ^^; ah well..cant complain that i lost...if i put in a lil more effort mightve come up with the goods..ah well...at least i won both my doubles..hehe..had sO much fun today...me and julian pretty much fluked a win in the boys...no idea how we won..hes sucha nice boy..hehe...fillin in for me in 2 weeks when i gotta go do my hsc speaking for jap...ah oh..andrea!!  didnt even know she was playing today..arrived 30mins late =P anyhooz..yea..had heapsa fun playign with her..shes like...funky?? actually has a go most of the time and talks?? haha...total hott euro babe =P kinda like christine.....  had the fattest headache a few hours ago..hadto go sleep it off...  hmm..as i thought...gonna attend a wedding end of this year =D samuel (mah cousin) proposed to audrey during their trip over to china/hk...mum thinks it was in shanghai after he met her parents..hehe anyhooz...this has kinda put me into a lil tight situation 

30,July,2004


     
       (Babyface - When Will I See You Again) When can my heart beat again When does the pain ever end When do the tears stop from running over When does you'll get over it begin  I hear what you're sayin' But I swear that it's not making sense So when can I see you  When can I see you again When can my heart beat again When can I see you again And when can I breathe once again And when can I see you again  When does my someday begin When I'll find someone again And what if I still am not truly over What am I supposed to do then  Please hear what I'm sayin' Even if, if it's not making sense So when can I see you  =*(  i heard dean...yea...hammertime!! of all people snapped it in PD today...the skips were all being too loud..and he was trying to work..and he goes 'WHY DONT YOU ALL JUST SHUT UP' =S people stressssssin cos of the trials in a week 

29,July,2004


     
       (Emi Hinouchi - Let It Be)  *yawnZ* cant seem to get a early nights sleep these days... so run down at school all the time... day before..oh haha..i was being stupid...'burn' was playin on my winamp..and im such a sucker for usher 

28,July,2004


     
       (Vanessa Carlton - A Thousand Miles) Makin' my way downtown, Walkin' fast, Faces pass and I'm homebound.  Starin' blankly ahead, Just makin' my way, Makin' a way through the crowd.  And I need you, And I miss you,  And now I wonder...  If I could fall into the sky, Do you think time would pass me by?  'Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles If I could just see you...  Tonight.  It's always times like these  When I think of you,  And wonder if you ever think of me.   'Cause everything's so wrong And I don't belong.  Livin' in your precious memory.  'Cause I need you, And I miss you, And now I wonder...  If I could fall into the sky, Do you think time would pass me by?  'Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles If I could just see you...  Tonight.  I, I, don't wanna let you know I, I, drown in your memory. I, I, don't wanna let this go.  I, I, don't.   Makin' my way downtown,  Walkin' fast,  Faces pass and I'm homebound.   Starin' blankly ahead, Just makin' my way, Makin' a way through the crowd.   And I still need you,  And I still miss you,  And now I wonder...   If I could fall into the sky, Do you think time Would pass.. us by?  'Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles  If I could just see you...   oh oh  If I could fall into the sky,  Do you think time would pass me by?  'Cause you know I'd walk a thousand miles If I could just see you.   If I could just hold you.... Tonight.  watched iROBOT today!! =D some of the effects were heaps good...but..was kinda dissappointing somehow...damn..will smith is sO buff...hehe..i guess he provided a lil bit of humor to the movie still..substandard..i didnt think it was that good =/  gosh..i think the world is coming to an end!! =O people are going inSANE!! as we were walking out of the escalators this chick jumps out in front of me and sez 'hey..my friend wants your number' *shock horror* =O lol...took a glance..and cos other people were pushing up behind me...started walking off =S tam said after..they said something like 'ohh..azn..think ur too good eh??' well..nO actually..i dont think im good enough!! hmmm..at least its gotten the guys a lil more creative...besides the normal 'studd studd *touch* tsssss ouch studd studdddd joke' =/ now theyve got the...'the girls that sit facing justin are straight' and..'look at the girls going in orbit round justin' blah!! i dont think imma gonna hear the end of this one 

27,July,2004


     
       (TiA - Ryuusei)   HAPPY BIRTHDAY DANNI!! ^^ *collaspes* i think ive said it enough for one year =S =O you know what...the florist lady was real nice!! gosh..i went to the same store last week...and some other lady was there...and she was tryin to rip me off!! *hmph* =/ oh...felt sO stupid walking thru hurrsie with that stuff 

26,July,2004


     
      *sings*   happy birthday to you happy birthday to you happy birthday dear DANNI!! haappy birthday to you hiphip HORRAY!! hiphip HORRAY!!   hehe..by the time i get thise posted itll be your birthday =) ..happy 16th hun *MWAH*  saw the grossest thing in english today..st00pid dean *traumatised* hmmmm..anyhooz today...oh...i was in hurrsie..and no..i didnt get slapped!! HUZZAH!! haha...but skeg was saying these lebo guys were looking at my jersey and then having a look at me 

25,July,2004


     
       (Fragma - Take My Hand)  dogged by the guys at church today..they all went missing after the service...so i ended up finding zita and ting who were talking bout hsc n stuff...hehe...tings so worried bout her esl english...but her english sounds pertty good..dont see why it should be a problem..and zita was all confuzzled bout it cos she didnt do esl last year..kinda acted as the interpreter cos my broken canto aint good enuf...english n cant mixed together 

24,July,2004


     
       (Brian McKnight - You Should Be Mine [Don't Waste Your Time]) Can't understand how he can treat you The way that he does Give me the chance to show you baby You're better off with me Girls: Oh so baby let me try, I wanna make you smile Brian: I wanna love you like you need to be loved Girls: I'll never let you down, I'll always be around Brian: And you should be mine  If he don't love you right, don't waste your time If he don't treat you like you should, then you should be mine  Why can't you see you should be happy And I don't know why You don't believe a man can love you For the rest of your life Girls: Oh so, baby let me try, I wanna make you smile Brian: I wanna love you like you need to be loved Girls: I'll never let you down I'll always be around Brian: And you should be mine  Girl, come into my world I'll love you the way that you need to be loved No worries no more, girl open the door And don't waste your time 'Cause you should be mine   hmmm...not a good day at tennis =/ lost every set i played *sighZ* and guess whos cut at me and pulled my net cable out at 1o3o?!?! =( i reckon i put up a good fight...lost 4 n 2 in the singles...hadto play up a seed cos morgan couldnt play...think he mightve reinjured his left wrist... ahh well..so i hadto play ben..whos like a pretty funny bloke...haha...we were both playing..heaps good when the other was playing craphouse...and fully laughing at some of the shots we came up with =P anyhooz...i came on the court with my raquet..and left it holding cairens...lol..broke the strings of both my raquets in the 2nd set =/ must be hitting the ball too hard =P hahaha..nahz...just bad luck i guess =/ andrea didnt play today..ive got some feeling shes avoiding me..lol..always pulling out..although..she is a notorious lazy bum...always turnin up 3omins late most of the time =/ hehe...at least it gave me a chance to get to know mia...hehe...i thought she was older than me..turns out shes in year 9...at st vincents...where danni was gonna 'go' =/ hehe shes such a nice lil chikka..got a coolies grunt as well =P prolly hits it harder than me half the time with that huge backswing 

23,July,2004


     
       (Cyber X feat. Tomiko Van - Drive Me Nuts)  blah..still dont wanna work..and the trials are gonna start the week after next?!?!  

22,July,2004


     
       (Christina Milian - Someday One Day) Day to day and each night I pray that this ends  That there's someone out there that's gonna melt my heart away And take me to another place From the loneliness that's driving me insane  I get so cold summer feels like the winter When I'm at home, all alone I just cry I wish that I could just lie like I'm happy But I can't hide this hurt inside  But I tell you someday I'm gonna find A guy that's gonna change my life And I tell you one day just wait and see True love is waiting out there for me  I'm like an open book just trying to turn the page Feels like I'm trapped in a maze trying to find my way Oh my heart's yearning for someone to call my own And I don't wanna sing another sad love song again  I get so cold summer feels like the winter And not a full moon of gloom that just cried? I wish that I could just lie like I'm happy But I can't hide this hurt inside  Take me away, away Far away, away Take me away So far away, away  Someday  uh...yea =)  everyone is totally weird today =/ somepeople are talking bout the weirdest stuff...like alex n changy..and then shero n everyone else in the channel tonight...and sezza n lawren =S  okay...im tired...really tired..been tired all day..been bumming round all day...dont wanna do anything..havent done anything...well...we went to kfc during the free period...and...someone stole a footy today..im kinda limping round atm..knee hurts real bad =/  oh...congrats with tam gettin his ps...uh..well i think you did...can never tell with you =/ 
     
    


21,July,2004


     
       (Kelly Chen - Star)  today..flew by =/ was only at school for 3hrs though ^^; were making soap in chem...and as i was taking a photo of skeg i forgot to turn the flash off 

20,July,2004


     
       (Usher - How Do I Say) How do I say, Hello I just wanna talk to you How do I say You're beautiful And I can't take my eyes off you I don't wanna say the wrong thing I wanna use the right words to impress you My baby, How do I say, How do I say?  I want you...Te deseo I need you...Te necisito Can I have you?...Tienas quesa mijo? What must I do?...Que nejapa sera? What is your name?...Como te llamas? So beautiful...Beles tu hermosa Can I take you?...Puerto tonierte? So precious...Ton precioso I love you...Te amo   we got our jerseys today!! yay =D just umm...copping alot of flak for mine 

19,July,2004


     
       (Ruppina - Free Will)  i hate jason!! 

18,July,2004


     
       (Hillsong - To The Ends Of The Earth) love unfailing overtaking my heart you take me in finding peace again fear is lost in all you are  and i would give the world to tell your story 'cause i know that you called me i know that youve called me  ive lost myself for good within your promise and i wont hide it..i wont hide it...  Jesus i belive in you and i would go to the ends of the earth to the ends of the earth for you...alone are the Son of God and all the world will see that You are God that You are God  mmm..i think this song touched alot of people at church today... big weekend for the lee family...yesterday ben got married to joanne =*) think theyve already gone on their honeymoon ^^ and today..cats baby nathan was dedicated to God =) didnt hafto fly all the relos over twice for it i guess =P the liller karen was at church today..havent seen her for agggggges...shes such a pretty girlie =P but..ugg boots O.o was talking to another pretty chickka michelle as well..shes been stalking me or something...apparently i live on the same street as she does?? O.o lol ohh...n pastor abraham was preaching today..hes still here after visiting from hk for the conference..that guys such a crackup..although hes heapsa powerful =D hehe..i bought australias number 1 album for last week today!! hillsongs 'for all youve done'!! =D its number 10 now though =/ haha..still kickin ass for a christian album though =P  no one was really in a talking mood today...well for the last few days..not sure why...can sorta feel tension building up again??...maybe its cos the holidays are nearly over...so i just went and played ns at night..the guys in there were a lil more talkative..prolly cos theyre alot more relaxed as uni students =/ too bad the hl WON servers are going down by the end of the month...kinda feels asif im loosing a whole bunch of friends just when im starting to get to know them... =/ msn stuffs up alot more when im playing ns...its like the incoming alerts dont exaclty come on?? like the thingo doesnt popup =/ hmmm...well...some chickkas were talking to me..haha..guys are alot more reclusive i guess...so hard to ns and chat though...not sure if i should just close ns..when they arent really talking bout the most important thing...or if i should not talk to them at all and have fun n play games...or..if i should try n do both...having laggy responses...which is prolly worse =/  ahh well...better get to sleep soon..might as well study tomorrow seein that ive mostly wasted all the other days...
     
    


17,July,2004


     
       (M-Flo - Come Again)   im officially in love with this song!! lisa's vocals are so damn smooth here...verbal doesnt rap as much..and takus at his best mixin his stuff  happy 81st bday ah por!! wishing you have continuing tiptop health and remain your lovely bubbly self!! =) hehe..had the whole family gathering thing again at aunt mays (piccies are up!!)...hmmmMmmm...every single saturday weve had a family gathering =D porpor was givin out red pockets?? lol..arent we supposta be giving her the presents??   haha...anyways..it was a great night out...everyone was alive this time!! the grown ups were playing their mah jong...cept wynnies dad peter...he was entertaining stephanie by playing scarbble with her..haha..had a camera war with wynnies digicam and andrews mobcam...lol...i swear wynnie wants to get photos of me to sellem to her friends or something =/  was a great night...nights like this..i guess i really appreciate the whole big family atmosphere...cos my ones pretty small...and i get to have time with my cousins and aunts...dont get to do that much...kinda puts into perspective somethings...ive got a pretty big and supportive family really...and i guess theyre all very loveable..cos even though their family..they can all be pretty good friends as well..people i can have fun with =D  wonder why amy doesnt take her bf to family gatherings =/ theyve been going out for yonks now...hmm...engagment soon?? ohhh..that reminds me...ms abson aka abO told us bout how her husband david (hes also a languages teacher down at caringbah) proposed to her..it all sounded pretty romantic...  they were on a trip to bali together...and one late arvo...before theyre gonna go out...hes all fussying over what clothes shes wearing..like 'oh...your wearing those shoes *frowns*..and that shirt?? get the other one on..' and yea..stuff like that..and they finally get out onto the busy street and trying to get a cab down to the beach..and theres all this traffic going round and they dont seem to be able to get a cab...until david finds this one taxi driver...and talks to him in indonesian (lol..pays to be a languages teacher i guess) and the driver goes fully crazy fast and gets them down to the beach a lil before sunset..and as the suns setting...david proposes (can hear all the girls saying 'awwwwwWWWWwwww' =P) and yea..the rest is history??   lol... after...she asked him wouldve happened if they didnt get to the beach in time to watch the sunset...and he said that 'he wouldntve have asked her..cos he took it as a sign' =*)  hehe...hmmMMmm...youre all wondering why we talk bout this stuff in jap class?? lol...ummz...abO was complaining bout how her older sister got engaged and didnt tell her first but instead told all her friends and THEN rings up and says 'ohh..pam..im getting married to so-and-so...sorry i havent told you..you arent angry are you??' XD LOL...i really think abO got pretty cut up bout that...haha...so you all remember to tell family first bout your engagements =P still doesnt really explain why we get so off topic in jap class does it?? *shrugs* =P 
     
    


16,July,2004


     
       (Lisa - Move On) There's a better love for me So I'm gonna set you free There's no looking back to see Gotta life ahead of me  =)  gosh...blogger..you can go suck some big donkey balls!! (haha..ur lucky you host my blogg for free =P) the supposeded 'upgrade' of the site aint working...lol...this stupid user friendly crap aint working for me...the whole thingo isnt user friendly and i think its made blogging even HARDER!! the whole layout is so ugly..cluttered and muddled!! not to mention hard to use!! 

15,July,2004


     
       (Hikaru Utada - Addicted To You [Up-In-Heaven Mix])  kk..i get a big *FAIL* today...if it wasnt for tutor..wouldntve studied at all...but ah well...it was worth it..people come first =) aww..sezza...dw bout your flight back to australia alone in the next few days...10hrs in hk airport cant be that bad...hehe...lotsa window shopping can be done =) stupid aussie embassy ppl =/ just give the boy a visa so he can get back and study =P glad to see you feeling better danni!! ^^ and..yea...im always here for all you guys...i havent got much of a life..but its fine *sobs* XD  hmmMMmmm...kk..not being modest here...but i reckon im a pretty nice guy (whoopwhoop..look whos got tall poppy syndrome =P)...lol..anyways...yea...i reckon im pretty aight with the people im friends with...i dont backstab or nothing...if i do do any kinda stabbing...itll be in the front lol...'cos frontstabbing is what friends do!' =P  so..my problem?? umm...im pretty good friends with people that my other friends dislike...and sometimes hate =/ sitting here thinking..why am i sO nice?!?! ahaha..but seriously...it kinda hurts when i hear bout people bitching really badly bout my friends..i feel pretty damn guilty when i laugh...and even worse when i join in 

14,July,2004


     
       (SugaBabes - Run For Cover) When blues, got me down Then I, get turned around I tend to, cut myself off From things, I shouldn't run from  It doesn't really matter Sometimes we run for cover I'm always on the outside  Stabbed me in the back Wanted things that I lack Sticking to your ploy Is this something you enjoy? Publicity and insecurity  Just wanna be me It's my need to be free  It doesn't really matter Sometimes we run for cover I'm always on the outside (on my own) You never seem to wonder How much you make me suffer I speak it from the inside  Looking right at me (at me) Won't receive my plea (my plea) Tell me what you mean (you mean) I'm not what's on the screen (oh-oh) Faking what will be (will be)  Fighting the fatigue (fatigue) That's quite enough for me (for me) Makes me wanna scream (scream, scream, scream, scream, scream, scream)  Keep it to myself (Keep it to myself)   *sighZ* tomorrow beings my study reigme for the trials n hsc...and if i start slacking off please tell me off and get me back to work 

13,July,2004


     
       (As One - Fortunate)  =) getting better day by day...somepeople are being the biggest sleepy heads though *cough* tam n simon *cough*...well...simon did ns with me for about 30mins...hehe...we won that game!! =D hehe....had alot of luck in ns today..most of my teams were pretty good =P funniest thing teaching 'marinehunter' to find the secret room in one of the readyrooms...templar and aephyr had him convinced it was a simple jump into the wall when they were just f4in' once they the the wall...roflz...rinehunter mustve tried jumping through that wall at least 50 times...haha oh..and some people take games too seriously/personally...gosh...im sorry im shit at the game..no need to get all pissed and personal bout it..rizzo n grim n cal had a lil thingo going today...somepeople are so up themselves cos theyre rich... bah...playing crap is one thing...but exploits n cheatin is another...cant stand it when people get away with that crap...and all just for the sake of winning..tsktsk anyhooz...i think thats as much ns as im gonna get this holiz...stopped me from working once i got home from school...  hehe..oh..school was heaps good..haha..never thought i'd say this but im actually glad i went to school today..got lotsa done..not sure how much ive actually learnt...but its all good...at least i got some work and study done..most of all..was a pretty fun day out...everyone came...tets...ibi..tom...dean..tomislav..alex...mark and jason..hehe..just being able to get out a bit and talk made it alot better...and ms absons always like the funnest and bestest teacher =) had pho for lunch!! mmMMmmm...jason was normal this time and ordered pho as well =) ive got piccies...hmmm...if i have time tomorrow..i might puttem up and stuff...  the house stinks atm...that chinese vomit medecine stuff O.o dad just doesnt like conventional normal medecine so he hasto stink the house up 

12,July,2004


     
       (Usher - Can U Help Me) Ooh Why Ooh Why Ooh Why  Living on the edge out of control And the world just won't let me slow down But in my biggest picture  Was a photo of you and me  Girl you know I try I work hard to provide all the material things that I thought Would make you happy  I'm confused can you make me understand Cause I try to give you the best of me  I thought we were cool maybe I was blind But never took time to see  Can you help me Tell me what you want from me Can you help me  Tell me why you wanna leave Baby help me Without you my whole world is falling apart And I'm going crazy  Life's a prison when you're in love alone  Ooh girl I love ya I need you to come back home You know I need ya  I don't wanna be alone  Girl I put your love Up on the shelf And I guess I just left it to die Now we're not together  Cause I hurt you too many times And now you're not around  I wish for every moment of time that got wasted We used it to make sweet love Baby be my guide please take my hand Want you to know that I got ya If you need it Don't want to be on the outside looking in  I gotta have you girl can't you see  Can you help me (can you help me) Tell me what you want from me Can you help me Tell me why you wanna leave Baby help me Cause with out you my whole is falling apart And with out you I think I'll go crazy Life's a prison when your in love alone  Oh girl I love ya  I need you to come back home You know I need you  I don't wanna be alone Baby would you please listen to me Oh  Please stay don't go I don't want you to go Give me another chance I wanna be your man  Girl you've got me  Down here on my knees  Crying begging pleeding  I'll do anything  For your loooove  Oh Oh Ooooh  Would you Help me (help me) (Ooooh) Tell me what you want from me (help me) Can you tell me (yeah) I don't understand I'm just a man (Just stay don't go I don't want you to leave) Help me Baby help me Without you my whole world is falling apart And without you girl  I'm going crazy  Love's a prison without your love Can you help me  Tell me Why(why)Why(why)Why(why)Why(why) Can you help me Girl I'll never stop cause your all I got (Please stay don't go I don't want you to leave) Can you help me (yeah) Help me understand I can't be your man  It's drivin me crazy (crazy crazy crazy) Oh baby oooh oooh oooooh no no  Ooh girl I love ya (I said I love ya girl) You know I need ya (ooooh I need ya) Can't live without ya (I can't go a day without ya) Ooh girl I love ya (oooh girl I need ya) You know I need ya (oooh no no no) Can't live without ya (Without cha) Ooh girl I love ya (oooh no no no no no no no) You know I need ya (no no no no no no no) Can't live without ya (no no no no no no no no no no) Ooh girl I love (If you understand) You know I need ya (Can you help me out, sing along) Can't live without ya (eh eh) You know I need ya (hey baby)     never felt a pain like this    danni..go to sleep!! i kinda had the feeling you were gonna camp out for my blog last night...so i hope i didnt keep you waiting too long..thanks though..i know you care =)    if only i could tell u...    its funny...cos last night...i found myself actually wanting to leave the house...after wanting to come home desperately at dinner...and...it mustve been past midnight or something...and i was looking outside...just wanted to take a walk...seemed pretty peaceful out there...with the ground wet.but it wasnt raining...but was kinda freaked out that a aze murderer or something wouldve come out to chop me or something ^^; another thing was...when i finally got into bed...i really wanted to get out on the tennis court to have a hit...and thats pretty weird..cos normally youd hafto drag me kicking and screaming onto the tennis court...oh and...i had this urge to go out and play a few tournments..havent done that for awhile as well..iunno...not like i want to add to the trophies...i think my trohpy days are over...i guess i really do like the sport...just dad gives me too much pressure bout it...ah well...coaching on wednesday...get to beat the ball up abit then    dont wanna hurt u...    im feeling alot better today..guess just doing work kept my mind off everything...well...that was until after dinner..then i started to play games...and that gave my brain time to wander round a lil...feeling more n more crap now =/ feeling quite weird atm...i mean...i wanna get outta the house...but i know that with other people i'll just make them feel crap...but i dont wanna exactly wanna be alone..but i also wanna?? haha 

11,July,2004


     
       (Emi Hinouchi - Painful)  dont read this if you dont wanna feel sad...cos it might =/  im feelin like a retard atm...iunno why...had a great night yesterday at rice...besides the running up and down chatswood to find alex n simon...was quite fun seeing how other churches do stuff though...making new 'friends' =) and this morning was aight..got to see everyone at church...mum was heaps sick though...couldnt get out of bed to go to church...so i hadto train it...just hasto be a cold n rainy day..n shittyrail just hadto have no trains from townhall to wynyard... big ben and joanne are getting married next saturday...not sure if we're going to it though...the united theme for all the christian churches in australia seems to be looking out for everyone and seeing who we can bless instead just focusing on us cos that was the main theme at hillsong conference apparently... oh..and i got a picture of the cutest baby alive...hes got the chubbiest pair of cheeks =P    


10,July,2004


     
       (Mariah Carey & Brian McKnight - Whenever You Call) Love wandered inside Stronger than you, stronger than I And now that it has begun We cannot turn back, we can only turn into one  I won't ever be too Far away to feel you And I won't hesitate at all Whenever you call  And I'll always remember The part of you so tender I'll be the one to catch your fall Whenever you call  And I'm (And I) truly inspired Finding my soul (Finding my soul) there in your arms (There in your arms) And you have opened my heart (Have opened my heart) And lifted me inside by showing me yourself undisguised  I won't ever be too Far away to feel you And I won't hesitate at all Whenever you call  And I'll always remember The part of you so tender I'll be the one to catch your fall Whenever you call  Ooh…ooh…ooh…ooh…ooh…  And I will breathe for you each day Comfort you through all the pain Gently kiss your fears away, yeah Mmm, you can turn to me and cry Always understand that I Give you all I have inside  I won't ever be too Far away to feel you And I won't hesitate at all Whenever you call  I won't ever be too Far away to feel you And I won't hesitate at all Whenever you call  And I'll always remember The part of you so tender I'll be the one to catch your fall Whenever you call  Oh, yes Ooh… Whenever you call Whenever you call   its saturday!! and i still havent finished my english assignment 

09,July,2004


     
       (Tension - Our Story)  the saints lost =( 28-14...and theyre all getting injured as well =/ ahh well...next week against the roosters!! =D  hmmm...does stress make people more angrier?? cos i reckon it is 

08,July,2004


     
       (Jay Z feat. Foxy Brown & Babyface - [Always Be My] Sunshine) Touch me with, a heart of gold I can't go a day without my sunshine Touch me with, a smile of gold I can't go a day without my sunshine, sunshine   *yawnZ* tiredness...been out on the run pretty much all day and im losing my voice =(  met up with everyone at hurrsie station...cept alex n jason werent there...and we get the call that his car is 'overdue for service by 6months n 400kms'..so he 'aint risking it' and he was gonna get his mum to drive them out to the ct... me simon skeg tam gavin and lawrence walked to market ct...and there werent any good movies so we just had lunch at mamas kitchen =) we had bout an hour to waste so we hit the arcades...me tam n simon played wartrans or something...its so hard 

07,July,2004


     
       (50 Cent - In Da Club)  yay!! im 17!! =D hehe..lotsa hugZ n..er...kisses to all you people out there ^^ especially all those peepz actually did something eXtra special... danni..being the firstest *mwaH* sezza..sendin that sms all the way from europe *mwa* simon shero jason alex changy dodo n all the boyz...thanks guys..one big non homo HUG going out to yaz =D n to all the family..mummy..daddy..aunts..uncles n all my relos =)) love youse ALL!!  hehe...also..thanks to the blues!! making it a great night!!! 36-14 over the queenslanders and winning the series 2-1 =D especially the dragons boyz...all had great games =D hehhe..thanks to the queenslanders for not spoiling the night i guess ^^;   mmmmm..bday cake ^^ dad was nice enough to get a bday cake for me...now im feelin fat!! XD  17..hmm..not really allowed to do anything that i wasnt last year...still cant go to pubs...cant drink...cant go paintball =S only thing prolly is getting my p's...which i don plan to get till next year XD  relos safely back in hk =) ..just dogg my bday why dont ya =P   blah..the whole day couldnt be perfect i guess...found out that stephanie got mugged the other day =/ she was working at the front counter all by herself cos the chinky owners are too tight to employ anyone else...and two chicks come in..one talks to her and gets all her attention...and the other one just walks into the backoffice and goes through her handbag..took her bankcards n cash 

06,July,2004


     
      hellos! well its.. 9.39a.m!! n i was  first  to wish justin a happy birthday! ^^ n it about 5 hrs? until justin is officially seventeen!! hehe hes getting old! anyways ill be off! best wishes huns.. love you heaps xox.   
     
    


06,July,2004


     
       (Namie Amuro & Verbal - Lovin' It) every day every morning I thank the lord above for the  kindness of your love  every day every morning I thank the lord above for the  tenderness of your love of your love...    ive been lounging round all day..but i HAVE gotten some work done =)  hehe..thanks for the early bday thingo danni ^^ wuv you as well =)  ur post hasnt turned up?? i'll quote ^^   heya 16 year old! *waves* next time ill post you'll be OLD! *points and laughs* seventeen.. =D love you anyways.. your still baby justin googoo to me =P.. xox.      Posted by danni to Pieces Of A Dream at 7/6/2004 09:13:30 PM  
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      lil quiz tam showed me...   urlLink   :: how jedi are you? ::   =O im offended..troublemaker..me?? never!! =P
     
    


04,July,2004


     
       (Hikaru Utada - Distance) I wanna be with you now (I wanna be with you right now baby, that is all I want yeah) Cuz I know this can't be forever We should stay together, just you and me I wanna be with you now (Nobody but you in my life) --Near or far--  I wanna be with you now Keep it going Keep it going don't stop Don't you ever let me go (Near or far)   its almost 5 and ive done no work at all ^^; sezzas gone over to other parts of europe..getting away from evil lil bitchy cousins...baibaiz ^^ im supposta go to hillsong conference tonight with skeg...sorry mate...mum sez i better not go...hafto kinda choose between rice n conference...so yea =/  hmm...last night at 'punchingbowls' =/ i caught mum trying to get the goss on me =O when i got there...mum was already there and she was talking to wynnie poo..and they looked n laughed at me 

04,July,2004


     
       (Mercury 4 - 5 Years From Now) Tell me what you are;  tell me who you’ll be  When the summers gone  and all the autumn leaves have fallen  What you gonna do, what you gonna do  Will it be someone else’s game you’re playing?  Why is that you need, tell me about your dream  Tell me when your childhood fantasy have blown away  Who’s to say you and I are here to stay  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you recognize my face in a crowd?  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me about the girl you wanna be  Will there be a place in your heart for me  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Say you will, say you will  Holding you tonight, movin’ in the dark  Time is moving faster then the world is turning  So I need to know, what is on your mind  The future seems as distant  As the sun that’s burning bright  Could it be that I’m, frightened that I might  Give it all away for souvenirs of yesterday  Who’s to say and I are here to stay  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you recognize my face in a crowd?  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me about the girl you wanna be  Will there be a place in your heart for me  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Say you will  5 winters have came and gone  And forever don’t seem to long  Will you wanna reach out for me?  Or will I be your memory  Of everything that your not now  I know that I got to stop now  You've got to tell me what’s up now  Please  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you recognize my face in a crowd?  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me about the girl you wanna be  Will there be a place in your heart for me  tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you recognize my face in a crowd?  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me about the girl you want to be  Will there be a place in your heart for me  tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you recognize my face in a crowd?  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me about the girl you want to be  Will there be a place in your heart for me  tell me where you be 5 years from now  Will you love me, still want me  Tell me where you be 5 years from now  reminiscient of last night =P  speaking of the party..changys parents werent all that happy when they came home late =/ apparently we could only have 'chicks or alchie'...one and not the other...awww...that means we cant have afterparty there =(  ive been bludging all day =/ was supposta go to lunch with mum and the relos...but cos grandma wanted to go...i err...got kicked out of the car 

03,July,2004


     
       (Move - Stay With Me [Groove That Soul Mix])  *yawnZ* im home ^^ sneaking in a post before i go to bed... today was the party at changys place...the day started off a lil slow...but it progressively got better =D and..i did not drink a drop of alchie =) and i indirectly stopped simon from drinking...well..while i was there...cos i made him drive me home =P  hehe..i got to simons place at like 11:3oish...when he wasnt even awake...so his nice mummy let me in ^^ bummed round playing games n stuff...and trying to sort out what was happening..lolz and unlike what some people say..i did NOT sabotage anyones msn...i was simply quoting =P  anyways...we dropped simons dad off at work at 4ish...and dropped over to my place so i could get a jacket...guess im not as hott as i though i was ;) =P and then we went to pickup lawrence...and went back to simons...we played ns while he had a shower... yay!! i actually did okay...won a game =) and pwoah!! lawrence...2vs1...skillz!! then...roden n alex turned up...and we went to hurrsie to meet up with changy...roden n alex went with alexs mum...while we went to pickup shero...lolz...in the end..we still got to dan murphys before alex XD thats where they decided what alchie they wanted...and changy got his sister to buy it for us...but some tight storelady saw changy with his sister and wouldnt let them buy any of it cos she 'knew he was gonna drink it and he was underage' so then we hadto go to theos...where changy stayed in the car!! =P changys sister drives so fast...simon had trouble following..hehe...well i guess 'heaven' is kinda a lil hard to get to...since everyone calls changy 'god' ^^; everyone was kinda hungry by then...and since its not good to drink on an empty stomach we went to maccas...me so...sheridan and roden all got into simons car and off we went to south hurrsie maccas... i cant believe simon didnt crash on the way..lol..cos we were pumping mercury 4 '5 years from now' and we were all 'singing' it really loudly XD  we brought the food back to changys...and jason was parked outside the house..just sitting in the car with his gf =/ was he trying to pretend asif something was going on?? lolz..cos changy had a look after and said the seats were lowered...but err...its jason?? XD hehe..anyhooz...after we finished eating at changys place..we started to play a few card games...i never lost so i didnt hafto drink ^^; mussa drove kwoka paul n sandii over...lolz...we found out while jason was at tutor..kwoka spent all day stirring shit with ruthie...sandii even had photos to prove it =P was played..umm..'jip' i think...i lost once in that...they were gonna make me take a shot of johnny O.o but shero took it for me =) oh...btw..smirnoff smells so bad...its like metho =/  the couples moved into the living room and had some quality time to themselves =P we got bored in the dining room so we moved into the living room...played assa n stuff...then the couples moved out...haha...first jason n ruth sat on the stairs of the house...but they came back in...and paul n sandii went into changys room O.o feel sorry for changy lolz...i dont think hes gonna ever sleep in his bed again XD hmmMMMmmm..lawrence also went to sleep after drinking a bottle of that red stuff...but...he wouldntve been in the same room as paul and sandi...and we had a peek in changys parents room..he wasnt there...and the only other room there was his sisters room...and she was in there O.o  went outside after that...shero went to dip his head in the pool to wake himself up lolz... and he was running round the outside of the pool to prove that he wasnt drunk..genius 

02,July,2004


     
       (Boyz II Men & Chante Moore - Your Home Is In My Heart) Even from across the sea (So far across the sea) I can hear you callin' me (Baby, come to me) Destiny controls the air (No matter where you are) Dream and dare to love again (Your home is in my heart)  I know the way I feel about you will last Oh, yes, it's gonna last and stand the test of time So your search for love is about to end Your future holds a place where true love begins  No matter where you are No matter how far you go I'll be there   ive been lazy with my bloggin today =/ people getting pissed tomorrow...im gonna feel weird...standing there with all these drunk guys round me =/  anyhooz..was LIED to 

01,July,2004


     
       (S.E.S. - Tell Me)  'be yourself day' today...otherwise known as 'being socially unacceptable day'...some people are sO whacky XD brrrRRRrrrr...i was being the socially unacceptable asian...was sO cold in my boardies n surfie gear..all i really needed was a boogie/surf-board to make finish the look...n maybe some of those wetsuit shoes..or flippers!! lol quite a few guys dressed in skirts n stuff...was sO wrong 

10,August,2004


     
       (Jimmy Eat World - Sweetness)  math 2u really wasnt that bad ^^ i could actually attempt each question..though i reckon..ive already lost bout 10 or so marks from sillymistakes and stuff...at least the test is outta 120 =P worrying bout roden and alex 

09,August,2004


     
       *RECAP*   (Mikuni Shimokawa - Tomorrow) WEEK OF TRIALS TOMORROW!! =O *breathes in* *breathes out* 

08,August,2004


     
      my aunt died
     
    


07,August,2004


     
       (Eagle Eye Cherry - Save Tonight) well we know i'm going away and how i wish - i wish it weren't so so take this wine and drink with me let's delay our misery  save tonight and fight the break of dawn come tomorrow - tomorrow i'll be gone save tonight and fight the break of dawn come tomorrow - tomorrow i'll be gone  there's a log on the fire and it burns like me for you tomorrow comes with one desire to take me away  it ain't easy to say good bye darling please - don't start to cry 'cause girl you know i've got to go and Lord i wish it wasn't so   huzzah!! go the dragons!! 34-14 over the storm...to make up for that embaressing loss to the cowboys =X jason ryles must be the best prop out there...mobile..heaps good defence..always taking on the line...gets the offloads...and can play 5/8th!! lol..he laid on a try for simmonds playing a first receiver =D  mums back!! she didnt cook last night though..lazy arse got takeaway =/  the whole suit thing is finalised!! blah...bout time its over...got a 100 reg coat and size 80pants...sounds very fat?? need to buff up or fatten up to 'fill' it XD omgosh...someone called when i was in the change rooms..was like...err..hi...you wouldnt believe where i am atm... XD i saw changys sister today at hurrsie ^^  ruthies going to america for awhile now...take care and have a safe trip!! might see you sometime in the holidays =)  not feelin so good atm..tiredish..and a lil sickish =S
     
    


06,August,2004


     
       (SugaBabes - Overload)  trials... ...are... ..hard 

05,August,2004


     
       (Maaya Sakamoto - You're Not Alone [Yubiwa - English Version]) I've waited for so long I can't remember- Where was my home? Their distant faces fade away I'm always on my own I can show a smile, It's not hard to do I can have the strength to go on But sometimes I wanna let go of everything When the thoughtfulness is not their game I teach by giving love High mountains seem higher endlessly when they're pebbles at your feet And if you should still fall into despair, there is one thing left to believe I lie in your heart always  Nothing is braver than honesty, my life is your faith in me  I'll be there when you need You don't have to hide from me What you are feeling now I fill your soul  We will seek together destiny Troubles have an end We will carry on hand in hand You're not alone  People searching desperately outside themselves, Caught up in thinking of what never helped And I'd forgotten too that love exists inside of me as in Those that I wanted from I feel you now  I'll be there when you need We will live together Nothing is in our way With trust in our soul  We will seek together destiny Troubles have an end We will carry on hand in hand We won't forget we have each other  Love is in the heart of all man You're not alone  maayas got such an angelic n soothing voice =)  well..yesterday was supposta be my big study day..cos i got home early from school..ended up staying up till 2 to finish a few study notes and stuff...at least ive got my english speech finalised... so what happened to those hours of planned study?? well..life..and people happened... first...was tam...he umm...fulfilled one desire...but...it ended up making him feel even more empty?? hmm..iunno..hes a very weird boy...tried to talk to him and all...but he cant ever lose an argument...and he doesnt like to accept other peoples point of views..and the thing he wants..is like..totally unreasonable...well...its pretty ummm...impossible i reckon...ahh well...he prolly just needed someone to talk to... and then...people start asking me physics questions!! i dont even do physics..even if it WAS year 10 stuff...dont remember doing that kinda stuff =/ ah well..helps to have friends who do physics =P do i look shifty?? cos dezza came and asked if i knew where to get new phones outright..great..outta all the people in church..i look like the one most likely to be shifty 

04,August,2004


     
       (Joey Yung - Lovin' You)  hmmm..i thought her last name was leung?? LOL...ah well..not really into her music..but this song is in my head for some reason...  my room is a MESS!! ive just been moving the mess from one place to the other...when im sleeping..the desk and floor is a mess..when im awake..the bed and floor is a mess... cos i dont even bother to unpack my bag these last few days when i come home..and when i have..just been throwing everything onto my bed..and..then...by the time i go to sleep...after 12..im all too buggered to pack anything up..so i just shove it all onto my desk ^^; been packing my bag in the mornings the last few days =/  ah well...2 days till the start of the trials...4min english speech..ive finished that!! just gotta memorise it..and a 3hr jap test..listening/reading n responding/written...gotta study that...im like..illierate at jap..dont know ANY of my vocab 

03,August,2004


     
       (Usher - Burn) I dont understand why  See it's burning me to hold onto this I know this is something I gotta do But that don't mean I want to What I'm trying to say is that I-love-you I just  I feel like this is coming to an end And it's better for me to let it go now than hold on and hurt you I gotta let it burn  It's gonna burn for me to say this But it's comin from my heart It's been a long time coming But we done been fell apart Really wanna work this out But I don't think you're gonna change it I do but you don't Think it's best we go our separate ways Tell me why I should stay in this relationship When I'm hurting baby, I ain't happy baby Plus there's so many other things I gotta deal with I think that you should let it burn  When the feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of ever being with someone else But you know that it's over We know that it's through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  Sendin' pages I ain't supposed to Got somebody here but I want you Cause the feelin ain't the same Find myself callin' her your name Ladies tell me do you understand? Now all my fellas do you feel my pain? It's the way I feel I know I made a mistake Now it's too late I know she ain't comin back What I gotta do now To get my shorty back o0o o0o o0o o0oh Man I don't know what I'm gonna do Without my bo0o You've been gone for too long It's been fifty-leven days, umpteen hours Imma be burnin' till you return (let it burn)  When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn (let it burn, let it burn, you go girl) Let it burn (gotta let it burn) Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know its best for yourself but you Hate the thought of ever being with someone else But you know that it's over We know that it's through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  I'm twisted coz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (o0o0o) I'm twisted cuz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (yeah)  o0o o0o o0o o0o o0o o0o0o o0o o0o o0o0o (can ya feel me burnin'?) o0o o0o o0o o0o o0o o0o0o So many days, so many hours I'm still burnin' till you return  When the feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of ever being with someone else But you know that it's over We know that it's through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn   just got home not long ago and im *buggered* and ive got tennis soon x_x i wored out that ive had 11hrs of sleep in the last two nights...on monday..was up till 2 doing my english essay...and last night was up till 1 doing my english speech was sO gronked this morning...lucky we werent doing much in english..slept through that and rool call =P and then..at lunch..we had 7-a-side soccer on..i got to play this time!! but..we lost 2-0 

02,August,2004


     
       (Chemistry - Two)  just got home not long ago...bus drivers take too long for their smokos =/ aww..thanks for hanging round hurrsie danni..you had credit!! =O! got to catch up on all the goss with sezza =P sorry for dogging you guys earlier...was eating with changy alex roden n tets...those guys can be sO slack..just coscos..i have friends!! 

01,August,2004


     
       (Hillsong - Free) would you believe me if i said That we are the ones who can make the change in the world today would you believe me if i said that all of the dreams in your heart can come true...today... would you believe me if i said that life could be all that you want it to be ...today...  and if i had wings i would fly cause all that i need You are and if the world caved in around me to You i'd still hold on cause Your all that i believe and the one that created me Jesus...because of You i'm Free  would you believe me if i said that God can make miracles happen today would you believe me if i said that you dont need to wait for the answer before you step out in faith would you believe me if i said that nothin is ever impossible...for God  just live your life with God inside you won't regret one moment of it and give all that you can for God, for God   best hillsong song?? =D skeg sez it makes him drive faster =P gosh...mark was sO obessed with it when it first came out...even recorded it onto his phone to listen whenever =P since its so good..imma uploading it for a week or 2...   urlLink Hillsong - Free (Right Click + Save)    parents went car shopping today...they decided to buy another civic...a GLi sedan in satelite mist...



