
28,May,2004



       
       urlLink G4TechTv  The new Channel launches today. Click above for the link.  
     

    


26,May,2004



       
       urlLink Is There going nowhere? GameSpot  There Inc., the people who brought you there, are thinking about stopping their consumer service. Guess we will know in 90 days. :(  
     

    


25,May,2004



       
       urlLink ThinkGeek :: Swiss Memory USB  I thought this was cool.   
     

    


23,May,2004



       
       urlLink |The Sims 2 Videos|  Just found this. The E3 movie for The Sims 2. Looks cool.  
     

    


23,May,2004



       
      Here is a new screenshot for Microsoft's Zoo tycoon 2.  
     

    


21,May,2004



       
       urlLink Spongebob MovieTrailer - Large   Here is the new Spongebob Movie trailer. It's not much but at least it is something. :)   
     

    


20,May,2004



       
       urlLink The Webby Awards: 2004 Nominees & Winners   The Winners of The Webby's have just been announced. Click the link to go to the page of Winners and Losers.   
     

    


20,May,2004



       
       urlLink ATI Radeon X800 Hands-On Preview   Here is Gamespot's review of the new ATI cards and how they will hold up to Nvidia's GeForce 6.   
     

    


20,May,2004



       
      Here is a new screen for "The Movies" game. Kinda looks like The Sims 2. :)   
     

    


19,May,2004



       
       urlLink |Nintendo DS|   Click above for the official site for the DS. Be sure to watch the Gameplay videos. 
     

    


19,May,2004



       
      This is a new idea for ekyygork.com. We hope you enjoy.
     

    


30,June,2004



       
      Japaneese toy maker takara(makers of Bowlingual) has made a machine that lets you control your dreams. Will retail in th US for about $140... Here is the press release.   urlLink Dream Workshop    
     

    


29,June,2004



       
      The New Trailer for the "Spongebob" Movie is out! Check it out at the link below.   urlLink Spongebob Movie     
     

    


03,June,2004



       
      Sorry for the delay in updating. Here is a link where you can win your very own Gmail account! The odds are 1 in 43,200... But who cares; it's free. lol (The most I have gotten is 4 correct)   urlLink Gmail Randomizer    
     

    


03,June,2004



       
       urlLink Tamagotchi Connexions   There is a new Tamagotchi coming out soon to the U.S. It is is already in Europe and Japan though.   
     

    


02,June,2004



       
       urlLink OQO Video   urlLink OQO Site  Above are the links for the first OQO video and the official site. If you haven't heard of OQO, It is a full computer that fits in your pocket.  
     

    


31,July,2004



       
        A new design just was released for the DS. The new design will replace the bland squareish caseing. The links are below.   urlLink  http://www.nintendo.com/ds/index.jsp  


11,July,2004



       
      Just found this on gamespot! The DVD edition of the upcoming Maxis game! Really cool. Preorder at the link below.   urlLink The Sims 2 DVD Edition with Bonus! | EBgames.com     
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      Check out the only true Google mirror! lol   urlLink elgooG    
     

    


04,July,2004



       
      I was searching google and came across two more gmail contest sites! Here are the links.   urlLink Free Gmail Invites   urlLink Gmail Guess the Number      ps. If anybody has a spare Gmail invite I still need one. :)
     

    


04,July,2004



       
      Just tried this. Amazing fun. Try it.   urlLink Geocaching - The Official Global GPS Cache Hunt Site    
     

    


04,July,2004



       
      Apple just announced their biggest cinema display ever. A redesigned 30 in. flat panel. Check it out at the link below.   urlLink Apple - Cinema Displays    
     

    



