
27,May,2004


	 
      "More you fight more you lose"     Today was boring....got my comp fixed....modem fixed.....lan line fixed....network connections to all the other comps in my house fixed....really boring...   
    


26,May,2004


	 
        Lovely day,wish I could see the world like this...oh wait I do see.....  Rain....Cooling Sun.....Burning  Rain+Sun.....Cool sunshine or Boiling rain  Raindrops....So fast I can't see what it actually looks like Sunshine..... Beautiful  Sunshine+Raindrops.....Beautiful Glitter  Rain......Causes deiseases by collecting crap on the way down Sun.......Causes skin cancer  **SIGH** I wonder how I changed my OWN attitude...  Used to be a 'Yeah....everyone is going to die....YEAAAA!!!!'  Then more like... 'Everyone is going to die? really?'  Now like 'die lah die lah....so what? we all got to die anyway...' 
    


24,May,2004


	 
      PHRASES of the day... 25/4/04 "Life is an examination hall,we are here to take a test,we can't leave till the test is finnished" 26/4/04 "If you don't piece together a broken heart you'll lose it"          I took the what colour is your heart quiz at http://quizilla.com/users/xdeadxstarx/quizzes/What%20Color%20is%20Your%20Heart? /    and guess what...Its blue... go read it if you care...  And to think I fell in love twice with the same girl once....Sigh............     Benjamin owes me $9.50 Rajen owes me $4.40
    


24,May,2004


	 
      I'm becomming cheerful.....this is wierd....
    


23,May,2004


	 
      Nothing much to day... ended up 3rd in class and 6th above all normal(A) students and I'm the only guy in the top 10 of my class.....and also the only guy in the top 10 of the level.....so I ask myself.....what did I do to deserve this? hmm? Nothing? no...I prayed....  Benjamin Wong owes me $12.50 now Lim Ding Jie owes me $2 now... Rajen still owes me $4.40.... Amos owes me   Previously  $16.50 $4  ....And also found out that scienticts can mind control animals now.....    
    


23,May,2004


	 
      24/5/2004  THE QUESTION  "What is Morality? Why do we need it? Is morality always correct? Can you tell people what morality is? Do people want to be moral? Is it bad to be moral?"  THE ANSWER  "Morality is WHAT I SAY IS RIGHT!,WE NEED MORALITY TO BE LOVED BY OTHERS!!!,Morality is not always correct,NO because the mordern society is filled with NON-MORALS!,No all human kind never wants to be moral,NO NOT AN ACTION OF MORALITY IS BAD!!!   THE PHRASE  "To be 100% sure someone loves you, you'll have die first"     
    


23,May,2004


	 
      M  Wait wait wait wait wait!!! where the hell are we? F  Right where we're suppost to be! M2  huh? and whares that? F  82nd street loosenville M  huh? there aint no signboards here know! F  yes I know....lossenville is some where in the desert! why would there be any signboards? M  ....yea...right.... M2  wait...whats that?  Tanks roll by...  M2  thats 2nd armor battalion... F2  why r they here? F3  they are attacking the northen stretch of Mandoi... M  MANDOI???!!! WHERE THE HELL ARE WE? F  lossenville...north loosenville F3  ...uh huh....wait till they see our little pet...  Opens flap covering camara  K  So Ameli... A  WHAT?!  K  why are we going to some ones house again? A  BECAUSE HE HAS A LAB IN HIS BASEMENT ANd...    The thing growls...and bites the cage    K  AND WE BETTER GET MOVING BEFORE THIS PIECE OF CRAP BREAKS LOOSE!! C  hey Amei? A  WHAT!!?? C  Are'nt there thousands of these things crawling around in Mandoi? A  yeah so? C  so...if those things multiply wont there be more than we can kill? A  so? C  So wont these things over run the world? A  yeah....so what? C  What do you mean by so what? A  so what as in so what if the world is over run? C  is'nt that bad? A  no...no more humans...to destroy... U  Ameli,Clair can't you keep quiet?   .....  dead silence  U  Thats better... U  So Kennily...you got any more of those shotgun slugs in your pocket? K  why? U  because if you feed it to this guy he'll stop biting the cage... K  HELL NO! U  why not its worth a try.... K  NO AND THAT IS FINAL!    Uriel stares at a girl in the front seat (not e drivers seat)  U  ...Hey Carrie why don't you speak at all? C  .....u U  hmm? C  i dono...gus 2 lzy 2 peak.. U  hmm what was that? C  berrrrrrrzzzz....sut up... U  ok ok....hey flooraze F  what do you want? U  .....never mind ( stareing at her eyes)   (amellyn) you in love or something?   (forise) hmm...by the looks of things he is...  Car stops by a house   F  Wood.... K  what about it? F  wont the wood rot? K  Hey...these people live in wood houses so be polite and keep quiet about it... F  Alright  Ameli opens the car door....  A  **YAWN**.....this is the place? U  Hell...I dono...your the navigator... K  Shut it you 2...we got a job to do...  Florise steps out of the car looking as stiff as a door  F  **owwie**...  Florise bends backwards letting her back flex....**CREEAAK** and her back creaks... then she steps out with the thing in its cage...it cahnges by growing some bones... now it looks like a ball  U  Now ain't that cute fur ball? C  c urcin? F  ball of dust... K  shut up and lets move...  Kenily opens the door and a (handsom) guy comes from his basement  G  Is that the Capping crew? K  Yeah...who are you? G  The guy who called you here K  Who is? C  GABRIEL!!! U  Gabel? C  Gabriel.... U  your boyfriend? C  No...but a friend... G  lets go down stairs if you guys want to talk...  Opens the basement door...stinks....of...dead...fish...  A  What the hell? U  what you doing? G  feeding..... U  Feeding what? G  Stuff I get from people like you....  Opening another (seceret) door...and the room is filled with cages...  K  How'd you get all the fish?
    


23,May,2004


	 
        suppost to keep this place as a "working" station.....for stories incase my comm crashes (as usual lol)  Don't think anyone in a right mind is going to read all this.....
    


30,June,2004


	 
      I got the bill cosby's comedy on my music
    


29,June,2004


	 
      I have come to a point of my life that I've been popular....  I've never been this popular in my whole life...  Its as if something has changed....  In me...   I've also come to a point of realisation... I realise much much more than I did before the holidays... some examples on how I changed and what I've learnt... : 1 Now I know the importiance of "Child spanking" ( hahaha... ) 2 I know that I was a flirt untill recently      3 I now know why teachers don't want to punish but its part of their job.... or the other way round.... The teachers want to punish but the job does not allow them to... 4 I know that I'm not strong but I'm average.... Its that most people around me are weak... 5 I'm getting weaker everyday if I don't "maintain" 6 I loss 5kg during the holidays and I'm now 58kg ( till fat  7 Girls would have as a friend........  8 mymind is filled with worries,problems and other crap 9 I'm never satisfied with my hairstyle 10 I'm more matured than MOST other CHINESE boys... However there are some... 11 I've been more mature than them scince the age of 11 12 I'm damn bloody confused in my current situation 13 I turn to god more often 14 I've got crushes ( I put crushes there for a reason... ) 15 I'm lucky or I have gods favor 16 I've also another fews chrush... 17 The importance of studying ( FINALLY!!! ) + + + + + s o  o n  s o  o n  e c t  e c t  If you are still reading, thank you for reading... please stop cause I've finnished...
    


25,June,2004


	 
      WITH MY EYES OPEN!!!
    


22,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    With my mom and dad&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jungle treking erm sort of...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    White water rafting&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Surfing&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Went shopping,Surfing,Riverrafting(Level 1,2),Body rafting,and Jungle hiking there too...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
      Me holding 5000000 Rp in Bali in the first week of june&nbsp; urlLink   
    


22,June,2004


	 
      There bowling tmr at 12..... I'm comming up with a new book/short story ............. 
    


15,June,2004


	 
      I went to NCC HQ to get some training on the M16A1 (how to Strip,assemble,Break,clean,reload,and a whole load of other stuff)  Stripping  After the command is given to strip the weapon  Satmp ur foot n shout Strip weapon (Rank)IC(in charge)Staff(staff stg)sargent(STG)Mchaet(Master STG)Sir(above master stg)  then you press the release magazine button to the right of the rifle and remove the magazine  Then cock the rifle 3 times and at the last time hold the rifle so you can see that no more rounds are remainding in the chamber(located behind the holder (looks flat and about the length of the holder)  Then turn the weapon mode to safe (located at the handle near the trigger(your thumb should be able to reach it)by pushing the line towards you  -|-                                                            / | \safe                                                         Auto semi-auto  then oh wait this is going to take a long time to write....Maybe I'll continue tonight  push the    
    


09,June,2004


	 
      to-da-yyeeee  very intersting day... went to play war games with myself when it was raining in centeral Singapore running around the back alley behind my house with a plastic pipe ready to engage...hahaz very intersting indeed I got a few cuts and bruses doing that hahahaz  Drunk 2 cans of root beer,eat 1 packet of potato chips and did 90 pushups (40 at differnt times of the day) to reduce fat intake......wierd huh?  and while running around like a crazy fool this afternoon I perposly made my NCC boots covered in mud...wierd as I say...  Love to all readers
    


08,June,2004


	 
      a good friend of mine is comming in 10 days time (18th) I hav'nt seen her scince I was 10
    


08,June,2004


	 
      FOr all the readers of this post be notifiyed that anything said has nothing to do with me even if it does       5 days in bali last week  I got 2 rings   One for a sovinior  One for giving away to someone  Someone speacial  Whos a girl  Who would have done her O-levels  Who would not have a bf  Who would not be around me for crap  Who.....ect....ect...ect    For those friends reading (espeacially the girls) Please take note the top^^nothing to do with you guys...
    


22,July,2004


	 
      &nbsp;`8.`888b&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,o888888o.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 888888888o&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 888888888o.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;`8.`888b&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88.&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88. 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88.&nbsp; &nbsp; `8.`888b&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8. 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`888b&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 88 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,88 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,88&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`888b&nbsp;&nbsp; ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 88 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888.&nbsp;&nbsp; ,88' 8 8888.&nbsp;&nbsp; ,88'&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`888b ,8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 88 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 888888888P'&nbsp; 8 888888888P'&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`888b8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 88 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888`8b&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`888'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; .8' 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888 `8b.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`8'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ,88'&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp; `8b.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8.`&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `8888888P'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8 8888&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; `88.  VCPR SCRIPT (for "Grand Theft Auto: Vice City")For play on Sony PlayStation 2Presented by BoredGamerLast Updated: 8/14/03Version 1.71Phase: Technically Complete  The following sites have hosting privileges:GameFAQs ( urlLink www.gamefaqs.com )Quotes of GTA ( urlLink www.quotesofgta.tk )  WARNING: THIS GUIDE CONTAINS EXPLICIT LANGUAGE.&nbsp; HENCE, IT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR ALL READERS.&nbsp; DISCRETION IS THEREFORE ADVISED.  IT IS BECAUSE OF THIS THE INITIAL RELEASE SHALL BE EXCLUSIVE TO GAMEFAQS.&nbsp; IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO POST IT ON YOUR SITE, E-MAIL ME FIRST.&nbsp; IF NOT, THAT'S FINE.&nbsp;  If you are e-mailing me about feedback, questions, or anything having to do with any FAQ, please send it to  urlLink Blublublublu1129@cs.com .&nbsp; If any e-mail is sent to Blublublublu1129 that does not concern a FAQ, it will be deleted/ignored, as I primarily use this address for FAQ-related stuff.  DO NOT E-MAIL ME ABOUT ANYTHING NOT RELATED TO VCPR.&nbsp; I will not answer questions on "how to's..." for any part of Vice City.&nbsp; That's what we have the fabulous FAQ/Walkthroughs for.&nbsp;  After the Monster Rancher 3 FAQ, I'm going to say this.&nbsp; If you don't have anything nice to say, don't say it at all.&nbsp; I know that not everyone is instantly going to listen to this, but if you wish to flame me for something on a FAQ, please don't even bother e-mailing because you will be instantly ignored and added straight to my e-mails' blocking lists, so that you can never e-mail me with that address again.&nbsp; Also with the last one, if you feel the need to falsely accuse me of plagiarism, please only do so if you are the author of the item that you felt was plagiarized.&nbsp; If you are not, you will be instantly ignored.  Please stop sending me files.&nbsp; I will not download them unless they are someone I know, and by this I mean someone I know -personally- like family or best friends.&nbsp; I have suspected that some files that have been sent to me are viruses (with good justification after being persecuted) and did not download them.&nbsp; This also means not to send me FAQs or any other material to critique.  Forenote: A little something concerning the order.&nbsp; I really don't care what order the whole thing goes into.&nbsp; It really doesn't matter.&nbsp; Yes, I know people can prove because they ripped the file and that's fine and all.&nbsp; The FAQ is in its complete (technical sense) form and all's well.  Despite what info is in your e-mail, I will ignore any VCPR e-mail under the following circumstances:  1) You are being an arrogant prick.&nbsp; If you act as though you are an all-knowing, I'm-always-right persona, YOU WILL BE IGNORED.&nbsp; If someone comes along and gives me information later that you had, but presents it to me without being condescending, then guess what... They will get the credit for it.&nbsp;  2) If it in any way pertains to the order in which the shows go in.&nbsp; It doesn't really matter what order they go in and almost everyone has sent me different orders.  3) You are sending me a file.&nbsp; Unless I know you (and trust you), any e-mails with attached files will be deleted without even looking at them.&nbsp; The reason for this is that people have been trying to send me viruses for the longest time.&nbsp; Just a few weeks ago, I got a message from Hotmail saying that one of their users tried sending me a virus, but they automatically blocked his e-mail before it could get here.&nbsp;  This list may actually increase in size as time goes by.&nbsp; I don't mean to sound like an ass or anything, but I've really had enough.&nbsp; It's a guide, people.&nbsp; No, it's not perfect.&nbsp; None of my guides, or anyone else's, are.&nbsp; I do appreciate corrections and e-mails with any material that can better this guide, but I do not appreciate being talked down to or seeing pathetic and asinine attempts to damage my computer.&nbsp; My computer is an eMachines, it doesn't need a virus to make it run worse.  INFO INVOLVING PUTTING MY NAME IN ADDRESS BOOKS:It has come to my attention recently that some of you out there have been putting my name in your address books.&nbsp; This is all fine and dandy by me.&nbsp; However, one, maybe more, amonst you have contracted the Klez virus (or something similar).&nbsp; I know this because I'm constantly getting e-mails sent back to me by MAILER-DAEMON and the like that certain e-mails that I didn't personally send are not going through because they have viruses in them.&nbsp; This is usually how viruses like Klez operate; they get into your address book, find a name, and begin sending e-mails using that name.&nbsp; I will say this loud and clear... CLEAN YOUR SYSTEMS!!!&nbsp; Download FixKlez or AVG Virus Scanner Free Edition.&nbsp; They're free, much emphasis on FREE, which means costs you nothing but time and hard drive space.&nbsp; You can probably find them on Download.com, if not do a Google search for them.&nbsp;  _______________________________________________________________________  UPDATE HISTORY  12/5/02- Saw that there wasn't a guide for this and seized the opportunity.&nbsp; Got quite a bit of the way through the first segment. It's 12 AM... So tired...  12/6/02-10:50 AM UpdateAlmost all the way through the first segment. -8:45 PM UpdateASCII title added.&nbsp; Completed the first segment.  12/8/02-12:51 AM UpdateGot quite a bit of the way through the second segment.&nbsp; -9:30 AM UpdateMore than half way through the second segment.&nbsp; -2:40 PM UpdateJust got done doing some Christmas Shopping.&nbsp; Tried to get the second segment completed, but have been interrupted since starting with putting the Christmas tree up and my niece coming over and all... Oh well... Started adding a little more and then I was interrupted by a phone call.&nbsp;  12/9/02-7:04 PM UpdateI've completed all of my studying for my first final exam tomorrow.&nbsp; It'll be absolutely nice to be on break!&nbsp; Changed a few mistakes that were found in the guide and gave credit to those who caught it.&nbsp; A bit of the way through the second segment.&nbsp; Not much of an update, but then again, I was studying all day.&nbsp; -10:22 PM UpdateThe special "wish me luck" update.&nbsp; This biology class has been a killer.&nbsp; I haven't failed a single college test, to my recollection, until now.&nbsp; I must pull out a good grade tomorrow.&nbsp; Added a little more to the second segment.&nbsp; Still trying to get through it.  12/13/02-12:38 PM UpdateBeen a few days since I updated this.&nbsp; I'm finally officially on Winter break, so I'm going to try to complete this guide and my Robotrek guide within the next few weeks.&nbsp; Don't expect too big of an update today or for the next few days as I have a concert, a Christmas party, and time to spend with my niece this weekend.&nbsp; Responded to all e-mails.&nbsp; So far, everyone's done a good job staying on topic with the VCPR and not e-mailing me about packages or rampages or any of that crap.&nbsp; The second segment is now complete.  12/17/02-8:08 PM UpdateSorry I waited a few days before updating.&nbsp; An e-mail I received got me thinking about something on this FAQ, and my mind is pretty much made up... Anyway, I've changed a few mispellings.  12/21/02-11:00 AM UpdateI've accepted the third part of the FAQ from someone who had started about the same time as me.&nbsp; However, since he worked hard on his as well, I accepted his portion of the FAQ.&nbsp; I'm right now in the process of correcting errors.&nbsp; Darkpowrjd's guide has been put up.&nbsp; The rest should be up later tonight.-3:20 PM UpdateCompleted.&nbsp; Some corrections made too.  12/31/02-1:13 PM UpdateI know people have sent me some corrections, and I'm sorry for not having taken care of these earlier.&nbsp; Made some corrections and added a little sidenote to the word "Jungian."  1/13/03-10:55 PM UpdateMade a slight modification to Jenny's laughing while Konstantino is chanting.&nbsp; Also changed, "your ains" to "it rains."&nbsp;  2/9/03-11:40 AM UpdateMore corrections added, and some interpretations.  6/29/03-12:50 PM UpdateAdding some stuff from e-mails.&nbsp; I've been getting a lot of stuff recently.&nbsp; Unfortunately, a lot of it was lost due to some complications.&nbsp; If you feel that your material has not been added and should, do send it back in.&nbsp; I WILL NO TAKE ANYMORE E-MAILS ON THE ORDER OF SHOWS.&nbsp; I've gotten a lot of remarks, quite a few of them overly arrogant and repugnantly cocky, saying something along the lines of, "This is the way it should be, so it has to be this way."&nbsp; Anymore e-mail on show order will be ignored.&nbsp; I've also corrected the "Plague all," chaging it to "Play golf."&nbsp; As a final note, do see the pre-FAQ notes, as I have included a list of types of e-mails I will ignore straight off.&nbsp;  8/14/03-12:00 AM UpdateJust a minor update.&nbsp; Changing one word... Heh...  8/27/03-8:25 PM UpdateI'm starting things nice n' easy, see... I've posted something more above to add to the Pre-FAQ Messages (which I'm currently thinking: "Hell... With all the shit I've had to put up there recently to either vent steam or let some people in on some no-no's that they've been committing, I may as well call it the 'Rant List' from now on.")&nbsp; Some spelling/grammatical corrections up now as well.  12/28/03-10:32 PM UpdateFixed a spelling error and added a new message and e-mail to the Rant List.  The scene on Positive Thinking was written by Darkpowrjd  Contents According to Joe-------------------------Section 1: Introduction1A: About VCPR and Pressing Issues1B: Characters and ActorsSection 2: The Script2A: Public Safety2B: Morality2C: Perception and Positive Thinking2D: My Favorite QuotesSection 3: Legal BitSection 4: Thank You and Goodbye  &nbsp; -------------------------/&nbsp; SECTION 1: INTRODUCTION&nbsp; \-----------------------------&nbsp;  1A: ABOUT VCPR AND PRESSING ISSUES  VCPR stands for Vice City Public Radio.&nbsp; There is only one show on this station, apparently... Pressing Issues.&nbsp; Pressing Issues is a debate program hosted by Maurice Chavez.&nbsp; The point is to bring radical point of views together and debate one topic.&nbsp; Of cource, each show somewhat strays from the topic and turns more into a fight.&nbsp; The best part about the program is the satirical comedy aspect.&nbsp; Each character portrays a part of our society: politicians, goths, preachers, over-bearing mothers... Each, of course, is done in a ridiculous manner, hence the satire aspect of the show.&nbsp;  One thing you should notice is that a lot of characters contradict themselves at some point or another (just a part of the satire aspect, of course).&nbsp; For example, Jonathan Freeloader and Michelle Montanius (even Maurice Chavez at a few points) costantly say that VCPR is commercial free, advertising free, and you get no blatant interruptions.&nbsp; However, they plug a lot of "valued sponsors" and interrupt the programing to beg for money (ahh, gotta love irony!).&nbsp;  1B: CHARACTERS AND ACTORS`  Maurice Chavez (Phillip Anthony Rodriguez)- The host of the only show played on VCPR, Pressing Issues.&nbsp; A retired clown and divorced man who is said to be "living on the edge", Maurice takes control of the show and tells everyone to shut up constantly.  According to jkoleck, Maurice is a parody of talk show host Ray Saurez.&nbsp; He hosted the show "Talk of the Nation."&nbsp; I will be looking into the site enclosed in the e-mail later and post some more info here on this FAQ.  Jonathan Freeloader (Patrick Olsen)- One of the people running VCPR.&nbsp; He used to be on a network station until he was fired.&nbsp; Constantly begs for money for the station with his partner, Michelle.  Michelle Montanius (Kelly Guest)- Works with Jonathan on VCPR.&nbsp; Seems to have a rather callous attitude.&nbsp;  Alex Shrub (Chris Lucas)- A state representative who uses his propaganda to give himself a positive image.  This in from ismacked:  "Alex Shrub seems to be a parody of George H.W. Bush (Shrub ---

21,July,2004


	 
      "Freedom never comes without a price tag... You'll always have to face something to get freedom, punishment , tourture , humiliation , disgrace , or even death.... But as long as you are willing to pay the price... You will always have freedom... It all begins with the choice." Gawain  "Be willing to fight for the things you think is right, even though certiant death stares you in the eye. Be willing to die for the things you belive is right. Be willing to suffer. There&nbsp;are no reasons why you must do this... Its all a choice.... You can choose whatever you like, just be willing to pay the price of your choice... and do not regret the choice you made." Gawain  &nbsp; "I do not love for sex, I do not love for money, I do not love because of charisma.... I love to be love in return; and thats all." Gawain  &nbsp; "Love,the answer on why I do that hit me like a bullet. It killed me, I&nbsp; died and lived again. And in that act of dying, I am reborn" Gawain    "I looked upon the corpse of my inner child, wondering how it came down to that, how it came down to the point of death. So I wondered... Little wonder... I was at war with myself, war has its casulties... He was one of them." Gawain  "I had a dream of my wife, she was dead, but it was all right." Max payne 
    


21,July,2004


	 
      I ask... I recieve....  God helps those who help themselves  Ask and it will be given to you, seek and you will find, knock and the door will be opened to you...  It works so well.... 
    


21,July,2004


	 
      This is just wonderful... I can't remember anything before last week.... Sunday.....  I only remember the importiant info.... Who my family is... Friends ... ABC....Teachers.... old teachers...ect  Other not so importiant info, I have lost.... AGAIN!!!!!  The first time was when I was 11 or 12.....  This is wonderful.... Just GREAT!!! 
    


20,July,2004


	 
      After so long, I finally am caught up with all my thoughts.... now its so hard to think stright.... I have to plan what to think about, because if I don't I'll go crazy....  Another one...  Because I can't think stright, I can't focus on homework and other stuff....  Time for the great thinking of nothing.... It really works  &nbsp;hahaha  Step 1:Close your eyes Step 2:Think of nothing Step 3:Lose track of time Step 4:Do this untill you've finnished planing your day or have fallen asleep...  HAHAHA 
    


20,July,2004


	 
      Hahaha &nbsp; what a question.... &nbsp; Its like ice cream; a real frozen solid block of ice cream. Its sweet and at the same time watery. Its watery and at the same time sweet. It has to be taken out of the freezer before it can melt. Blind luck is when I take it out for you.... I hate taking it out.... I really hate taking it out... I have to look through a whole freezer filled of stuff before I find it. However, it is worth the effort.... &nbsp; Eat it too fast and I'll cause you brain freeze, eat it too slow and it'll melt to water. &nbsp; But once you know how it was made, you'll find somethings you never wanted to know.... &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    


16,July,2004


	 
      Smith "Why Mr. Anderson? Why? Why get up? Why keep fighting? You should know by now its impossible to win. Do you belive you are fighting for something? Are you fighting for freedom? Are you fighting for peace? Could it be that you are fighting for peace? Perhaps love? They are all words with varibles... Only a human mind can come up with something as ridiculous as love. Why Mr. Anderson? Why?! Why do you persist?!" Neo "Because I choose to" &nbsp; Me&nbsp; +&nbsp;&nbsp; quote from the Oricale &nbsp; There are always choices given,wheather you've seen them or not they are there. But with these choices which you see,you'll have to make one, but which one, you'll have to make up your own damn mind" 
    


13,July,2004


	 
      No matter how cold and heartless the world will get, you'll always find that you are colder and more heartless than the world..... But if you see the world nice and good then you will be nicer and better
    


12,July,2004


	 
      "If you find out your perpose here is a horrible perpose, would you still forfill the perpose?" 8.00 P.M
    


12,July,2004


	 
      "We see ourselves as the way we want to see ourselves, but how is that suppost to change how other people see you?"
    


12,July,2004


	 
      "We all go through lifes hazards, some get the worse some get the better, It'll be a real problem if you are the hazard of your own life..."
    


12,July,2004


	 
      why do love? For romance? For sex? For companionship? For who the person is? Why love if you know that you'll not be together forever? Why love when you know you are not going to get what you wany? I love others to be loved by them... and thats all I love for... to be loved  Hate???  Why do you hate when in this world you can't kill? Why hate if you can't kill? I hate because I see them as people who would do anything to be at the top.... I don't like those kind of people... who think that they are the most importiant people of the world.... what people call egos..... I happen to be one of them... thats why I hate myself
    


09,July,2004


	 
      On my music... Might take awhile to download... 8 MB
    


08,July,2004


	 
      Heres another funny one more
    


08,July,2004


	 
      theres alot to learn from that game.... many metaphores and good phlosofies  "The past is a gapping hole,you try to run from it but the more terrible it grows,its edges yawning at your heels. Your only chance is to turn around and face it. But its like looking down into the grave of youre love. Or kissing the mouth of a gun, a bullet waiting in its dark nest ready to blow your head off."  "If you try to escape you'll fall down back into the hole you were trying to escape from, only the hole has grown deeper."  "The Genius of the hole: No matter how long you spend climbing out of it you can fall back to the bottom in an instant."  "Throw the rules out the window, odds are you'll go that way too." 
    


06,July,2004


	 
      It makes me happy in the weirdess situations
    


05,July,2004


	 
      ...I've just realised while listening to Porcelin...  "To be at war with yourself is to be at war every minute of your life" Gawain 5/7/04 8.12 P.M
    


04,July,2004


	 
      1.I'm a show off 2.I'm a flirt 3.I've got a mind which can't hold back and think before taking action 4.I'm wierd ( I'll explain later ) 5.I'm scared of simple things 6.I'm rebelious 7.I taking god's forgiveness for granted 8.My otherself suddenly going silent and I'm not doing anything about it 9.I'm irritating to the society 10.I'm taking god's gifts for granted  *4. Things which make people misserable make me happy.... walking in the rain, sleeping in the mud, getting sick , cutting myself ( When I feel less pain when I'm angry )....ect   I might hate myself but I still love the ones around me.... I'm not going to be different if you talk to me its all in the mind
    


04,July,2004


	 
      The old me is back... no smiles no selfrespect no happiness  I'm not sure how long this is going to last but as long as I'm like this I'm not the kind of guy you would like to hang around with.... Or maybe I just need sleep.......  Or maybe its because I've found reasons to hate myself again..... and theres a long list of it....  And if anyone is wondering why I'm always wearing black you have read the reason above I was depressed all the time , no friends , people I can trust , people who I can talk to....ect ect  Now I got all of the above but I hate myself now....Congragulate me...
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ....Some gun maniac ( like me ) would love this picture&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
      ....depressed...
    


02,July,2004


	 
      I have no idear how I changed but I have, I'm happy and I'm cheerful ( so many years since the last time)
    


02,July,2004


	 
      ...Now I'm getting hysterical laughter sitting on my seat giggling.... omg THanK you!!!  I want to thank the lord for lots of stuff lots lots!! I need to ponder if I want to know them all! Thank god 10 examples: 1:Good Life 2:People ( First time in my whole life I'm saying this out loud ) 3:Forgiveness ( me being forgiving ) 4:Farvor ( I'm so blessed ) 5:Guns ( ...some people might not thank him though... ) 6:Nature ( ??? ) 7:Happines ( First time I'm saying this out loud too ) 8:Life ( This too... ) 9:Happy people ( Their happiness rubs off on me, this too.... ) 10:Love ( Needless to say )
    


08,August,2004


	 
      Thats much better..... May it be from the fellowship of the ring 
    


02,August,2004


	 
      ....change of music..........  dono why I'm chooseing these noisy music but I choose it anyway....  I've discovered some stuff on the topic on me being a flirt.... it seems that all guys who reached pubertity, has the self confidence to talk to gals... do the same things that I do..... 
    


02,August,2004


	 
      "We're all like grass, like grass,like grass I lost all 12, all 12 of them.....WHO EVER IS IN CHARGE HERE DON'T LET THAT MAN GO.... ok ok ok feet move, move,move,move don't touch, don't touch, I'm moving I'm moving..."   "Who desides who dies?! Who desides who lives!? THIS IS FUTILE! Ehh... You see I'm standing way up here and I'm not being shot at! Not one bullet! Why?! Why do they all have to die and I can stand all the way up here and nothing happens to me!!??" 
    



