
14,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ben in action!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Juzz wannna say that i am sorry if your picture isn't here.. well that's probably cuz you're too beautiful! Well this is juzz a few of the hundreds of pictures we have taken in camp so if u want more, purchase the camp cd!
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Hey, what do u think of the pics? If i insulted anyone, im so so sorry... pls tell me if i did ok? thx!
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    And the finalist for the best female are...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    And the finalist for the best dressed male are...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Is that Puss in boots?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    'leng lui' very tired wor....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Presenting.... the 4 stooges!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Troy's cell + Shanker's cell = overload of testosterone!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Teens juzz can't get away from the camera, eh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Night fever, night fever...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Pastor Tim engaged in a friendly chess tournament with a camper&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Cougar + Moose = VICTORY!! yea, baby yea&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    What happened to the traditional proposal with the ring??&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Camp comm. bonding moment&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    5-second fame during talent time&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our very own darth vader and anakin skywalker!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    How do you wash this goo off?!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Victim of his group members!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Teams cracking their brains for a debate during workshop&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The 'banana team' leading in worship&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is how it looks like in the evening&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is how it looks like from inside&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Hi.. i noe the pics were suppose to be up like few days ago but u see the thing is i left my USB cable at my granny's so cannot upload.. sigh.. anyway, now that its here, feel free to comment ya.. :)
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Yo peeps! wazzup?!  Youth camp 2004  was amazing! The pastor was so way cool. He totally connect with the youth! And the place was super cool, literally... u noe la up there in Genting, well actually we were in  Peacehaven . So here are a couple of pics for u guys to enjoy...      
     
    



28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    aikz? y they not singing wan?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    so cute!! ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    sanzo, mickey, dasher, ultraman&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our beautiful class!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Kah wei, yen pei, sook kuan&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Thuva, azelah, hidayah and steph&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ida and Mei Yee&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Liz, Kit Mun, Shalini and Mich. The 4 stooges!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,June,2004


	 
      Yo peeps! Wassup? Juzz thought i share a couple of pics of our very own classmates. You never noe how different people look when they are posing for the camera (hehe..) 
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    yen & kah wei&nbsp; urlLink   
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ru ching & zhi xin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    khasnida, nelfi, azmira, amalina&nbsp; urlLink   
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    me, ida, micky, dashni&nbsp; urlLink   
    


05,July,2004


	 
      hey... in case u wondering since when did our class have a blog?! well, i juzz wanted to post a couple of pix of our classmates la.. no biggie.. so if u dun see urself, chill, dun get pissed off ya. i will upload it sooner or later cuz currently my server very slow.. pls tell me if i insulted antone or anything..k? aku berfikiran terbuka...
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    our Thai fren and mandy&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    mazzy, ida, mei yee and me! i look so unphotogenic... *sob&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    yee bin and elmi...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    kanit and mandy&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    steph and vidyah&nbsp; urlLink   
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    JAC!!!! u spoil nice pix!!! hehe... kidding...&nbsp; urlLink   
    



21,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Kinda gothic don't u think? wait! is that goku???&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


19,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Assunta's very own cosplay!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


19,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    one big family reunion coming right up!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


19,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    my 16th bday. can u guess where i was??&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


19,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ending of the show....nite nite! Cya next yr!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Cultural dance&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    second(or third?) cultural dance... i danced!!! damn cool wei...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    You can't really see but they're throwing some dude into the air...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    They all wanna go home... ;(&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    do we look alike?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    yen, yien and von&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The cultural dance&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    the drum performance&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    They're all waving us good bye! *sob... well, there's always next yr!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm sure by now u noe that i'm obsessed with those drummers..hehe..*blush*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Kinda dark but, i can see!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The drummers at Bon Odori&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
      Hey peeps! welcome to my blog, juzz pix of me n frens and maybe a lil' abt me self... feel free to comment ya ;)
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
      hey...not so many pix yet cuz must edit a few..patience ya..abt the sports day wan rite...i dun hv pix of hermine cheerleaders..anyone got? and if u want me to post any pix, or remove feel free to e-mail me. but if u send virus, i will make sure u will suffer so badly u wished u never did that!! 
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    FRANCIS JUARA!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Clare cheerleaders&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    And some more..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    More cheerleading&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Assunta cheerleaders&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our marching team!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Victory is mine!!!! & Erica's...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Up close & personal&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Assunta Volleyball Team! Well, half the team..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Snake lady...SsSsSs...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Commercial: Check this out!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Left: Julia, Nisa, Ida, E Von, Devinia, Menisha, Mei yee&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ADAM!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ainaa & Ida&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Aikz???&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    again, me is missing in action&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Oh...forgot to mention... it was Ida's sweet 16&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    NinaCroft&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ida's sis, Ida&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ainaa by the pool..wonder what she thinking...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Don't ask...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yay! Food! Our recess got delayed for like nearly two whole hours!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    The new board's theme for their year&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Now we get our respective certs... &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Now all we're missing is white face paint & red noses..Ahahaha...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    happy people with NO more duties!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Pic with Mrs Toh.. Sweet..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Poor Nevina..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Time for group pic! Don't they look happy?? ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Woo Hoo!!! We're SO off duty!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our musicians.... Naveena & Nicole!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Singing school song informally&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Speech by Lin Jing before handing over the job to the new Head girl&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Us singing 'Kau Ilhamku'&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Singin' prefects' songs with the new board&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


09,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Prefects of 2003/2004!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    



