
31,May,2004


    
       
      My butt hurts. From sitting on it. All day.  Ow.
       
    
    


30,May,2004


    
       
      Went to the Red Barn. Got the ballet shoes. All was well.  Stopped at McDonalds on the way home. I ended up paying for the food, and Mom payed me back with what she had. She still ows me $3.00 - don't worry, I won't let her forget. 

28,May,2004


    
       
       HAPPY BIRTHDAY IDINA MENZEL!   And why does it say I've only written 2 entries when I've written three? [well, now four, but...]
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
      I've only been awake for 30 minutes, and I'm already bored to tears. Nothing to do online. Nothing to do in reality. It's sad.  Today we're going to the Red Barn to get white ballet shoes for Sound of Music. I guess I need them for one of my dresses or something. I'm not that fond of the Red Barn. It's fleamarket 

28,May,2004


    
       
      This is an entry in my blog.
       
    
    


28,May,2004


    
       
      Such a lazy day. I really haven't been motivated to do anything but lay around all day. Nothing at all. In fact, I think the only thing I did today was go to McDonalds. In my Pajamas. It was fun. o_0 We only went for the toys. I got a Chomby.   So...this is my first entry and you know it owns.
       
    
    


04,June,2004


    
       
      I am  so bored!  -headdesk- Mom and Ryan are out seeing Prisoner of Azkaban. I already saw it earlier today, but I was going to go again tonight... but the showing was sold out. =/ The one I went to today was sold out, too. Huzzah for Fandango! :D I ended up sitting on the floor so that I could sit with people I knew. Julie and I are going to go sometime this weekend, though, so...that's good.  The movie was awesome. When Hermione punched Draco in the face, the ENTIRE theater clapped xD I love it when they do that. It was darker, but it was also funnier, if that makes sense. Hm.  I'm gonna go beat my head on the wall some more. Update again later.
       
    
    



