
31,May,2004


	 
      it feels good 2 b bak.. but also tiring. u mite wonder where i was. well lemme tell u. i was in rockford.. brb g2g use bathroom..ok im bak.. wat waz i talkin bout? o yea, i waz in rockford which iz about 1 1/2 hours away from where i live (chitown). i went 2 rockford 2 visit my cuzez, aunt & uncle plus we were invited 2 my 1st-frend-in-america's crib. i like going 2 her crib cuz shez sorta like my 2nd best frend, but den her cuzins from NJ came over. i like 1 of her cuzinz cuz shez nice & polite but da other 1 iz a real bitch, i mean if u dont like some1 & theire trying 2 make u like them i mean u dont have 2 show da h8. i think dat girl had 2 much of dat h8rade, she needz 2 lay lo on dat shyt. ok so i had a pretty bad time @ their crib cuz itz like watever i said she would give me a cold look. i waz about 2 go like 
"wtf u lookin @?" but den i didnt wanna say dat cuz of my frend. yea so eventually (thank God) i got out of there & went 2 my cuz'z crib where i had a nice day. me & my boii cuz were playin his new ps2 game & me & my girl cuz went 2 dis park close 2 her crib & i waz sk8 boarding on her sk8 board. im actually not horrible 4 a beginner. she.. kinda.. iz. she bought dat board like a loong time ago & she waz begging her ma 2 buy it 4 her & den finally, finally when she got it... she decided 2 giv it up. if i had somn like dat, i would practice it evryday or @ least evry other day. she saiz dat she somtimz only practice it like 2 times a month! i mean cmon.. ok watever man. so yesterday i had a so-called "online bf" & he waz all sweet & shyt. & guess wat.. 2day i dont think were like dat no mo. i mean itz like he aint even trying. yesterday he mentioned my name 5 times in his pro, 2day he didnt mention it once. im dissapointed. it waz nice while it lasted eh? yea, im gona go b sad now cuz evry1 iz ignoring me & da ppl who would maybe talk 2 me r not online. so im gonna go b sad now. :( 

30,May,2004


	 
      itz all RAW!
    


28,May,2004


	 
      i have a correction to make. u know when i said in this previous entry about how i dont understand y we cant wear our class grad t-shirts 4 this assembly? well i just remembered how it waz last year, we will have 2 assemblies. da 1st one, every1 will b there while we sing our grad song & we have 2 dress up nicely 4 that. but da second 1, only da upper grades will come (i think) because it will b our gradu8ion practice & thats when we wear our class grad t-shirts. ok datz all i wanted 2 correct b cuz i waz wrong. once again: i say GOOD DAY! lol.. fezzy fezzy..
    


28,May,2004


	 
      hi people, howz it going? well i've been a little bored & maybe disturbed. why u ask? well.. i mite have seen a certain someone & believed at that time his/her words. That person HAS changed. o well not that it matters. so yea.. i went 2 da mall w/ may & milena yesterday (dajana waz supposed 2 go but she apparently waznt home), & i bought da white sox "its not a cap, its a flag" & then we went 2 rave cuz me & milena wanted 2 buy somthin 2 wear 4 da assembly on thursday, cuz we will b performing our graduation song 2 da lil ones. so stupid ms.whitehouse decided to make us wear "spring-like" clothes: brite colored shirts (baby blu, pink, yello, lite green..) & dark colored pants or capris. o & there absolutely cannot be any jeans worn. wat a fag. i dont understand y we cant wear our class grad shirts just like last year's 8th graders did. it sux. o well wat can ya do? so i just hope that they let me gradu8 in da real gradu8ion @ taft. my ma said shez gonna take a day off 2 c me gradu8. God i hope i dont fail her & have 2 go 2 summer skool or somn. well thats all i wanna say 4 now i guess. ta-ta.. until we meet again! (im such a doofus)
preppy girl in movie 'mean girls': "omigosh! that's so fetch!"  leader of da preps: "stop trying 2 make fetch out of things. it's not gonna happen!" dude preps r so damn annoying. ok ima go now. peace out 2 mah homeyz. ok bye
    


28,May,2004


	 
      hi.. yes i am surprisedly back by request. I dont really care about the ppl who h8 this blog b cuz if dat iz the case, they shouldnt waste their time reading it. understood? ok good. now i would like to mention things dat happened 2day. well 1st of all, i woke up and went to skool. then our first class waz gym. in gym i decided 2 shoot some hoops w/ may & jenini & matt (dork) & sidali were tryin 2 make a shot @ our hoop from like the other side of the gym. speaking of which, doing that really pissed me off b cuz i almost got smacked w/ da basketball really hard &  think jenini already got hit by her stalker, (accidentally). he iz freeky, he alwayz follows her & talks 2 her & moves towards her, but he aint fine. HELL NO not even close. datz da scary part. a scrawny odd-looking dark kid claimin he iz puerto rican. he iz da only puerto rican dude dat i saw in my whole life who iz ugly. i mean i thot puerto rican boiiz were supposed 2 b fine, but hey i guess not. so 2moro im supposed 2 go 2 da mall w/ may, dajana, & lena. but den i dono cuz u c ima money spender & i hav bout $123 & my ma iz like "well itz not so bad if u spend $20" & im like yea sure. now she saiz "itz ur decision" if i wanna spend it or not. so i dono.. should i?? well u kno i could but den i wanna buy new nike's & a white sox hat (itz not a hat itz a flag..yea my ass). so ima look dat stuff up on da net & da price & shit & den ima c. ok so armin iz leavin 4 bosnia 2moro & when he comz bak he aint gonna b goin 2 taft but 2 lincoln park.. ima miss dat boii. hez like da only bosnian dude @ dirksen, except 4 edvin but hez a 7th grader & plus armin iz da bomb, edvin cant beat dat. & all da rest of da ppl r either serbian or somn completely diffrn. now look watz funni here.. i got may thinkin dat i like armin. ok sure yea. im not dat much of a bitch 2 take away my good frend'z big crush. i jus dont think so, even if i did like him (which i dont, i only like him a lot as a frend even tho he aint even my frend, sadly) it wouldnt matter a bit. so now im jus hopin 2 pass 8th & go 2 taft & snatch one of da cute, nice, minimally perverted guys. thank you. goodbye. you are the weakest link and who wants to be a millionare? lol ok bie
    


30,June,2004


	 
      Hello, today I was of course on the computer, then I went outside with Lena & we saw Sexii Boii on his bike with his friends. Then we went to Subway (Eat Fresh. lol) & got the Italian B.M.T., damn it was good. Then we hung out outside all day and checked out guys. Then we saw Justyna with these two rocker dudes, they are SUCH a bad influence, I noticed that the one dude that was walking along Justyna's side, when they were passing by Lena & me, he was talking about how he burned a building down with porno magazines. Seriously man I know that she likes rocker dudes but she doesn't have to go with guys that do bad things, not that I care I mean she's old enough (I hope) to make her own decisions. Then we bothered bullshit (a.k.a. the perv but his mom calls him Sidali). Then Jackie surprisingly said hi to me, but it was a preppy hi & she was walking with this dude he was so.. Ugh.. sorry it's just a big change because she first hung out with Mexican & black gangsters & now she's going for the quiet type (don't worry he's still Mexican). Then we saw Mart circling around his building and the surrounding, but it was obvious that he was trying to err.. well.. check me out. He was all smiles & shit. Then Sexii Boii totally ignored Lena & me, I think I rest my case about the fact that he doesn't like me, but then Lena said that he was looking at me & smiling, but that's the same thing he did to her though, (sigh) I'm so confused. By the time Lena & me were totally annoyed by Mart circling the buildings from across the street, he comes by and starts talking to us, very obvious that he was checking me out, then later he demanded sunflower seeds from Tom (a.k.a. Dennis Rodman, also known to May as "Roddie Hottie") and Tom's friend but I don't know the guy's name. Lena pointed out to me that Rodman, I mean Tom, looks very much alike to Pavel, from our graduating class, & at first I didn't believe her, but as I really took a good look at him, he DOES kind of look like Pavel. It's actually a little scary, o well. So then later Mart had to go to hell (a.k.a. "The store"). After he left Lena said "Finally he left!" Then we went walking around and shit & as soon as we got up to walk around "the hood" once again, there comes Pat & his perverted smile on a bike (the smile was on Pat & Pat was on a bike, not vice versa or verse vicea, lol). Then he starts talking about how Mart always makes him look bad in front of girls, like yesterday when Pat said that he never disrespected a girl & Mart said "Yea right, u switch them like socks! & u even cheated on her (talking about me of course)!" So Pat said that that's not true & then he said this weakly "I never had a girlfriend in my life." I was outraged by his lies, him and Mart never stop lying, it's a constant circle with those two. Then Pat said "Are u going out with Martin?" I OF COURSE said "NO!" & he said "That's what he told me." But I really am not sure what to believe, I mean it's possible he said that because those two always talk crap about people and each other plus they always lie. The whole time us three (Lena, Pat, & me) were talking, Pat was checking Lena & me out, he thinks that he's so slick and that if he looks really fast that I won't notice. Sure why not. So Pat tells Lena & me that he's going to ask the next girl out that walks past. There comes a little three year old girl and I'm laughing my ass off and so is Lena. Then Pat goes "Unless it's a little girl or a grown woman." HA ok. So there comes a girl (used to go to our school last year, name's Olivia I think), just as she passed Pat said that he couldn't ask her because her mom was there. O don't worry, I'm going to make him continue the dare tomorrow. Then we were talking & shit & there comes Sexii Boii, that whole "shy boii" image is really not his real self. He could be just like Pat u know. Well Pat was just joking around (or was he?) when he told L.T. "U have a nice ass." (While almost falling off his bike from laughter) & L.T. says "Thanks man." (always smiling lol) & Pat says "Can I touch?" L.T. goes "Nope". Then Lena & me were laughing & Pat was like "What you think I'm gay now?" & we're like "No" & then L.T. said "Why don't u touch her ass or her's?" & then I was thinking "He's not as innocent as he looks." Then Pat said "U don't ask a girl if u can touch her ass, if u ask her, she'll say 'no' or 'why'." Then L.T. went around polak world more. Then we were talking on & then L.T. comes by again (still riding that weird bike with a steering wheel instead of handles lol) & as he passes, Pat smacks him on the ass. That was weird but funny, I guess (well Pat was sure as hell laughing his ass off). He said that 'chicks with dicks' was just something him & Mart did when they were bored at his house (ok yea that's what I'm going to do when I'm bored..NOT). Do u know that guy I told u about, his name is Darius*, he drives a red Volkswagen, he smokes, he's lately trying to be a pimp, & has a hot friend (sorry lol I had to say it), o yea & he shaved his head.. "Remember The Hideous". Do u have any slight idea what I'm talking about? Well anyways..He always looks at me from his car & it's SO obvious, I mean he even looks back while driving & then the 4th time he passed us, all of his friends from the car were looking at us too. It was suspicious, why would he be interested in me? Especially now that I don't like him... Hey Jenini guess who I saw today.. the STALKER. He was freaky as hell, he grew his hair out a little, he looks like a Horney I mean Harley Davidson dude. He was staring at Lena & me.. it was so weird man. May was at Svetla's today. Right now it's 11:40, but I started writing this blog around 9 (yes I changed the time) & Kam called me at 9:48 pm. He was in the car, driving from his old home to his new home. Then he didn't want to seem too obvious that he liked me, so he asked if I knew May's phone number but I told him that she's not home, & Svetla's I didn't know, I lost it somewhere, so yea. By the way, Pat asked me if Kamil calls me & I said "Yea when u guys were at Home Depot." So then Pat laughs about how he had to translate because Kam's parents were ordering paints & his parents can't speak even three words of English (give 'em a break, they've ONLY lived in the US for 9 years) & Kam doesn't know how to translate & explain things good in Polish. Then Pat was saying how he hates people who can't speak English & asked me how long I was here (5 years) & how come I can speak it so well & don't have an accent. Well I don't know, I have a gift for languages (among OTHER gifts), so I'm talking about how I used to speak German & he goes 'Eis my weis' (it's actually 'Eis mein weis' but whatever) & asks me if I understand it, well duh it means suck my dick, no thank u VERY much. Then my mom calls me to come home & I went, this time not angry about going home so early (9). So I guess today was an 'ok' day. You know maybe Pat does have something that makes girls like him, well he tries harder than some guys but it doesn't really matter. But I think that whole "going to an all-boys high school called St.Pats" situation went to his head, but what was funny was when he said "U should see when we have gym classes, it's like a damn gay pride parade." So Jenini I still think u have a little bit of hope about Pat not going to your high school, but then u never know. Everything should work out fine though (but I am NOT going to dance in the cages at Club Soda, HELL NO). Well I'm going to go now (sheesh these entries sure are getting long aren't they, ewww bad thought), goodbybye
    


29,June,2004


	 
      Hey there, what's up? Well today I first woke up, then was bored and played games on the computer (not the kind of games you're thinking of..). Then when my mom came from work, we went out of the house to go shopping & then I saw Kamil & waved to him. He completely moved today, so that made me extremely emotional, but I just don't get why, I mean I will most likely see him again you know, like if he comes for a visit or something. So then we (parents & me) went shopping to lots of stores and the heat was killing me & I got pissed off & demanded that I get driven home so that they would go to Sam's Club by themselves. They agreed to it. So when I got home I saw the moving truck still there. They either worked too slow or had a whole bunch of stuff. Then as they were done loading the stuff, I could hear Kamil & his bro singing "Magic Stick" from 50 Cent, LMFAO. Then they left, then I was supposedly going to Lena's house but she wasn't home (STILL shopping) so just as I was about to leave to go home, there shows up Martin & Kiki. Mart & me talked for a while but then I said that "I guess I should go home now" & Mart insisted I stay. So I said "ok" since I didn't have anything better to do anyways. We were talking & shit & then we were around my old place, where I used to live before, when all of a sudden there comes guess who... Pat. He was talking to Mart about perv things.. You know.. & then Pat asked why we were hanging out together & if we were having a "sex talk". Yea MY ASS WE WERE. Then Pat was hanging out with us & checking me out at the same time & he was talking about how he isn't going to listen to rap anymore, but that he's now changed & a techno dude (he laughs SO weird, he especially laughed when Mart asked him "what is it always with you and pants?" & then I asked Mart what it is with Pat & 'chicks with dicks' & when he asked Pat that, man he was laughing). Then somehow came the conversation of Mart saying "So you're really going to Taft?" & I said that I am & then a couple minutes later Pat goes "Biljana (he can't spell my name for shit though) you're going to Taft?" & I of course said yea & then he goes "Then I'm going there too" so I say "Why?" & he says "So we can be together" with that perverted smile on his face. As I remember it, he HAD his chance, didn't make a move so too bad he's out, besides, there are ENOUGH perverted guys at Taft without him getting his groove on. Not that I care if he goes there or anything. & then later when Pat left to check out little girls, Martin keeps asking who I was with yesterday & I said "Jenina & Lena" & he goes "Who?" & I repeat myself & he says "yea she's a goth" & I'm like "what?" & he's like "She is!! I was at May's once & she was dressed so.. gothic!" I'm like whatever, then Kiki goes "What's gothic?" & Martin taps her on the head & says "You have a lot to learn." You know what? My parents are fucking ASSHOLES!! I never wanted to say that on this blog about my parents but you know it's true. They don't let me have guy friends at all, they keep talking bullshit, DO THEY FUCKING WANT ME TO BE A DAMN LESBIAN???????? I mean WTF MAN??? I just don't get them. This sucks. I should be able to be outside with and be friends with anyone I want, regardless of gender, race, sexuality, style, whatever the fuck they are, if I like them it shouldn't matter. Why can't my dad just go away for months and months so that I could live my life however I want to, without him telling me who to be friends with. I don't know what I should do, you know that I'm addicted to guys, I mean I HAVE to be friends with guys they are what keeps me cool, and I'm not about to give that up, no matter what. But parents are really stupid though, the more they tell us not to do something we like doing, the more we're going to do it. Anyways.. when I was with the guys, Pat said that Kamil likes me & I told him that I know that already & then him & Mart kept insisting that I should go out with him & I said that I'm not going to take that advice, especially coming from those two knuckleheads. & then Pat said that he knows that I like him too, & I said that I don't. Then all of a sudden Pat said that he's going to get his eyebrows waxed & he asked me if I get mine waxed, lol damn. Then he said that his are kind of going to look like mine, man what is he gay now? Whatever man I should stop talking about him (he thinks he dresses preppy, yea Phat Farm is really preppy) people are going to think something. You know what I think that Kam is thinking, if I went out with Pat & Mart, two jerks, then why won't I go out with him? Well I was dumb back then, maybe instead of those two, I should've given Kam a chance. O well what can you do now, it's way too late, I kind of hoped that he would call me today or something, but he didn't. Most likely he was too busy with well.. moving in. I understand. Let's see what else I could talk about... I'm going to go outside with Lena tomorrow but she can only stay from like 1 pm to about 5 pm because she has to go shopping for flip-flops tomorrow. What the FUCK was she doing today all day?? I get annoyed real easily don't I? Hey it's just that I don't have anyone to hang out with except for guys but I'm not "allowed" to hang out with them, so I'm going to be outside until like 4 or 5 & then I have to stay at home all day with my dad's stubbornness and rudeness, listening to that shit the whole time. I don't know what I'm going to do about this, it's way over the line. I'm going to go now since this entry is seemingly long and I should make it shorter by shutting up now. So good bye & I hope that you're happier than me & that your parents let you have guyFRIENDS. Toot-aloo
    


28,June,2004


	 
      Hi. It was a nice day today. Jenini and I were so glad that she could come over to my house, but it was so difficult (for my dad) to find Jenini's place. I mean dude she even gave me the address & my dad was like, "No, we're supposed to go that way! There are no houses here!" & I even thought that I saw Jenina but I was like, "...Nah," (it turned out that it really was her in the end). So when it turned out that I actually was RIGHT.. My dad was trying to say that he meant something else, but I was thinking, "Don't you feel salty now, dirt off your shoulder!" Damn I'm weird right? Anyways, Jenina said she did see us pass by, but we still came, just later. So we went outside, picked Lena up to hang out with us, hung out outside, went to Dunkin' Donuts, checked out guys we like, amongst other things. Then Doug & the "Pink Pimps" were like trying to hit on us or something. Then one of them pushed Doug into Jenina & me & I told him that they're "way too desperate", then one of them said "Ooo she hurt you!" They are really lame to tell you the truth. Then all of a sudden, Kate came to hang out with us, (don't know why), & she was complaining about how bad the ice cream cone thingy was (it was just like a bunch of ice in a cone with concentrated juice poured over it). So I asked her why she was eating it if it was bad & she said "because it's cold". Nice reason there. As I was looking at that cone thingy, I remembered the movie "Jackass" & when the guys took one of those paper cones, put snow in it, peed on it, & well.. ate it. I know it's sick but it's a sick show, what can you do? So then we saw some "dark sides" which weren't exactly my idea of 'pretty'. What sucked about this day was first of all the fact that Doug is always trying to be a pimp & it's getting to be sad because he's not good at it at all (unlike some guys [cough cough]). The second thing that was SO sucky is that Jenina got in trouble because of her "curfew" but it all seemed like a big misunderstanding to me, but she still got in trouble but I really really hope that her mom won't be too mad & that I can see her sometime again soon. :( 
    


27,June,2004


	 
      Hey lol sup? Was goin on? Not much here I guess, you know what's weird (right now you're asking yourself,"Is she going to start every entry with 'you know what's weird?'?")? Well... By the time I wrote that stuff in the parentheses I forgot what my main point of 'you know what's weird' was. Damn, this always happens. Wait now let me think of what else I'm going to talk about...Umm... Ok well let's talk about Pat & the song "Yeah" from Usher. Even though some people are bitches sometimes, I still need to chill out & not pay attention to their bullshit. I went to Munchkin Monuts (get it? More nuts? lol I'm high on sugar, don't ask) with May a couple half-hour ago & we were just coming back home from DD's & all of a sudden we hear a loud, hearty "YEAH!" from a car & I said, "Man seriously if that wasn't Pat.. Man I don't even know.." & May was laughing. But I knew that it was him because I mean he's famous for that 'quote'. Then I saw "fishy Kate" & the girls Jenini & me used to call "Bitches Incorporated" & you know since Kate & me stopped being bitchy to each other, she always waved at me. But for some reason she didn't this time, you would think that she didn't see me or something, but she saw me & clearly, she even looked back twice. No wave, no little preppy "Hi!", nothing. Then me & May pass by to throw something in the garbage can & we walk past the polak world again & Justyna says hi so I wave back to her & also say hi. Then ALL OF A SUDDEN Kate manages a preppy little hi, but if Justyna wouldn't have said anything, neither would she have. May thinks Justyna is fishy but I don't think so, that girl is way cool, just like Klaudia & I'm with my girl so when Klaudia decides not to be friends with Justyna anymore, same here. Well... Maybe. It sucked that Jenina couldn't come over to my house today, I really wanted her to & she wanted to also but her mom didn't let her. So hopefully, she'll be able to come to my house tomorrow. Now I remember what I wanted to point out in the beginning of the bloggie entry, ok what I think is weird is the fact that I was so sad the whole day, I don't know why but I think that it has something to do with Kam moving & I was cranky all day up until he called me, that like totally brightened my day. You can kind of notice it in my last entry which I also wrote today. I'm pissed in half of the entry & then all of a sudden I start laughing about my dad & the small glass table in the middle of the livingroom. lol. May said that she thinks he's still trying to make me like him, but I don't know what he wants, I mean I already like him, but I like him as a friend, not like you know (& don't say 'no I don't know'). Ok well I'm kinda watching a movie now but I was hoping either Pat or Kam would be on the internet, but hey I guess not. So Bybye
    


26,June,2004


	 
      Whooohooo!! White Sox won! That was one hell of a game.. we were leading since the beginning & then at the end, we won 9-4. i was scared, I mean we started the 3-game series off by losing the first game, & it's very important to prove which team is the city's best. The second game, we won 6-3, by then I was relieved and by winning 2 out of 3 games, we won the 3-day series, it was cool. You have no idea how long I've waited to go to one of these games with a small group of my friends. I've waited since July 5th, 2003. I asked my parents if I could go & my mom said no because my dad wouldn't ever let me go on the train in the middle of the daylight with some of my friends to see a 3 hour White Sox vs. Cubs ballgame. It's understandable right? hell no, because I've awaited it for so long. Everytime I write in my blog my mom passes by & reads something from it & she saw the first word of the title of the blog & she's all like "What's that?" & I'm like "None of your business." & she's like "Biljana!". Man seriously hasn't she ever heard of the phrase "curiousity killed the cat"? She should think about that, because I'm really annoyed by people butting into my business & privacy. They should fuck off, just like Jenini said the other day. You know what else? My dad has absolutely no sense of decoration, I mean  with furniture & shit. He put a tiny glass table in the middle of the livingroom & it looks hideous. Just picture it... two reasonably sized couches & a tiny little table in the middle. lol. man. it jus looks funny, especially with my dad sitting on the couch with that look on his face like "what are you looking at? This table looks good here. O what do you know anyways..." Kamil just called me. yay. Him & his bro & Pat & his parents (not sure about the parents) are at their neighborhood Home Depot (in Bloomingdale) & well he decided to call me. Awww isn't that sweeet? lol I was like "so who's with you? your parents?" & he's like "yea & my bro & Bryda." I was like "Yea he always tags along doesn't he?" & he's like "Yea, actually I asked him to come." I was like "o ok". & then he was like saying how he missed me, hmm.. I wonder if that's true. O well.. it was nice hearing from him, we always used to hang out & then all of a sudden we stopped, don't remember why, but ok. i'll talk l8r g2g now.
    


26,June,2004


	 
      Hi there? Wassup? Well let me once again tell you about my day. I woke up around 10:45 am & I was on the internet until about 2:40 & then my dad made me go with him to pick my mom up from work downtown. I didn't feel like going, but my dad will never take 'no' for an answer. I was already getting carsick from the heat, traffic, & annoying Serbian radio talkers people whatever. Then when we came home, I called Lena to go outside with me, we wanted Jana to come with us but she couldn't. I didn't want anyone else (except for Jana or maybe JUstyna, but she was nowhere to be found) to come hang out with us anyways. So I called May & she didn't answer & like half an hour later her mom calls me to ask me if May is with me. Of course she isn't. I'm not missing her like I used to when she went away for a while, I actually am not even sure that I care that much anymore. In my opinion I think she needs someone who is more.. well.. "Punk-rock" & adventurous, because that's definitely not me. May IF u read this all I'm hoping you don't get mad because I'm supposed to express my feelings on this thing. Change the subject.. You know what I don't understand? How some people just care so MUCH about the little, unimportant things in life that they don't realize how little they care about the big, important things in life. Just think about it.. does it matter to you if I tell you what color nailpolish I got today? & even me with my new digi-cam, I mean it doesn't mean A FREEKIN THING. Calm Down Mode. You know what strange thing happened today? (Obviously you don't.) Well Lena & me were walking & across the street was Bernard & some guy who appeared to be Javier. Lena & me were trying to identify this guy because you know Lena is blind without her glasses (lol) & I knew that Javier couldn't have gotten so damn tall, because he's known to me as shorty. By this time, we knew not to stare at them any more (rite Lena? lol..), so we're talking to each other & all of a sudden there comes a whistle from across the street. We look over & hear a guy say "Biljana.. DAMN!"...it was Douggie. I was weirded out but @ the same time, surprised. Aww maan!! Jenini just signed off. Poor baby, it's goin to be ok. We'll get our lives back on track when we get to high school. I guess Jess has just caught up with the high school life & is kind of busy right now, I don't think that she's avoiding you purposely. And you know the poem in your profile really touched me, we all have our bad days, or maybe, say, months in this case. Sidali keeps on calling me "horseshit!" & I call him "pervert" & "bullshit". He's so rude. Lena said she could recognize me from far because of my "walk". lol :P  I feel sorry for Ada, she can never go outside, she's always stuck in her house. & her brother who's like a 4th grader or something, can go outside whenever he wants, all because they favor boys in China. 
Really old ass guys keep honking at me & saying stuff to me in the polak language, damn I'm not Polish, what's wrong with these old freaky perverted fags?? Anyway, I saw hott yellow (or in other words, Thomas) today, & he looked so cute with his jeans pulled way down so that I could see his boxers. Awww. lol. He barely even looked at me. But seriously, why in the face of the earth would a hot Polish 'junior-in-high-school-to-be' guy, like me?? Seriously, there's got to be more of a variety out there. He wouldn't go out with me, I'm not THAT luvvable. Well I'm actually not sure what else to say here except for "I miss L.T." & "Have a good one". Bybye people, enjoy your ice cream. & don't scream because it's too late for that. 
    


25,June,2004


	 
      Hi there, I hate making the one person who reads this sad, but just like yesterday and just like everyday I have to express my true feelings toward life and everything else. So remember yesterday when I was talking about how I most likely wouldn't miss Kamil? Well I was wrong, I don't think he even moved yet but I already miss him. He's a really cool, funny person & he is the friendliest guy in this whole neighborhood. You don't see much of that around here. I'm not going to forget all the memories, I hope he comes to visit us again. I remember that time that cockroach & that black guy snapped at me when they saw me wearing my white sox hat sideways. And we were about to start fighting if it weren't for Kamil. I was the one who was supposed to leave but now he's leaving. It'll cause a change in the atmosphere, I just don't know why but everyone is leaving me, either physically or mentally. It's getting tougher for some reason, we got to make it through. Just think about it, I mean it could've been worse. We could be poor hungry people in India on a polluted river waiting for the kiss of death. Thank God we aren't in a situation as bad as that. But I still feel for those poor people. Man I'm making everything worse here, maybe you people aren't in the mood right now but I'm going to tell you a joke. Ok there was a cop & when he came to work he realized that he wore a black and a white shoe. He didn't really care though because he couldn't go back home anyway. Then his boss came and said "Why are you wearing different shoes?? People are always talking about how the police is stupid so now you want to go out and make it all true?? Go home and change." The cop said ok and went home. A couple minutes pass and the cops is back looking the same with the unpaired shoes. His boss is like "What happened?? Why didn't you change your shoes??" The cop goes "Well.. At home I also had a white and black shoe." ha. Stupid cops. Right now It's 1:18pm & I'm watching BET, Eminem has his countdown of videos on now. Today I'm only going outside with Lena, and maybe Jana later when she comes from school. I don't know what I should do about that whole bff situation, I mean yesterday's blog entry made Jenini realize that maybe her bff & her are drifting apart too.. Maybe this is all just a stage in our lives, maybe it will pass soon & it will all be good like before, but you know maybe.. it wont. Hope for the best & don't worry about the rest. Much luvv & luck! ;)
    


25,June,2004


	 
      Hey you! Yes you the fat cop with the donut in your hand! Why don't you go to Munchkin Monuts & gonuts??
    


25,June,2004


	 
      Hi, man today it couldn't have been more boring, but u know I'm slowly losing a friend is what I think. Ok I have to spill this now because it's gone too far & I can't not talk about this.. especially to something so special as my bloggie. & just so you all know, don't get this wrong, I'm not back-stabbing, I'm expressing my feelings, after all isn't that what you're supposed to do in a bloggie? Ok my so-called bff is losing control of herself & her actions, or at least that is wad I feel is going on. My feelings are really getting tangled up in all of this and I don't think I'll be able to stand it much longer. As a matter of fact, I don't even think that our friendship will last through the summer. Much deep anger has been expressed toward me, but not only me, also my other friends. I don't understand where this anger is coming from because I don't remember when I did something so terrible to her that she would have to get such cold revenge on me. Even if I did do something, wouldn't you think that I should be informed of this, I would apologize for it & make sure never to do that again. Or maybe it's my jokes, maybe I over-did them, maybe I have offended her with that & that's why she is mad at me.. I mean me without a joke is like peanut butter without peanuts or spelling my name without the letter 'B'.. I mean it's ridiculous & impossible. But hey if it's my jokes that bother her then fine I will turn down the humor, that's no problem. I don't get why she changed on me, maybe it's that whole rocker thing, maybe it's her cousin's influence, maybe it's some other reason, maybe it's all my fault, maybe it's not. But all I should say about this is that it has to stop, soon, because if it doesn't I'm done with this friendship, I don't need this kind of crap, I've tried to put up with it but I'm not a very patient person. I'm not going to sit around & wait until the moon circles the earth, or whatever. It was all great before that whole "disobey your parents" phase came along, as I think about it, her cousin definitely did play a role in this.. ok now let is talk about something else.. last night I watched a movie called "The Craft" & it was about some witches, it kind of freaked me out, but it was a cool movie. Today Svetla came over, lol she didn't change one bit except for the dark tan, it looked good on her. Then last night Armin came back & Lena was very happy (awe). Kasha didn't talk to me in a while, not that I care. It's cool to hang out with Justyna because she's so laid-back & simple. She called Kladusha in Poland & the first thing Kladusha says is "Wassup Nigger??" lol. Dan Hedrih is obviously a freeman now, he's been out of juvi since a couple days. Speaking of Freeman.. I hope he doesn't know me anymore. Pat (from Dicksen) is still constantly eating something lol. Noel & the "Pink Pimps" still trying to be gangstas, but they're really wankstas (wannabees). Pat B. still hitting on lil girls, his new phase:: tampons. I haven't seen Sexii Boii or his bro around for a long time, I wonder where they could be. Jenini is so cool & understanding, Jessy is so lucky to have her as a best friend. :) moving on.. you have NO idea what Darius* did to his hair, I mean he literally "un-hot-ed" himself, he's like bald now, in other words WHO THE HECK GAVE HIM A FREAKING HAIRCUT??? Today was Kamil's last day in this hood because he is moving to Schaumburg, I doubt that I will miss him, but hey you never know. I wonder who will be R.Kelly-Wannabee's "bestest" friend now, maybe Ludacris will move up to the position (don't bother because you people don't know who he is, he's Pat's best not bestest friend, his real name is obviously Chris). But I don't think it really makes a difference because R.K. is moving also, most likely he's going to attend Jenini's school. So all the fun & perverted times will most likely be leaving us, then bad people will move to this hood & there will be nothing left of us except bad people. Yes I do have a bad outlook on life, but sometimes people refuse to face the truth. Sure as hell should sometimes. I haven't heard from "Hot boy Aldin who grows corn in Iowa" in months, I don't know where he's been. And Van stopped sending me e-mails, I mean he's constantly online but I don't really feel like saying anything. My dad is pissing me off, he always says such stupid things, I can't even believe it, he's always bothering me too. My mom's a little stressed. No one goes online anymore, I have nothing to do. I'm not going to go outside w/ "bff" anymore, I cant bear the insults. The conclusion of all this is.. LIFE IS TOUGH... AND WHAT DID YOU EXPECT???
    


24,June,2004


	 
       [feeling]: still furious & bored  [looking at]: tv  


_________________ hi, waz goin on? well im still mad @ a person from yesterday & 2day i decided not 2 go outside & shit jus so i can chill out. so i waz downloading songs & once again i found out da white sox lost a game.. how many timez will this happn? i dono wat 2 say, i actually feel that da new manager ozzie guillen didnt bring a change 2 da team dat much & some of our good players went 2 other teams 4 mo $$. but our loyal playaz stayed on da southside. big props 2 yall. u kno watz weird? ok im obsessed w/ music, i've been obsessed w/ it since da 1st day i waz born, 3/22/1990. i simply enjoyed it, music makes me happy, when evrythin else goes 2 hell, i still hav da music. but u kno wat.. from all my frendz.. only 1 of dem likes hip-hop/rap. which iz so damn gay. & da prolem iz dat i cant even hang out dat much w/ jana & talk about da music 2 her. u kno wat im sayin? so i jus ax 1 of my frendz "hey did u hear dat new song from soandso..?" & theire like "i dont listen 2 rap". & u kno wat else.. some of yall out der (u kno who u r) used 2 like rap/hip-hop b4 & now all of a sudden itz like u've been smacked in da face & all of a sudden ur quote iz:: "KILL HIP-HOPPERS, I LOVE ROCK!" i dont get it man.. somtimes i feel like any second now evry1 will start likeing rock & shit & der will b no mo hip-hopping & rapping, cuz u kno yall r killing it more & more evryday. it all sux. im not sayin dat ppl who like rock suck, im ok w/ u guys but itz those who liked rap b4 & now all of a sudden u wouldnt b caught dead listening 2 it. srry 2 say dis but u guys r hypocrites, i mean ur sayin "rap sux" but u used 2 like it b4.. itz practically like sayin "lil kids r dumb, they suck" but u used 2 b a lil kid. proves my point rite der. itz ok whoever disagrees w/ me cuz dis iz my blog & itz der 4 da purpose of me sayin watever i feel. i dont mind comments so go ahead. did u ppl hear about mary-kate olsen? she has anorexia, ppl had told me that they thot so long b4 2day, but i didnt believe it b cuz the twins denied it when  People  magazine interviewed them in april. obviously celebrities lie 2. i think that mary-kate iz dumb, i mean she has EVRYTHING that n/e 1 would ever want & wat doez she do 2 show her thankfullness? she starves herself. rite now i really dono wat else 2 say. u kno when i get mad itz a part of da planet Mars, the god of war in Greek mithology, also my sun sign's planet, im an aries in case u didnt kno. well ok tootle-oo 4 now.  urlLink  
    


23,June,2004


	 
      listen up, any of yall who r tellin me how 2 act, wat 2 do, & wat 2 say u can fuckin kiss my ass! if u think ima listen 2 ur shit den wat da fuck hav u been smokin?? yall cant change me, yall dont like me den dont b frendz w/ me, im not fuckin dumb. 
    


22,June,2004


	 
       [feeling]: funny..   [looking at]: um..  
hi there, lemme ax u somn, did u kno dat der actually iz a day in da year where poor lil perv peepL celebr8 their "talent"? by now if ur not confuzed den plz stop being so SMART (*sneeze*sneeze). yes it iz dat which u hav been waiting 4.. PERV DAY iz 2moro!! yay! lol.. jus in case u didnt kno, i would like 2 inform u dat im officially JOKING U DORK. but u kno wat, since der iz no1 2 talk me out of dis rite now, i declare 2moro official perverted ppl day. hooray 4 "the few but proud".. o no wait, datz 4 da marines. srry im a lil perky 2day but u kno guys can do dat 2 u. i dont mean do as in DO but do as in make u b like dat. man im obsessed, hez so undiscriptable.. lol doz dat word even exist? i didnt think so. u kno wat? i jus thot of somn, if i keep talkin bout how nice & sweet & (lol) beautiful he iz, den maybe jus maybe 1 of my frends may start 2 like him 2. (gasp!) omg.. (gasp!) hope not, so ok i'll shut up about him rite now & in case ur wondering, yes i did have my daily dose of sugar 2day.. actually it waz a double dose. ha. letz c how i could start making dis blog funny.. well speakin of funny how about i tell u a lil johnny joke. a new teacher waz tryin 2 make use of her psychology courses. she started her class by sayin, "evry1 who thinks ur stupid, stand up!" After a few seconds, little johnny stood up. da teacher said, "do u think ur stupid, little johnny?" "No, ma'am, but I h8 2 c u standin there all by urself!" 
ok dis next joke iz sick so BEWARE.. dont read it if ur lil & dumb..:

21,June,2004


	 
       [feeling]: exhausted   [observing]: computer screen 


hey srry im jus tryin somn new out & seein if it worx, yea. ok. aw damn! itz almost 1am & i hav like 7 more hrs of sleep!! ahhhh!! g2g bybye.
    


21,June,2004


	 
      hewo fuends, 2day waz so tiring, my dad & me came bak from dropping off a load in Grand Rapids, Michigan & i barely got n/e sleep. den when i came home, i didnt wanna sleep but den l8r i had 2 cuz i simply waz falling off da computer chair from exhaustion. now instead of sleepin, im here talkin 2 u, thus explainin da title. 2day da weather here in chi waz absolutely marvelous.. except 4 da rain & thunder & da fact dat there waz a possibility of a tornado.. yea. i keep tryin 2 change my letters in da blog, like 2 make dem smaller, & when i preview it, it loox good.. so i 'republish' & itz still da same like it alwayz waz, sheesh. 2moro lena's dad iz driving lena & me 2 da mexicano hood again, we r gonna go visit our favorite principal, Mr.Burns. hez such a kool short guy & he truly luvvs children, unlike keating. & plus we r gonna go visit our teachers.. omg i cant wait itz gonna b so sweet. u kno @ our gradu8ion, dat mornin june 15, keating talked 2 mr.Burns & he wished me a nice gradu8ion & good luck in hii skool. i mean iznt dat sweet of him? he still remembers me. :) da only bad thing about dis iz dat i hav dis killer headache rite now cuz of lack of sleep & i also hav 2 wake up @ like 8am 2moro. o well it makes it worth it, man i jus hope it dont rain 2moro like it did 2day. hmm.. letz c wat else i hav 2 blab about.. o yea, i waz plannin 2 go 2 da white sox vs. cubs game (1 of da games @ least, since der will b a series, da 25th, 26th, 27th) & i dont think my whiny parents would let me cuz i wanna take da train der w/ possibly these ppl: lena, jana, jenini, & may if she iz not in SK by then. but i REALLY REALLY wanna go cuz i luvv u.s. cellular field & i luvv da white sox & i wanna prove once & 4 all dat we r better den da cubbies tubbies (.blows raspberry.) & my parents r truly whiny (well actually itz mostly my dad) cuz i wanted 2 go wait fo 4th of july @ da 'Gracanica' w/ milena & her ppl, i mean itz only checkin out fireworx & even mexicans go der, it dont matter wat religion u r, but no i cant go cuz my dad iz bein an ass. man u kno who i miss??? dats rite, L.T., man seriously i think i even like him more den his bro, i mean yea his bro iz cute & i kno he waz checkin me out & stuff but seriously L.T

20,June,2004


	 
      sup peepL, nm here, 2day i went w/ lena & her ma, dad, bro 2 my old hood, "Da Mexicano Hood". it waz kinda kool seein da old place again. & except 4 som construction, nothin changed, evrythin stayed da same. perv mexicans still roam da streets, not dat i mind, but they do annoy peepL somtimz. & while lena'z peepL were @ lena'z cuzzinz crib, me & lena went 2 visit my old skool hopin dat it waz open but it sunday so wat da heck did we expect? on tuesday mornin we r gonna go visit mr.burns, our old kool principal & also our old teachers (not old agewise but old as in b4 but not n/e mo). so den as we saw dat da skool waz closed, we went shoppin a lil bit & jus walkin around. it waz SO difficult 2 cross da street cuz der iz som1 driving there constantly, & if it waznt 4 me (lol) lena would've been ran over. lol dude i will talk l8r but rite now i g2g 2 detroit w/ my dad. & i saw L.T. 2day yay!!!! lol ok bybye luv ya 
ps:: mark & mart r so good frends now, how happi 4 dem. 
    


19,June,2004


	 
      i didnt c L.T. or his relative T.T. outside @ ALL 2day.. dat jus kills me man. altho evry1 tells me otherwise.. i still think dat der iz no hope w/ da 1st guy.. b cuz i will NEVER gather enuff courage 2 go & talk 2 him or even say "hi" cuz im afraid of rejection. it dont matter.. i'll jus wait 4 som1 else. bybye once again. :')
    


17,June,2004


	 
      hi.. srry 4 not writin yesterday but i waz kinda.. well busy. may & me were outside till 9:20.. until eventually my ma called me & axed me wher da hell i am. wait brb g2g p. ok im bak. look i hav a prolem.. itz somn dat happnz 2 me constantly. ok so u hav a bf & u luvv each other & shit & like about 3-4 months after da break-up u c him again, he loox diffrnt all of a sudden, he loox so sweet, nice, & u feel like u've known him 4evr & dat u belong 2gether, all da feelings come rushing bak & u wanna b w/ him more den ever. if u think im crazy dats ok, but somtimz jus so u kno.. itz da hormones talkin. & somtimz i feel like i've made a mistake. o watta hell? wat am i hiding here n/e wayz?.. dis iz about.. pat. ok u guys dono him like i do, itz not ur fault, itz not his fault, itz jus dat u havnt been der, u havnt had a good chance 2 get 2 kno him.. he barely ever iz "himself". jus in case u didnt kno, guys like 2 show off in front of their frendz when it comz 2 girls & it may make u think dat hez a jerk like dat in real lyfe but u never 'really' kno wats inside. now about me thinkin dat it waz a mistake: my big mistake dat i still regret waz goin out w/ mart. hez an "ok" person 2 hang out w/ & crap but i dont think he should ever b considered somthin they call "boyfrend material". no offense 2 him, but some guys jus arent cut out 4 dat. n/e wayz..dats where da mistake started & hell it didnt end 4 a long time. i've been harassed about it, made fun of, & all sorts of other things like had snowballs thrown @ me & a hatred-relationship w/ som1 dat took a while 2 fix & crap. BUT i dont care about wat other ppl did about it & how they reacted, i jus care about how i waz sort of lying 2 him. i didnt really luvv him, but i did care 4 him.. as a frend, which bak den i didnt realize so i jus kept on goin cuz i didnt wanna break his heart & make him h8 me. which still happnd despite of that. now wat made it even worse waz.. 1st i broke his heart & den i did somn even tho he told me never 2 do it, but i luvvd pat b4 him & his words couldnt stop me. still 2 dis day.. i dont think dat pat ever liked me, i think dat he waz jus fakin it 4 som reason, like 2 make mart jealous or jus 2 play me. & he did cheat on me u kno.. altho he alwayz denies it, but i kno. so pretty much, my blog title stays true.. these are horrific tales of today's teenagers, 2 b so young & yet 2 roam freely w/ ur actions. watch out 4 da influence of drugs, beer, hashish, coke, & dat sort. live ur lyfe 2 da fullest, dont let guys play U but play THEM. & make sure 2 think b4 u speak, especially when speaking somthin so precious as those 3 little words: i luvv u. o & dont trust n/e 1.. u never kno how they mite turn out l8r & change on u.. this iz not alwayz gonna happn but im sayin dis jus so u kno. good luck in lyfe, believe in urself & dont focus on guys. they will alwayz b der n/e wayz 2 comment on som like dis "ur eyes r uniquely colored" when he waz actually chekin out ur breasts. stupid mexicans. plz dont ax.   ps:: yesterday scott kennedy waz chekin me out & if he would hav been ANY more obvious.. man i would've been like "2 much of dat crack made u 4get not 2 b obvious when ur checkin out a girl, u moron"
ok well bybye 4 now.. ttyl w/ God's help & i like da song "jesus walks" from kanye west. bye.
    


17,June,2004


	 
      hi.. ok 2day waz a nice day i guess, now i kno somn 4 sho.. da 2 guys i like ARE broz. o well wat can ya do. derz no way i can pick between dem, i mean dis time this iz truly called impossible. i'll jus name da guys by their initials since itz not like n/e 1 will kno 4 sho who it iz. so i kinda sorta think dat t.t. waz checkin 1 of us out 2day cuz itz like he waz walkin on da sidewalk w/ p.a. & den as soon as he passed us, he turned & went bak da same way. so iz he doin dis on purpose or iz it an accident? hmm... & man his jeans were so low u could c his boxers. lol. yea. dont ax me if i waz enjoyin da moment, cuz dats jus obvious Duh. lol. n/e wayz.. i dont think dat dis dudes bro likes me or will ever like me cuz well i dono y but hez such a nice, funny (beautiful lmao) person & y would he wanna go out w/ me? itz weird man. these few days itz like da only thing i talk bout r guys.. im obsessed deal w/ it. u kno may tole me dat derz nuin wrong w/ likeing 2 guys but der IZ somn wrong w/ likeing 2 broz. dats wat i think @ least.. 1 day it will all blow up in my face. u kno wat? adi iz really talented w/ luvvy dovvy (o-o here comz k8 w/ da spelling police! watch out!) away mssgs & poems. i mean she really knos how 2 make it rhyme & how 2 make sense out of it. she iz also really pretty i jus feel srry 4 her cuz of how she likes jerks u kno, but den again shez also a show off w/ dat whole "blow jobs" story. i dono man i jus think dat evry1 has a good & bad side & ya g2 kno who u'z frendz w/. now k8.. derz definitely somn "fishy" as may sayz, goin on w/ her. her smile iz jus so fake like man i cant believe it. u kno dat lil voice inside ur head? well mine waz extremely loud 2day. like i almost said 2 k8 "so.. how did dat pineapple taste?" & den i almost yelled out 2 l.t. "hey hottie!!" i mean seriously i wish der waz a mute button on dat lil voice cuz itz drivin me nuts. not those kinds. so 2day dat ana bitch waz bein a real well bitch.. i mean she yelled out 2 my bff dat shez a bitch, i wanted 2 smack da shit out of her. but den i yelled out 'ur da bitch'. & den yaill keeps comin 2 polack world 2 c ana i guess. LMMFAO!! he even got rejected by HER! shame shame shame boii-o. ok ima go now. much luvv bybye.
    


16,June,2004


	 
      hi, 2day waz an "ok" day. now horrific truly has a new meaning.. im talkin bout... my EYEBROWNS I MEAN EYEBROWS!! i went 2 da bathroom 2 p, but my unruly eyebrows mesmerized me. i mean man dude guy. once again lemme advise u.. a teenager'z lyfe iz all & all about TLC. 
Thieves
Liars &
Cheats.
it doznt get any better den dat. o & of course a couple tremendo mosquito bites. ha. im not funny. 2day i watched a world-cup soccer game: Portugal Verses... hmm wat waz dat other team dat cant afford good shoes so they play slip-'n'-slide on da grass?? o yea! of course how could i 4get: Russia. srry guys but damn ur offense & defense sux, but hey u never kno.. good luck next year. if i hav 2 chew dis gum (holy crap i almost wrote 'guy') n/e more.. i'll...i'll spit it out. yea datz a good idea. i hope jenini can come 2 polack world 2moro after she iz finished w/ doggy-sitting. lol doggy-sitting i luvv dat word. u kno wat i dont get? how SOME PEOPLE can luvv jerkasses, jackasses, dumbutts or watever u wanna call em. i mean if a guy iz constantly bein a jerk 2 u then how in da face of da earth can u luvv him??? like i said.. TLC luvv. ok bybye. muchy luvvy dovey. lmfao im such a dork ok bye. ;)  ps:: itz now down to 3 guys since i found out dat darius* smokes.
    


15,June,2004


	 
      hey!! 2day waz grad day!! it waz kool, a lil exhausting but kool. i mean i saw all my classmates & mystery boii. so dat waz fun.. i felt like we havnt seen each other in days when it waz jus.. well.. 1 day. & u kno when i said dat i waznt sure if im gonna cry @ gradu8ion but im prolly not? well.. as most of da time.. i waz wrong. da 1st 1 dat cried waz jana den nini started cryin & den as i saw dem, so did i. yea. i waz a lil shocked of myself. but i guess it waz 4 a good cause, & @ dat time losing fluid waz not a killer. so im really happy dat skools finally over!! & btw just in CASE ur wonderin wat da titles r alla bout.. lemme tell u a lil story.. well it all started once upon a time in da kingdom by the sea, a maiden there lived by da name of annabel lee. lol damn i cant believe i still remember dat. now.. da title. 1st of all "blame it on da new kid!!" iz about when we were @ gradu8ion & jana waz da 1st one 2 cry so den when i waz talkin 2 nini on da net a couple minz ago & she said "jana started it lol" so im like "yea blame it on da new kid! wait.. shez not new". so i thot dat waz funny & added it. da next title.. u kno dat polish dude i like called "mystery boii", well derz him & hottt yello & i think dey r both hott & nice. now i looked in lena'z bro'z yearbook (cuz her bro goes 2 taft) & i saw hottt yello in it & his last name iz da same as "mystery boii"'z!! which brings me 2 a shock of thot, thot of shock, watever... wat IF dey r broz?? wat if im crushin on 2 broz? how bad would dat get.. or maybe dey r cuzez which makes da situ8ion "closely rel8ed". so now when nini comz 2 my crib on "da day after 2moro" (lol it waz stated by accident), we hav 2 do mission impossible, but in alternity itz possible. so-called "thursdsay'z" destin8ion (if thurs. iz da day after 2moro..) iz:: polak world or also called pole-land by me & telly da celly. lol dude im goofy 2day. so i hope deir not broz.. cuz if dey r.. lotza prolemz. ok c ya luvv ya bye bye. 
    


14,June,2004


	 
      hi there... umm i jus wanted 2 tell u, itz weird bein frendz w/ ppl who r each other's arch enemies.. kladusha & kasha. den, i would also like 2 tell u somn i noticed recently.. derz 4 guys dat i think r hott & their all POLISH!! itz freeky cuz i used 2 h8 polax.. no offense. so da guys r.. nah.. im not gonna tell U!! itz 2 publik here.. da next thing.. u c me in a tabloid: "Shocking news revealed! Biljana's latest crushes & all the scoop! Only in this issue of "Horrific tales of 2day's teenagers". lol dont ax y im actin freeky.. da amanda-ness is really contagious. ta-ta 4 now i g2g sleep itz already past midnite! goodbye my luvvez!! hellz yea!! lol
    


14,June,2004


	 
      hi.. 2day waz da last day of skool & it waz ok i guess. wat am i TALKIN bout man?!? t'waz da last day of skool!!! WHOOOHOOO!! YEA!!! (clears throat) (shuffles papers) (silence) yea. im calm now. 2day waz pretty good 2 tell u da truth. after 4 dayz of holding bak, i finally told jenini & may my "confession". it waz about who i like.. dont ax who cuz im not tellin no1 else. i like dis dude cuz hez jus cute & funny lol. there now ya kno y. richie'z really annoyin me man. he keeps stealin my words, i mean jus cuz may can do it dont mean he can. bak 2 my day.. dat "person" dat i "like" (lol) we shall call him "mystery boii", well i axed him 2 sign my autograph book & he smiled @ me & signed it!! yay!! it waz kool, i luvv boiiz dat arent afraid 2 smile.. unlike some PEOPLE.. douggie never smiles n/e more cuz hez supposedly a "pimp" & he tries 2 b kool eventho itz better when he smiles, but u kno, watever. dirt off ur shoulder doug. 2day we got our class pix & somn they may call "yearbook", but 2 ME, itz not a year book, itz a pile of papers stapled w/ plastic cheaper den a $2 ho & misspelled truthfullnesses & funnies. itz ok i guess, but i wouldnt call it a "yearbook", no pix, no cover, no nuin, jus "Class of 2004". im gonna miss som ppl who arent goin 2 taft. like 4 example: jenini, richie, matt d. (lol), armin, svetla, cia, bryan, luke o., mimma (lol go gators!), amanda g. (good luck in texas gurl, lol ti si majmun), tom, joel (previous list waz in no particular order). so yea. man y do i keep sayin yea. maybe cuz i wanna yea. lol. im j/p ppl who reads this. well since i cant think of n/e thin 2 talk bout n/e mo & since my job iz 2 jump from subject 2 subject, letz jus c how many ppl r online on my buddy list. 10 out of 72.. datz.. sad.. derz telly, other mimma, mikey*, me, jenini, richie, milano*, kam, slim shady, & my ex-online-bf stevie. blue haired blonde eyed boii, shit i mean blonde haired blue eyed boii. lol. dont u jus H8 colds?!? well i do.. u kno how i tole u evry time i sneeze my eye twitches? well now b cuz of my cold, evry time i chew or swallow food, da back of my ear itches & i cant scratch it 4 som reason. itz very bother-a-bibel. man i feel srry 4 jenini, she wanted "person she has a crush on" 2 say somn 2 her cuz of somn she wrote in this particular person's autobook, BUT this certain person didnt say nuin, 4 some reason. which iz y i felt srry 4 jenini. itz gonna b ok sweete. ima go now bye. (im still happy doe cuz of my crush person's smiles)  :)  :(
    


12,June,2004


	 
      yello!! we r all gathered here on this special occasion 2 c this weird lil bloggie & 2 hav a few laughs @ it. heh yea ok normal voice now. i am so dumb 2 tell u da truth... (long silence)... umm.. wanna kno y? well u all kno dat i can b bitchy somtimes (audience says: true). but i mean even i have a heart (audience: u do?!?!?). shut da heck up. u kno ya g2 4give ppl no matter wat they hav done, u hav 2 4giv dem somtime. now dis iz good. BUT der iz an excuse & itz about mart. u can go on w/ ur life w/out 4givin him even once. y? b cuz he doz NOT deserve it. he iz such a freekin jerk & i cant even explain it. i alwayz 4give him cuz i feel srry 4 him & hey itz cuz hez a total dork who has no frendz & all dat shit. so i beg of u, som1, da next time i go soft again & 4giv him 4 his bullshit PLEASE smack da shit out of me & tell me not 2 b a dumbass. thanx a bunch. ok now dat i got dat out of my system, i saw adi 2day w/ her hair & it really loox good. it matches her perfectly. i thot dat it would look weird since she said it waz dark, but itz lite brown, so itz all good. i saw hottt yello 2day & God help me but man i really dono but derz a 50% chance dat "hottt yello" iz dom!! dat iz not good. he waz chillin w/ peter.. i wonder y. dude i wonder where he livs.. please dont let him b dom plz plz plz. & yea im still obsessed w/ hottt yello, but i think dom iz real hott 2 but derz no point in liking him since i flicked him off last year 4 pretty much not a big reason & he liked me last year. o well lyfe sux wat can ya do.   :(   i want a guy tho. 4 sho. bybye ppl
    


11,June,2004


	 
      ya man.. lol.. jamaica.. who wouldnt wanna b there now? 2 get away from da hot hectic city? o well. man my dad iz really weird. i found directions from my crib 2 nini'z & hez like "how far iz it?" & i said "not even 2 miles" & he said "datz close, u could walk there" & i said "yea". 2 minz l8r, he goes "dont even think about walking there" & im like "yea". dude hez weird. mart still thinx dat hez a goth. LMAO. & he tole nini dat shez a gr8 goth. somtimz ppl can b dorx. u kno watz weird? evrytime i sneeze, my eye twitches & it really annoys me. & another thing dat annoys me iz my dad'z constant spraying of cologne in da house. 2day ima b really bord i think. cuz derz like nuin 2 do rite now so i doubt dat der will b l8r. u kno how my ex kept axin me out over & over again? well now he keeps axin me 2 go outside w/ him, dat it'll b "like old times". suure. i dont think so. n/e wayz.. i waz jus readin adi'z pro & all i hav 2 say iz DAMN SHEZ FUCKED IN DA HEAD. she "LOVES" pat (dude from 301) & hez da biggest jerk der iz. & she colored her hair brown, i think datz cuz bebe waz tellin her dat blondes r dumb & adi would do n/e thin 2 b popular & peer pressure ALWAYZ gets da best of her.. im talkin smokin bluntz, blow jobs, hangin w/ da worst, not goin 2 skool or doin da work & guess wat.. her mom dont giv a damn about dat shit either. yep. dis iz wat she callz lyfe. well ok im done here. ttyl maybe 2nite or somn. bybye
    


11,June,2004


	 
      im alwayz busy.. never hav time 4 my bloggie or me. itz all cuz of dis grad stuff but hey itz almost over, i only hav 2  more dayz of torture & nervousness. on monday iz da last day i hav 2 c da insides of da barn EVER & tuesday iz da grad day. i jus wanna get it over w/ & move on 2 SUMMER TYME!! yay! lotza fun & flirtin w/ hottiez, chillin w/ good frendz, & gettin annoyed by 'rentz. hey itz all part of lyfe. now i would like 2 take this oppurtunity 2 tell u wat happnd 2day. i'll try 2 tell u it in small words. it waz our luncheon & i went 2 skool w/ may, rockergirl*, her sis, & nina*. we came 2 skool & mr.ass goes "biljana go strait 2 room 107." fuckin fag! i h8 him! ms.k tellz nikki, bebe, & me dat our attire iz "innapropri8" yea.. my ass. so my dad comz & bringz my skool pants 2 change into. den when we get 2 da barn, may gave me her skirt 2 try on & it fit me. den jus when we r about 2 leave 4 da luncheon, some fat african lady comz 4 'lice chek'. she tole me i hav a 'sore scalp' & dat i hav 2 'shampoo' it more. wat a fag!! some of us hav dry skin dude, cant do shit about it. den arrive @ dino's (cheap place) & der we get our ribbons (which we got ppl 2 sign), our certific8z (jus 1 in my case), & our autograph boox (which we also got ppl 2 sign). i only got 18 ppl 2 write in it cuz we didnt hav enuff tyme but we gon get some tyme on monday. plus i didnt get 1 person, who i wanted in da book, 2 sign. dont even ax who since im not tellin yall. so we kinda had a good time & shady wrote "stay cool!!!" in my book. lol. im cool. datz jus.. cool. i g2 say man, 1 of my frendz iz greedy, i mean dont HOG our men. now i wanna fullfill my thnx 2 my peepz. big props 2 jenini cuz my girl has gutz!! congratz!! may thnx 4 alwayz bein so sweet 2 me!! alex thnx 4 da funny timez!! jana thnx 4 bein a gr8 frend & u did a gr8 job havin frendz on both sides!! it aint easy!! lena ur da sweetest cutest frend evr!! klaudia u've alwayz been kool & understandin our diffrnc, u da bomb!! i luv ya'll!! & last (but not least, n/e mo) i would like 2 send dis mssg out 2 k8: a gr8 weight has been lifted off my shoulders but i now need 2 learn how 2 balance myself w/ out it. 
ALL U GUYS R DA BOMB, EVEN DOZE DAT I HAVNT MENTIONED, DONT THINK I 4GOT. CUZ IT AINT GONNA HAPPN!!
I AINT GONNA 4GET YALL SO DONT 4GET ME!! LUV YA'LL PEACE OUT && CONGRATZ 2 DA DIRKSEN C/O 2004!!
    


09,June,2004


	 
      4got 2 tell ya somn.. ok well i dono if i mentioned it or not but jana has a new bf named bojan & hez kinda ok i guess. on a scale of 1-10 hez like a 6 or somn like dat (2 me). & 2day waz a big step... dey frenched!! omg i waz so happy 4 her but den freeked out @ da same time, so it waz.. confuzin. & i couldnt believe it cuz u kno da gurl has more experience w/ guys now den i do & maybe yall think dis iz stupid but i dont want a close frend of mine whoz my age 2 go off bein more experienced den me. i jus hope she dont take da xtra step if ya kno wat i mean. ok ima go now. bye. comment as u like.
    


07,June,2004


	 
      hey peepz, srry i didnt write in mr.blogger a.k.a. bloggie 4 a couple days but i keep 4gettin cuz i waz used 2 not havin a bloggie since i erased my old 1. yea, so 2day waz a busy day.. poor footsie. :(   lena & i went 2 da mall & i brought like a whole bunch of cash & she didnt bring n/e cuz she didnt really feel like buyin n/e thin so i bought us food... yay! & i bought shoez 4 da luncheon & gradu8ion (1 pair tho). their blak & kinda hii & den i bought a shirt 2 match my skirt 4 da luncheon. so we had a pretty good time @ da mall & we were jus walkin & talkin (lol walkie-talkie) & thinkin of which stores 2 go 2 next when guess wat.. jus guess who we c.. we r jus like walkin & den im like "hey lena look in front of us who it iz" & shez like "wat??......omg" & den shez all hiding behind me & der in front of us waz: pat & some dude i dono. & im thinkin "WTF man?" i noticed dat it waz pat cuz of his weird walk, itz unique so it had 2 b him. he walks like dat dude in 'edd, ed, & eddie' (no wonder dat dude iz on his buddy icon Lmao). so den hez all showin off & like "well look whoz here, hi" (all smilin & shit) & we're like "hi". & den (now tell me if dis iz a coincidence) lena & me were standin der 2 find out where 2 go next & we were about 2 go 2 da food court when derz pat again "hello again" & im like all confuzed "hi". & im like iz he followin us or wat. cuz yesterday lena & i went 2 minute-man (lmao.. not da guy, da gas station) 2 get some snax & den derz pat across da street & hez like "hi biljana" (like alwayz) & we're like "hi" & him & his frend (not da 1 from da mall) cross da street purposely & walk about 4 meters behind us 2 minute-man (lol again, not da guy.. da gas station). we enter & den im thinkin "plz dont come in here, plz dont come in here" & dey come in der & again he greets us & lena & me werent sure wat 2 get so we were like walkin across da whole store tryin 2 find somn & we saw dat da guys already had like stuff dey wanted 2 buy but dey were obviously 4 some reason waitin 4 us. so as soon as we paid & got out of der, dey were practically like 2 meters behind us. i mean dude if pat wants 2 hang out w/ us, he could jus say so instead of like sorta followin us. i would b more den happy 2 let him hang out w/ us, i mean itz not like hez some huge r. kelly-obsessed pervert who hits on any female his eyes c... hehe on other thot.. he IZ. yea. man talkin bout perv ppl makes me tired. (yawns) 2day we were practicin 4 gradu8ion & i waz so scurred & u kno evry1 has som1 dey walk w/ down da aisle [heh no we're NOT gettin married ESPECIALLY NOT (note:: word 'NOT' iz supposedly underlined 5 times) w/ da person im walkin w/!!] w/ som1, depends on da alphabetical order cuz since my last name starts w/ da letter 'B', im somwhere in da beginnin & i sit w/ bart on da rite & jess b. on da left, no offense but deyre both fat asses & i can barely sit der w/ rare room space. it sux. i mean jess i can stand som how but jeez.. ok i'll stop since i hav been offendin dese ppl practically all day & itz jus wrong & mean. im srry. u kno dat 1 hottt guy dat i liked dats real tall & a polak (sadly)? well.. adda (adrianna) & her sis even got deir paws on HIM. i waz pissed off yesterday i mean yea i dono him & yea i would NEVER hava chance w/ him, but itz like man @ least leave da hottt boii i like alone. o well watevr. im bein shellfish & yes dey could hav him. cuz im all talk & no do & i should "put my $$ where my mouth iz". im srry but im jus pissed off rite now. & 2day he looked @ me @ da end of da day which waz like 8:30 or somn & my hair looked like bloody hell & i didnt even kno it cuz lena never tells me when i hav flaws on my face & he jus gave me dis look & 2 me it waz somwhere in between an "im dissapointed" look & an "omg look @ ur hair" look & also an "i dono u" look but den again it waz also a cold look it looked like 2 me. plz dont ax me wher da hell i get dis bull from but i jus think i can read ppl. ok ima go now. da only reason i wrote dis much waz cuz my frendz were kinda not listenin 2 me 2day, ignorin me, & interruptin me. o well, not dat i care but i waz jus pointin it out. & yes i am shelf-centered & shellfish. thnx. bye.
    


07,June,2004


	 
      hi sup howz it goin? may waz jus shocked @ how much i wrote since she last read my blog. (MUAHAHAHA..evil laugh) thnx..may.. she jus added da "muah" 2 "hahaha". ok n/e wayz.. yesterday i waz absolutely bored, like a slug, moving from couch 2 couch, almost dying from da unbearable heat. & no1 waz there 4 me, all my frendz were either not home or didnt feel like goin outside or weren't allowed 2 go outside @ all. arrr i waz mad.. ok dat waz way 2 pirate-y. a dark secret unveiled 2day of a person we kno so well. yea,i cant tell u rite now since im in skool & som1 who passes by mite read my thots. evil evil-do-ers. and another 1 bites da dust. muahahahaha!! der comes mr. bitch. sheesh now alex comez & axz me who mr.bitch iz & i 4get wat im about 2 write. o da pain da torture! lol j/p. do u ppl think i need a guy 2 kinda slow my mind down? do ya? well if ya do, raise ur hand rite now. ok. i c how it iz. dont listen 2 me. FINE. dude im playin. ok i'll go now cuz may keeps sayin "umm.." evry 2 seconds cuz she didnt do her hmwk & she dono wat 2 write 4 her summary. ok now shez done & i think dougz listenin 2 britney spears LMFAO. ok c ya L8r cuz i aint got nuin else 2 say. (hey derz mr.bitch again) ok ima go now. thnx 4 listenin. bybye
    


04,June,2004


	 
      yo sup? yea itz me AGAIN. shut up, dis iz MY bloggie... dude who da fuck am i talkin 2? n/e wayz... ok u kno wat, 2day waz a LOONG ass day. 1st of all, jana & all da other ppl who didnt take da constitution test last year (if u dont take it or if u fail it, u wont gradu8 from 8th grade) had 2 take it 2day. they all studied as hard as they could & unfortun8ly failed it (they can re-take it) EXCEPT 4 a preppy lil polak named k8. she cheated on da most important test u could take in ur whole grade school life, i mean cmon not even i cheated on it last year. so evry1 knew dat she cheated on it, even mr.s but i dont think dat hez gonna do n/e thing since shez polish & so iz he, & he likes polish kids better den da rest of us (yea i kno itz prejudice). so since it jus waznt fair, we all urged jana 2 go tell on k8 2 mr.s. she didnt want 2 cuz k8 thot dat jana waz her frend (lmfao) & jana didnt wanna get mixed up in shit like dis. but no it waz mostly my fault & den lena said she would go w/ jana. they went there & told mr.s but all he said waz "ok". den jana regretted wat she did even after we told her dat it waz da rite thing 2 do. a lil l8r, lena, may, viki, & i were waitin 4 jana cuz she had 2 tell us somn (shez a street patrol person). so we waited & den i told jana wat lena told me kam did. i jus dont get how he can b such an ass & he expects jana 2 go out w/ him. well he heard us talkin bout how jana waz gonna tell on k8 so he rushed 2 tell k8 dat jana told on her. u kno he cant b frendz w/ both of us since we're enemies & he cooperates w/ both sides, but hey i guess he chose their side. i dont give a fuck. so when i told jana dat he did dat she couldnt believe it shez like 'hez not my frend n/e more'. & i seriously believe dat dis time he crossed da line. feel free 2 post ur opinion. so den as we were talkin 2 jana, i noticed dat ella looked like she had cried. & im like 'watz wrong hunny, y r u crying' & den she gives me a hug & starts crying. & im like 'wat happnd?' so jana starts tellin wat happnd wrongly & den ella corrects it, apparently some boii in her class waz harrassin her & pullin her hair & when she tells da teacher, da teacher dont do shit. & den we're all like 'dont worry' & den jana got scared dat shez gonna get it from k8. den me & may & lena & viki went home & a couple minz l8r, jana calls me on da fone. she tells me dat her & ella took seper8 ways home. ella went da original way cuz she said dat k8 iz her 'frend' & jana went around da blok cuz she waz scared of k8 & her frendz & da consequences. i waz jus like laughin @ how dumb dey were cuz 1st of all dey SEPER8ED!! i mean if bitchez start shit den stay da fuck 2gether! den ella said dat k8 iz her "frend" i mean hello shez acting. den as ella went home she saw k8 & she told ella 'i never cheated on dat test, i studied hard 4 it' & ella (how stupid of her) said 'my sister told on u' & den k8 said dat she didnt cheat & den ella said 'ru gona beat her up?' & k8 said no & jus when ella waz about 2 leave, k8 said 'im not gonna beat her up but my frendz r'. & den i waz laughin when jana tole me dat, yea she has soo many frendz. den jana said dat she regrets wat she did & bla bla & i told her not 2 worrie. o yea & i 4got 2 tell u, dis mornin while i waz waitin 4 may, mr. fuckin brown marked me tardy. MOTHAFAKA!!! DATZ 4 U!! U OLD WHITE BITCH!! but no cris didnt get marked tardy. den also i tole may yeserday dat i thot robby waz cute & funny.. ly perverted. lol. she waz a lil surprised. den 2day as me & may were sellin chox by jewel, derz dis hotttt guy dat i keep seeing 4 some reason (IM TELLIN U ITZ DESTINY lol) & he waz checkin me, & den he looked @ me & i looked @ him & may waz like beggin me 2 go 2 da pop machine where he waz standin & 2 ax him 4 change. we were debating dis 4 like 15 minz when may recognized dat i waz a chiken & gave up. den we were goin da same way he waz 4 a couple minz, i wonder y... may. & den we met up again like 2 times & da 3rd time he waz way far from us. but seriously man i saw dat guy like 6 times & not all @ da same location. plus hez a sox fan, & may wantz me 2 say hi or ax 4 his # but im 2 scurred. we now call him 'hott yello' lol cuz he waz wearin yello. den l8r we went 2 chill w/ 'fat & retarded' lmao j/p dude. & we were all talkin & shit & den big mac came & we were all talkin & mart waz tryin 2 flatten a tire when may tole him 2 stop. & den we went home @ like 9:10 pm (if my dad waz home he would hav killed me) & it waz funny cuz me & may were both goin away from mart & he waz jus standin der like 'wtf' & den he axed me wer he livd & i said 'do u need som1 2 walk u home' hez all like yea & den i waz like playin him like i waz gonna go w/ him & den i waz like nah & he waz all 'aw man' & den when i crossed da street he said dat hez watchin me, i waz fully aware of dat believe me. yea but i waz gonna do somn else, nvm dat itz jus my perv side. so when i came home, 2 my luck my ma waz sleepin, dat waz nice. actually, she still iz.. & yes she IZ breathin thank da Lord. ok i think im done here, i ratted evry1 out & datz dat. yay. ok bye.
    


02,June,2004


	 
      hi, i've been totally mizundaztood. ok i'll tell u y now. now. no not now. wait. wait. ok now. well u c, der iz my ex (my best frendz cuz) & well he jus still kinda makes me feel warm inside (not like DAT). now i kno itz over, i said it a million times & i dont want it 2 b happenin again but all dat iznt gonna change how i feel. no i wont get bak w/ him, itz just teenage confuzion rite now. ok. yea so i think dat he'z not so bad & i H8 how ppl put him down. i just dont like when ppl say somn bout som1 when they dont even truly know that person, especially if i still have some tiny feelings 4 dat person. another thing.. as they r dissing him, they r also dissing ME. y? well b cuz i went out w/ him, makes me da same as he "supposedly" iz. yea i do diss my frendz constantly b cuz itz just a joke, so those of u who DO get mad, ur not dat good of a frend. so wat i basically think dat may iz thinkin (may if ur readin dis, im srry 4 mentionin u hun) iz dat im like still in luvv w/ her cuz, which iznt true cuz i only like him a lil still, as a good frend. b4 i 4get dis (AGAIN) i wanna say dat i wanna go 2 da white sox game on sunday june 13th w/ u may but i keep 4gettin 2 tell u, & i hav 2 order ticketz in like a couple of dayz if were gonna go. ok. i hope u read dis in case i 4get (yea yea AGAIN). bak 2 talkin bout my ex.. i kinda miss talkin 2 him & shit like dat, but now it all jus became awkward, & b4 it used 2 b like 'watever u wanna say, say it' & joking around, well those times r gone 4 good. i jus g2 go on, i did but den i came bak.. 4 some reason. maybe dis iz jus da part of me dat feelz srry 4 him, i dono & i dont think i should care no mo. ok i'll shut up now, im supposed 2 go 2 sleep now but i dont feel like it. da only reason im alwayz on da net iz cuz im hopin som1 will talk 2 me. da only reason i alwayz go outside iz so dat guys can hit on me. da only reason i alwayz say hi 2 pat instead of ignoring him iz cuz i dont feel like arguing after all da shit i called him & i dont want him 2 get mad @ me.. jus like 4 evry other person, even tho pat doznt deserve my frendship. NEVER judge a book by itz cover. i didnt kno & now i g2 lay lo on da insults (not talkin bout pat cuz i'd still flick him off anyday). i hope dat only a small minimum of ppl read dis cuz dis only serves 4 da purpose 4 me 2 pour my heart out. bye g2g (BUSTEEEDD!!)
    


30,July,2004


	 
       Lol. Hello there fellow aliens, (ahem) I mean humans. Shh it's 11:01 & I'm still online. Ok the bald man mentioned in the title is Sidali &amp; he's back from wherever the hell he was. Of course I was once again called the ever-popular "horse shit". & Armin told Sidali "Sidali you're not funny...". Buurrrnn!! I got to come up with a good comeback for that dumbass. He was commenting on my shitting habits (made-up OF COURSE) &amp; I told him "U want to get slapped?" & he says "I already got slapped" &amp; I say "Yea by your mama" & he says "How do u know my mama?" &amp; I say "Well I know your daddy better". Awe man that was a nice burn. Lena was laughing her butt off. Armin was just standing there, faintly laughing & checking Lena out. But unlike the other guys, it wasn't noticeable. Ok so we dissed each other back &amp; forth & then when I was going home, Sidali said "Biljana I don't like u!" &amp; I said "I don't like u either! (mutters) bitch.." Then when Lena was going home, she told me that Sidali said "Where's Biljana? Is she afraid of the dark?" Lena said "You're afraid of your ass". Lol. Even though that makes no sense it's still funny. I missed Jenini &amp; our bus blues. Lol Her story of it is much funnier. Here if u want to check it out, her blog is the bomb.  urlLink www.browneyedfool.blogspot.com  So I have to go now. Sadly. And I shall talk tomorrow. Bye 

    


28,July,2004


	 
       Hi there. Well I got a funny little story to tell u. It happened yesterday though. Ok so I didn't eat breakfast or lunch & I felt like going to Subway (Eat Fresh lol). It kind of started out as a joke &amp; I asked Jenini if she would go with me. She said that she was going to ask her mommy. Before I knew it, her mommy said yes & Jenini was on the bus to my house. When she came we went to my house &amp; then to Subway. At Subway we got some grub & then went to my house again. I asked Jenini what she wanted to do today &amp; she said that she didn't know & it wasn't even 2pm yet &amp; she had to be home by 8:30. So I got the funky idea that we should go to the movies & see the long-awaited "The Bourne Identity" or as they write it on movie tickets, "Bourne Identity, The". Jenini agreed &amp; while we were on the internet waiting for my mom, Kasha asked if she could hang with us. It was kind of awkward but it's not like I hate her, so I said yea & invited her to the movies with us. She first though about it for a long-ass time &amp; then eventually she said that she wanted to go but that I wouldn't want her to. That's bullshit, man. So I set the record straight, but she still didn't want to & said that she was going to hang with us outside when we get back. The movie was starting around 5:15 &amp; ended 7:15. SO around 7:30 we were supposed to see her & Lena. So anyway, my mom couldn't drive us because of her fear of losing a parking spot on the street. So Jenini &amp; me were stuck taking the... BUS. On the way to the bus station, we cross the street because the Pink Pimps & etc. were by the school &amp; we were afraid to, once again, attract attention. Not that crossing the street changed anything. We just kept on converse & then Doug said "Hi Biljana" &amp; some other stuff that I couldn't hear good. But it was something about "looking good" probably. I said hi back but ignored the rest, whatever it might have been. Then we kept on walking, & on the way there, there were so many guys (of all ages &amp; races) honking at us & saying stuff to us &amp; smiling at us & turning up their crappy-out-of-style-techno-preppy-girl-singing-euro music. That was a little too graphic wasn't it? Heh. Yea. So then we almost made it to the bus stop, when our freaking bus drives away. It was 4:44 pm &amp; we had like a half-hour to get to the movies. So Jenini told me that the bus comes like every 15 minutes or so. Then I looked in my wallet & realized that I only had two $20 bills. I needed to get two singles because I wouldn't get change back from the bus driver. Then I ran across the street to Minute Man. They had NO CHANGE. How retarded are they seriously? Then I ran back &amp; told Jenini that they had none. She was surprised, so then we asked this girl that was also waiting for the bus. She didn't have any money with her. Then we ran all the way to Dunkin Donuts & the dude took his time but he had to take some out of his pocket, that was nice. Then we ran back &amp; we were almost to the bus station, when the bus passes by. We were waving, but the bus driver didn't care, & there wasn't anyone even behind her. What a biatch. Then we walked back to the bus stop. It was like 4:58 by now. At 4:03 came another bus, which wasn't' t ours, &amp; Jenini's mom was on it. Lol. She was like "What are u doing here?" & Jenini was like "Mom! What are u doing here?" &amp; then the bus driver left with Jenini's mom on the bus. Then we waited some more time. Other buses passed & I asked the lady if she was going our way &amp; she said no, that we had to take another bus. By now it was like 5:20 or maybe even later. It was that same lady that didn't want to stop for us. She was giving me directions on how to put the freaking dollar in the dollar slot & how to take the ticket. Bitch. It was $1 per person. She told me that we had to take another bus to the movie theater. But the bus stop was like half a block away. Well maybe her fat ass has to take another bus but we can walk there. So in that same bus was Ashley Kennedy (sister of Scott) &amp; some other girl. They asked us if we were going to the mall & I said that we were going to the movies. They were dressed all preppy-ly &amp; pink. Then we all got out at Gunnison & some other street. We walked a little &amp; then to the movie theatre. By now it was like 5:55 or something. We went inside to buy tickets. Then we went to buy some po...pcorn & drinks. Before I even got a chance to order, the guy insisted we buy this huge tub of popcorn with which u get two drinks &amp; a choice of candy bags. I bet that would've been expensive so I said no & that we wanted a small sized popcorn &amp; two cokes. He was being stupid the whole time & went like "THIS is your SMALL popcorn". I'm like "It is? Ok." What a fag. Sheesh, money doesn't grow on trees. Then we went with our stuff into the dark movie theatre where we heard people punching each other (in the movie, not in reality). Then we sat down &amp; watched. It was pretty interesting except for the fact that we missed the beginning of the movie, which is when u learn everything about what's going on. That kind of sucked. There was this old couple in front of us who just kept on doing that "clear your throat thing" & it was annoying. And then later Jenini &amp; me put our feet on a little part of the thing u lean your arm on. The lady turned her head really slowly back to us, like we had committed a felony. What are old senior people doing watching an action movie in the theatre anyways? I though old people didn't like that stuff. O well. So then we watched the movie, awesome chases, awesome new & old Beemers, awesomely hott Matt Damon &amp; awesome Europe with languages I mostly understood. I'm going to get both of those movies on DVD. My neighbor has the first one, so I'm going to burn it on my CD. Then in like the middle of the movie, I forgot to turn off the telly so Maja calls me. I turn it off so that it doesn't disturb the movie-watchers. Maja is only using Lena & me because she doesn't have any other "friends" at the moment. When the movie finished, it was 7:14 &amp; Jenini & me disappeared out of the movie theatre in an instant. We threw half of our medium-sized cokes away. Then we walked to the bus stop. We again attracted lots of attention. If we had crossed the street to the other bus stop, we wouldn't have missed another bus &amp; would've been able to use that card once again & not pay $4 extra. So we missed 3 buses in 1 day. Lol. But I seemed to not find it sad, but hilarious. Then finally around 7:41 (5 minutes earlier would've saved us $4, stinking bus driver had to go take a freaking piss probably) the bus came. Then we exited &amp; I said, "Thank God we're back". Then I told Jenini how the Pope always kisses the ground once he gets out of a plane safely. Then she mentioned "What if there are germs on the ground?" & I heard "What if Ms. Falby's germs are on the ground?". Then we walked back &amp; saw Bebe, Zampini, Rita & someone else but I can't remember who. Then across the street walking by the school by himself, was LS. When he saw me, he looked down &amp; I did the same. We didn't greet each other & that was the first time since we met that we didn't say hi to each other. O well, I don't care, his loss. Then Jenini &amp; me went to my house to eat because we were hungry (or at least I was). We ate lasagna & later Jolly Ranchers. It was good. As we finished, it was like 8:15 already &amp; I called Lena to go outside with us for a couple minutes. No one picked up the phone, so we were headed to her house. I rang the doorbell &amp; the door buzzed. Then we waited in front of the door & no one came out. I knocked &amp; Lena said "Come in!" Then we came in & she was like "Aren't u guys a little late?" I'm over there thinking "Little??" But Lena changes &amp; I use the bathroom & then we go outside. Lena tells me that Milan came over &amp; that he was acting all dumb & talking Serbian &amp; whenever Lena made fun of him & the way he talks, he would playfully smack her on the head. She said it was weird. Then we walked around Polak world, it was kind of deserted. But I saw Matt &amp; some other Polaks all the way behind the last building, I think that's where they smoke shit & smuggle crap. Heh, that sounded funny. Then we walked toward the pool &amp; on that side was Kasha & some other Polaks. We greeted each other &amp; then passed by. Then we went to sit in Polak world & awaited "the call", because it was almost time to leave for Jenini &amp; me. Then a couple minutes later my ma calls to tell me that my dad's waiting on the parking lot to drive Jenini home. Then we get into the crappy little red Kia Sephia. We were listening to the Beatles, my God. & then came the song, "You aree sooo beautifuuul" &amp; it almost made me puke. Then I changed the radio station to B96 96.3, The New Killer Bee. Then Jenini & me talked until we got to her place &amp; I thanked her for coming. Then I went home & went on the net. Then I did my fingernails, they look pretty stupid to me, but whatever, I tried. When KZ comes back from Florida tomorrow or maybe he won't come outside tomorrow but the day after, but the main point is, that I'm not going to talk to him at all, just like LS. The reason is because he ruined my friendship, or what was of it, with Kate. He shouldn't have told her that I hate her. That was back then, I don't hate her anymore, but even if I told her that, do u REALLY think she'd believe it? No. Yesterday I started out with $51 &amp; after Subway, bus tickets & a movie, now I have $6. So I'm going to go now, I've been typing for about 2 hours &amp; this must be the longest blog entry in the history of blogs. So I'm going to go take a shower now & hope that the temperature goes up because today is skirt day, but currently it's 71 degrees Fahrenheit. So bybye &amp; have a shweet day. 

    


28,July,2004


	 
       All right. All right. That was an inappropriate title but I need to express the anger. He is such a freaking jerk. If u don't know who "he" is, then let me tell u. L.S. Ok so this is what happened.&nbsp;Around 5 something pm, L.S. calls me on the phone to see what I'm doing. We talked for a while & then all of a sudden he has to go because his mommy came into the car &amp; he's too scared to talk to me then. This is what I figured since he suddenly had to go. But he told me that he's going to "call u later". Riiight. Like that's going to happen. I knew he wouldn't call me but I didn't give a shit. So around 7:55 pm Lena calls me & tells me that she feels better &amp; that if I want, we can go outside. I say ok & we go.&nbsp;She tells me how she saw L.S. with these chicks Renata, Marlena & some other one. She said that he looked extremely happy. Anyway, Lena &amp; me walked around for a little & then we went to sit in Polak world. Whoa. I just saw the weirdest thing&nbsp;on the TV. There was a weird, say, "cartoon"&nbsp;on the news about Kerry & Bush. They were competing about whose land it is by singing (with different lyrics) the song "This land was made for u &amp; me" (that's not what the song is called but I forgot what it's called, I think some Johnny guy wrote it). O & at the end, Bush &amp; Kerry joined hands, it was a funny sight to behold but it was also strange. Anyway, on with the Polak world crisis crap. Well Lena & me went to sit there, when out of nowhere comes L.S., he was hanging out with Kasha (whom I waved to 3 times but she didn't "SEE" me) &amp; her cousin & cousin's friends before we came. All righty then. He came to talk to us &amp; we talked for a while & then I said "it's not illegal to sit" &amp; he's like "aw u took my spot" so he sat a bit farther away. I take it as, he did it on purpose. Then the third sentence that came out of his mouth was "So where's your friend?". & out of us 3 (Maja, Lena, &amp; me), Maja's is the only name he can remember. Then came&nbsp;Ivana &&nbsp;Patricia (a fat & skinny duet, Polaks of course). He started talking to them, they surrounded him. He didn't talk to us at all anymore. Then eventually Kasha came when she saw that Lena &amp; me were being ignored & were talking to each other. I hate him. He is such a jerk. But yet Lena thinks I'm jealous. I used to be jealous because let me ask u, how would u feel if ANY girl that passes by talks to him &amp; sits next to him & flirts with him &amp; u like him? But once again, I don't care, I like someone else (who, by the way, ignored my "hi" today, it wasn't that he didn't see me, because he looked me right square in the eye, but he can't say hi once again, he did it last week). So then Kasha told us quietly that she doesn't like those girls either, she once greeted them but all they did was give her the cold shoulder & look away. Then my dad called me &amp; I had to go. Lena (she's really nice, maybe I should have done the same last time but I was too scared) asked Kate if she wanted her to stay & Kate said yea because she didn't really have anyone to talk to. L.S. didn't say bye, not that I expected it, I'm just telling u. Then I went home &amp; thought of what a dumbass I am. Next time Lena & me are hanging out somewhere, &amp; he comes, without K.Z. that is, I'll just walk away. I have enough people bullshitting me, I don't need another. Hey look, it's Maja being online. I hate her too. For God's sake, why doesn't she just tell him that she likes him too & that they get together, damn it. O yea, Brandon apparently likes Maja, man I don't get it, he's a nice guy &amp; she's just weird. Whatever, I'm not the one to be telling people who to have a crush on. It's all good. Maybe I should change my quote since SOMEONE already stole it. O yea & u know how I talk to people on the internet, I have been seeing a lot of them using my little, thought-of phrases. I don't mind if it's one of my friends, but if it's someone whom I dislike, then that's going to be a problem. U know what else? L.T. IMs me &amp; says "Elo laska". I looked the word "laska" up in the free Polish online dicKtionary & it said that the word means "stick". Um... "Elo" might mean hello but "laska"? Did he call me a stick? Lmao. Whoo. That's funny but then again, weird. Why do most guys treat me like shit? Is it a tradition? Milan came back from Serbia &amp; Lena saw him & he was constantly talking Serbian but he NEVER used to talk Serbian before, just English (except, of course, with his parents). &amp; Lena said that he sounds weird & that he's acting weird. That's... weird. Man I don't know what to say today. I like a guy that's maybe taken already by the biggest hoe in the hood, no offense. Omg, now I realize where she gets all the money to buy those expensive clothes! Stupid me. Just like in 50 Cent's song "In the hood they say... 'there's no place like hoe biz' ". That's only a part of it, there's also showbiz, I would prefer that &amp; possibly it pays better. That's a big maybe again, because hell I've never been there. Heh. Or have I? Hmm... I guess it's a mystery. I'm like trying to cheer myself up, but it's not really working. I'll tell u what will cheer me up, never to see this Polak hood again. They're all jerks &&nbsp;the manager of Polak world&nbsp;(with his Harley) is trying to be all "popular" with Fierce. That's what I call one of the tall, muscle-ly Polaks (he's kind of&nbsp;hot, lol nah). So anyway, how's your life people? Holla back below on the "comments" link. Thanks a bunch &amp; much love to the non-jerks. Peace. I holla.  

    


27,July,2004


	 
       Hi there. Umm... just in case u haven't noticed, I'm trying to hurry. Because I just realized what time it is & that I have to get off off the net in... let's see... 4 minutes! I'm not that fast with my thinking. Ok so yea today I woke up at 6 am again &amp; went with my dad to Detroit, Michigan. Home of our famous Eminem. YEA! So then we went to these people's houses & my dad left me with this lady, my dad's friend's mom. She was so nice &amp; really funny. Just like my mom. We talked & talked &amp; she showed me pictures of her younger son. Man the brothers are hot, even though they are older than me. It's like theire "tall, dark & handsome". Well not that tall but yea. So anyway, I sadly couldn't meet the younger son of hers because he had to work. But I saw the Ferrari they used to own. Hell yes I said FERRARI F550. Tight ass s***. Fo' shizzle ma nizzle. Lol. Man I love that car plus the guy standing next to it was mighty fine. O yea &amp; they sold the car to some dude in Florida not so long ago. Did u know that only one oil change in a Ferrari costs $2,000? A lot isn't it? O well I have to go now. Man parents are annoying. Talk to u people later &amp; yea. Peace. (Man I love Ferraris but don't forget the beemer....beeemerrr...) 

    


26,July,2004


	 
        Hi. Yesterday I  tried  to write a blog entry but my stupid, retarded computer froze 3 times. Then I had to restart AOL & I lost the whole entry that I wrote, plus it was long. How sad. Anyway, yesterday I was happy because Jenini could come over to my house. It was all good &amp; we&nbsp;went to pick up Lena&nbsp;to hang out with us. It was nice, friends hanging out & having a "picnic" (sort of). Then Maja came to join us, out of nowhere &amp; uninvited. That kind of ruined it. Nothing I expect ever happens, just the exact opposite. I'm already getting used to that crap.&nbsp;She's just like a second Nicole. They could practically be related.&nbsp;There's something that most Serbians & Bosnians have about them, something special &amp;&nbsp;unique. Maja, on the other hand, doesn't&nbsp;have that. She's completely Americanized. She lives in the Abercrombie & Fitch world. I don't&nbsp;currently want&nbsp;people to call her a "friend" of mine, because that's not easily obtained, it takes time. Just like with everyone else. But then again, some people are just not meant to be my friends. That could be the case here, but&nbsp;u never know. Life always&nbsp;plays tricks&nbsp;on u. And another thing, there's something fishy about her & I don't trust her right now. Ok change the subject. Today the weather is pretty crappy. Are we supposed to call this time of year "summer"? It sure doesn't seem like it. I read on AOL about Saddam writing poetry, one of the poems being about Bush. I hope that it tells the truth, because Bush only wants to be an evil dictator to our nation &amp; he wants to fulfill his father's wish. But don't think that J.Kerry is much better, because Bush & him are cousins. So pretty much whoever wins, they're all unfair, rich a******s. Mostly all politicians are the same. That is my opinion. Yea sure why not, I hate everyone. But my friends are still there, for now. Show the love people. &amp; if anyhow possible, listen to Kanye West & his song "Jesus Walks". It's true that u can't spell crap without rap but it's not crap. I'm being serious. Ok well see u later. I'm supposed to hang out with Lena, Maja, (blah) &amp; Pat & his people today.&nbsp;LS is a total jerk & he's not cool anymore, just a faker like everyone else. Congrats to Lena that her crush likes her &amp; I wish everyone the best of luck. Much love &amp; until next time. Peace.  
 



    


24,July,2004


	 
       Hello there. I bet you're wondering what the title's&nbsp;about. Three names: Milan, May, K.Z. What it's all about? Well Milan left for Serbia at the beginning of July. May left for Slovakia today :(. And K.Z. left for Florida today but he's coming back in a week. So next Saturday is a good day. I'm going to miss him but it's only a week so it's all good. May's coming back in a month. Milan's coming back pretty soon, not sure when, but before May. So I went outside with May for about an hour to say good-bye, talk & listen to music. We saw K.Z. &amp; Peter (doesn't matter who u are but u probably don't know him)&nbsp;but there was NO greeting. Rudeness. We went to Lena's so that Lena could say bye to May but when I rang the doorbell, there was her sis (extremely tired-looking) &&nbsp;we woke&nbsp;Lena & her sis &amp; bro&nbsp;up (12:35 pm).&nbsp;It was mean of me but o well. Then Lena went back to sleep. Then later May left :(. I was on the net until my dad had to go pick my mom up from work, wanting me to go with but I didn't want to. So I stayed home waiting for Lena's call or IM. She IMed me around 3 something (I think) & we were headed outside. Then we went to sit in Polak world &amp; all of a sudden out of nowhere, there comes L.S. on K.Z.'s bike. Then he said that he'll be right back with K.Z. He comes back & says that K.Z. is all wet or whatever because he was playing with waterguns with the little Polak dudes. Then we talked &amp; then there comes Peter & K.Z. I don't know what''s wrong with K.Z., he (for some reason) seems pretty sad about something. I don't know why. Lena told him "Why are u sad?" &amp; he said " I am?". So yea. K.Z. Had to get to Florida with his parents & sister, then L.S. &amp; Peter were left. Then Peter goes to follow K.Z. on his bike & he tells L.S. that "I'll be right back". I can't even count how many times I've been fed that line, hell it's Pat's favorite. So then L.S. is left all the way on the other end of the wooden board sitting thing in Polak world. I'm like "They all left u".... "So how is it down there". And he tells me to come sit there. I'm thinking "Should I sit  right  next to him or about half-a-foot away?" So I decide to do the second one. Then I sit next to him &amp; he tells Lena "And u come sit here" (on his other side, he was sitting in the middle of us). Then we're talking & Peter comes. L.S. Is all like "Look, one here, one here". &amp; Peter's all like "Yea... pimp". Then we're all talking & somehow we started talking about Kasha. I know L.S. likes her, he's always playing around with her. Then L.S. says something about Kate &amp; I go "bitch" like under my breath. & he says "Why don't u like her?" &amp; I start explaining, in short form. Then he says "Yea I think I told her that u don't like her" I'm like "What? U did?" & he's like "Yea... I think it was K**** (K.Z.)" I'm thinking "O shit..." &amp; then (speak of the devil) there comes Ana & asks L.S. if he's seen Kate. He says no &amp; tells us "Why is she always asking me if I saw her, it's like I'm going out with her or something..." & I'm thinking "You're not but u wish u were". I mean he's too good for her, Lena asked me if I was jealous. So yea... What else is new? Lol sorry for changing the subject. I like him but I'm not jealous, what am I supposed to do if he likes her more than me? O well. They'll see when I learn Polish, all those guys will want ME. Yup. Ok I'm being stupid now. I didn't get a chance to go to HIN today because my dd was drunk &amp; couldn't drive me & Lena. Sucks doesn't it? So I have to go now. Blah. L.T. wants to *yea* me &amp; Lena badly. Like today she asked him "What's up?" & he said "My d***". PERV. Pat's going outside on Monday, Lena made him, she IMed him. So yea Jenini holla &amp; see ya'll soon. Peace.  


    


23,July,2004


	 
        Hi people. Yay! I'm having fun! Finally they've made   urlLink www.blogger.com   simpler. Hooray for the people behind the scenes! Thanks a bunch. Anyway, I have to make this short because it's after eleven pm & I'm supposed to be off the internet but hey my dad is sleeping so I'm safe for now. About my day, or should I say days, well on Thursday July 22, 2004, which was the day before today, which was yesterday, I went with my dad to Michigan &amp; back to pick up & drop off loads with the truck. That morning &amp; this morning I had to wake up at 6 am. Then yesterday we came back at 10 pm, that sucked. Today everything was the same except that we made it back about an hour earlier, so around 8:45 pm. That was good. I have Saturday & Sunday to chill out with Lena if that's possible. May's leaving for SK tomorrow at 1 pm. I'm going to miss her. :(&nbsp; But she's coming to say good-bye so that's good. But what sucks is that I really wanted to see the movie "The Bourne Supremacy"&nbsp; (Matt Damon is hott) which is the sequel to "The Bourne Identity" with May. But there was no time because it came out in theaters today & bla-bla-bla... Long story. So I want to go to Hot Import Nights (HIN) tomorrow. It's at the McCormick Place from 5&nbsp;pm to midnight. Then at 2 am, the Playboy 50th Anniversary chick is going to tell the people which club the after-party is going to be at. Of course if I were to go, I probably wouldn't be able to stick around after 8 pm. But not like that matters since I'm probably not even going, just like all the White Sox games I've missed. If u don't know what HIN is, it's a car show with hot imported street race cars there. U can also enter your own car but of course some things have to be souped-up in it. The girls come for the hot guys & some (like me) come for the hot cars. The guys come for the hot cars &amp; Playboy girls. I REALLY want to go. I've never truly been up close to those kinds of hot cars, which is why I'm looking forward to it because I'm a street race car fanatic. So tomorrow I'm hopefully going to hang out with Lena. I think we pissed off Maja, because we went outside without her, I even told her that I was going to call her but I didn't feel like it. So while we were outside, she was coming from the store with her mom, & she barely looked at us &amp; just looked away. Man I don't even care, I have enough friends. It's just that she doesn't know how the world works around here & it'll take her a while to get it. Which is exactly why she's not currently fitting in. I'm sorry for being rude &amp; not understanding but when she finally gets how this Chitown shit works, she can truly hang with us. It's not like I immediately had friends either. So anyway, I talked to Pat last night & tonight. Yesterday he was extremely happy, excited &amp; nervous but also scared. Tonight he's just really sad. I hate when people are sad, makes me sad. But if u want to know what's going on with him, let's just say it has something to do with a girl & her ex-boyfriend. So sadly Pat &amp; the chick, didn't work out because of the ex... He tells me stuff like this, but don't tell this to anyone, I would be dead. Kam doesn't call me anymore, that's really good. I never know what to say when he calls me & he always calls me at the wrong time. I hated that. But now it's over, at least that's what he has me thinking. I haven't seen L.S.,&nbsp;Tom,&nbsp;or&nbsp;K.Z. in at least 3 days. That's way too long. So hopefully I'll see them tomorrow or the day after because on Monday I'm being forced to go on the road with daddy-o again. How fun. Blah. So yea I guess I'm going to go now, got a full weekend ahead of me, along with lots of things to do. Bybye. ps:: Jenini when will u be online so that we can arrange a day when u can come to my house (if anyhow possible)?  

    


21,July,2004


	 
      Hello reader. I purposely skipped yesterday's entry because I was a little, umm... tired I guess. First I'm going to tell u about yesterday. I went outside with Lena & Maja & we were hanging out & stuff. Then we went to Minute Man & while we were coming back from MM, we saw L.S. & K.Z. About time L.S. calls him outside. Not that I have a problem with his friend Tom but he barely speaks English so it's tough to hold a conversation. When the guys came back from MM, were were all hanging out & talking (L.S., K.Z., Lena, Maja, & me). They got to know Maja & stuff, but they're afraid of her, lol it's the whole "I came from Texas" thing. So anyways, L.S. still likes me, it's noticeable. He's still a hottie. So then we were all talking & he again asked to see my crappy telly & I asked to see his cool telly. Lol this sounds so wrong if u don't know what telly means. I "secretly" got his number off the telly, so what though, he got mine off my telly a week ago. So we have each other's numbers but there's really no point because I would never have the guts to call him & I don't think he would want to call me, the Freshie (Freshie not in a good way). So then we were all still talking & Maja was practically flirting with L.S. but I still got the major... um... loving lol. Out of total peace, all of a sudden there comes the little 1st grader named Bart & his little friends & they start throwing clumped dirt at us. We are all like "Wtf?" but they kept doing it until we went away, when we went away they still kept throwing though. Lena was pissed & L.S. was like "Aww man it's in my hair." I was thinking "Aww poor baby". Lol. So then we got tired of the dirt throwing & L.S. went over to them & before u knew it, they were gone. We were surprised & asked him what he said. He told as that all he did was tell them "If u guys don't stop in 5-4.." & as soon as he got to 4 they were gone. Anyways, I just talked to L.T. on the internet & he said "u BITCH" for no reason & then i said "fuck u" & he said "when" & I said "haha yea u wish" & he said "yep". & Pat is online, but I'm too chicken to say anything. So yea I still like L.S. but I didn't see him today, maybe him & the guys went to Hooters or something, I mean u could go anywhere if u have a car (or if Tom has a car in this case). So let's talk about my day shall we? I mean, let me talk about my day shall I? Ok. That's better. Well today I woke up (once again awakened by the loudness caused by parents) & couldn't go on the internet all day until now. Then I baby-sitted my little neighbor & his little friend & let me tell u those boy do NOT know how to share. Every 10 minutes they argue about a toy "mine" "no mine" "MIIIINE!!" Sheesh. Then I went outside with Lena, once again not feeling like calling Maja for SOME REASON. "Well it's all about the guys isn't it?" u might ask. But I tell u, no it isn't. By the way, today I saw Jana & her cousin Snjeza & Jana accused me of going out with Justyna's bro. Yea sure, I wish. So then Lena & me were walking around & let me tell u, short-shorts can work some magic. So many guys honked & said stuff to us. Sasa said a comment. Lena's boy was checking her out. It's all good. I guess. Except for the fact that "my boy" didn't show up, therefore explaining the title. He's probably cheating on me. How could he? After all we had... lol I'm just joking. U know what? I hope that Jenini can come to Polak World soon. Well tomorrow I have to go to Michigan with my dad because he doesn't know how to operate the computer in his truck, so I'll be away for two days, maybe back later Friday or early Saturday. Sucks badly doesn't it? & u know what else? I have to get up at 6. AM. Aw man Pat just signed off... I want to talk to him, it's been like about two weeks & maybe longer since I've last seen him or talked to him. Stupid fat kid who wants to beat him up. So anyways, I have to go now. Well not really but I don't know what else to say. Thanks for the numerous comments & keep them coming. Goodbye.
    


19,July,2004


	 
      Hello. Today my dad again woke me up at 7:30 am. I hate this. I'm always tired when I get woken up that early in the morning. So Lena & me (Maja was supposed to come but I didn't feel like calling her, I'll have to call her tomorrow... I kind of ditched her but o well) went outside around hmm... let's say 3 or 3:30 pm. L.T. is EXTREMELY happy. Everytime he passes by he smiles at us, even worse than before. But before it used to be cute but now it's too much. Although no guy in this neighborhood has an ass like him, I once again apologize for being so graphic. This ALWAYS happens to me, when I like a guy, he doesn't even know I exist but when I'm over him, he starts liking me. That's my luck, what can u do. So Lena & me hanging out & then L.S. & Tom came, they talked to us a little, then they went to put away the food they got at 'Hooters'. I bet they had fun there. L.S. said that they tipped $8 to this one waitress... damn that's a lot for a tip to one person, once again my opinion. Then when they left, Justyna a.k.a. Sk8er Gurl, came & we talked for a couple minutes & then she left to go to the park again. Then L.S. & Tom kept coming & leaving. Then Kate came & she talked to us for a while & that's when I found out why Tom always speaks Polish, he came to the U.S. for a vacation, he actually lives in Poland. So he only knows a couple words in English. He's not so bad, he smokes some tight ass cubans though. Justyna told us (while L.S. wasn't there) that her bro said that there was a new chick (Maja) & that she's hot. & when Lena told him about that, he was all like "I said that?". I knew that he liked her, it was kind of noticable. But he supposedly still likes me. I'm always into the "pimps", someone tell me why? So Pat never goes outside because he's afraid of this one dude who wants to beat him up. I wonder what Pat did to deserve that honor, by the way, the same guy wanted to beat Chris (Rini's bro) up. Maybe it's all connected. But Lena & me kind of miss talking to Pat, he was pretty friendly. L.T. said that he talked to Pat yesterday & that he still likes me, not that it matters, I'm just saying. Then today L.T. took a cheap little marker & wrote on one of the stone poles that Lena & me are hot girls. & then he told us that Pat paid him a dollar to do that. What's really weird is that most guys that like me, like Lena too, what so they think? That this is a 2 for 1 deal? Not going to happen. Kamil didn't call me even once today, but I called Pat to talk to him. Someone picked up the phone, but all I could hear was loud techno music, supposedly in Polish. Some drivers are retarded, when someone's phone rings, aren't u (the driver) supposed to turn your gay little Polish techno music down? Sheesh... so when I couldn't hear nothing but music, I hung up. I didn't get called back & didn't expect to. So Mart was walking down the same side of the street as Lena & me today with May's bro. As he passes me, he looks me up & down & says "Yo". I just look at him in disgust & turn away. SCORE!! Lol sorry but that's what he gets for fucking around with me (not in that way, HELL NO). So today May went outside with us for a while but then she had to leave. It was nice to finally have her around for a while. She's really busy now though because she's packing to go to SK. She's leaving on Saturday, but she'll be with us in spirit. But I hope she has fun & a nice summer. What am I going to do the rest of the summer? Probably find a new guy, or something, hopefully I'll find one that's not a "pimp" or something of the sort. So L.S., my new opinion about him is that he's hot with his 6-pack & I love his eyes but I just wouldn't want to get hurt or something. Well I'm going to go now, got nothing else to talk about. So people of the freaking earth, leave a freaking comment! I beg of u! Thanks Bye.
    


18,July,2004


	 
      Hi. Today I woke up at 7:30 am, the reason was because we went to Magic Waters in Rockford. What I really hate about my life is that everytime I expect something to turn out one way, it turns out a completely different way. I expected today to be really nice, just like last summer when we went to the same spot, but it was awful, my dad & uncle ruined it all. My uncle is trying to tell me what to do, what an asshole & my dad was acting like he was all that. I'm so annoyed by them. But hey at least we kind of had fun (Lena, Nikki & me) in the pool & stuff & I got a really nice tan. At least that's what I think. Anyway, I talked to L.T. on the net yesterday, I told him something kind of revealing & right after I said that, I get the message "this is not L***, it's his brother". I was shocked but all I said was "kool". Lol. I'm keeping it cool, I get too mad at people anyways most of the time. The only guy that I don't want to get mad at is L.S. I decided what I'm going to do. I'm going to tell him how I really feel & not lie about crap, because I've seen the way he looks at me & I want to give the same back to him. This is all going to turn out fine, hopefully. What kind of made me make this decision is my aunt's little quote that she told me today, "It's never too late." But the thing is, it had nothing to do with what I'm talking about right now. Sometimes being brave is good. Right? I change feelings really fast don't I? I mean just about a week ago (maybe less) I liked L.T. a lot (but hey maybe it was just the umm... behind lol), but now.... nah. Now I really like L.S., he's awesome... awesomely hot. But it's not all about that, personality is more important than looks. And those of ya'll who judge people, don't hate. So yea, I will make myself have the guts to do what I've got to do. Justyna being there might ease the situation, but hey she's always out with Edd & Chicken, it's getting annoying. And u know what else is annoying? Kamil. God. He calls me every freeking day just to "see what you're doing". I can't stand it anymore & my dad keeps asking who it is & I have to lie to him because if I tell him that it's Kamil I'll get in trouble since my dad has problems with me & guys. But damn I don't even care when it comes to L.S. Even if I get into trouble, It'll be worth it just so I can see him. So yea I'm not going to get too excited because I will probably mess something up... or I won't get a chance to talk to him. I hate the part of me that's shy, but I was never supposed to be shy but it's because my parents were way too strict when I was little, so it kind of stayed with me. Stupid shyness. So I'm going to go eat blueberries now with cereal. Sweet. Ok bybye muchy luvvy (to a special someone hehe). ps:: im bak... & L.T. IMed me while I was away but I'm not saying anything back, don't ask why. 
    


17,July,2004


	 
      O boy. Hi. I'm such a dufus (no that's really not funny this time). I really regret denying that I like L.S. That was so very stupid, my stupid dignity & pride of playing with guys & their feelings. I noticed something different about him today, like every 2 minutes he would take a deep breath, like something is bothering him. Lena thinks that he is sad. I should'nt have taken her advice, I'm so stupid, I should take my own advice not people's. I always mess up something when it comes to guys, it's a freaking tradition. Anyway, aside from my stupidity, Lena & me met this chick, she's Serbian & she came from St.Antonio, Texas & she has a Southern accent it's really cool. Her name is Maja (pronounced Maya) & she's 14 & she's going to go to Taft with us. She's kind of nervous to meet new people & crap but o well. So to tell u the truth, me have competition. I'm not in the mood to say anything else so I'm going to go now. Bye.  :(
    


16,July,2004


	 
      Hi. I barely had any sleep last night. One reason was because I was hungry & I can never sleep when I'm hungry & another unfortunate side effect of hunger is having too much time on your hands & then thinking about guys. Anyway, Lena & me went shopping around 1:30 pm & came back around 4 pm. I thought that I told her to call me, but she never did, so my mom told me & my dad to go to the store to buy something for my mom. As I was away, Lena IMed me & asked me if we are going outside. I don't understand why she didn't call me instead of IMing me while I was NOT THERE. So 10 minutes after she asked me if we are going outside, she tells me that she's going to the park with her bro & sis & that we can go outside tomorrow. I got ditched. Even though she promised me, she still ditched me. I mean is it so hard to pick up the phone & call a person? Sheesh. So in the IM it said that she was coming back at 8, which wasn't true because her bro went on the internet again at 7:18 pm. We could've gone outside but I guess she didn't want to because she didn't call me or nothing. Whatever. She's like the only friend I have right now (except for Justyna, her bro, & K.Z.), everyone else is just not available. I'm not mad or anything, I'm just telling u. U know what's bad about being reasonable-looking? When a guy likes u, u never know if he really likes u & ur personality or if he just likes u because of your looks. That sucks doesn't it? Yea. Well I'm not sure what else to talk about... L.T. didn't IM me yesterday, I would IM him but I don't have his s/n. I don't even think that we'll be able to chat on the net because I can't stay no longer than 11 pm, & he probably goes on later. How gay is that? O well, once again there is nothing I can do. Not that it matters, I know that L.T. likes Lena & me & some other chicks, but he likes me the least probably. All the cute ones are always pimps. I spent $44 on a skirt, shirt, belt, wallet, & 1 lingerie item. That sucks too. Can anyone tell me what DOESN'T suck? Guess not. Ok well wish me luck for tomorrow. Peace out.
    


15,July,2004


	 
      Hey. AGAIN. I was nearly done with my entry when all of a sudden it all dissapears and I have to start all over again. Damn this crap. This time I'm going to make it shorter because my fingers are getting tired. Of typing that is. Ok I woke up around 12 pm & went on the pc. Went towards Lena's house because we were supposed to hang out outside. As I pass Polak world, Justyna & L.S. (her brother) tell me to come over there, he makes me mumble so I said that I'll be right back (at least that's what I think I said). Then I met Lena & we went to Polak world. We talked to the guys & Justyna for a while & messed around when Lena notices a noticable flaw on my face & we decide to go to my house to fix it. As we are leaving, L.S. flashes me. Lol. The boy has a 6-pack! Hot as hell. So the guys are going to stay there but Justyna has to go meet Edd, Chicken & some other dude at the park. It's all good. We come back & there are L.S. & K.Z. all by themselves. We all joke around & stuff. Then here comes Kasha, Ana & some other Polak girl. They mess it all up, they leave, later comes this Bosnian girl named Meliha (gay name), what a bitch. She obviously doesn't like Lena & me because she looks at us evil-ly all the time. She started flirting with L.S. & that totally ticked me off so I told Lena that we're leaving. Then we walked around & came back about 20 or 30 minutes later. We eventually have to pass Polak world so we do & L.S. tells me to come there & I say "Why?" & he says that K.Z. has to ask me something. So I stand by him & he looks up (because he's sitting there) & all he says is "Hi". Then L.S. introduces us to his friend Tom, another Polak with tight jeans. Then other people come to mess the day up, like tall Polaks with their crappy Nissans & Civics with techno music. Then Nicole comes out of a car all showing off. Then comes the Incorporateds again. Then L.T. comes around a couple times & Lena gets the info out of him about Pat. Pat is on vacation & is coming back tomorrow, perfect time to bother him about why he didn't tell us that he's leaving. And Lena said that she's going to tell him that she missed him, not for real though, but pretending is good. L.T. got Lena's & my screen name. He said that he's going to IM us. But on that little paper was also Kasha's, Ana's, Martha's, & some other Polaks' screen names. So he's a pimp now or something? Whatever man. K.Z. told me that L.S. likes me, I know he does, I can see it in his eyes, & he asked me like 10 times if I like him. I'm telling u that I do, but I told him otherwise because if he really wants to know he should find out for himself, not from his friend. But then again, is there a point in liking him? I'm just another girly that he thinks is cute, I mean I bet he switches girls more than socks. That's what it looks like, his motto might be "Pimp for life", but then again, that's how it kind of is with me too but I'm not a jerk about it or being obvious. I don't think I want to hang out with them again, it hurts me, u know when there's a guy u like & some other chick is flirting with him or trying to get with him. It sucks & it's gay. So Lena & me are going shopping tomorrow, besides, it's supposed to rain. I hope it ruins their little get-together just like they ruined ours today. So Mart wants to play games with me. He prank called me today about ten times & I got pissed off at him & started cussing, he made a Hindu voice but I knew that it was him. That ass-wipe. I'm going to beat the shit out of him the next time I see him, I saw him today but I couldn't do shit because he was with May's bro. Seriously he shouldn't mess with me. Ok well bybye I gotta go my dad is being an ass again. See ya.
    


14,July,2004


	 
      Hello there. I was going to write a new post yesterday, but the website was messed-up or something of similar difference. Every time I want to write in here, I don't know where to start because lots has happened since last post. So anyways, Justyna told Lena & me that Justyna's brother (similar first name as L.T. so we'll call him L) & his two friends (let's call them K & P) think that Lena & me are "cute". Awe isn't that sweet? Juniors-to-be think we're cute... to tell u the truth, they're not so bad themselves. Anyway, about the title, that whole L.T. thing was (just as I thought) a fling, every day I like him less & less. I guess I'm not into that whole "shy boy" thing anymore, & yes I am sure (but his ass is still cute, lol sorry). U know like since I met & talked to L, K, & P, they kind of made me realize that boys my age, freshmen-to-be are a bit, dare I say it... Immature, & I've always had a thing for guys that were about 2 or three years older than me. Don't get me wrong, I'm not going to stop liking guys my age, but ones that are a wee-bit older seem better. So today was totally boring. My dad made me go with him to this company & it's located all the way downtown, all just for an application. & while we were asking for directions, there were a bunch of Mexicans there & they were all staring at me, freaking perverts. Then Lena calls me & tells me that there's been a change of plans, last night she & I decided to hang out with the guys (L, K, P) or someone of the sort, but these girls call her because they are "bored" & want her to hang out with them. Can u imagine right on that day when we planned something they have to be stupid? I was pretty mad. Then I was on the internet until like 6pm or something & then Adi IMs me & asks me if I want to go to Subway with her & I say ok because I didn't have anything better to do anyways. Then I go to Minute Man (that's where we were supposed to meet) & all of a sudden L.T., Rafael, Chris P., & that dude that got the top of his hair highlighted decide to go to Minute Man too. They leave & Adi comes with Richard (Jana's ex), I was kind of surprised, he was really shy at first & it scared me for some reason. Then we went to Subway, then on the way back, we decided to go to the school park, on the way there, we met this one 8th-grader-to-be dude, I forgot his name but he kind of looks like Robert/Walter a.k.a. Robbie. Then at the park the Lacey bitches were there looking at me all weirdly like they're surprised because I'm hanging out with Adi. Bitches. Edd* & Chicken* were at the park too, playing catch with a baseball. Then we went out of the park & to Berwyn Avenue where Richie wanted to go to Grandparents' Park to check on "his kids". The other dude decided to go with him & I was asked if I wanted to come with but I of course said "no that's ok". So Adi & I went to the corner of Berwyn & Oakview & she said she's going to go home so I said ok & also went home. What a stupid ass day, man I can't believe it. Hopefully tomorrow Lena will be able to come with me, if I were her, I would've gotten out of it around 5pm already. Because those girls are too young to be hanging out with us, they would go "Ewwww" to the things we discuss. I mean seriously, I'm not trying to be a smart-ass here, it's just the truth. Hopefully I'll get to see the guys again tomorrow because they're a cool bunch to joke around with. & also Justyna should be there (that is if she wants). May's going to SK soon, not this Saturday, but the next. I'll miss her but I hope she has fun. Dude I'm so bored, it's only 10:03 pm, I feel like the whole day has just passed me by. Well anyways I got to leave now, I wish it wasn't so but seriously. Ok well bye. Talk to u soon hopefully.
    


11,July,2004


	 
      Hello there. Long time no see, I mean hear, I mean write, o whatever u want to call it. Ok let me tell u about the past couple of days. First of all, yesterday May called me to go to the pool with her but I knew my dad would never let me, turned out to be true so I couldn't go. Then the best thing EVER happened, my dad wanted to go to Rockford since he was really bored. He wanted me to go with him, but this time I didn't want to. I had the best time, if my dad would've been home, he never would've let me go anywhere. Anyways, yesterday I went with May & her parents to Navy Pier & we saw beautiful fireworks, but the best part of it yesterday was when we were looking for a parking spot. 2 hours. It was so much fun!! (Joke). We left at around 6 or 6:30 & came back around 11:30, sweet huh? It kind of made up for me being sad about not being able to go to Club Soda, because every Saturday I want to go, but would never be able to. Then today May calls me to go to the Bensenville Water Park with her (a.k.a. "The pool") & we all very well know that my dad never would've let me go but since he wasn't home (yay), my mommy let me go. BUT guess who also went, Mart & his family. As soon as we got to the pool place, he jumped in the water & pretended that he was drowning (female lifeguard standing by). She got pissed & told him that he can't swim at all anymore, but they let him later though. Then later around 6pm we went home. I took a shower (2 1/2th time today) & wanted to go outside. Lena's mom didn't let her because Lena's hair was wet (so was mine at the time) & her mom said that she would get a cold, but it was 83 degrees Fahrenheit outside. Damn. I was ok with it until May said that she didn't feel like going, but I wanted to go so bad. Then my mommy & me went to throw the mail in the mail-thingamajiger. Then my mommy told me to go to the school and back & that maybe, just maybe, I might meet someone who I could hang out with. So hell why not? Since I didn't have anything better to do, I walked all the way to the school. No one in Polak World. Barely anyone on the streets. So I walk to the school & turn back, when all of a sudden, I see a guy walking across the street, toward me, but kind of far away so I couldn't identify. As I'm getting closer I'm all like "Damn he looking FINE from here, I wonder who it is. But then again... If it's one of those tall Polaks, maann I swear I hate those jerks. I won't even give him a look, better not be one of them." So I keep on walking & the guy keeps on walking & he wants to cross the street, right where I'm at. Then I look from the corner of my eye & BAM! All of a sudden it all clears up... Pimp Parker. Lol. He's all dressed hip & shit... kind of hot to tell u the truth but please don't get the wrong idea. So then I'm thinking "Man should I say something? Like a 'Hi'?" But I decided not to say anything, me & him know the routine, just ignore each other. Then I looked at him & ignored him until he passed by, a little while later I look back & he's walking & looking back at me, then we both turn around. Ha it was funny. Then I went home & then May says she wants to go outside (yay!!). So we go outside for less than half an hour & no one was out there man.. maybe the school park, u never know. Anyways... I recently signed on to BuddyPic (u can meet people there while having your profile & shit). There was this 18-year-old-to-be guy who sent me BP mail. He said he was moving to Chicago in august & wanted to get to know me & go out with me (he's being way too forward if u ask me, but no one asked me of course). I'm not even sure I like him but I guess we could be friends, no harm in that. There's this dude on BP & he's 15 & he's supposedly ChitownShady. Lol. I mailed him & asked "r u the real Slim Shady?" We shall find out soon. Hopefully. Man I haven't seen the guys around for so long (L.T., his bro, Pat, Bartek,...), I hope to see them tomorrow to see what they have been up to. Did I tell u that my new curfew of the internet being online is 11 pm? Doesn't that suck? Yes father's rules. But hey it's 11:18 now & he's asleep. Muahahahaha! Ok lol I think I'm going to read Jenini's bloggy & then go off the net. Luvv luvv bybye.
    


08,July,2004


	 
      Hey there. How's it going? Well today was just a completely strange day. There was so much hurrying up & stuff. First of all I woke up, dad tells me that his friend & his friend's 11-year-old-immature-little annoying-pretending-to-be-sweet granddaughter are coming to our house in two hours. I was furious. I planned a day of hanging out with my friends & my friend Jenini coming to my house, but no my dad's friend invited himself over to our house. What a fag. The strange thing actually is, that NO ONE notices that I don't like the chick, & my God isn't it obvious? I wouldn't mind that she's 11 but she's really immature, even for an 11-year-old, but her friends are just like that so I'm not surprised. Whatever. So then later May invites Jenini to her house, meanwhile my dad says that Jenini can come to my house, but too late. Then I'm stuck in the house being bored as hell. Finally Lena, Jenini & May come & my dad gave me permission to "ditch" the girl. That was nice. Then we went to Grandparents' Park & played volleyball & acted stupid & talked about bullshit. Then we saw Rini & she said that she hasn't heard from Jana in a while, same here. I don't know what's going on because before her cousin came, she always called me, at least every other weekend & shit but now nothing. O well what can u do? But then as I think about it, Jana promised Lena & me that we were all going to hang out when her cousin comes & that we're going shopping & to 6 Flags. What a liar. But then again, I only have like $15 left from more than 4 G's. One day I'm getting it back right? Yea I hope so. Anyways... Then we (not Rini) went back to our hood & we saw Justyna & Ed*, Chicken, & this other rocker/goth dude whose name I don't know. They were across the street from us. Then we saw BB the preppy bitch & her lame "crew". She always says hi unless she's occupied with stealing guys. So then we went to Jewel, Justyna & the dudes followed us for some reason, while half-way there, May changes her mind, "Actually I don't want to go." So I told them that we should go into Walgreens to lose Justyna's crew. We go in there, they sit outside Walgreens. We walk around the store once & look outside, they left. We leave without buying anything. On the way to Lena's house, Chris (Rini's bro) & 'that Arab kid that Jusyna beat up' were at Minute Man & the Arab kid asked May if he could see the volleyball May was carrying, just as she was about to throw it to him, I told her not to. Then we keep on walking, two minutes later there's Arab kid riding a bike & Chris on the pegs. Arab kid pushes the volleyball into May's ribs in attempt to steal ball. May gets hurt. Runs after kid, they chicken out & hurry & leave. May stops running but her lungs hurt. We go to Lena's to get more cash. We now have $7.70. Just as we left Lena's gate, Chris screams out "May*" & tells her to come over there where him & the Arab kid were standing. I tell them to come over here. They come, Arab kid's a big ass chicken, sheesh. So A.k. comes in front of us & says "So what happened?" & I'm thinking "WTF?" Chris says "U better apologize because that's what we came here for." A.k. apologizes & I say "Shake Hands." A.k. says "No I'm sorry for hitting her..." I'm like "No u guys shake hands (Lena & me demonstrate). Kid's so scared & confused that he must have pissed in his panties. Then they start being jerks & I start threatening. They run away. We leave while dissing. On our way to DD's, there is the little-wanksta-Phat-Farm-wearing-bitch's boy Lacey & his brothers. They are all retarded. That little boy always starts shit with me, just for fun. God help him when I get to Taft, I'm not telling u nothing yet, but shit is going to change. The Laceys are going to change their attitude shit towards me too, they better recognize who they're talking shit to. The little bitch called ME a bitch & a whole other bunch of shit along with his ugly-ass-no-one-would-ever-fuck-them brothers & friends. They said I should grow breasts. LMFAO. Have they ever looked at their friend Nicole? Ha. BTW they have no dicks so why are they talking to me? Omg I'm not even going to start with that, little kids, who cares. So then we go to DD's & guess what. The food & stuff costs $10 something & we have $7.70. Do the math. We don't know what to do, so the man who's next in line says that he'll pay for us. How sweet. The lady that works there, BTW, is a bitch. So then we go towards home &... whoa I just lost my train of thought right there. Umm.. wait, we passed the school, Douggie*, Arnie* & some other dudes were there, didn't say shit (probably because of BB). Then we walked, passed Polak world but there was no one there except for that stupid bitch named Ana L. I hate that chick, she doesn't have anything on her except for that nasty attitude, tiny clothes & stupidity. She was flirting with a couple of the tall Polaks, u know those that told me to fuck myself. None of the people I preferred were there, unless of course they were hiding out in the back smoking that shit. Then May & Jenini went to May's house & my dad had already called me & I walked Lena home partly & there were Zamp* & Hedri* & the Pink Pimps & BB & some other bitches in the back by her gate. She decided not to go that way, so she went by the front door. I walked home by myself & I could hear Zamp & some other dudes talking about "look at that ass" & then all of a sudden they started talking about how I was "trying to be...". Fucking Fags. What I don't get is how they think I give a damn & because it bothers them, that I'll change my shit. Hellz Naw, they could kiss my phat ass. Then I went home & (tear) didn't see L.T. ALL day. How sad. But Kam did call me while that 11-year-old chick was at my house, I was wondering if I should answer but then I did, I was acting nice & shit. I'll play him back, don't worry. I feel like I've missed something by not talking to L.T. & Pat. I don't know why, but I like strange comedy, which is what they bring. I want better, more costier clothes, I have few good clothes & it's sad & I also am officially BROKE. Not funny Svetla. So anyways, I spent my Thursday night playing with my little 1 1/2-year-old neighbor. My life is so boring. Adi especially made me realize that today. She said that this year was the most boring for her ever. I asked why. She said that it was because the people around here do the same thing every day & they never get bored of it. Do u people realize this? How do we not get bored? Are we made to function this way or are we just really boring, awfully safe people? Man.. I'm out. I don't even know what to say anymore. I mean it's strange that someone finally made me realize the truth & all this time it's been here right in front of my nose. Goodbye & until next time, if there is going to be a next time.
    


07,July,2004


	 
      Hello. Today I was calling California; D.C.; Kentucky; New York; Zagreb, Croatia; & Dragocaj, Bosnia. Why u ask? Well my cousins are supposed to come to the U.S. & they currently reside in Bosnia & these American dumbfucks messed the information up, not only that but they didn't inform my people when they should get interviewed & shit. So I'm pissed off, I barely went outside today, my dad said I could only stay until 8:30.. What bullshit! It wasn't even dark then, even little kids don't go home at that time. It's bogus. Anyways... When Lena & me were outside by ourselves, L.T. passes by with his friend on a bike & as he passes by, they turn & pass by again & he tells me, "I can see your panties." Lol & the worst thing is that I just happened to wear pink-lined underwear that day. Damn! So yea that was my flashing. Then I saw Pat but we didn't hang out or shit, too bad it would've been fun, u know what I'm saying? So then we went to hang out with Justyna & the rocker dudes & chicks. It was funny, this guy named Ed* cut his finger & wiped the blood on cars, then he kept on cutting a little more & many cars were covered with a little blood. Ok maybe it isn't funny to u now like I'm saying it, but if u were there u would've seen how he explained the event so funnily. Ha then this little Arabian kid came, Justyna beat his ass a couple months ago, & Ed told him to come there & he was coming, slow as hell, & then Ed was like talking to him & walking towards him. The kid was backing up but still smiling, that was funny. But Ed was just trying to be friendly here, kid's too chicken (btw, on the back of Ed's shirt it is stated that "Hell was full so I came back" Ha). So then May calls me @ 7:30 & I say that Lena & me "have to go". Then she says ok & we leave. We hung out with May a bit & then we played volleyball until 8:27, when I had to LEAVE. Stupid mofos. So I would rather have hung out with Pat & L.T. because it never gets boring with them. By the way, lol I seriously got to get some nicer underwear, when I say nicer I mean "hotter" but if you're thinking thongs, I'm thinking HELL NO. But yes it's Vicky's Secret. YAY Jenini is coming to my house tomorrow!!!! Sweeeeeeet! Whoops I forgot an "e". So I wish I could get to actually know L.T. better but it seems like he has his eye on someone else. That's all right though, I get it. So I'm going to go now, So bored. But u have fun & watch "Stanley" tomorrow on Playhouse Disney. Ta-Ta!
    


06,July,2004


	 
      Hey there how's it going? It's very unfair-ish on my side of the road. I was hanging out with May all day long, we went to Grandparents Park to play volleyball. It was fun, at first I was so bad at it & then I got better & that's when it was fun to play volleyball. May & me were talking about lots of things, we took a couple of breaks, then played again, then all of a sudden there comes Shadow (his real name is: I Don't Know; Don't Worry About It; Whatever) & I say "hey" to him but I don't think he heard me because he was listening to some mad beats & then he looked at me. But the sun was shining in his face so maybe he didn't recognize me, plus that whole "smoking weed" situation makes him even crazier than usual. So then May & me went to her house, which made us decide to go to the mall, which we did. Then while at the mall, these guys were following us & saying stuff to us & then when we turn around they turn around, to act as though they weren't the ones saying stuff. Riiight. Lol man I got this black shirt & on it, it says (with white print), "Brunettes Do It Better". Lol that was so funny at the moment when I found it. And then May found a shirt (Ha I almost wrote 'shit') that said "It's All Good" on it! That's my quote girl! But damn it was way too tight so I didn't get it. But I did get the brunette shirt, but it was just $9. Good price for a store like KOhl's, right? Yup. Man I miss L.T. he's so cute, man I'm REALLY "pointing out the obvious" here as May says. God why do I always like guys that have something to do with Pat? O yea, maybe because every guy in this whole freaking neighborhood has something to do with Pat! Even the hott older guys, HOW in the world does he do that? Is it that whole Polish thing? Is it possible to change your nationality as u can change your religion? Hmm... If one of my friends read this, he/she will smack themselves on the forehead & say "Damn she's slow!!" Lol I'm just joking my loyal people. Wow there are actually (wait... 18 minus 2..) 16 people online on my buddy list. That's amazing, it's never gotten that high. Aww man.. Bad thought.. Yes again what did u think I only think of butterflies & little birds & bees.. LMAO birds & bees IS what I think about. Ha. I crack myself up sometimes.. Get it? "Crack" myself "up" sometimes.. Nah u don't get it. So... I can't wait until "The Day After Tomorrow" (lol so dramatic) because Jenini is coming over again!!! YAY!! I missed u Jenini! Ok that was too much. But I'm STILL happy from yesterday lol. Aw man I saw this awesome new store at the mall, I have no idea what it's called but it's so... Well... Me. It's hip-hop-ish clothes, but there are two bad things, first of all, the clothes are way too expensive for my wallet. For example, one of the shirts cost $35. Now that's too much in my opinion. And the other bad thing was that most, not all, of the jeans & shit were kind of big, u know for a more "fuller" person. But hey at least the shirts were nice. When I get successful & rich, I'm going to go shopping there. YAY! Wait.. I'm never going to be rich.. (tear).. O well, it's good to fantasize. Aww man bad thought again. Now wouldn't u like to know what the title is all about? Well when we were at the mall, May saw Mike, Nicky, & these two blonde chicks. So May went over to say hi & they were so unenthusiastic, but Nicky was talking on the phone though. So a couple half hours ago, May talked to Nicky on the net & he said that he doesn't remember being at the mall, & that it must have been his brother. But then... He doesn't have a brother (that's what May says). So I'm REALLY confused & plus Mark stole my quote!! How rude.. He should get his own quote, not steal others'. Geez.. kids these days.. lol it's a joke. So how's your sex life so far? LOL by this time u people have to be a little lost, right? OMG I just thought of something, when we were at the mall & those guys were following us, this one guy came up behind me and he..... Ok take a pause for u because I want to know what you're thinking right now, u sick little person u (whoever u may be) with your little... Whatever. So anyways.. What was I talking about? O yes the dude at the mall, well he bumped me on the ass with his ass, it was funny but yet strange & he was like "I bite too". LMAO what a weirdo. I mean come on he wasn't even fine. I'm joking, I'm playing (not with u), chill out man. Geeses! O-tay! Well I'm going to leave now & I'll let u enjoy your night life, or the night life u don't have (don't worry about it, neither do I lol), so yea.. I'll just, like, talk to u later. Supposedly Lena, May & Alex are going to come with me outside tomorrow, so we'll just see how that works out. Wish me good luck! (Please don't let anything bad happen, please.... aww man..) Ok lol I'm out, Bazooka! I mean Peace!
    


05,July,2004


	 
      When am I going to get some Kielbasa? LMAO joke, I heard Serbian is better. Naw I'm just playing about the whole THING.
    


04,July,2004


	 
      Hi! Sorry for being so preppily happy but o man I'm really happy. Want to know why? Well... I was just chilling out with Lena & we were sitting in Polak World I mean something's got to happen there right? And yea so finally around like 6 or something like that, there comes Pat, L.T., Bartek, & Chris (Rini's bro). So there I go freaking out again (I always do when L.T. comes around, don't know why), & they want to get some cigs from L.T.'s so-called "friend" who's like 26 or something. She's all like "(something something in Polish & then) ID". So Pats like "Yea I got an ID right here" & he holds an "air ID". So then L.T. tells her that he has some cash & gives it to her. She takes it, says something in Polish & then drives away. Supposedly she went to the store to get some cigs for them. Then Pat, L.T., & Chris chill out with us & they talk funny stuff & then Pat keeps asking me "Do u know Eirini Peroules?" & I'm like "Damn how many times are u gonna ask me that?" & he's like "I don't know, I'm just trying to start a conversation here." U know I think that when I'm not there that he's going to ask Lena out, because when they were passing us one time today, L.T. said "Ask her... Ask her" & Pat was just looking down. What's weird is that Pat gave me one of those starry-eyed looks & he was so nice to us, OMG it actually scares me, I had to look away because just in case I might get the feelings back again. But it was cute though. It was nice hanging out with the guys & when my dad called me on the telly, I got up so that he couldn't hear the guys & Lena told me that L.T. said "She has a nice ass." Lol SCORE!!! & a while before, he also gave me a look, it was so cute OMG. Lol I'm sorry people. Am I freaking u out yet? Good. & then when I was going home, there were these two dudes, wow they were fine. Sorry, but hey I'm single for now so I can look around. & they were looking at me & I was looking at them & then when I passed them, one of them whistled. WHY do I have to have strict parents please tell me WHY? Damn though. But I'm really happy now, I think that he likes Lena more though, because he sat next to her, not me.  :( O well, lol tomorrow I'm sitting on the other side & he BETTER sit by me. :) Lol I'm just playing, u know me. Ha. Ok bybye see ya later. ps:: I don't think that I want to chill with Justyna anymore. 
    


04,July,2004


	 
      Hey there people. Today I was in Rockford to visit my cousins. It was nice I guess, we barbecued. My cousins' godparents also came & their daughter, but their SON didn't come. We had a nice time, saw fireworks, listened to beats, had a ride in the Subaru, this my friend, is what I call life. The bad thing though, was that the Sox lost the whole three-game series. Out of three games we didn't even win ONE. And the worst thing about that is that Cubs fans were being asses about it. I mean so what? We beat them when they were at our place, Wrigley Field sucks anyways. As they say, "Home is where the heart is", that quote was meant for our team. But I still believe in those guys, I know that they can do better if they only try a little harder. Now about my day again, my cousin (name's Misel,he's 16 & has a driver's license), my other cousin (Tanja, she's 13), her friend (Melanie, her age) & me went to Volcano Falls, it's a place of games, go-carts, soccer cages, batting cages, mini-golf, & other stuff. It's really cool there & my favorite places to go is the go-carts & the batting cages (hott guys lol). There was this one really hott guy, so him & me were giving each other little looks constantly, but I couldn't do or say anything to him because my cousin was there & well it's just awkward. But I kind of regretted not saying anything.. He was FINE. Lol but yea what can u do. Just when we got up to leave, I heard a "Damn!" coming from behind but I don't really think that it had anything to do with me, never know. Then we went to my cousin's crib, had nice food to eat, my friend came, we talked about stuff, I took pictures with my camera & it was fun. This holiday, 4th of July, is my favorite holiday, & since I was in like 4th or 5th grade, I wished that I could spend my holiday hanging out with friends and well... maybe a nice guy. Wouldn't that be nice? Yea.. but one can only dream. Especially about me having another boyfriend, since the last two were failures. But like I said, mother & father know what's best.. yea my ass. Today Lena calls me & my dad keeps interrupting with,"Who's calling u? Who are u talking to?" & he's doing that constantly, it's so very rude when I'm talking to someone & he thinks that he's more important than the person I'm trying to have a conversation with. Yesterday we got into an argument & I was sent to my room. All because I'm not allowed to talk or see guys. Well just guess who's fault it will be when I become a lesbian??? I don't even think THAT will make my point. I hope it makes Nikolina's point. She can't have guy friends either, but she said that her parents hate gays & lesbians so maybe she'll be happy & things will change. O well. I'm still screwed, but don't think for a second that I'm going down without a fight. No way. Fighter for life, if it doesn't go the nice way, put up a fight. That's my motto. Well I don't really know what else to say but I miss my friends. & I also need a man, if I could have one but it's impossibibel. Yea.. Well TTYL bybye.
    


02,July,2004


	 
      Hi there. Today was a pretty sucky day. Nothing new at all except that Pat likes Lena, but he looked upset because everytime he passes by on his bike, Lena whispers something to me, mostly centered around him. Lol. U know today I got the strange idea that Lena should play him, acting that she likes him & be all flirty with him & then after a week or so, continue that & then tell him that she was just kidding all that time. But as I really think about it, Pat has feelings too, (supposedly) & we should treat others just like we would like to be treated ourselves. L.T. has a nice behind (lol sorry but it's true). Here's something so obvious, Kam calls me every day just to "see what you're doing". Today he called me 3 times. 3 times!! Unbelievable... I'm not going to go out with him because I feel sorry for him, hell no. Once again pops up this question, why does he like ME? I mean c'mon it's me, I'm fat, boring, well anything but preppy. Whatever man. U know what I hate most about Pat? He lies, a lot. First he says that he never lied to a girl, but that one time that he had just met me & already made up a lie, how low can he go? Awww no not like that. I asked Lena what she would say if Pat asked her out & she's like "Hell No." Isn't this strange: I have 11 out of 71 people online on my buddylist & I'm not even talking to one of them? I'm so bored man, I should've just stayed home & be bored all day that receiving Polish criticism from "The Mafia." Speaking of mafias, I really want to see all three parts of "The Godfather," but it's rated R & not that I have minded other times, (lol "Slackers") but I heard that it was the bloodiest movie ever made so I'm deciding to watch it when I'm at least a year or two older. Lena & me were sitting close to Polak world, but more toward the other building, & there were at least a dozen Polaks on the driveway of Polak world & they were talking like usual, with their 'popular' bikes & as Lena & me were talking, there comes a guy on a motorcycle & his girl is on the back of the bike & her g-string was showing & Lena was like "Wait 'till they see that.." & just as that bike was passing by the guys, they were all like "Whoa!!" all loudly & crap. It was funny, like they've never seen a g-string before HA, well obviously Pat has, (LMFAO) his story titled "The Time I Got Really Excited At   Victoria's Secret  ". I saw Kasha today with her preppy, bitchy, Abercrombie Chick friend & she was all like "Hi! Omg Do u wear contacts?" & I'm like "Yea" & she's like "It looks so cute!!" & I'm here thinking "WTF? How can contacts look cute??" But I instead said "Thanks." & Pat was checking her out (obviously). U know what sucks though? There's no point of me liking guys, because I can't go out with him anyway. My aunt told me that my mom started dating when she was in 8th grade, but my mom doesn't care because every conversation with her is about "Yes but this is America!" Yea I'm going to get killed here in "America" if I go out with a guy. What a crappy excuse, sometimes it's better to have learned your lesson the hard way instead of your parents not letting u do anything. Just like that one caged bird, that was one true poem. Well I don't know what else to talk about, so I'm out. Peace.
    


01,July,2004


	 
      Hi.. wow I honestly didn't think I could ever get SO bored. MAN seriously, I would've done anything today just so that I wouldn't be bored. Well.. almost anything. I still can't believe that Ana, Kate, & Kate's two sisters could all go to Club Soda but I couldn't. I wonder how the hell they got there & if their parents knew that they were there. Hmm. What do U think? I should've done something at least today, all I did was chat with people on the internet, almost die from the heat, think & I was actually that bored that I started dancing to one of the songs I was listening to.. shut it! It was a good song. Yea I know.. I'm a strange person. A strange Bosnian person that is. lol. Man. I wonder when Jenini can come to Polak world again.. I know I'm annoying with that but I really want to know. Unlike Mario Winans who doesn't want to know, with his song "I Don't Wanna Know." Did u people know that I do illegal things, I mean I would tell u but ya never know when a donut-eating-crooked-justice-hating cop might stumble upon this thing. I got the First Amendment of the U.S. Constitution to protect me though.. Freedom of Speech! (Sighs) I love America (no not really). Maybe I could find another 'Little Johnny' Joke. Let's see... o here's one:: A couple was worried about the size of their young son's penis, so they consulted a doctor. The doctor told them that the only thing he knew that would correct this problem would be for them to feed Little Johnny wheat toast for breakfast. The next morning Johnny came to the breakfast table where he saw a plate on the table with a huge stack of wheat toast on it. He asked his mother what the big stack was for. She replied, "The top two slices are for you, and the rest is for Dad." HA.. lol ok here's another one if u don't mind..:: Little Johnny's sitting in a coffee shop, staring at a girl wearing the tightest pants he's ever seen. Finally his curiosity gets the best of him, so he walks over & asks, "How do u get into those pants?" The young lady looks him over and replies, "Well, u could start by buying me dinner..." lol ok here's a sick one :: Little Johnny goes on his first date. "How did it go?" his mom asked. "Great. I gave her an Australian kiss goodnight." "What's an Australian kiss?" asks his mom. "It's like a French kiss, but down under."  Eww, ok now I don't really think I have anything else to talk about, so I'm going to go. But know this! I'm not going to spend my day looking at po...pcorn any longer! I am headed out to the outside world to see its many magical wonders. So farewell & make sure to call me anytime u want if u want to hang out with me, because company is always welcome (unless its nicole or any other of the preppy bitches or the "pink pimps"). I said "So long, farewell, to u my friend, goodbye, for now, until we meet again (familiar lol? muahahaha!)."

    


10,August,2004


	 
       I came there a bit late. I saw that something was up but didn't know exactly what. I knew that it was about u. U and your friends. That's why the undercovers always come around here. Right? I looked around and realized what must have happened. It was close to happening each of the three previous times. It had never gotten this far. Now it eventually did. It was your fault and it was about time. Everyone told u but u didn't listen to them. U just had to learn your lesson the hard way, maybe u still haven't learned, who knows. It wasn't easy seeing u stand there, handcuffed. Looking at us from the backseat window. Everyone was there. Everyone saw and knew what happened. No one really cared that much though. Everyone took it as an everyday thing. But not me, I was the only one with the pain in my eyes. U didn't know I cared. Hell, I didn't know I cared. Now I know. Hopefully it will turn out ok. No one will get hurt. The feds just make a big deal out of everything. Even Kasha got searched. No big deal. But u and the other five were taken downtown for police reports. What are those anyways? Just some pieces of paper that follow u around for the rest of your life? That go with u to every job interview? It's just a little worthless thing, but o well. It'll be different around here for a while, without u. Only if they chose it not to. Then you'll be back tomorrow or something of that sort. And then there's another subject. Another person. In complete doubt. Don't ask me why we never had a chance because u know the reason. It was partly your fault for never believing in us. U always though it was all a lie, when it couldn't have been more true and real. Maybe I was the one that ended it but nothing would have happened anyway. U didn't believe in yourself and how much someone could truly love u. It was just a game to u. Which is why we never moved from square one. Two years we've known each other and nothing happens. Now u know why it never worked out. It was both our faults. Pride, denial and doubt. The worst enemies. 

    


08,August,2004


	 
       O yea and I forgot to tell the world about my new shoes. They're new Reebok G-Units that just came out a couple days ago. Don't hate. Lol just playing. :P 

    


06,August,2004


	 
       Hello. Yesterday I was outside with Lena and Justyna. On the way to the park we stumbled upon Rita and Dalia (who happen to be cool with Justyna) and we were talking. Then Sidalia stole my soccer ball and that's when Arnie revealed the "secret", that Sidali likes me. Then later the "much perfumed" Bebe came. She was trying to ride Justyna's skateboard (LMAO). What a sight. Then later they left and we (Justyna, Lena, me) went to Grandparents' Park. We were playing soccer and then one of my girls had to go "P". Then Justyna had to go wait by White Hen for her brother to come with the car because they had to go somewhere. Lena and me were offered a ride home but I declined it. So then Lena and me had a conversation about some guys' behinds. It was funny and very informational. Then we went to my house to get the football. We were playing football by Polak world but it was more towards the school but still around there. Right by where Mr."Freddy" was. My arm was hurting badly so it was tough to throw the ball at first. Later it got easier but my throws still sucked, not even a single spiral. Then there comes Ana and that other Polish chick. Ana's greeting me like we are the best of friends. Then they go hang out over there and I know that they're watching us play from the corner of their eyes. Then come the Tall Polaks (Fierce, Darek, and so on). They start talking to Ana's friend and then Ana leaves. The chick is standing there by herself with those guys and they're talking. Lena and me just keep on playing. Then there comes Aleks and I greet her. A while later Mimma is passing by and we talk for a little. She was supposed to meet Aleks so we told her which way she went. She leaves. The Polaks keep talking and I don't mind, but it really sucks when they just stop and the only thing u hear within the silence is Lena's nails scraping off the football as she throws it. Then there came Sk8er Gurl (a.k.a. Justyna). She chilled with us. She tried to do the ollie again but kind of messed it up, hell it ain't as easy as it looks. Then I told her to switch with me so that she plays football with Lena and that I can try the skateboard. She said ok. I was riding the skateboard pretty well for a beginner, I could get reasonably far with it. Lena was like, "How do u do that??" and I'm all like, "Do what??" because it's fairly simple with just a little bit of practice. Besides, Justyna's skateboard is easy to handle since she and her brother wore it in so I'm pretty comfy with it. When J learned how to say the word "what" in Serbian/Bosnian, she kept repeating it and being so happy that she knows one word at least. Then I got bored of it and told her "F U" in Serbian/Bosnian. She asked Lena what that meant and then kept repeating it to me. Then I started saying stuff to her in Polish. Then we were calling each other names in Polish. It was hilarious because I mean come on... am I Polish? No. Then Lena and her were play-fighting clumsily and I was just observing and laughing my butt off. Then I became red with exhaustion from all the footballing/skateboarding. Then J called Edd's cell for the 20th time that day because he didn't call her back and he was supposed to. Then they were talking and a couple minutes later J had to go. Lena and me stayed for like 15 more minutes. No one and I mean no one was outside. Except for this dude who asked us if we had a cell phone and I said that I don't and then I hid it. Lol. That was yesterday. Today I had to wake up at 4 AM and my parents and me were going to Detroit, Michigan to our friends' house. It's a four-and-a-half-hour drive just in case you didn't know. The people live in a ghetto hood and it's tight because they're really nice to their neighbors and their neighbors are really nice to them. Anyway, the lady, who's like my mom's age, has two sons. The older one is 25 and the younger one is well... younger, let's just say. I've been to their house once before but I didn't meet the younger son because he had to work that day. When I saw him today I was SHOCKED. He is the hottest, nicest guy I have ever met. He has black hair in tiny curls, dreamy dark blue eyes, and the cutest smile. Plus he's funny and nice. Did I already mention that? Sorry if I did but damn. And I got his picture. Yay! I was in the house with the lady, her husband, their neighbors, my parents, and their younger son when I got this thought. I was thinking what I should talk about just in case sometime during the day before he goes to work, what if all those people go in the backyard and he's here with me? And then I was like, "Nah that's not going to happen." Then later they all go in the backyard and he had like 15 minutes before he had to leave for work. He started talking to me and I was talking too and he was like making jokes, it was funny. Then he had to leave, that sucked. He told me to find him a girlfriend in Chicago, but that's just in case I don't grow up at a fast pace because if that's the case I could be his girlfriend (it's a joke but I don't know how to explain it good so yea). His mom told me that he told her that he wishes that I was a little older and they were all like playing around that I'm going to be that guys' daughter-in-law. That was kind of retarded... they always do that. Then later when hott guy left, his brother and the brother's wife came. I already met them last time. Really cool people. Out of a conversation about truck driving, it turned into how I reminded the lady (hott guy's mom) of an actress and that I was pretty. Then her older son said that he has no idea where I got the beauty from since it's not my parents (joke). Lol that was a nice burn. Then we left and I got a pic of hott dude standing by the Ferrari he used to own. Then we left their house and came back at like 8:30 PM because we had to make some stops along the way. All in all, it was a nervous day and I don't know why but I'm always shy around grown-ups, especially if I don't know them but then it was different with the sons of that lady because they were so... I don't know... homey? That's a funny word, reminds me of the Simpsons. Lol. Ok well I should go get some sleep now. A long day of playing football, going to Norridge Park to watch a baseball game, and hanging out with Justyna or whoever else might be around Polak world awaits me (and Lena). So ta-ta for now.  

    


06,August,2004


	 
       Hello. Today wasn't so bad. I was happy that Jenini could come over and I got the crazy idea (yes again) that Jenini, Lena, and I should go to the mall. We arrived without any trouble. We first walked around, I looked at shoes and future clothes (things I couldn't afford). Then we went to eat some pizza and B.D. lady wasn't there. Neither were Collin, Mike, or their "black" friend. Then we went to Bath and Body and there I put on two different lotions. One was vanilla flavores and the other was cocoa flavored. That produced a strange scent and it was, dare I say it, funky. Lol just kidding. Later we went to Kohl's and tried on hideous pink outfits. It was actually hilarious and I ended up buying a shirt (don't worry it's NOT pink). The only reason I bought it was because it was cheap and I'm cheap. Don't take it the wrong way. Anyway, then we went to Rave and tried on stuff just for fun. Then we went to Claire's and tried on strange sunglasses. Then we went to the Food Court again and we got fries and vanilla ice cream, Jenini and me ate ice cream and fries at the same time. Our poor teeth. After that (I'm not really going in order here) we went to this one store where they had cool clothes that were not for my wallet and there I tried on these Baby Phat shoes and they were cool but a bit narrow by the toes. And since I have a big toe, that wouldn't work out. I decided to get half-a-size smaller shoes but they only had a full size larger which is a 10. So I tried them on, the toes were fine but the shoes were kind of big so yea. For three weeks I've been coming to Lady Foot Locker to look at these shoes that I really liked ( urlLink www.ladyfootlocker.com ) . Today I finally tried them on and they look really "not me". Tomorrow my dad is supposed to buy me shoes but I have no idea which ones to get. Now what? But then maybe I should go to Finish Line at the Lincolnwood Mall to buy Birdmans( urlLink www.finishline.com ) . Or maybe I should get G-Units which are from Reebok but then they're expensive. So I don't know. I'm so confused... how about Phat Farms?( urlLink www.finishline.com ). Or maybe I should get those Baby Phats? ( urlLink www.babyphat.com  I don't know people. Please someone leave a comment to tell me which ones I should get. Thank You. Ok so on with the talk. I feel really bad because I made Jenini be late and her mom is mad at her. This is the second time this happened and it was my fault both times. I really want Jenini to come to the White Sox game with me on the 30th and it would really suck if she couldn't go. But that's not the point. I feel bad because I do this all the time. It wasn't even Jenini's fault. I mean she asked me if she could call her mom to tell her that she's going to be late but I told her that she could call later. That sucks. I'm dumb. I don't deserve to have good friends like that. I always screw it up. So bye. :( 

    


05,August,2004


	 
       Hello. Idiot-ism came very easily today. So this is what happened. First of all, around 5 pm Lena & me decide to go outside. And because it was kind of chilly outside (around 68 degrees Fahrenheit) I got the crazy idea that we should play football. Lena (as always) agreed and we headed off to Grandparents' Park. On the way there, we heard some guys calling after us twice. I couldn't see who it was very well but I had a weird feeling that it was LS and KZ. LS really doesn't give a damn about us, we could get run over by a car, for all the cares and he would never visit us even once. I know him like my freaking palm. He's transparent. On the other hand, KZ does care. Although I have no idea why, he actually cares about us and wants to hang out with us. Which is exactly why him and LS followed us to Grandparents' Park. I knew that they were going to do that. I don't know why, but today I predicted many things correctly. So Lena and me were going and went to play football at the park, when I saw them sitting on a bench about say 150 feet, or so, away from our location. I could tell that they were looking over here but we kept on playing and completely ignored them. A couple minutes later Lena was "body language-ing" me to look kind of behind me but to my right. I look over there and there they were, so quiet and pretending not to know us or see us. They couldn't get more obvious. After a while, I asked them what they were doing here and LS said, "We were here first, Kid!" I said, "Yea right u took the short way around." They looked at me as though they meant to say, "Huh? What's she talking about?" I just kept on playing. They were cheering us on and they were commenting on how I couldn't "not-catch" the ball at least once. Then LS called me, "Mr. I thrown hard and fast... I play football for a living." (He was "imitating" me) Then they kept making noises so that I wouldn't throw it good and so that I wouldn't catch it. But I kept catching it every single time. And when I would sometimes bend over in order to reach the football, they would go like, "OOOOOO!!" Stupid. My perfect catching record wasn't broken until Lena "accidentally" smacked me in the forehead with the football. The guys were cheering because of my broken record. Then KZ kept making moaning sounds like he was doing someone, that COMPLETELY threw my concentration off. I dropped it two times. That was IT. I was pissed off because of that. I started going towards like him like I'm going to smack him or something. LS immediately got up and started walking away. There was no hesitation. KZ got up just a little after him and he said, "Well I guess I should be going now... so umm... see u later." and I'm like, "Where do u think you're going?" Then I was going after him and he kept walking faster and faster. Just in case u guys don't know me, I wouldn't have done anything to HIM, just to scare him a little. So I kept on going and then all of a sudden I heard Lena yell, "Watch out behind u!" But I wasn't listening. LS wrapped his hands around my waist and turned me three times in a circle. Then he let go off me and I fell on the ground. He started running and I ran after him, but I was too tired and didn't feel like catching him. So I let him go. I walked back to Lena and he walked to KZ. He looked over and I flicked him off. He was surprised. Lena &amp; me kept playing football for a little and the guys were laying on a bench observing us. Then I told Lena that we should go to my crib. She said, "Ok" and we left. The guys didn't follow us this time. Even though LS made me smile a couple of times, he's still not back on my good side. Lena and I walked back to my crib and we chilled there a little. Then we left again to go to the park. We had a little bet going. We bet $5 on if they were still at the park, Lena lost because she thought that they were. That was the first time she lost a bet to me. We played for a while and then I threw a perfect, strong and long spiral, just simply out of nowhere. Then a guy happened to walk by and told me that I had a strong arm and he gave me a 'thumbs-up'. I was so proud of myself. Then when he passed by Lena told me that he flatuated. Heh. Then we played for a while and then later, started heading home. On the way home we played football and I got smacked in the jaw by the ball and almost got run over by a car. Then we saw Kayles walking and I was shocked. He stopped to talk to us and I could smell the fumes even from a distance of about a good ten feet. Lena asked him where he had been all this time and he said that he was in hell. I asked him to describe this "hell" and he said, "Well imagine spending a month and a half at the house of a relative who u hate the most." I was like, "Ooo that's bad, so who's this relative?" and he said, "My brother." I was shocked at that, I couldn't imagine someone hating their own brother, I mean if I had a brother I would look up to him. But whatever. Then he asked to see the football and Lena looked at me as if to say, "Can he see it?" and I nodden positively. He threw it to me and it was a nice spiral, a little low, but that was the tree's fault. Then he left. Then we walked on and kept throwing the ball. For some reason I get this thrill and my adrenaline is running when we play from different sides of a street, I guess it's the danger. Then we kept on going and there was baldy, a.k.a. Sidali, from across the street. He crossed the road to chat for a while and I dissed his gay bike, it was a BMXer with shiny rims. He said it was his sister's. Strange things happen to strange people, why would a girl who doesn't BMX have a BMXer? Whatever. Then Lena threw the ball, it hit Sidali in the back, it falls into the street, a car comes and stops. There stops another car behind it. I run like hell into the street and get it. Everyone stares at us, I assure them that everything is allright. Out of nowhere, KZ and LS show up. They laugh. They go another way then us, I keep looking at LS and he says, "What?" and I say, "Nothing." We keep going towards Polak world and they cross the street back and follow us. We go on a parking lot, behind a building, we wait there for a while and then pass by Polak world to see if they are there. KZ had his back turned to the real world, and LS was right next to him but had his back turned to Polak world. It was obvious that they were hiding something. There was a flame between their hands, they were trying to light one. Minors smoking, especially in a place as visible as that. Not even I am as stupid as that. KZ saw us coming but he didn't hide it because they know that we wouldn't snitch. Or would we? So then we walked to Lena's house to see if her "lover" (lol) was in the park. He wasn't, there were Edd and some other dudes. Sidali was hanging out with Nicole and her bitch. Then he told Lena &amp; me to "hold up" for him. I flicked him off. Then when Sidali came I asked him why he doesn't go hang with the hoes and he asked me if there's something going on between us since she just called me a bitch and I just called her a hoe. Then I kind of pissed him off and he left and didn't come back. I kind of feel bad about that, I somehow always come out to be the bad one. I apologize. Then Lena and me went to sit outside of Polak world and on the way there we saw Arnie. Lena was once again too shy to say anything, he didn't either. We went to our destination and we chilled out, then a couple minutes later (8:15) my mom calls me to go copy something in Jewel with my dad. My dad got mad because my mom made me "stop my football game early" and because she was too lazy to go. I understand it's because of being over-worked, but I was actually having an "ok" day and she went and cut it short. I want Jenini to come to my house tomorrow or maybe the day after, but in other words, ASAP. O yea and also Svetly, but then I would have to talk to my parents about that because she lives kind of far and maybe she would have to sleep over. I don't know, I got to see. So anyways, I don't know what to do about LS and KZ. Why do they always kick me when I'm high (that's from a song)? Well I should go away now. I have nothing else to talk about and besides, I've already written too much. No one will read this anyway. Well ok bye. 

    


04,August,2004


	 
       Hello. Today was kind of crappy. Thank God my telly was turned off last night because Collin had called me at 1:56 am!! He must be crazy... I called him today but he didn't pick the phone up. So anyway, about my day, first Lena & me went outside &amp; were walking around. There was not much to do but just walk around. We saw LS several times, either by himself or with some other guys. "Fake" skaters like for example Waldo. LS saw us but we don't even bother to greet each other anymore. He couldn't even look at me. It's truly over. I'm saying this like there was actually something between us. But there wasn't. Anyway, my friendships with everyone are kind of screwed up right now. Justyna doesn't hang out with us anymore at all. When she told us that she met some rocker guys I didn't realize that we were going to get ignored like that. Things completely changed after she met Edd* & them. I also saw Iga today with this one Polish chick but I forgot her name. Iga got braces, it kind of looks "unlike" her preppy self. She greeted me &amp; I greeted her back (I was surprised because I thought that she forgot me). We also saw Mary today, she talked to us for a while & then Ana called her over there like "Omigosh!!..." Lena &amp; I must be the only chicks around high school age in this neighborhood who don't talk to any of the Polish guys (Pat doesn't count though). Speak of the devil, he just signed off the net. Lol. U know, it's not like I really care, I mean I'm just trying to point things out. Did that just sound wrong to me or did the rest of u hear that too? Ok well I was going to tell u something important but now I forgot. Jana, Lena & me are going to go to the mall some day soon &amp; believe me I want to meet more guys there, but I wouldn't mind simply just Collin & his friends. So anyway, I don't know what else to talk about so I'm out of here. I hate the tall Polaks, they're so mean &amp; stupid. I'm faking things like being friends with Kasha & Ana, &amp; Iga, Jackie & Aleks. It's kind of gay. What's even gayer... I have no guy friends. Seriously need to get some. Guy friends that is. Ok whatever, this was a stupid, useless entry but at least u had something to waste your time. Heh. Ok well have a nice night, day, whenever you're reading this. O yea &amp; don't be a hoochie. Lol, don't ask. 

    


03,August,2004


	 
       Hi. I don't know how to describe today. It was a day-mare. First of all it was supposed to be a day of hanging out with Jana & Lena. That turned into Jana being grounded because she accidentally forgot to wash the dishes. So it's just Lena &amp; me. Not bad at all but listen to what happens later. Ok so since there was almost no one outside, we decided to go to the mall. & since we are both kind of broke, we just brought enough money for the bus &amp; pizza. On the way to the bus station, Pat #2 (not my friend but this jerk from our grade school) says something to Lena from across the street. She flicks them off, then this Lacey dude says something to her & she told him to "fuck off" &amp; he said "ok". Then when we got to the bus station, so many perverts were honking at us & saying stuff. Ignorance is the best. Then eventually the bus came &amp; it was around 5 pm, not sure of the exact time. We paid & got a transfer card in return. When we got to Gunnison &amp; Cumberland, we got out & walked like two blocks because we didn't feel like waiting for the next bus to the mall, besides, exercise is good for u. When we got to the mall we walked around &amp; looked at the stores. When we were coming out of this one store called FYE (a.k.a. For Your Entertainment), there were these guys behind us that we passed (they were checking us out, like 14 or 15-year-olds) & then there were these 11-year-old boys in front of us who were like practically running. Then one of the guys behind us was like "Hey Kevin come here, let me hook u up... which one do u like? C'mon man." &amp; the little Kevin guy was like "No... I don't know u man, get away from me" & then those little dudes ran away while the older ones were following us for a while &amp; then they kind of got left behind. Then Lena & me walked around for a while longer &amp; then we were hungry so we decided to go to the (dum, dum, duum) Food Court. We got pizza & drinks. &amp; just guess who was like 2 tables over... those guys who were following us. Then Lena & me were just talking &amp; stuff & then we saw one of the guys pass by us. Then comes that cleaning lady a.k.a. Blind Date lady to us &amp; says that the guy that just passed by us was on a dare from his 4 friends, he was supposed to say hi to us but he was too scared. So he just passed by us like nothing happened. Then she said that we should make them feel like fools & that WE should say hi to THEM. I was like "ok" &amp; stuff. Then the lady goes over to the guys' table & tells them that they are chickens &amp; they were laughing their asses off. Then she made that guy who was too scared & his friend come over to us &amp; sit by us & get to know each other. She was like "So tell her your name, what's your name?" &amp; he goes "John" & then she asks for my name &amp; I tell her & then she's commanding him to have a seat right next to me. Man the lady's nuts lol. Then she left &amp; then the dude's friend was like "That's not his name, his name's Collin*." & we all start talking &amp; Collin asks for my number so I give it to him. It was kind of awkward but funny. Turns out that Collin already goes to Taft & he's going to be a Sophie (I think...) &amp; his friend Mike* is our age & he's also going to go to Taft. Then eventually I said that we should go &amp; we did. Then we went to the newly-opened Target. We looked at bras & stuff &amp; laughed our asses off at some of the gay bras. Then we got out of Target & there was Collin standing by the escalator, his back faced to us. Then I waved to him &amp; said "Hi!" He shyly replied. Then Mike waved to us from the top of the escalator. We waved back. It was funny. Then we walked around & while in the bathroom, my telly rings. It was Collin. I couldn't pick up so I just silenced it. Then when we got out, telly rang again &amp; I was able to pick up. It was Mike calling from Collin's telly saying, "Collin wants to know if he can walk with u guys." & I'm like "Sure, where are u guys?" &amp; then I couldn't hear him so I hung up & then we kept calling each other &amp; then Lena called them form my telly & Mike said that they were outside &amp; then he said that they'll be there in "two seconds" & we waited &amp; waited & then Collin calls me &amp; says that they'll meet us in Target. We went there & they were joking around with this lady who was selling binoculars &amp; such. Then she told us, "Can I help u?" & I'm like, "We're with them." LMAO. With them. Anyway, then we were walking around &amp; whichever move I made Collin was like right next to me, always moving towards. But not too close. So then Lena & me had to go or we would miss the bus. We went on the bus stop where we were dropped off (which was a BIG mistake) &amp; waited for the bus to come. I was thinking that it wouldn't really matter which of the 2 bus stops we were on but I was wrong. We waited for a bus that said "81W" & there it came. Saying "81W Jefferson Park". Idiot, idiot, idiot. Ours was supposed to say "81W Cumberland". So we got on &amp; we were rambling & rambling when I finally realized that we were somewhere where we weren't supposed to be, which meant WRONG BUS. O crap, the worst thing was that we were like more than 6 blocks away from our starting point (the bus stop by the mall). I had never been in this part of the neighborhood before &amp; I swear I thought we were in Poland. We asked this one lady about the bus but she said that she didn't speak English & I said, "Which language do u speak?" &amp; she looked at me in total confusion & then I said, "Polish?" &amp; she's like, "Yes, Polish, Polish." & then we waited &amp; waited & then I got scared &amp; tried to figure out how to get back & which street we came with, we were on Gunnison &amp; Austin. It was tricky. Then we crossed the street to ask these two ladies for directions & I asked "Do u speak English?" &amp; she said no, then I asked this other lady & she also said no, then I asked her if she knew how to get to Cumberland. We kind of understood each other, she spoke in the little English that she knew &amp; I spoke in English & Bosnian. But the point is that she saved us. The exact spot that we were on was the bus stop for our bus. When the bus finally came, I thanked her. Lena &amp; me waited & waited &amp; it was a long while until we got to our starting point. I couldn't believe it. Then we finally got to Cumberland & Harlem, where we got out, but we were supposed to go on Foster &amp; Cumberland. Well what can u do when I'm stupid as hell? Then we walked all the way back & when we finally got there, there was Doug &amp; his friends & Rita &amp; Iman across the street. That bitch had the fucking nerve to say, "EWW!!" to me. I said "Go fuck yourself bitch." Sorry for being so graphic but these people are real jerks. Anyway, it was already past 8:15 & me &amp; Lena had to go. We hugged & stuff &amp; she went her way. I had to go by myself & pass Polak land, where there were like 20 or so Polish teenagers by the entrance. They were like surrounding the sidewalk, just enough for two people to pass through. As I passed by, I looked around &amp; then looked down. One of the "tall ones" said, "Chcesz" & when I didn't reply he repeated himself a little louder this time. I looked at him meanly &amp; said my ever-popular, "I don't speak Polish." Then his friend was imitating me stupidly & I was about to burst but I just passed the potheads. I hate them all &amp; Kasha isn't getting a greeting from me anymore. This is where I draw the line, because when she's with them, she never says anything to me. Bitch. They're all using me for crap, those fakes. I hope they all fail in Taft. Then I walked on & to my house. I was almost dripping wet from all the running, madness, &amp; nervousness. I took a shower & then found myself here talking to u. Now I'm leaving u &amp; besides I'm not supposed to stay on this long. Ok well bye. 

    


02,August,2004


	 
       urlLink www.xanga.com/LilBosnia  
    


01,August,2004


	 
       Hey. Well Jana saved my day. Instead of sitting here all day, she called me to ask me if I wanted to go outside with her & her sister. I, of course, said yes. Then we went outside, had some fun, went to Minuteman &amp; while Jana & me were waiting for her sister to come out of MM, all of a sudden a bunch of hotties show up in front of MM. There was Shady, Damn &amp; some "hottie" according to Jana who was driving. They came in a car in front of MM for a second & then disappeared. Right before them came this guy in a car who was about his late 20s &amp; the car was parked right in front of where we were waiting. The guy went into the store to buy something & there was another younger guy waiting in the car. I was too chicken to look who it was &amp; then when I eventually turned around, I saw that it was Tom. LS's friend. He was smiling at me & I waved to him &amp; smiled, then he nodded back. He's nicer than LS, but it doesn't matter, besides, May likes Tom. Then the guy came back a couple minutes later & they all left. Then later I told Jana about Tom &amp; she said that she never saw me waving to him. Lol. She was right next to me, too busy talking away. So then finally Jana's sister came out & we moved on along our "journey". Then we went to my house for water &amp; after we came back, Polak world was full. Full of Polaks that is. Heh. Along the sidewalk where we were walking was Matt & Bartek blocking it with their bikes. Bartek kindly moved away &amp; then so did Matt so that we could pass through, I wouldn't have budged one inch onto the grass. I don't know why though. And can u believe that LS had THE NERVE to call me today?? I was thinking, "Should I pick this up?" Since I was pissed at him, but just because I wanted to know what the hell he wants, I picked it up. He was saying that KZ came back from Florida & that "we" should come outside. I said that I didn't really have anyone to go outside with at the moment &amp; then he was saying "Why don't u call that one girl, K**** what's her name? The one that came from Texas? U know..." & then I hung up on him. Ever since Maja came here, he's been using me to get with her. That bastard. I was about to tell him off but I didn't have the guts to. So yea. Let me tell u one thing, I don't want to have anything to do with LS anymore, if he calls me again he'll regret it. Badly. Ok I should be heading to go watch TV now because it's 11:16 &amp; my dad is going to get a fit if he wakes up &amp; I'm still on the internet. So I'm watching a re-run of the new episode of "The Dead Zone" It's actually not as scary as it sounds. Ok well bye, have a nice week. 

    


01,August,2004


	 
       Hi. Today is going to be a beautiful, sunshiny day & guess what I'm going to be doing? Yes that's right, sitting at the computer chair glaring at the screen, all day. Today, as u might know, was supposed to be my shopping day, but since my parents had to give the new little baby $100 (it's like a tradition, when a baby is born u have to give at least $100), I have to wait until next week to go shopping. But I don't mind though, the little baby is so adorable. It's tiny little fingers &amp; toesies. Lol sorry. & it was so peaceful yesterday. Brb got to go eat, or not. My mom over-heated it so now I have to wait until it cools a little. Anyway, Lena went yesterday to Milan's house for a BBQ &amp; Milan's friend "Raki" (I think that's a nickname) was being an ass when we were in a chatroom & I got pissed &amp; exited the chatroom. Then all of a sudden there comes Milan on his screen name & assures me that it wasn't him &amp; that it was his friend from "rock ford". I didn't really believe him because he loves messing with people but it might have been. Then I tell him that it doesn't matter, I meant that as in "I don't care" not as in "it's ok I believe u". So then there comes Lena on Milan's screen name who was supposed to be "at home" (at least that's what "Raki" said). Then Lena is like apologizing for him & that it wasn't Milan &amp; stuff & I'm like saying that I know &amp; that Milan already told me. I don't get it. I mean Milan obviously only wanted me to be his girlfriend, & after asking me out twice I still said no &amp; he didn't IM me anymore after that. So being friends, to him, wasn't an option. But for some reason he still cared about if I got mad at him, but why? I don't get it. So anyway, I also talked to Pat on the net yesterday & damn I'm so stupid. Well I said hi to him &amp; asked him what's up & he said not much &amp; then I asked him if he was busy or if he felt like talking. & he said that he felt like talking so then we were just talking &amp; then I asked him who else he was talking to. He said "Luke" & I asked him "which one" because there are like ten Lukes around here &amp; it always confuses me. So he said that it was the one that used to go to my class, but I didn't know that he meant "graduating class" I thought it was more like "classroom". So I was thinking Luke O. But I think he meant L.T. so anyway, I said "wow u know him too?". & he didn't say anything after that. I am so stupid lol. So yea. Today I'm not going to be doing anything because Lena is going to be at the park BBQing again. I would get bored of it, but o well. Did I tell u that Maja called me yesterday &amp; when I picked up the phone & said "hello?" she hung up? That bitch. First she complains to Lena that she thinks that I don't like her &amp; why I don't ever pick up the phone when she calls & then when I pick up she hangs up. Who does she think she is anyway? By the way, she has a crush on someone who doesn't give a shit about her, but I don't know who it is though. How I know is because of every away message that she puts on, it's always about that stuff &amp; yesterday it said something like this "My hart hurts :'( ". I was like thinking, "wtf?" So Pat's online right now but I'm away & this is what my away message says, "not here because of my stupidity so leave a mssg 4 me &amp; I'll reply later or if u really want to talk to me then call the cell at 960 1832 thnx". Lol my point is of people to think that I'm fighting someone but they won't think that & I've been away for like an hour &amp; a half already. I hate Nicole's gay screen name. Her screen name is colored in like red, orange, green, light green, blue, pink, & purple. If I didn't know any better, I would say that that's the gay pride flag. Lmao. Whoo. Man I'm so bored I've been typing for such a long time. I guess I should go now, my parents are going to be at this dude's house so I'm free from like 2 pm to God knows how long. I mean home alone, I could do ANYTHING, lol almost anything. There's so many things. Not like that people. Ok well I guess I should go now. Bye &amp; have a shweet day. 

    



