
03,August,2004


     
      I wonder if I'll wake up in the morning.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      200 mg Zoloft + 100 mg Celexa + 20 mg Vicodin + 20 mg Adderall = a hot bath from heaven.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I fucking hate you.  You think its okay to do this.  To get on my case.  And yell. And scream.  And grab me like all I am is a ragdoll.  You wouldnt put up with me if I ever tried any of this.  But you continue to do so.  You yell. You scream.  Then you calm down enough just to talk bitterly at me.  You say the meanest things.  Do you understand what you're saying?  Do you understand your words make me want to slit my wrists so I can never hear you again?  Dont you fucking get it, mom?  You're the reason I'm this way.  And to think I protected you. To think I defended you.  Fuck you. Fuck you.  I dont understand.  "Youre going to have a hard life, Kristine.   Be thankful you have a roof over your head and food to eat right now.  Because you might not have it in the future."  Maybe I wont. Maybe just because of this  And all the other times this has happened   I wont. Maybe I will just finish this.  I'll end it. Then you wont have to worry anymore.  You can fucking get on with your life.  I'm sorry you adopted me. I guess you didnt get what you wanted.  Dont you wish they had a return policy on children?  Oh sorry, shes a fucking fuck up. A fucking loser.  I dont want her anymore.  Take her back. Can I have my money back?  Oh dont worry, just put it on the card.  Fuck you. Fuck you.  I'm not worth it anymore. 
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      .i.t.h.i.n.k.i.a.m.g.o.i.n.g.t.o.v.o.m.i.t.w.h.y.d.i.d.i.e.a.t.t.h.a.t.g.o.d.d.a.m.n.s.o.u.p.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      udon noodles + miso + mushrooms + tofu + green onions + soy sauce = love.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I may have caused a suicide.   
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Its been twenty-four hours.  I dont know what to think.  Did he go through with it?  I have to assume so.  I could have stopped him.  But I didnt.  Perhaps I couldnt have changed his mind.  So now I'm left waiting to read his name -  [In the Irvine Obituaries]
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      [And you said 'My life is like a bad movie,' and I said, 'Thats true of all of us']  I need something to focus all of my attention on.  And the paper thats waiting to be written isnt going to be it.  I need something. I need someone.  I need .s.o.me.t.h.ing. else.  Fuck it. I cant pay attention.  I need more drugs. I need more pills.   --

03,August,2004


     
      |Make the same mistake :t:w:i:c:e:|  Once, twice, third times the charm?   Perhaps? But it seems as if I've started over so many times.  Still breeding the same outcome.  I feel like a failure. I'm running into the wall once again.  I see the signs. I see the lights, but I never see the wall.  Three more days, and then I'm free.  I'll never have to go back there again.  Three more days and my life is over.  Because I dont know where I'm going after this.  Sure, I know whats planned. But thats never the problem.  Its what I dont plan for. Its what I dont see coming.  That I run into again and again.  "Hello, wall. Its nice to see you again."  Except I never see him. I just run blindly until I can feel his abrasive touch once again.  Story of my life.  Story of my death.  Whats coming next? Life, [version 1.6].
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Letter I wrote Clayzor about babysitting the kitten tomorrow:  + + + +  Instructions for .l.3.3.7.k.i.t.t.y.z.o.r.  Separation anxiety like |m|a|s|s|i|v|e|.   Okay. So Georgia is awesome, you should know that by now.   You need to feed her at nine o’clock, noon and four. All she eats is a [little] teaspoon of the wet food all smooshed up so it’s easy to chew.   Lets see, give her some water every once-in-a-while and plop her in the cat box on the hour(ish). Hopefully she won’t take a dump on your carpet or something, that would be depressing.   Other than that she’s pretty .ea.s.y. Be gentle, but don’t worry about messing around with her – She’s a tough cookie. ^.^ /meow/  I’ll stash some of her kitty treats in with her as well, if she looks a little famished just remember this; ‘Dooooo it!’ Oh yeah. Best advice ever.  Hum. What else … She loves to chill with you, so just let her on your lap whenever you have a chance.   .Wa.r.n.in.g: Major bonding sessions ahead.  I don’t know what to tell you. Have fun. Be safe. Use protection. [Haha, gross. Please don’t have sex with poor little Georgia, it might be a little traumatic for her.]  W00t. You’re my hero.  - The Teenster.  + + + +  I've got to get through this.   Why am I so goddamn attached?
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I dont want to leave her.  And I dont want to miss him.  But I guess I owe it to her.  Camping in the desert until Sunday.  I should be home in the evening.  Dont expect to hear from me much.  Grandpa will be in town.  [meow] I'm going to miss Georgia.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Such a sleepy little kitten.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
         ^ My kitty is an .a.s.ia.n. with fur.  [More] normal:   
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      |m|e|o|w|
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I've found myself a sidekick.  I hope this takes some of the pressure off.  I want this to work out.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      [Spontaneous] |c|o|m|b|u|s|t|i|o|n|  I dont deal with emotion well.  I dont deal with |anything| well.  I dont know if I can bring myself to go tomorrow.  I dont know how I'm going to cope.  I'm really .up.s.e.t.   I. Am. Crying.  
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I need a .si.d.e.k.i.ck.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Housewife. From. Hell.     .a.p.r.o.n.s. = /sex/
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I feel very [fifties] housewife.  I'm wearing an apron.  That I sewed from scratch.  Pink. Orange. Blue. Green.  All in a row with white [b][e][t][w][e][e][n].
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Now I have to make a CD so I dont look like a du^mb^a^ss  Sifting through all the albums in front of the class.  .p.r.e.s.e.n.t.a.t.i.o.n.a.l.b.u.m.  1. "Drive All Over Town" 2. "St. Ide's Heaven" 3. "Pictures of Me" 4. "Bled White" 5. "Stupidity Tries" 6. "Bye"  My burner = sex.   
    


03,August,2004


     
      i.d.i.d.n.t.e.v.e.r.r.e.a.l.i.z.e.h.o.w.l.o.n.g.  [this] might .t.ak.e.  Project notes for tomorrow in Band / Choir:  + + + +  .b.i.o.g.r.a.p.h.y.  Born Steven Paul Smith, 06 August, 1969. Lived in Ohmaha, Nebraska until his parents divorced. Moved near Dallas, Texas with his mother. Decided to play bass at age five. [Inspired by the White Album] Picked up playing the piano by nine, for one year. At age ten, Elliott began drinking alcohol. Began playing Clarinet during middle school. During the late seventies Elliott visited his father in Portland. When he was twelve, his father gave him his first guitar. By fourteen, Elliott had begun using marijuana. In the mid-seventies, Elliott began experimenting with recording. His freshman year he moved from Texas to Portland. He lived with his father, a psychitrist:  "I would have liked to have done the same job. I've read a lot on that subject; particularly Freud. But anyhow, I was never the type to become a psychiatrist or a psychologist; I don't have enough to offer other people. As a kid, I wanted to be a mathematician, but then I realized I'd ever be able to be independent, that I'd have to work for a business or some other organization. I turned back to my one passion-music ..."  Elliott attended Lincoln High School. His first band was "Stranger Than Fiction", which made several tapes. In 1986 [age 17] he wrote "Condor Avenue" - ended up on "Roman Candle." Elliott graduated named a National Merit Schollar at Lincoln. Attended Hampshire College - Political Science / PHilosophy. Formed the short-lived "A Murder of Crows" Met Neil Gust, who wrote gay-themed songs: "homocore" or "queercore." They formed the band "Heatmiser" and began playing in 1992. Two years later they released "Yellow No. 5" and "Cop and Speeder." Elliott didnt like the music he played and could not relate to it. Eventually, Elliott went solo and released "Roman Candle."  .d.i.s.c.o.g.r.a.p.h.y.  --

03,August,2004


     
      Should I feel guilty for this?  Should I be counting down the days  Until I never have to see these people again?  Why do I take so much care in some things  But not in others?  Why am I the way I am?  Why did I turn out like this?  .n.a.t.u.r.e. [vs.] /n/u/r/t/u/r/e/
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      --

03,August,2004


     
      I have no more energy.  I have no more creativity.  I no longer have a 

03,August,2004


     
      I have a lot to do.  A lot to think about.  But emotions dont stop to think about  The deadlines I must meet.  [Fuck you] .c.h.r.o.n.i.c.d.e.p.r.e.s.s.i.o.n.  [Fuck you] .z.o.l.o.f.t.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      All these ghost-towns share a name, "Anywhere, USA."  Sitt.ing. in my computer chair  Putt.ing. off all the work that needs to be done  Eat.ing. popcorn and   Gett.ing. fat  Wish.ing. things weren't as they are  Know.ing. they'll never change  Find.ing. the strength to give up and  Hat.ing. myself for it. 
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Been wearing my sexy emo glasses.  They're hot like fire.  Went out to dinner with the mother unit.  Food solves all our problems.  She suggested we go to Jenny Craig together.  Does that mean she thinks I should lose weight?  [Sigh]  Now I'm home. Wanting to take pictures...  So I can be creative and edit some more.  But my mother took my digital camera.  [Pout] [Sigh]  Its going to be a long night.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
         Can you see me through these walls I'm trapped behind?  I didnt think so.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      w.h.y.c.a.n.t.i.f.o.c.u.s.a.n.y.m.o.r.e.  Focus, damnit. Just fucking [focus].
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      . Everybody's . dying . just . to . get . the . disease .     What started all of this?   Where did my life go?
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      My feet are asleep.  

03,August,2004


     
      - - -: I just cant even imagine you liking to drink. - - -: You seem too smart. Me: I didnt do it for fun.  Me: I dont do it much anymore. - - -: Why did you do it then? Me: Because I was depressed. And I didnt want to remember what happened. So I drank until I couldnt feel or remember anything.  Whats 'h'a'p'p'e'n'e'd' to my life?  Where did I go --

03,August,2004


     
      I miss being beautiful.   I miss fooling everyone around me.  I miss being sober.  I miss having fun.  I miss being thin.  I miss having friends.  I miss knowing what I wanted to do.  I miss feeling everything.  I miss the past.  I miss what I was. Who I was.     I miss ... Who I used to be.  
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      "You're pretty when I'm .d.r.un.k."      I'm coming down. I hate being sober.  I just want to be [n] [u] [m] [b].
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I totally snarfed that pumpkin loaf.  I feel ill.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
         ^ I look rather feline.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Oddly enough, I'm starting to miss my dad.  Five or so more days until he comes home.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      So we're fine now?  Just like |t|h|a|t|?  Sleep on it. Yell in the morning  And then we're fine?  I dont understand.  You try to make me happy with stupid things.  And then turn even those things 

03,August,2004


     
      |g|r|o|s|s|e|
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      [Screams]  She comes in at 6.30: "Take your dog outside. Shes barking."  I take the dog out and feed her, go back to bed.  7:30: "Kristine, get up."  What the hell? Its only seven thirty.  "Do you want to check your IMs?"  "Uh? What?"  "I'm going to disconnect your computer from the internet."  What the fuck?! Okay. Not only this, but yesterday she unplugged the keyboard,  Took my cell phone,  And yelled at me for an hour.  So, I get up. Go to check my e-mail and get the directions for the girls that have to come over today...  AND THE FUCKING COMPUTER IS TURNED OFF.  Why does she keep turning it off?!  Its my computer!  First the keyboard. Then the modem... AND NOW YOU'RE TURNING IT OFF?  What the hell.  I give up. I'm pissed.  And on top of that, there were three really important voicemails that I didnt get because she had to be all high and mighty and take my cell phone.  [Screams]  
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      I had to count my breaths last night.  Make sure that I didnt [forget] to inhale.  And I shuffeled in the dark looking for tissues  So I didnt get blood on my sheets.  / These drugs do nothing for me. / 
     
    


03,August,2004


	 
      [edit] [edit]     I am in love with this movie.  And Harry.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Its official: Georgia is gone forever.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I have been on hold for over ten minutes.  [With my own mother].
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      "I know what died that night, it can never be brought back to life, [once again, I know]."   
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Kristine Hayes Young Musicians & Artists Willamette University 900 State Street Salem, OR 97301
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I thought this was too good to be true.  .a.n.d.i.t.w.a.s.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I am scared.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Holy shit. Mae is so [good].
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      The kitten wont stop .c.r.y.i.n.g.  She must have learned that from me.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I dont know what I accomplished.  I dont know if I'm doing the right thing.  They say they support me.   They say they understand.  But why am I feeling so guilty?  Why is it everytime I see a glimpse of her I start to cry?  My life is falling apart.  Over two other lives that I've taken in.  And now I'm going to lose both.  One by choice. One by chance.  Its all going to be gone.  And then what? Then what do I do?  I can only hope I feel better than I feel now.  Because right now  I dont want to know what feelings are.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
         Shes going to light up someone elses life.  And I'm okay with that.  As long as shes loved. Thats all that should matter.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      "How are you?" "I'm fine." "You sound tired." "I slept." "You still sound tired. Are you okay?" "I'm fine." "You sure dont sound like it." "I'm alright." "I'll talk to you later then."
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I've filled out the papers.  I've packed up the bags.  Its over. Its done.  'i'a'm'g'o'n'e'
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Dont you get it?  Dont you fucking get it?  Its not all about you.  Its never about you.  I dont fucking care about you.  I dont want to hear your stupid stories.  Dont you understand?  Or am I too subtle? Too vague?  .g.e.t.a.f.u.c.k.i.n.g.c.l.u.e.  I dont care about you anymore.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      "You wanna get boned, you wanna get [stoned], you wanna unglued like no one else." Damien Rice.  "And dont say no to [pills]." Minus The Bear.   "You just cant shut up and let go, with all the [drugs] in the world." Courtney Love.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Why does every single thing around me make me cry?  I. Dont. Cry.  Why am I crying?  Whats going on?  [sobs] I cant do this any longer.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I cant deal with any of this |anymore|.  Its too much.  This is all too much.  I'm going to have another   [n] [e] [r] [v] [o] [u] [s] .br.e.ak.do.w.n.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I = desperate.  I = upset.  I = cold.  I = furious.  I = restless.  I = so many negative things.  And you cant do anything to change it.  |i|a|m|s|o|r|r|y|
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      --

03,August,2004


	 
      I have had very spotty sleep for the past four nights.  This = war.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Its all over. Everythings over.  Why did I try?  I ruined it. Again.  [No - - - - -, its not what you're thinking.]  /i/t/s/o/v/e/r/  My [l] [i] [f] [e] is over.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      If I .fu.ck.up. the kitten is gone.  If I'm .per.fect. the kitten is gone.  The kitten is [gone].  Georgia. Will. Be. Gone. Forever.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I have a very sexy sunburn.  --

03,August,2004


	 
      Clay's alarm = suckage hxc.  He didnt get to kittysit.  [sigh]  Camping was fun. Mucho random goodness.  Cold weather. Wind. Kyacking. Hiking like theres no [tomorrow].  --

03,August,2004


     
      I've decided its too much work worrying about clothes and make-up and hair and such.  Its so not worth it.  Yeah, its okay to want to look nice once-in-a-while, but I dont understand the girls who wear heels everyday with   mini skirts straightened, dyed hair loads of make-up and a perfect tan.  I used to be more like that.  But theres a spectrum, with two extremes.  Where do I lie now? In the middle? Towards one end?  I dont think it matters.  As long as you're happy, as long as you're content why should you need a classifaction?
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      --

03,August,2004


     
      [un]written letters. [un]stamped envelopes. [un]addressed futures. [un]declared loves. [un]kept promises.  --

03,August,2004


     
      --

03,August,2004


     
      --

03,August,2004


     
      Oh man. What a headache.  Didnt get too much sleep last night.  Fell asleep on the couch and woke up at one thirty not knowing what had happened.  Went upstairs, couldnt sleep. So I read until three-ish.  Merh. Woke up at seven to the sounds of my dad fiddling in the garage.  Wasnt sure what time it was since I dont have a functioning clock in my room as of now.  So I read some more and realized how early it was a while later.  Got up anyway.  So tired. My stomach hurts.  I give up.
     
    


03,August,2004


     
      Somewhere between raspberry laffy taffy and [Pepto Bismal].  + + +  My skitzophrenic room kicks ass.  --

03,August,2004


	 
      --

03,August,2004


	 
      Out of the twenty seven hundred songs I had last week,  --

03,August,2004


	 
      "I feel as if I should be playing leep-frog in this position."   

    


03,August,2004


	 
      .s.l.i.t.m.y.w.r.i.s.t.s.   --

03,August,2004


	 
      Theres something very wrong with this picture:  --

03,August,2004


	 
      [screams]  .i.c.a.n.t.d.o.a.n.y.t.h.i.n.g.r.i.g.h.t.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      .k.i.l.l.m.e.n.o.w.  --

03,August,2004


	 
      Yeah. uh-huh, isn't life grand?
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      --

03,August,2004


	 
      [worry.x.core]
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      Anes7he7ized: How are you? - - -: Good good, realizing what a failure I truly am. Anes7he7ized: [hug] Whys that? - - -: I through my stash out, and I just realized I've  been at this shit for two years straight. Anes7he7ized: [big eyes] - - -: I've been addicted and relapsed, arrested twice,  and sold a good few ounces. Anes7he7ized: Eep. - - -: Broken a heart, and lost many many friends. Anes7he7ized: I dont think you're a failure. Anes7he7ized: Because if you were, you wouldnt even be  realizing that right now. Anes7he7ized: [that being what you just told me] - - -: ....You have no idea how happy your statement just made me. Anes7he7ized: [I hope that wasn't sarcasm] - - -: No, I mean it. Anes7he7ized: [smiles] I'm glad, because I meant it.  Anes7he7ized: I think you're a really great kid, - - -.  We all get wrapped up in things that we dont always plan  on. But its okay. As long as you realize what you want to  do with your life, regardless if other people agree with  it. - - -: That is so god-damn insightful, you should have a  little statue somewhere.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I feel rather ill.  More than ill.  I feel dead. I dont know why.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      - - -: ::knows:: moi: [pretends not to know]
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I cant breathe.   I dont want to breathe.   I never want to breathe.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I need to have my lips cut off, And my chest smashed in, My hands thrown away.  I need to be eliminated. I need to be gone.
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      "It was supposed to be so easy."
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      I pierced my nose last night.  I didnt think I could actually do it.  --


