




30,June,2004


	 
      Shes the sexiest thang in the world. Big butted and big breasted. Enough for me to grab ahold to atleast. Shes my baby and will always be ( locked up in my basement) just kiddin :P i love you baby talk to ya later 
     

    



30,June,2004


     
      Shes the best thang in the world. She is big butted and breasted. She has all the stuff i need to hold on to. Shes my baby and will always b in my heart for ever. She will always b mine ( in my basement that is) just kiddin! :P i love you for ever. Talk to ya latter
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Kelly. Well theres alot 4 me 2 say. First of all, shes my baby. shes number one in my life. shes hte light of my life. shes the reason that i get up everyday. she has one of the most amazing people in my life. her eyes r one of the most amazing things. espicially how they change colors. she also has one of the finest ass and lips in the world. beleeve me i would know. anyways i hope that we never break up. so far weve been goin out since 5/10/04. i luv her more than anything in the world and would do anything 4 her. luv u kelly   
     
    



05,July,2004


						
						    She got back today from Pennyslvania!!!! I wasent able to talk to her this whole weekend because my phone didnt have a signal...I wanted to talk to her so bad. I also just got back today from West Virginia. LOL. Dont worry, my family isnt like that. LOL. I had an awsome time , but it could have been beter if my baby was there. I have a secret to tell. I got drunk at the campsite. My mom lets me drink now and then but not alot but my Aunt Belinda bought a lot of drinks for my cuzins because their dad is cooler. Anyways they gave me some of the drinks that they had. Ill just give you the name of a couple of them . Mike's Hard Lemonade. Smirnoff Ice. Bacarthy Silver ( is that have you spell it?. Jack Daniel's. Budweiser and some other stuff which i didnt know the name of. I wish my baby was here. Well im busy talking to my baby so I'll talk to yall later. Luv u kelly!                                           

						



16,June,2004


	 
      Im so freakin tired of grown ups not trustin there kids. Me and kelly werent doin anything wrong except her mom not knowin i was at the movies but it wasent that bad. I mean it wasent like we were tryin to have sex or anything like that.....maybe a kiss of two but not that far. It gets on my nerves that parents do that kind of bull shit, and i tired of parents intereferin with me and kellys relationship. 

14,June,2004


	 
      i miss her so much/. i can barely make it through the day since i never get 2 c her. :( i hope that we get to go to emerald point tommorow. Oh well i just found out that we cant. AWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWww. Well atleast we get to go to the movies and 2 dinner tommorrow. I cant wait. ill finally get to c those wonderful eyes and lips. Yuuuuuuuuuuuuummmmmmmmmmm. LOL :P i hope that i get 2 c her somemore since i dont c her alot. :(. i wish that i could go over 2 her house some more. Oh well i cant wait till her pool party
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      I miss her so much! I was out of town this weekend and i didnt get to c her because of racing I would have rather stayed at her house instead! She is the reason for me to get up in the mornin and i didnt get to  talk to her but a little this weekend. i missed her so much. But thats gonna change since i get to spend tha nite at her house. ( hopefully...) i cant wait till i get to see her again. Shes my baby and will always be in my life. I hope that we never break up and i think that we could have a relationship in the future since weve had relationships with each other in the past and now in the future. I cant wait till i get 2 c her. She is so wonderful. I had tha worst week ever! i missed her all this weekend because i didnt have a reason to get up. I wasent gonna get to talk to my baby so wat was the point of gettin up. ISSAC SHUT THE FUCK UP! lol :P i luv u tons and tons and tons kelly  Shane  
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Kelly. Well theres alot 4 me 2 say. First of all, shes my baby. shes number one in my life. shes hte light of my life. shes the reason that i get up everyday. she has one of the most amazing people in my life. her eyes r one of the most amazing things. espicially how they change colors. she also has one of the finest ass and lips in the world. beleeve me i would know. anyways i hope that we never break up. so far weve been goin out since 5/10/04. i luv her more than anything in the world and would do anything 4 her. luv u kelly  
    


09,June,2004


	 
      Boy do i luv partys. i went to one the other day with my baby. Boy was it gettin steamy up in there. :P i had the best time. There r alot of tips 4 u 2 know about throwin a party. FIRST u need to have a variety of music so people dont get pissed off if u dont play any of the music that they listen 2. SECOND u need to have a mix of snacks and alot of alcoholics. Espicially if im there. boy do i luv smirnoff ice. THIRD do NOT have chaperones or parents at the party. It makes it so boring. FOURTH let there b games so people can get close and personal. well those r all of the tips that i can think of now so ........i guess ill leave u with these tips. Me and my baby r gettin hot so im runnin out of time.
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
      So everyone has been talkin about the water park in north carolina. Well ive got sum news for yall. all that stuff that they tell u is bs. u get there and u have to pay 26 fuckin dollars to get in the gate. 26 dollas, can u believe that bull shit. ANYWAYS u get there and u c the new ride the EdGe and u want to ride it. Well let me tell u. if u dont ride it rite when u get through the gate ull b payin alot of $$. So i wouldnt recommend u goin to the park unless ur rich or u have a season pass:P to bad for u . me and my baby have one and were the lucky sons of bitches. LOL
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
       Im goin racin again. Im gettin tired of all of this bs. I wish that for one weekend that i could sit at home or go over to my babys house instead of goin to this fuckin races. All i do wiht my free tiem is work on those stupid gotcars! Every weekend i have to leave out of town to go to a race and run descent. I get so tired.                    ANYWAYS i have been havin alot of fun time with my baby so far this summer. We have such a great relation ship. I know that all of yall r jealous. LOL. just kiddin. naw im not. I hope to get to c u soon baby . its been 4eva. cant wait till the next time we go to the pointe. well thats all 4 now . luv u bunches. 5/10/04
     
    


05,July,2004


	 
       She got back today from Pennyslvania!!!! I wasent able to talk to her this whole weekend because my phone didnt have a signal...I wanted to talk to her so bad. I also just got back today from West Virginia. LOL. Dont worry, my family isnt like that. LOL. I had an awsome time , but it could have been beter if my baby was there. I have a secret to tell. I got drunk at the campsite. My mom lets me drink now and then but not alot but my Aunt Belinda bought a lot of drinks for my cuzins because their dad is cooler. Anyways they gave me some of the drinks that they had. Ill just give you the name of a couple of them . Mike's Hard Lemonade. Smirnoff Ice. Bacarthy Silver ( is that have you spell it?. Jack Daniel's. Budweiser and some other stuff which i didnt know the name of. I wish my baby was here. Well im busy talking to my baby so I'll talk to yall later. Luv u kelly!                                          
    



