
26,June,2004


     
      im so bored that i tried to pick all the seeds off my strawberry but then  i just got more bored so i atee it but i didnt taste to good it was still kinda whiteish so it was like sour and that is like the only interesting news that i have well i got go and i think i might take a shower or something but yeah bye
     
    


20,June,2004


     
      this is a test for al those ppl who THINK they know me what u do is read the questions then after that leave all ur answers in comments okie dokie( dont forget to put the # of the question by it) i ll give the results later kk 1. how many toes do i have? 2. how many siblings do i have 3. what subject am i reapting next year in school( which may not happen cause i got a c and that int right so my mom is goin in to fight with shcool! YAY!) 4.what is my middle name? 5. what instrument do i play? well that is it ill give results later and if i dont like results ill just make another test! HEEHEHEHEH! 
     
    


12,June,2004


     
      i suck at ddr im absoultlty awful but it is so fun what to do ?
     
    


11,June,2004


     
      it is like  the morning i dont want to run today so i wont i want to sit around and be lazy that sounds like fun so far i have read for an hour and a half this morning! i am readinghe best book ever it is part of a trilogy it is the second one the trilogy it about a classs of seniors who had to have there 5 period gemotry clss in a bomb shelter because their skool ws over crowded and then thier teacher steps out of the room to make a phone call and then they realize that the period was over so they left to go to thier next class( they couldnt hear the bell through te 3 feet think cement walls!- i wonder

10,June,2004


     
      it is like  the morning i dont want to run today so i wont i want to sit around and be lazy that sounds like fun so far i have read for an hour and a half this morning! i am readinghe best book ever it is part of a trilogy it is the second one the trilogy it about a classs of seniors who had to have there 5 period gemotry clss in a bomb shelter because their skool ws over crowded and then thier teacher steps out of the room to make a phone call and then they realize that the period was over so they left to go to thier next class( they couldnt hear the bell through te 3 feet think cement walls!- i wonder y)  when they went out of the room no one ws there so they thought that it was a fire drill or some thing so they walk out side to seee the busy streets of new york city completely abandoned! that was when they realized that they where the LAST ON EARTH! that is the name of the trilogy(last on earth) i suggest u  check it out cause it is REALLY good! well my breakfast is here so bye!
     
    


10,June,2004


     
       im not a very sentimental person but i can keep a secret(clyde! and u too josh!) i wont tell who u like im a good person and i want to earn ur trust not throw it away(silly gooses)even if i dont sware i wont tell any one(really i promise)!
     
    


10,June,2004


     
      i told my friend josh that if i made a blog then he would have to tell me who he likes well i figured out who he likes and i have a blog he said he wanted to start a blog revolution which just shows how GAY he is(jk) and now i want to go do something worth my time and mabye ill do something else after that like add on to this blog but for right now i think id rather die (no effense josh)
     
    



