
30,June,2004


	 
      hmm.. well hello.. i guess today was alright.. meh i'm still not feeling very happy.. it sucks quite a bit.. i went over to sukis with my brother to watch a movie.. we rented "Duplex" it was pretty good.. then we just hung out.. his little sister was being really nice to me.. and she gave me a hug.. twas odd.. meh.. then.. after that we went to pick up Rory from his girlfriends house.. i swear to god.. rory was jerking off in the car.. i could hear it.. but i didnt want to look.. i was in denial.. it was VERY strange.. ugh.. anyways i need to block that out of my memory right now. Umm okay its gone.. anyways.. hmm yeah.. then i got home.. went on the computer.. and guess what i'm still here.. god i'm so pathetic.. some person said my life was pathetic.. and told me i should go kill myself.. it was very nice.. heh.. yeah.. i'm somewhat tempted to take her advice.. but i probably don't have the guts to do it anymore.. oh well i guess thats a good thing.. hmmm so.. yeah.. thats all i wish i were drunk.. good day -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


28,June,2004


	 
      ugh.. depression.. it gnaws at your fucking soul.. and there's nothing you can do about it. everything is so fucked up.. i don't want to be here anymore.. it doesn't make any sense.. nothing does.. i just want to sleep and never wake up.. this world would probably be a better place without me.. its not like i contribute to it in any way.. i just use up resources.. I'm not useful in any way.. It's so sad when you have no one to talk to .. i can't relate to anyone.. i feel so alone.  I don't know what to do.. -sigh-.. oh well i'll sleep it off i guess..  goodbye.
     

    


26,June,2004


	 
      allo.. today was an alright day.. i only got three hours of sleep last night and then i had to get up and act in some film bleh it was tireing.. i had to bus home and i swear everyone smelled like they hadn't put on any deoderant.. ugh.. twas annoying but anyways.. then i came home and slept all day and i felt disgusting.. i hate sleeping all day it makes me feel sooo bad now i'm worried i fucked up my sleeping pattern.. and i'm starting summer school soon.. bah anyways after that jem invited me over to hang out. so i went and had a shower and went out.. it was fun.. we watched uhmm.. hmm i don't remember the name.. we watched a movie lol and he made me a peanut butter and jam sandwhich lol woo i feel special annd yes.. my mom didnt want me to bus home for some reason so my dad came and picked me up.. gah.. i really like jem.. its so confusing.. -*hits self in the head* i'm just an idiot.. anyways then i went home.. and now..  HERE I AM wow.. amazing! anyways i'm tired so i think i'm going to go watch tv.. bye bye -lots of love and saliva, Kira
     

    


24,June,2004


	 
      lol tonight was soo fun.. and weird.. took stacey to see fahrenheit 9/11 which i FUCKING HATED.. it was the most obnoxious cocky sarcastic movie i've ever seen and what made it worse was the fact that it was over such a serious subject.. like thered be like dead burnt up blown up babies and children.. and then in the background thered be like happy music.. and fucking michael moore saying some bullshit about president bush and everyone would just burst out laughing.. stacey and i were on the verge of tears.. there were like burnt bodies.. and body parts strewn everywhere.. it was disgusting.. most of the time michael moore was just putting words in bushs mouth and it was just stupid.. it was pointless.. and somehow he managed to string it all out into 2 hours.. stacey almost fell asleep.. ugh.. anyways after that stacey and i went to her brothers hockey game.. it was SOO bad.. ugh.. i dont even know where to start.. there was this cocky idiot on the other team.. number 30.. and he kept on like pushing people for no reason.. and he kept on sticking his stick up the other teams ass.. and it was just so fucking stupid i was so pissed off at him.. i was yelling at these retards who wouldnt shut the fuck up i was like SHUTUP!!! they're like "we have nothing better to do.. we're from sook" hahaha fucking idiots.. and there were these two girls who were just sooo stupid after the game there was this HUGE fight and the refs didnt even do anything about it they just stood there and let it get bigger there were like people kicking the shit out of other people on the rink and oh my god it was so bad.. there was blood on the floor and crap.. i was yelling at number 30 when he came out so were stacey her mom and andrews girlfriend it was fuuunn.. anyways.. after that there was this asshole yelling at staceys mom and she got SOO pissed off.. they were just yelling back and forth.. but yes.. that was my day... i'm soo tired right now so i'm gonna stop typing lol bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


22,June,2004


	 
      hey hey! what a day.. today was awesome.. it was STACEYS 16TH BIRTHDAY annnd midsummers eve.. it was great... stacey and i did so much.. we went to the mall and to the beach and celebrated midsummers eve.. it was darn fun!! So yes at the mall stacey had to buy a bathing suit.. and i had to run to roots and get us two shirts.. one says tree hugger (mine) and the other says happy camper (staceys) and they rule. After that my dad drove us to Gyro Park we laid in the sun... for a few hours.. and ate food... and tried going in the water but remembered we have a fear of jelly fish.. and there were two in there so we ran away..  We realized we were being watched by strange perverted men.. men whom we didnt KNOW!! anyways.. yeah.. they were creepy.. and they watched us as we were getting ready to go .. they were sitting on a bench.. DAMN MEN AND THEIR STUPIDNESS!! and yes.. after that we went and changed in the bathroom but i found that my bottle had somehow burst into a million pieces.. and everything was soaking wet in my bag.. soo i had to wear staceys shorts.. and yes.. it was poopy.. we also took pictures! after that we were sitting on a bench waiting for my dad to come.. there were these odd asian mafia dudes sitting behind us and one of them farted REALLY FUCKING LOUD.. and i wanted to yell .. "YOU'RE DISGUSTING" but i did not because i thought they might kill me.. annnnnnndd yesss... then we came back to my house and walked to get some chinese food which was darn good.. and then we went to catch the bus home.. and some strange dude said "nice ass" so i shook my fist at him and yelled "YOU BASTARD!!!!" and stacey and i just yelled at them.. then we came home.. and went out with candles at a blanket.. to celebrate midsummers even.. we put wax EVERYWHERE.. and thenn when it got dark we decided to walk back..  as we were walking back we took some cool pictures.. one was odd.. i think we took a picture of a ghost.. but yes.. thats about all we did today and it was AWESOME.. anyways.. im going to go watch lost in translation again.. gooday. -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


20,June,2004


	 
      Well. not much really happened today.. i woke up... went on msn.. forced myself to have a shower even though there are baby spiders everywhere..  denise called me to babysit tonight.. I made fathers day dinner with my little brother and yummy chocolate milkshakes we had burritos and spring rolls which were damn good.. i got full really fast though annnd yes.. then i went babysitting.. and we went to the park.. it was soo hot at the park i was getting a headache.. this stupid bitchy girl i used to babysit with there.. the few times i babysat her she was a fucking terror.. she kicked me in the crotch and guilt tripped me.. and we went swimming and she tried to drown me.. i fucking hate her lol she was talking to her friend about how she threw water on some girl and told everyone she pissed herself and she told the girl how she spread some rumour about the girl saying that she picks her nose.. ugh shes such a hoebag.. but yes.. thats about all denise gave me a present to give stacey tomorrow.. i bet you wanna know why.. well i'll tell you why.. TOMORROW IS STACEYS 16TH BIRTHDAY yayyyy -excitedness-  well anyways im off bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


19,June,2004


	 
      woot.. i'm going to watch that movie tonight.. i downloaded it and hopefully its good.. i started watching it earlier this evening but then i had to go out.. my day started out at mcdonalds.. it wasnt very interesting.. i ate.. and then drove out too sidney to clean my nannys house.. i did that for about an hour and then she paid me 40 dollars. which was freaking crazy.. because.. she usually pays me like 25 dollars when i work for 2 hours.. after that i drove home.. i was supposed to hang out with Jem today but he got sick and then.. i donno what happened he just didnt come online at all.. so i cashed my check and.. my dad went grocerie shopping finally .. annd yess.. then. we went driving around trying to find a new bikini for me.. because i was supposed to be going up island (which isnt happening anymore) soo yes.. there were none at Old navy there were none at Winners there were none at zellers.. so we went to mayfair mall.. and i bought a really cute one with polka dots on it.. it ties up at the sides.. and its like a string.. type thingy for the top..  i feel so naked in bikinis lol but yes.. before that i had to wait in the car.. and once again i got overheated and started reciting made up poetry about me wilting in the back seat of a brown car.. my parents just laughed at me.. then i went and hung out with stacey at babysitting..and staceys mom said we werent going up island tomorrow cuz it was fathers day.. which made me quite sad cuz i really wanted to go.. but oh well -tears-so that was my day. And now here i am THE END -lots of love and saliva, Kira
     

    


18,June,2004


	 
      Today was awesome.. a great way to end the school year and start the summer... stacey and i hung out.. I met her after school.. she bussed to my house and i met her down the street.. then we came back to my house.. we had to wait for my dad to get home so we could drive down to the zone radio station to pick up my movie pass i won to see Fahrenheit 9/11, we went to the park but the grass was too prickly so we came back to my house and decided to start watching Donnie Darko.. My dad came home.. it was SCORCHING hot today.. we went to the place and picked up the ticket.. i asked my dad to pick up some pizza.. soo we did..YAY.. and chocolate milk which was darn delicious.. we went to go pick up my mom at work.. there were these clouds coming in and it was starting to get really windy.. i kept thinking we were gonna have a twister.. lol so.. my dad went into the hotel to wait for my mom.. stacey and i were getting really over heated and delusional lol we were sitting in the car sweating and laughing sooo hard.. we started singing songs in opera voices.. and we sang the munchkins song from the wizard of oz movie..  and stacey was singing really really loud.. and this lady in the other car was looking at us.. and stacey blew her a kiss hahah.. there was this moth wing in the car.. and stacey and i were freaking out.. stacey like came over.. and she was holding me so tight lol it was soo funny.. i was like dying because it was sooo warm.. it was soo windy and stacey said there were ashes on her she said it looked like mount saint helen blew up lol so yeah we sat in the car for a half an hour laughing and talking.. yah .. it was fun.. then we came home.. and had pizza.. my family was fighting and i was getting all mad at them so stacey and i went upstairs.. We fell asleep on my bed for like an hour or so.. and when we woke up we were sooo hot.. cuz the door in my room was closed.. and we had no fan.. we were soo warm.. that we were just sitting there laughing.. i like fell on the floor laughing so hard.. i dont even remember what we were saying but it was sooo retarded.. we were so parched.. we were just lying on my bed.. stacey started like having a seizure hahahah it was sooo funny.. she was just twitching and hitting my bed hahah (she wasnt actually having a seizure) i got the hiccups really bad.. and i was like whimpering.. laughing.. dying and hiccuping all at the same time lol then we got some water.. and went outside and ran around in the hose and then we went to the park and laid in the grass.. which was darn funnn and there were some random guys like 20 feet away just smoking weed in the field.. it was funny "You think you know but you have no idea.. the diary of random guys" hahahah but yes.. hmm after that we came back to the house and watched the rest of donnie darko and thennn we walked to the hyacinth and sat around for a while talking about fate.. and sluts.. annd then w estarted getting attacked by bugs so we started walking home.. on the way down my street we saw something in the middle of the road that looked like a dead animal stacey was about to pass out.. so we started walking towards it.. and we were scared that it was a cat.. we were right in front of it.. and it still looked like a dead animal.. so then i wanted to figure what it was so i started going towards it.. stacey decided to come with me even though she was so freaked out.. i was worried it was a cat.. whcih is why i wanted to see it.. cuz if it was someones cat i wanted to tell them.. we neared it.. and then.. it was a branch.. hahaha we were laughing so hard.. but seriously it actually looked like a dead animal from afar.. it looked like it had legs a tail and a head and fur and everyone.. it was also dark.. and maybe we spent too long in the sun today.. but it was the scariest thing ever.. but yes.. we took a piece of the branch to put into our scrap book.. that shall be started soon enough.. anyways.. that ended our day.. staceys still here.. but shes going home in a few mins. Sooo this was a damn long entry.. so i'll end it now lol bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


17,June,2004


	 
      duude this is so crazy.. i won free movie passes to see farenheit 9/11 next thursday off the zone!! I'm so excited! I hope i can take jem.. i wanna call him but its like 3 in the morning and hes probably busy lol. god im such a dweeb.. i have no one too tell and im so damn excited.. but no ones online and everyones asleep in my house and i cant call anyone! duuuddeee.. im sooo excited.. i've never won anything in my life.. this is fucking sweet here.. look at the e-mail i got from them!  Hey, guess what, Kira?  You win!  Yeah, we drew your name randomly to win a double pass to the Zone Premiere of  the new Michael Moore movie, Fahrenheit 9/11, next Thursday!  Now, the passes aren't in yet, but when they do arrive, we'll give you a call  at *number censored*.  When you do get the call, come on down to The Zone to pick up your passes.  We're  on the top floor of the Rock Research Centre -- 2750 Quadra Street, near Hillside,  and open Monday-Friday from 8:30 am - 5:00 pm.  When you come in, we'll ask you  your home phone number --*number censored*-- for confirmation.  Congrats, and thanks for being in The Zone.  Much respect . . . _______________________________________________________________           The Zone @ 91.3 :: http://www.TheZone.fm/    hehehe i thought it was a fucking joke when i saw it in my e-mail but it isnt! oh my god.. lol i get excited over such small things but i needed to tell someone.. so i told it too my blog -giggles- okie im going now! bye bye! -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


17,June,2004


	 
      Well today has been a DAMN HOT DAY.. and im eating pasta.. UGH PASTA its so  hot.. hey guess what... JEM WORKED TODAY.. wow.. isnt that just amazing.. im just so proud of that kid.. hes growing up before my eyes.. -tears- sooo yes.. today.. i went to the doctors.. man i did nothing today but lay around in my pjs.. SHIT I got pasta sauce my shirt! darn nabit..  so this weekend.. im going up island with stacey.. and hopefully hanging out with jemmy boy sometime as well.. and thenn on monday its staceys birthday so i need take her our for lunch and buy her a rockin b-day present.. annnnd yes.. thats all im too lazy to type so im going good day -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


16,June,2004


	 
      hello.. so.. its 2 in the morning.. i can't stop thinking about.. "relationships" and how i'm so afraid of commitment.. It's really hard.. when you can't express yourself properly.. I feel really vulnerable when i tell someone how i feel.. which is why i dont do it.. i feel like if i dont.. it wont hurt so bad when it doesn't work out which is stupid i know but its how i feel.. it seems like relationships are really pointless.. when i know it will never turn out right anyways.. I'll always get hurt.. no matter what. Guys always seem nice in the beginning and i feel like they're like that just so they can get what they want.. when they have it.. they don't want it so much anymore.. I guess im really pessimistic about the whole thing.. but its hard for me to think any other way .. when every other "relationship" i've been in has turned out VERY bad.. I haven't really been treated well by men.. so its a scarey place for me to be when once again i know theres a possibility that im going to get fucked over... man i make no sense.. im just an idiot.. i need to sleep.. i hope jem gets a job tomorrow. anyways im off to bed.. night night -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


16,June,2004


	 
      Well I just got home.. i met stacey at the school so i could go to the mall and hand out some resumes too people.. i think i did okay.. it was really draining i get really nervous when doing things like that.. anyways after that i went tanning.. and then we went to winners to look at stuff.. i got this really cool shirt.. as stacey said.. it is the equivalent of a teddy bear in a shirt.. its so soft.. and comfy and stretchy and tight.. it is the best t-shirt ever.. and i'm wearing it.. after that we went back to staceys and then too lilys for a mary kay makeup party.. it was interesting.. i got to put on makeup and wash my face and stuff.. but yes.. then they drove me home.. yeppers.. that was my day.. at the moment im eating kraft dinner.. im really hungry and bored. so i think im gonna go watch tv.. good day -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
      Allo.. I am tired.. and very hungry.. I only ate perogies today so i feel like im dieing.. Im gonna go babysitting tonight and eat all their food.. Stacey was supposed to be coming.. but i can't get a hold of her for some strange reason. Today i hung out with Jem downtown.. it was really hot.. and i felt kinda sickly.. and now im really dehydrated but im too lazy to get up and drink water (mostly because i despise water) I wish i liked it.. then i could be cool like all water drinking maniacs.. The crazy violin dude was playing his violin downtown but he wasnt wearing his darth vader mask which was a let down.. i think i'm in love with him.. and his sexy schizophrenic ways.. mmm buuut yess.. there were all these people and they looked like they were going to the moon.. they were all serious like.. and walking in line.. but they were only going whale watching.. but yes.. i need to go call someone so im going bye bye -Lots of love and saliva, Kira
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
      i feel like my stomach is about to explode.. and a huge alien is gonna come out of it.. god this sucks.. im freezing cold.. my throat is sore my head is stuffed up and an alien is about to jump out of my exploded belly.. YUM.. ugh.. i still i have to go out and give people resumes.. well someone brought me lindor chocolates this morning.. i havent eatn them yet cuz i might throw up and that would be a waste of lindor now wouldn't it? i think so. God its so nice out.. i wish i had money so i could actually enjoy it.. DUDE last night i had the strangest dream.. i dreamnt that stacey me and karoline!? of all people went to mexico.. and we went for like 3 days and when we were trying to get back on the plane karoline got on the plane but stacey and i were stuck cuz the lady kept ignoring us.. and then there was like this huge earthquake.. man it was fucked.. but yah.. i need to shower and stuff.. its like 2 o clock.. and im gonna be late seeing stacey if i wait any longer.. bye bye!  -Lots of love and saliva, Kira
     

    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink heres staceys blog 
     

    


12,June,2004


	 
      Yah so, as the title explains.. I got ditched again.. Which fucking sucks.. So yah.. I'm bored. I don't even know why I'm writing.. I guess its because I have nothing better to do anyways. Bleh.. So.. I think that spider laid spider eggs in my bathroom because last night there were two baby spiders crawling on me.. And when I was in the shower there was another one crawling on the shower curtain.. My house is infested with bugs.. Its pretty disgusting.. I don't even want to imagine how many bugs I could have eaten in my sleep... oy.. Gross.. But yah.. sooo.. What to do today.. Guess I'll just watch finding nemo or something.. Or go back to bed one or the other.. mmhmm! Life is grand.. Yep yep.. Okay I'm going now.. C-ya -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


12,June,2004


	 
      Well.. Okay so I transferred all my stuff onto this.. Because I'm sick of my layout.. And I need some change.. At the moment i'm talking to good ol jem.. He's the coolest guy ever.. And stacey is the coolest girl ever.. Well today was a boring day.. I went tanning.. And then I came home.. And pretty much just talked to jem, then I had to go to the doctor.. I was having some major chest pains.. And yesterday I had an anxiety attack.. I went to the hospital but the emergency was way to busy.. Darn nabit.. So I went home and I still thought I was going to die.. The doctor I spoke too today prescribed me with some pills and told me I should get some counseling and learn some breathing techniques. But yes.. That was my day.. Now IM sitting here... Still talking to jem.. Damn we talk a lot.. And yeah.. I'm hoping its sunny tomorrow so I can be happier.. And that is all good day -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


12,June,2004


	 
      Ranted: June 11th 2004 Feeling:sleepy well its 5 in the morning.. i spent most of my night crying over abused animals in slaughter houses.. yah i watched the videos.. for.. an hour.. and i was pretty upset.. ugh.. okay i cant keep typing about it i'll start crying again .. eh hem.. yes.. i have a feeling i wont be hanging out with stacey considering.. i've barely slept tonight..i also cant sleep because there was a huge spider in the bathroom and i woke up my mom to take it outside and when i came back it was gone.. and i was worried i was gonna fall asleep and have it crawl into my mouth or sit on it or something.. so i was half awake.. and then finally i fully woke up at 4 30.. and now here i am.. uggh im so fucking bored..a nd i wannna sleep because my eyes are burning but im too afraid. i donno how or wheni got so afraid of spiders.. but apparently im quite afraid of them..but yes.. bugs hate me.. they've been attacking me all night.. i have a huge bug bite on my back.. and i feel like SHIT.. mm bitching is funnnn.. i wonder if i ate the spider.. ugh okay i dont wanna think about that.. gros groossss.... YUCk... i think i might just sleep on the couch.. uggh.. i need to sleep good bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: June 4th 2004 Feeling:hungry/tired allo.. i just woke up.. its almost 2 o clock.. i donno why I'm writing.. im bored.. and i need something to keep my mind off my stomach eating itself lol. Well yesterday was an okay day.. i hung out with stacey as usual loll and i had speghetti.. nummy. lol.. we were walking back from the mall.. and they were doing construction on the street that we usually walk up.. they were making a sidewalk i believe.. and so we were trying to figure out how to get up the street. She said we could walk up the side.. so i started walking that way.. then she started walking the other way and we just walked into eachother .. lol can't say thats ever happened before.. musta been the heat.. anyways apparently one of the construction workers had waved her over.. and she just assumed that i knew what was going on lol.. yah.. so we were walking by those damn perverted guys. I think its no good when guys get together in a group and build stuff in the hot sun.. but yes.. they were .. commenting on stacey and i.. and.. stareing very rudely.. but yes.. its fun knowing i have power over those dickwads. Anyways.. yes.. then later i came home and sat around on my ass.. Woooot annd theeen.. nathanael came online and such.. and he said Jem wanted me to call so i did.. and we talked for an hour i believe... and yes.. had a rockin good time.. rrgh.. my stomach.. is eating away at itself gaaahhhh maybe i'll go make a veeggie burger... okay that doesnt sound like a good idea.. cuz i almost threw up.. maybe i'll just stop writing and curl up on the floor in the fetal position until my dad gets home from shopping.. meh.. okay.. enough i talk to much.. goodbye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: June 1st 2004 Feeling:just grand.. grand indeed so today was an all right day.. i suppose.. i was supposed to babysit for denise.. but then my bus from sidney got back a little late.. sooo i didnt make much money.. oh im rich 25 dollars!!.. well at least i can buy lunch tomorrow.. or even better a bathing suit.. how bout that eh.. mm i love peanut butter and jam sandwhiches they are just damn good!! but okie.. you know what .. everyone needs to vote green do you know why? of course you don't .. because all the other parties suck!! so vote green.. because.. it would be really good to have some hippies running canada rather than up tight rich bastards.. fuck the liberals fuck the ndp fuck the conservative.. VOTE GREEN or i'll murder you.. and then eat you.. thats how it goes in my game.. dude.. im retarded.. enough of this non sense.. just vote green good day  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: May.25th 2004 Feeling:perty good Yes jeremy i am the fat blonde girl.. nice of you to notice.. personally i think this is just another lovely portrayal of how immature you really are.. great job!! -thumbs up- you should have just said it to my face.. but alas you are too much of a baby to actually say something to ones face.. nice job putting it in your profile there. .. anyways.. at the moment im babysitting.. im thinking of applying at some places for a job... today was a pretty ugly day.. but i went and got the new lord of the rings and watched half of it.. now here i am babysitting.. i've been reading this really good book called "dude wheres my country" by michael moore.. its very good! in fact i think i'll go read that now.. bye bye :)  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: May.23rd 2004 Feeling:good good Well today was quite the sluggish day.. i hung out with stacey in the heat.. dude it was sooo hot.. we went walking around.. everywhere and i took off my shoes after a while cuz my feet were getting so hot.. we just ended up laying around in different places all day until we got to my house then we ate and went and tried to take a nap in my bed.. it was so hot outside but we were all bundeled up in my blanket... and it was soo warm that when we went back outside again we were freezing and i had goosebumps anyways then she went home and i just sat around.. oh yah i saw jeremys mom walking on the flats she said she was sorry and that she missed me around the house.. and that jeremy wasnt old enough to be in a relationship.. which was obvious lol but shes cute.. i miss his mom too lol.. meh.. anyways i watched this really funny movie about these two gay guys and yahh.. tomorrow im going to go see "SuperSize Me" with Nathanael.. i was gonna go to the victoria day parade but then i decided i didnt really wanna go... but im getting up early anyhow so i should go to bed in a minute.. well i guess i'll go now.. since.. im finished writing about my day.. bye bye :)  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: May.19th 2004 Feeling:not.. so happy. more like sad. okie here comes the emo crap.. yah. suddenly i just dont feel so happy anymore.. once again i am single. probably for another 9 months or so.. yay.. 9 months of loneliness.. no cuddles no kisses no nuthin. its pretty lame i guess.. cuz i guess i finally figured out i cant ever be good enough for anyone.. no matter what. God summer sucks.. seems like everyones in love with someone.. and happiness is what most people are at this time. it really sucks.. bah fuck it.. this entry is pointless. night.   Ranted: May.17th 2004 Feeling:hapPAY Hmm okay so i lied about this weekend being crappy.. it was GRAND!!! well today was anyhow.. and.. yah the other day i hung out with stacey.. that day i met her a tillicum after she went tanning then we walked to try and find a hair cutting place.. but failed until we went to the shell station and got a phonebook!! -thumbs up- then we walked island haircutter.. and i got me hair cut.. it looks much better . no more split ends.. annnnnnd I GOT IT LAYERD. yah thats right bitch i dont look bald. yes and then we walked to mcdicks.. and got yummmmy frys and such... and the dude who was giving us food said cheers... i will remember him forever and for always. Then we walked to shoppers and then we sat around outside.. we tried to people watch but ended up car watching instead.. grand fun if i do say so myself.. stacey wants me to be a makeup artist.. annnd hmmm. and then today stacey came over and we went to hyacinth . and then we went to the baseball field... -dun dun dunnnnn- and yes.. we saw a hose.. a fire hose... and we went running around the field trying to find a tap.. we were like digging at the wrong tap.. and trying to pull it off when we realized the real tap was right next to the hose... yesss.. and then we furiously PULLED it off and stacey got all dirty.. and then we were like laughing and crying on the field.. people must have thought we were on crack.. then we plugged in the hose and when we finally got it on we didnt want to get wet anymore..and then we flooded the field while contemplating whether or not to get wet.. then we were throwing this waffle ball around in the middle of the field and this guy came and we ran and jumped over this fence.. but we couldnt get over it and i hurt my crotch.. but she made me jump over even though the dude wasnt around.. and then we ran really far too this tree..and observed... and no one came out for like an hour.. so we were lying under this tree and some old lady waved at us.. and we were hoping she would let us join her for tea.. but she didnt.. and then we made puppets with acorns.. and there was some random business dude in a suit and stacey tried calling hi to him but he didnt even look.. -tear- and now suddenly we have appeared in her house.. but IT IS NOT THE END OF OUR ADVENTURES!!!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: May.15th 2004 Feeling:...uhh YAY? Hey Hey.. what a day.. i got dumped.. WOOT being dumped is like the greatest feeling in the world.. it makes me want to fly.. yah if you couldnt tell i was being sarcastic.. duddee.. this weekend has been sooo crappy .. so much fucked up shit has happened.. and after trying too put a bunch of roudy kids to bed.. i get dumped.. OVER MSN no less. wow.. thats called being a man.. wouldnt you say so? oh well you cant expect much from a person who doesnt know how to dial a phone.. or knows how to come and see you more than once a week... i think maybe hes gay.. because i dont think i did anything wrong.. OH WAIT.. i didnt put out enough.. thats the reason.. i just wasnt as horny as he thought i was .. and you know whats bullshit.. when someone bullshits too you about WHY they wanna break up with me.. just too make them seem less mean.. K NEXT TIME just say the worst.. at least then i'll feel a little better knowing that my assumptions of you being an asshole WERE TRUE.. by the way.. you needa stop flirting with fat blonde twinky chicks.. dumbass.. die.  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: May.2nd 2004 Feeling:bored hmph.. i am the uber loner.. i think i got ditched.. oh well.. i should be used to it by now.. BLEHHHHHHH.. oh well at least it got cloudy so i dont need to feel bad.. i made cake.. i make cake like every day.. theres something wrong with me.. im going to get fat from making and eating so much cake.. but i havent eaten this cake yet.. i dont thinkn i want too cuz i ate so much cake batter so my stomachs a little queesy.. hmm yah so i donno what to say.. im cold.. and i was really sick yesterday annd yes maybe im still sick and that is why im cold.. or maybe its because the windows are open.. i should close those.. yah.. good idea.. good day  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April. 25th 2004 Feeling:sickly I guess its been quite some time since i wrote anything productive so here i am.. bored because i got le ditched by le boy.. bah.. he was drunk when he said we were gonna hang out anyways.. so i guess it doesnt count *rolls eyes* ahh well i pretty much did nothing today anyways which is pretty fucking lame.. and now i have a migrane GREAT well isnt this just a lovely day haaa.. well anyways.. yesterday jeremy came over and we rented veiw from the top which was cheesey and predictable.. and there were SOME funny parts but there were like no twists.. everything was soo perfect.. and blah it bugged me.. because well things arent that perfect and if they were i'd be one happy Son of a bitch right now.. i needa go rent a horror movie. life isnt really like those.. but close enough.. well anyways i feel like shit.. so im gonna go.. lie down.. or something.. good day!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April. 20th 2004 Feeling:good YOU KNOW YOU GREW UP IN THE 80'S IF:   You've ever said the word's "Psyche" or "The Bomb". You knew who to call when there was "something strange in your neighborhood" You knew what Willis was "talkin' 'bout You've read at least 15 Berenstein Bears Books you ever thought you could "prevent forest fires" or "take a bite out of crime" You wish every day off could be just like Ferris' You remember when the prizes were INSIDE the cereal box You've put playing cards on your bike so they made noises. You've ever played Simon You Remember playing and being entertained by games such as Zelda, Mike Tyson Punch out and Super Mario Brothers. You thought mario kart was "the bomb" when Super Nintendo came out You've actually enjoyed waking up early so you could watch cartoons before you went to school or on the weekends. You remember the Power glove for Nintendo - You watched the wonder years You know that Snorks are underwater Smurfs and not an aquatic breathing device You still know all of the original Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. You know that the Shredder isn't just something your mother makes salad You got super-excited when it was Oregon Trail day in computer class at school. You always lied about everything you had in kindergarden, you thought the more you have of something the cooler you were.(ex: more instruction booklets to a game) You thought the Goonie's was the greatest movie ever. You appreciate the simple fun of the original Nintendo Games You could breakdance, or wished you could. You remember when Toys R Us still had Geofrey the Giraffe on all of its storefronts You remember the kit kat commericals You remember when happy meals came in boxes you remember the comic tv version of batman You remember MTV before Carson Daly and The Real World You can remember what Michael Jackson looked like before his nose fell off. You took Lunch Pails to school. You remember being brainwashed in school with tv cartoon songs such as "Conjunction Junction, what's your function?" You still own tape cassets You remember the Reces Peces candys, not the reces peces buttercups You remember thinking you were cool if you wore your bookbag on only one shoulder You remember when it was ok to have fake cigarette out of those "pop" lollipops You were led to believe that in the year 2000 we'd all be living on the moon. You remember when Pepsi was the choice of a new generation You've downloaded the best 80s theme songs You remember when it was "no duh" and not just "duh". You remember constructing a egg protector for a school project you had where you had to drop an egg off the school roof. You know what a "Whammee" is. ("No Whammy, no whammy, stop!!") You can still sing the Toys-R-Us song You remember mr rogers neighborhood, reading rainbow & sesame street You remember the Ernest movies. You always perfered reading "Choose your own adventure" books. You hear "Oh My God" and you automatically finish with "... Becky look at her butt!" You still get the urge to! say "NOT " after every sentence. You remember when the big huge ugly original gameboy After you saw Pee-Wee' s Big Adventure you kept saying "I know you are, but what am I? " You had or attended a birthday party at McDonalds. You know what it meant to say "Care Bear Stare!! " You remember Alf, the lil furry brown alien from Melmac. You remember seeing movies in school on a film projector. You remember when "floppy discs" really were floppy. You remember the Flintstones Kids, A Pup Named Scooby-Doo You know or use to know Jenny's phone number You used to expect green slime to fall on your head if you said "I don't know" You cut your t-shirts sleeves and wore it with your homemade Levi shorts You wanted to be on the show "Wild and Crazy Kids" You still watch the Simpsons If you can remember a funny accident involving a slip n slide or a dart board You thought bb guns were the shit! You remember when McDonald's sandwitches came in styrofome boxes You remember when it stopped being fashionable to pull your socks up to your knees You had a crush on Sandra Bullock The SNICK line up was Clarissa Explains it All, Roundhouse, Ren and Stimpy, and Are You Afraid of the Dark If you never use to care what your hair looked like. You use to throw things at your friends, even if they hurt for a practical joke. You had all the different types of playdough Your first computer didn't have a mouse You remember the green screen computers. Nickaloneon was the shit and never could be replaced. and you could never imagen "Cartoon Network" You Collected Goosebumps. Your School played Dodge Ball. You watched the Cartoon Express You prefer the simple ATARI version of Frogger over the overblown Playstation version  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April. 14th 2004 Feeling:good 40 Things You May Not Know . . and probably don't need to! | 1. Money isn't made out of paper; it's made out of cotton. | 2. The 57 on Heinz ketchup bottle represents the varieties of pickles the company once had. | 3. Your stomach produces a new layer of mucus every two weeks otherwise it will digest itself. | 4. The Declaration of Independence was written on hemp paper. | 5. The dot over the letter 'i' is called a "tittle". | 6. A raisin dropped in a glass of fresh champagne will bounce up and down continuously from the bottom of the glass to the top. | 7. Susan Lucci is the daughter of Phyllis Diller. | 8. A duck's quack doesn't echo ... no one knows why. | 9. 40% of McDonald's profits come from the sales of Happy Meals. | 10. Every person has a unique tongue print. | 11. 315 entries in Webster's 1996 Dictionary were misspelled. | 12. The 'spot' on 7UP comes from its inventor who had red eyes. He was albino. | 13. On average, 12 newborns will be given to the wrong parents daily. | 14. During the chariot scene in 'Ben Hur' a small red car can be seen in the distance. | 15. Warren Beatty and Shirley MacLaine are brother and sister. | 16. Chocolate affects a dog's heart and nervous system; a few ounces will kill a small sized dog. | 17. Orcas (killer whales) kill sharks by torpedoing up into the shark's stomach from underneath, causing the shark to explode. | 18. Most lipstick contains fish scales. | 19. Donald Duck comics were banned from Finland because he doesn't wear pants. | 20. Ketchup was sold in the 1830s as medicine. | 21. Upper and lower case letters are named 'upper' and 'lower' because in the time when all original print had to be set in individual letters, the 'upper case' letters were stored in the case on top of the case that stored the smaller, 'lower case' letters. | 22. Leonardo Da Vinci could write with one hand and draw with the other at the same time. | 23. Because metal was scarce, the Oscars given out during World War II were made of wood. | 24. There are no clocks in Las Vegas gambling casinos. | 25. The name Wendy was made up for the book Peter Pan, there was never a re-corded Wendy before | 26. There are no words in the dictionary that rhyme with: orange, purple, and silver! | 27. Leonardo Da Vinci invented scissors. Also, it took him 10 years to paint Mona Lisa's lips. | 28. A tiny amount of liquor on a scorpion will make it instantly go mad and sting itself to death. | 29. The mask used by Michael Myers in the original "Halloween" was a Captain Kirk mask painted white. | 30. If you have three quarters, four dimes, and four pennies, you have $1.19. You also have the largest amount of money in coins without being able to make change for a dollar. | 31. By raising your legs slowly and lying on your back, you can't sink in quicksand (and you thought this list was completely useless). | 32. The phrase "rule of thumb" is derived from an old English law, which stated that you couldn't beat your wife with anything wider than your thumb. | 33. American Airlines saved $40,000 in '87 by eliminating one olive from each salad served in first class. | 34. The first product Motorola started to develop was a record player for automobiles. At that time, the most known player on the market was the Victrola, so they called themselves Motorola. | 35.Celery has negative calories! It takes more calories to eat a piece celery than the celery has in it to begin with. It's the same with apples! 36. Chewing gum while peeling onions will keep you from crying! | 37. The glue on Israeli postage stamps is certified kosher. | 38. Guinness Book of Records holds the record ! for being the book most | often stolen from Public Libraries. | 39. Back in the mid to late 80's, an IBM compatible computer wasn't considered a hundred percent compatible unless it could run Microsoft's |Flight Simulator game. | 40. Astronauts are not allowed to eat beans before they go into space because passing wind in a space suit damages them.  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April. 13th 2004 Feeling:great great :D Well today was a pretty good day...i ditched family counceling too hang with jeremy.. which is.. ALOT better then councelling.. anyways soo i hung out at his house ann dwatched some television .. he asked me out i said yes.. oh man i feel so cheesey talking about people asking me out.. soo im just not going too.. hehe.. annyways.. soo we hung out for a wee bit and such and then i had to go babysit.. so he walked me too babysitting.. oh man im gonna miss his hair *tears* annd annd yah soo i went too babysitting and denise wasnt there but she left a note on the door saying i could let myself in soo i did and then i babysat jade while mckenzie was at t ball practice.. annd jade and i went too the park..and i thought she tired herself out but she was just as hyper when we got home haha and then mckenzie came home and i gave them a bath and i sorta kidna watched the game UGH i cant beleive the canucks bombed SOO BAD i was sooo pissed off!!! *anger* they better do good next game or im gonna smash something haha.. hmm and yes anyways after babysitting i came home and i was tired and sore so i had a bath.. and now its about 11 30 at night.. and i had a craveing for cake.. so .. its in the oven right now... id rather have some noodles but im too lazy to walk to any stores! annnd yes.. soo i shall go now.. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April. 5th 2004 Feeling:lonely ugh.. i feel so selfish right now.. but i need to complain to somthing so.. this website is gonna be it.. cuz my diary didnt feel good enough.. I'm sooo damn lonely.. its been 7 months almost and i'm still single.. why am i single!!?!? what is wrong with me.. am i too ugly.. do i talk too much do i talk too little.. why am i not good enough! Maybe i'm just too weird i've been hearing that alot lately.. seems all the stupid twinky girls have boyfriends so maybe if i just started dressing like a twinky and acting stupid i'll get one.. ugh.. i'm kidding myself.. i don't just want a boyfriend.. i just wanna be loved.. i know i sound like such a cheeseball.. but being loved is the most amazing feeling in the world.. knowing that the one you love loves you back and knowing you can hold them and kiss them whenever you want.. *sigh* i wish i could.. its so depressing.. everyone has somone and now that its spring its gotten even worse.. i feel like i cant even enjoy the beauty of it all.. its been so gorgeous lately.. but i want to enjoy it with somone... i was reading my book today and it had a really good part of a poem by Percy Byshe it goes like this "Nothing in the world is single, All things by law divine. In one anothers being mingle- Why not i be with thine" Oh god.. now i know what it feels like to be hopelessly and utterly in love.. i'm so disgusted with myself and really quite embaressed.. i'm quite tempted to just delete this whole entry but i wont cuz its good for memories.. *sigh* i think its just this book im reading it makes me feel like i need romance and love.. i'm such a nerd! bah i'm just gonna shutup and go back to reading.. it'll get my mind off this bullshit thing called love *tears* goodbye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: April.1st 2004 Feeling:good "Common i'll bet you a dollar! i need to bet on sumthing?!" -Stacey  "I AM NOT BETTING A DOLLAR ON WHITNEYS PROFILE!!" -Me "Yahh well... at least you dont look like you have an STD every time you go near a pop can!" -Stacey "you stupid white marshmallow imma stick U on a peice of stick and burn you!" -Me "and then we'd be like the dali lama... cuz.. we're uber cool.." -stacey "He looked like some artistic nerdy dude.. trying to do an interperative dance.. to explain... like.. fuzzy peaches..." -Me "I bet you my mind is clearer than your t-shirt on wet t-shirt night!" -Internet dude  Ranted: March.25th 2004 Feeling:disgusting! Oh god.. i ate mcdonalds for breakfast again.. i really need to start eating healthier i swear every day for three weeks ive eaten take out! we needa go grocerie shopping.. i need a salad.. or fruit.. oh god i need fruit.. i had strawberrys yesterday with strawberry dip * drools * it was sooooo GOOD.. dum dee dum right not is 8 50 int he morning.. i went to sleep at 12 o clock last night at woke up at 4 but for sum reaosn im not really tired.. my bodies messed up it wakes up and goes to sleep at strange times.. ive decided to start writing in my journal again.. cuz i cant write alot of personal things on here lol cuz too many people read it.. but of course you will get the odd tid bit of personalness hehe.. im craving oranges right now.. anyways.. hmm my friend told me that he read that an asteroid has a 62% chance of hitting earth in september! woot we have sumthing too look forward too.. i bet president bush will say it was a terrorist that sent an asteroid flying towards earth.. lets hope it kills him first.. hehe then i can celebrate before i die .. at least for a few mins anyways.. i guess it all depends where it hits.. im really hoping its far away from canada.. ohh man.. i'm suddenly really scared.. cuz if an asteroid hits and causes a huge earthquake VICTORIA WILL BE COVERED IN WATER omg... we needa move.. im sooo freaked.. drowning is like my worst fear.. well death is.. but drowning would not be a fun way to go.. ahh.. omg.. im.. gonna like.. gah.. i donno.. im scared.. i hope it doesnt hit earth! :(:(:(:( i should go out and party all summer and travel. lol like thats gonna happen owwy. my neck is soo sore.. i think im gonna go take a nap... cuz i cant hold my neck up lol.. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.20th 2004 Feeling:Lumpy/fat oyyy.. hellooo.. i just ate so much mcdonalds.. i feel like a hog.. oooyyyy.. .well.. anyways... i slept over at staceys last night.. and we took like a gazillion pictures and they turned out really good considering.. im blah.. but anyways.. stacey decided to have an internet fight with sum dude.. who was being really mean and calling us hoes and saying im not a buddhist and stuff.. and it really hurted me. but eh.. sum people are dumb bums. annd umm hmm well i got 3 hours of sleep cuz we didnt fall asleep till 3 am.. and stacey had to get up to go babysitting.. so now its like 10 am.. and i cant sleep because i hafta go out at 1 with my nanny cuz shes taking me and my brothers out for icecream.. eww.. no more food.. *gurgles* oh yes.. i should have a bath or sumwhat clean myself cuz i'm so damned dirty.. so.. i'm gonna go.. GOOOODBYYYYYEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE :D  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.19th 2004 Feeling:lonely Hey.. its 4 in the morning and i'm just really bored.. i have nothing in particular to write about .. my "spring break" has been very dull.. nothing interesting has happened at all.. today i went and babysat and found out i got a permananent babysitting job every tuesday until September... so theres a wee bit of money for me.. hmm.. stacey and i are going to sum pet show at pearkes on saturday. and when we go there i'm going to volunteer at a local pet shelter which should be fun! because i love animals.. and speaking of which.. i was watching the news today and i heard that the canadian government has ordered the killing of all golden eagles to save the fucking vancouver island marmot.. which i find is really retarded.. mostly because its humans who are killing off the marmot.. but no.. they have to blame it on another innocent creature that is just trying to live and do the natural thing that all animals do.. but.. its not like i can do jack shit about it.. what makes humans that they have the right to kill off a species of animal??? why dont they just let nature take its fucking course instead of stepping in tryna be the "hero" when really their not helping at all! it disgusts me the way humans act today.. and it ugh i dont even know what to say about it.. its just so frustrating.. *sigh* but anyways.. lately ive been feeling quite lonely.. and i have no idea why.. stacey thinks i shouldnt be wanting or looking for a boyfriend in the first place because i'll just end up getting screwed over again.. which is probably true.. staceys always right. but bah.. i just feel so freaking lonely.. it feels like everyone has someone .. and i know that un true but everywhere i look theres stupid cute couples and im like "aww DIE" *tear* im such a jealous whore.. ohhh well.. thats enough of my ranting and complaining today.. so i shall let you get on with your day/night.. bye bye love  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.16th 2004 Feeling:hyper alllooo tis i.. me.. kira.. yes! well i went and got CHINESE FOODtonight and omg its gooddd... and then.. and.. then.. i went for a walk..and then.. i went and paid my dealer back and thennn.. i went to macs and got FUFU BERRRRRRRRRRRRRYYYYYYYYYYYYY twas good.. and then i walked home.. and now im SO COLD.. and i wanna go rent a movie and cryyyyyyy my lil eyes out.. right now im listening to incubus.. i got ditched today.. which really FUCKING SUCKS cuz then i didnt get to make any other plans.. which sucks even MORE.. and so i am screaming inside.. because.. because i feel like it.. grr.. im such a loner.. i need FRIENSDN NICE SMART COOL FRIENDS. DAMMNIT TO HELL i haveagoraphobias.. i want to stay inside FOREVER AND EVER so people you should come and visit me while im stuck in my house and i will be an albino.. do you know why.. BECAUSE I WILL GET NO SUN.. because i will keep my curtains closed all day and i'll be muttering to myself and rocking back and forth saying "i have agoraphobia.. i wanna stay inside for good!!!" and then my friends will coem over and me blinded by my whitness even though no sun will be shineing on it to make it reflective. but it will be reflective anyways!... you get me Bee.. of course you do.. damnit.. i have allergies.. my sinus's are clogged and you know what that means SPRING IS HERE ITS HERE AND LOVE IS IN THE AIR.. but i cant smell it cuz my sinus's are blocked up.. so there is no love coming in for me.. none at all.. NONE.. everyone has sumone but i do not.. all i have is my fufu berry bottle.. oh man.. im a lonely old man with her cats... freaking hell.. im gonna go sit in my dryer for a bit again.. and warm mmyself up bye bye all ye faithful lovers of the west!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.15th 2004 Feeling:sleepy Well heylo.. its sunday morning.. 1:17 am.. im vurry tired.. i only got 4 hours of sleep last night and i had a very busy day yesterday.. i fell asleep at midnight and woke up at 4 am for sum strange reason.. and then i got my dad to take me too mcdonalds for breakfast..then he drove me and my brother to my nannys house in sidney so i could clean her house and ben could do sum yardwork.. i did that for a couple hours and made 20 bucks.. then we went to the bank and cashed our cheques.. but i couldnt cash one cuz my nanny accidentally put 2003 on it instead of 2004.. soo yah.. it sucked.. hmm then we went to london drugs and got me sum hair dye.. then we drove to the brick to return our tv and get a new one.. (which is way better then our old one) annd.. yes then i came hom.. my mom dyed my hair.. (golden blondeishness) and it looks alright i suppose.. its a little lighter then before and my roots are covered but it isnt really a noticable difference.. after i dyed my hair.. and all that jazz.. my dad ordered some pizza.. and we ate it..then i went upstairs and cleaned my room.. then i looked through the storage room for old picturesof the family my brothers and me.. and it was really cool.. *sigh* it makes me miss being a little kid.. soo i did that till around 10ish and then i went downstairs and watched sum television.. and now here i am.. sitting on the computer bored.. and planning on going to bed in a minute.. tomorrow i think im just gonna relax.. and then everyones got the week off for spring break so woot! but annyways im gonna stop talking now.. my fingers and eyes hurt.. night night  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.13th 2004 Feeling:bored Well alloooo there.. im vurry bored right now.. i woke up at 3 o clock this afternoon feeling quite sick.. but i feel alright now.. i went to the peircing place to get my lip peircing shortened and changed to a metal bead.. and now it looks MUCH better.. annd.. then i came home and played Geneforge 2 for a couple hours but i ended up dying because i stole sum chicks potions and she saw me.. heh.. yah.. so i got ambushed by gaurds and DEADDDDDDDDD.. but yah.. so .. im bored.. how are you? oh yah.. thats nice.. last night i was up until 7 in the freaking morning.. i shouldnt do that anymore.. tomorrow i hafta go to Sidney to clean my Nannys house.. woot.. i get mula! annd yessss.. thats about it.. i have no idea.. what else to say.. im very hungry.. i think i might go make some cake or sumthing.. chocolate cake mm.. *drool*.. well im off.. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.8th 2004 Feeling:frustrated!! rrgghh.. i wisshh.. i didnt have feelings!! feelings are stupid.. and they make you sad.. i feel like such a god damned twinky.. being sad over boys and such.. okay.. u know what.. im just not gonna talk about this cuz i feel stupid.. anyways. emm.. well this weekend was pretty uneventful.. i hung out with cam.. and my mom.. and stacey.. and thats about it.. im getting a new computer in my room as soon as i can talk to the dude whos selling his.. and then finally i will be able to have sum privacy and get away from my stupid brother.. and he can be happy cuz he will have his computer forever and for always *shakes fist* well right nowits 12 o clock.. at 2 30 i hafta go to the eyedoctor with my dad and help him pick out a new pair of glasses.. and then im going to the school to meet up with stacey and go for some coffee. and yes. how exciting!! SPONGEBOB IS ON hehehe.. but yah i need to write more often in here. it feels like i never write.. meh.. im gonna go make sum lunch my tummy hurts .. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.4th 2004 Feeling:fine.. If I could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. The long term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience I will dispense this advice now. Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth; oh nevermind; you will not understand the power and beauty of your youth until they have faded. But trust me, in 20 years youll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you cant grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. Youre not as fat as you imagine.   Dont worry about the future; or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubblegum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind; the kind that blindside you at 4pm on some idle Tuesday.   Do one thing everyday that scares you   Sing Dont be reckless with other peoples hearts, dont put up with people who are reckless with yours.   Floss   Dont waste your time on jealousy; sometimes youre ahead, sometimes youre behind the race is long, and in the end, its only with yourself.   Remember the compliments you receive, forget the insults; if you succeed in doing this, tell me how.   Keep your old love letters, throw away your old bank statements.   Stretch   Dont feel guilty if you dont know what you want to do with your life the most interesting people I know didnt know at 22 what they wanted to do with their lives, some of the most interesting 40 year olds I know still dont.   Get plenty of calcium. Be kind to your knees, youll miss them when theyre gone.   Maybe youll marry, maybe you wont, maybe youll have children, maybe you wont, maybe youll divorce at 40, maybe youll dance the funky chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary what ever you do, dont congratulate yourself too much or berate yourself either your choices are half chance, so are everybody elses. Enjoy your body, use it every way you can dont be afraid of it, or what other people think of it, its the greatest instrument youll ever own..   Dance even if you have nowhere to do it but in your own living room. Read the directions, even if you dont follow them. Do NOT read beauty magazines, they will only make you feel ugly. Get to know your parents, you never know when theyll be gone for good.   Be nice to your siblings; they are the best link to your past and the people most likely to stick with you in the future.   Understand that friends come and go, but for the precious few you should hold on. Work hard to bridge the gaps in geography in lifestyle because the older you get, the more you need the people you knew when you were young.   Live in New York City once, but leave before it makes you hard; live in Northern California once, but leave before it makes you soft.   Travel.   Accept certain inalienable truths, prices will rise, politicians will philander, you too will get old, and when you do youll fantasize that when you were young prices were reasonable, politicians were noble and children respected their elders.   Respect your elders.   Dont expect anyone else to support you. Maybe you have a trust fund, maybe you have a wealthy spouse; but you never know when either one might run out.   Dont mess too much with your hair, or by the time you're 40, it will look 85.   Be careful whose advice you buy, but, be patient with those who supply it. Advice is a form of nostalgia, dispensing it is a way of fishing the past from the disposal, wiping it off, painting over the ugly parts and selling it for more than its worth.   But trust me on the sunscreen!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: March.3rd 2004 Feeling:happy happy!!! Welll ello there.. it is.. 5 30 in zee morning.. im glad to see that ur awake?well im quite bored but happy none the less been keepin myself QUITE busy these days.. which is nice.. im going to summer school in 4 months!! so i better get crackin! on my social time that is..soo.. tomorrow i am hanging out wiff zeee loverly nathanael.. and zen on thursday im going to go see Singing in the rain with suki.. and on Fridaayy.. i was sposed to hang out with camm.. but i do not know if zat is happening anymore! me just dont know!OMG Sesame street is on soon!! Im soo excited! :D:D:D.. well i have decided to become a vegetarian ONCE AGAIN i know i know. i keep going back to meat.. but this time! im actully going to try! soo wish me luck.. i got this Peta thing in the mail and DID YOU KNOW GM car company used to use dogs as crash test dummies! theyd literally smash the dogs into walls and kill them just to see what would happen! how fucking disgusting is that.. i was appauled by it.. the human race is soo stupid and cocky they think they can hurt animals just because they cant talk or cant fend for themselves.. WELL SCREW WHOEVER THINKS LIKE THAT because i love animals.. and animals rock my socks off.. soo.. if u wanna get in the way of that ur gonna hafta go threw MOI first.. but.. i dont think that would take too look since am i wee.. buuuuuuuuuttt i would try my best.. anywayyss. i am hungry and over tired.. soo i am going to go to sleeeeppp bye bye my loveers!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.25th 2004 Feeling:soooo tired *yawn* its 1 o clock in the afternoon and i just woke up.. im soooo freaking tired.. hmm its raining and ugly right now.. but its nice frum inside.. as long as im not out in it.. umm.. last night.. Suki took me over to this dudes house.. his Name is Rorey.. i donno how to spell it :| but anyways he was vurry nice.. he lives on a FARM! which is soo cool.. and he has a HUUGGGEE dog.. i forget the dogs name but he was huge.. but i really like him.. he was so cute.. anyways.. and he has a nice kitty.. and he has CHICKEENNS lol anyways.. soo i got to hang out in a hay loft.. it was nice up there.. and umm then.. we decided to go to sum marshy area... it was all muddy and such.. and then.. we crossed over sum water.. and suki and rory got all soaked.. and then i got soaked.. cuz after we crossed theres like these grasses that are pretty much floating on top of the marsh... and i sunk in a bit. and thhheenn yah.. hmm.. so we went back.. and rented sum movies.. and got sum food.. annnd.. we watched sum of Darkness Falls tis a very creepy movie!! but then we got kicked out.. etc etc... and that was my night.. and now im just tooo lazy to type so im gonna go.. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.22nd 2004 Feeling:bored Well.. this weekend has been quite uneventful.. which is good.. cuz i was tryna not to do so much .. all i did was.. go on a 5 hour shopping thingy with stacey which was. umm well made my feet sore.. and she dropped my.. she dropped my sweater in the sink lol.. and i was really bitchy and i found out why later.. gah i got my rag out of nowhere.. so cassie was working so i asked her if she had anything but she didnt.. so we ran to zee bathroom to find there were no tampon dispensers! haaa.. im gonna complain cuz thats not cool.. so yah i rummaged through my purse and luckily i had one..butcha.. so i had a wet sweater andmy period.. and there was the hottest guy at west 49.. and ijust want him but i cant have him.. because im to much of a baby to say anything haha.. oh well... hmm hmm.. lets see...i also went to travis's last night and watched "desperado" it was stupid and cheesy and i didnt like it at all.. cuz there was too much blood.. the sex scene was pretty hot though haha.. but ya.. on the way home i saw sum fresh road kill on the highway.. and omg.. it was soo bad.. i started crying.. cuz yes i know im a baby shutup hehe.. it was no fun though!!.. anyways.. i just woke up about an hour ago. (its 3 o clock) and im boreddd.. vurry bored.. i did yoga for the first time in a couple months last night.. and boy am i outta shape.. i wasnt very flexible and my body was killing me.. but thats what i get for not keeping up with my work outs!! but its not my fault.. cuz my cat pissed on the yoga book... but i used it last night anyways haha yah im dirty.. what can i say.. bleh its cloudy.. how stupid.. i just wanna go back to bed.. but im not going too.. butcha.. im too lazy to say more so im gonna go.. bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.18/19th 2004 Feeling:fine *yawn* my body hurts.. my legs are growing it sucks.. well today sumone hacked my account but i e-mailed msn and they gave me a new password which is good.. umm after that i went over to whitneys and went cruising in a rice rocket with sum asian dude named Leon.. annd.. we went and got food.. and he bought me orange julius and we played lotsa DDR and then we went home.. well that was my night .. dont really have much to say.. im kinda bleh.. bye byes *mauh*  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.18th 2004 Feeling:sad..:( sumone hacked my account.. so.. add my old one zipporah69@hotmail.com :( *sigh*    Ranted: Feb.17th/18th 2004 Feeling:nothing.. im just here to write about cam.. bleh.. Well hello.. im sposed to be writing about cam right now.. but i have no idea what to say.. hmm.. its 1 o clock in the morning and im running on 4 hours sleep so its hard to think... umm hmm cam is the biggest stoner ive ever met.. but hes still kewl.. he has nice hair.. i like to touch it.. lol.. umm.. hes cool to talk too.. he likes to rambel.. he has nice eyes.. he has a girlfriend named Ema.. they are happy together.. umm.. he came with me to get my lip peirced and he paid for it too.. so thats nice.. umm.. hes an all around cool guy.. he likes to listen.. hes always happy.. he plays rugby.. annd.. hes vurry tall.. he likes to make fun of my shortness.. and calls me a midget. (fucker).. annd umm.. we once watched boweling for columbine together.. we were sposed to see the butterfly effect but he dissapeared for a while.. hmm hmm i once gave weed to a homeless man when i was with him.. and.. we went to a pyramid scam meeting once.. and umm.. he has a really cool bong.. and he has a brother now! he goes to esquimalt school.. he has lotsa friends i think.. he umm.. *thinks* his best friends name is Austen.. his moms a lawyer.. and his dads.. sumthing.. but their both nice.. his moms scared of answering the phone.. hes umm.. umm.. is very pretty.. he once ironed his hair and people thought he was a female.. uhh.. umm.. errmm.. he likes.. stuff..? ohh he reads.. i think .. well maybe he used to.. i donno but he has alotta books.. and umm i donno this is hard lol.. umm umm.. well to sum it up cam is pure perfection and hes a grand guy. hes like.. a donut..but better lol and sweeter so maybe like sugar? lol and yah i donno what else to say cept for he is awesome.. annd yah.. lol there u go cam.. i wrote about u for long enough but now im going to bed cuz my head hurts.. and i cant feel my face... have a grand day at school bye love *mauah*  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.17th 2004 Feeling:sad/depressed/dissapointed.. bleh..i feel like shit.. lifes a bitch... and so am i.. fuck i have really bad luck when it comes to guys eh?? its like every one of them does sumthing more to fuck me up and make me hate the male population more and more..maybe im meant to be a lesbian.. fuck.. well i donno.. anyways.. last night i went downtown with travis.. and walked around.. w00t... we got pizza.. and then we went to the internet cafe.. annd umm then we met sum dude named Scab who played us sum songs on the guitar.. and he had a cool dog.. i gave the dood 3 bucks.. and umm yess.. then i got stuck downtown for 2 hours.. cuz my bus never came.. and i met sum interesting people.. two of them were pretty nice.. they thought i was older though.. their frum saltspring and one of ems lived on his own since he was 14 cuz he does was in the music buissness or sumthing and bought him a house there annd. they let me smoke sum weed with them.. and then they caught their bus.. and then i met a guy named ryan.. who has a baby thats 19 months old named Latoya.. he invited me to see a movie but i had to go home so i gave him my number instead.. and then i met a guy who was an actor and is sueing the movie industry for a million dollars cuz they screwed him over.. annd he was interesting cept he was 30.. and he thought i was 20.. gah what the fuck is up with that.. i look lime im 12 dammit.. anyways.. yah.. it was an all around interesting night.. i met a drunkard too... he was funny.. but then finally 2 hours later when a bus never came i called my dad to pick me up.. and yes thats about it.. today i went to the doctors and had a horrible experience :S bleh it was gross.. and yah now im just sitting around being depressed about junk.. but i should try and be positive.. *does a thumbs up* .. anyways.. i gotta get started on this stupid comic book im making for travis for his b-day.. so i should go.. bubye.. PS.. MY MOM GOT A JOB.. YAYYYY!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.15th 2004 Feeling:headachy/toothachy Heyyloo.. w00t w00t.. valentines day is finally over... i was so depressed yesterday!! i saw so many cute couples it was soo sad.. but yes anyways.. yesterday i went and got my hair cut.. and it looks kewl.. and then we had my dads birthday dinner.. and then i went over to the place stacey was babysitting at and we took a bunch of pictures... and got sum pretty cool ones.. and we watched Romeo and Juliet on TV *tear* and umm hmm.. i slept over at staceys and we had good laughs.. annndd.. annndd.. yes.. i would like to upload the new pictures on here but their too big so if u want them just ask me and i'll send em over.. but anyways right now im really bored soo if u wanna hang out.. im sitting right here *geeky smile* hehe well i should be going.. bye bye *muah*  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.14th 2004 Feeling:bitter.. lol dam valentines day to hell it deserves to die.. bleh dam lovers.. *jealous* well i just woke up its an ugly day.. i got a rose though.. w00t.. my head hurts... and i feel like im going to throw up.. how perfect for a day like today... yahhh i have no idea.. what to say.. im sposed to go to 2 places tonight and i donno how im gonna pull it off.. stacey wants me to sleep over and nathanael wants to watch movies.. woo i love this song.. (Blink 182 - i miss you) its loverly... last night i watched RomeoAndJuliet.. gawd i love that movie tis so good i cried as usual lol.. oh yah and its my dads birthday!! Happy birthday dad!! .. i dont think he reads my website.. ohh welll its the thought that counts.. Im getting my hair cut soon :D:D:D finally... its so long and ugly now and split endy .. yahh i donno what else to say... i still havent figured out whether or not im gonna move to vancouver.. its up to me really now.. and i have noo idea.. i either live with my strict unucle have no life.. and get an education.. (AND NO INTERNET) or.. stay here.. annd.. tough it out.. which i do not want to do.. neither of them sound very appealing so if you have any insight as to what i should do.. it would be very much appreciated! yep yep.. i wanna keep writing but i donno what to say.. OH the suns coming out :D great now i can sumwhat like valentines day.. *makes guitar sound* If i met you in a scissor fight.. i'd cut off both your wings! bla blaaa bllaaa HEY MEGA loo mania.. your no jesus yah your no fucking elvis..... mm brandon boyd how i love theee.. anyways i think youve heard quite enough of my useless rambeling for today! bye byes I loves you *gives everyone a big huge sloppy valentines kiss*  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.11th 2004 Feeling:donno.. well then. ive had an interesting week so far i spose.. last night i went downtown and met up with this dude named.. Nathanel..i think i spelled that right.. anyways we went into chapters and hung around looking at books.. and then we went to zzas for sum pizza.. and i got two huge peices of pizza a giant double chocolate chip cookie.. and a chocolate milk.. and then a jones soda lol.. and we sat around there for about an hour i guess talking and then we walked lots.. and walked more.. and i saw the dude frum Excep communications who invited me and cam into a pyramid scam meeting and i tried to say hi but he ignored me lol.. nice guy i was gonna ask if my parents could try but ohh well his loss! Well i think im moving to vancouver its kinda unclear if i am.. or when.. but hopefully its soon.. im gonna miss my cat tho :( i had a horrible dream last night about my parents.. and this morning i ran downstairs and i started balling my eyes out cuz i saw my mom and out of nowhere she asked if i had a nightmare.. she said i looked pale and my pupils were huge.. so now im worried that my dream will come true.. i hope not :(:(...but yes.. im bored.. becuz i have nothing to do tonight.. soo yeas.. thats about all i hafta say for today.. bubye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.8th 2004 Feeling:happy! wooow its such a beautiful morning.. its 10 o clock right now and i had a fun weekend.. on friday i went downtown with travis.. and sat around in the mall looking at hot chicks? lol.. yess.. annd.. yah we pretty much sat around for 3 hours doing nothing lol.. but it was still fun.. and then on saturday suki took me to mcdonalds for breakfast and then we went for a walk at thetis lake.. and t henn we went to flemming beach.. annd then.. we went and saw big fish.. big fish is a veryy good movie i liked it alot.. it was all cutesy and it made me feel all warm and cozy inside.. you should see it! hmm.. soo i might be moving to vancouver to live with my uncle.. and go to school.. soo goodbye too all lol.. :( i'll miss u hehe.. but yess.. that was my weekend soo far i have nothing really more to say.. just that everything is grand and pretttyy.. bye byes *muah*  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.3rd 2004 Feeling:...pissed off.. whhaat the fuck.. sum dude added me on msn and i went to look at his website and he copied EVERYTHING on mine.. first of all he copied one of my old layouts just changed the picture on top.. and second he fuckin copied all my likes and dislikes and my style of writing.. what kinda person cant come up with their own fuckin opinions on life.. what a loser.. heres his website check it out.. its gay.. http://www.chosen1.cjb.net/ YOU ARE A LOSER WHOEVER YOU ARE .. dumass. and if ur reading this.. STOP COPYING ME come up with ur own fuckin opinions!  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Feb.3rd 2004 Feeling:bored/tired *yawn* tis 7:30 in the morning.. i wish i wasnt awake right now.. dammmit.. ive been awake since 4 30.. cuz i fell asleep at 8.. i got back from vancouver yesterday it was.. umm interesting to say the least.. heh. hmm hmm.. i really dont have anything to say.. im just bored.. and my body hurts.. mmm i want eggo waffles.. i think i might have one in a bit.. gah.. i need drugs.. UGGH MY STUPID BROTHER ATE MY WAFFLES.. stupid stupiiidd.. i wanted them very much.. my family eats everything.. hmm its getting daylight.. maybe i'll go take a nap.. does anyone wanna hang out today..?? :):).. no? well okie.. im bored of writing.. all though i havent written much.. anyways bye bye  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Jan.28th 2004 Feeling:alone .. *sigh* sumtimes i wish that there was sumone.. out there that had a mind like mine... its so depressing to think that im one of very few people who think like i do.. its soo hard to be alone in my thoughts all the time.. i feel so insane.. abnormal.. i mean i cant carry on a conversation with anyone about the way i think becuz then their like..o. yah.. i see what u mean.. well... im not gonna talk about this anymore.. cuz.. i dont really understand.. *sigh* am i just really insane?? is there really anyone else out there that actully has the mind to talk about like different shit.. i mean.. talking about.. sex.. and girls.. and guys.. and clothes is sooo fuckin boring.. people need to open up their mind too new things like just explore different possibilities.. maybe thats why im soo depressed all the time.. cuz im just so.. screwed up in the head and i think about crazzy things and theories.. yah im just insane.. i wish i was like everyone else sumtimes.. all involved in worldly things.. fuck.. no one understands.. whoevers reading this right now is probably like "ooo lord that girl needs sum major phsyschiatric help" oorrr is probably saying im quite weird.. which i am BE WEIRD WITH MY FOR CHRIST SAKES lol i need sumone weird.. sumone who can talk to me about time travel and different dimensions and all that jazz.. and if ur wondering why im talking like this.. i just watched Donnie darko.. it was THE most amazing movie ever!!.. watch it.. maybe u'll be enlightened and start thinking a little differently.. a little abnormally.. ive realized.. ive just put on a mask my whole life to be this person thats considered normal to society.. and normal to all my so called "friends".. but now i think its time i take it off.. becuz.. im not me and it sucks.. this world that we live in has put "normal" into a small box.. and if u think or look or act outside of the box.. ur not normal or accepted.. people need to be more accepting.. not being normal is what EVERYONE fears the most.. but really its what we all need to be.. becuz apparently.. if i think about dying... im insane.. and i needa go on pills or see a phsychiatrist.. but i dont.. this is just the way i am.. its time we stop trying to diagnose.. certain things that we call "problems" and just.. u know embrace them .. and embrace different outlooks and embrace different people.. becuz if we had that life would be verryy different.. and hopefully a better place.. but anyways.. im insane.. and i ramble.. so i shall go bye bye :)  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Jan.26th 2004 Feeling:dirty lol Hey there.. well tis monday.. annd yes.. this weekend was pretty good.. on friday i went to see the butterfly effect with a bunch of people.. it was sooo good!! Sum guy ive never met saw me at the theatre and he said i was tiny :( i was so embaressed lol.. but anyways ummm on saturday i hung out with stacey and went shopping.. and then went and babysat till 12 30.. and thennn.. hmm.. on sunday i slept all day cuz i was sick annd today i was sposed to go hang out with travis but he got sick too hmmm so right now im sitting around in my pjs.. stilll and its like 7 30 at night lol .. dammit Valentines Day is coming up :( sooo depressing haha o well.. i'll have vanlentines with my.. hmm.. self haha .. im probably gonna be babysitting all night.. anyone wanna come and comfort me with icecream? lol look at my profile pic thats how i feel about valentines day lol sum dude was gonna take me to the John Mayer concert on the 14th buuttt.. i dont think thats gonna happen.. stupid liars :( i loveeee john mayer whyyy cant i see him :(::(:(:( butcha.. i dono what else to say so im just gonna go bye bye i love you all *mwa*xxoxo  **LoTs Of LoVe AnD SaLiVa -- KiRa**  Ranted: Jan.20th 2004 Feeling:bleh.. lonely..anti social heylo.. i just finished watching a movie.. it was odd.. all about smoking weed getting drunk and doing all sorts of other things like having threesomes and such.. anyways its 12 o clock in the morning.. and ive had alot of stupid shit on my mind. i seriously never thought i could feel this alone.. i think im mostly bringing it upon myself.. becuz every time sumone messages me i just press the lil button that says "ESC" im feeling sooo anti social.. i need drugs.. or alchohol.. solve all my little problems.. it seems ive lost.. all my friends.. but.. i dont really think ive ever had any real friends.. well not as many as most people think they have .. i really cant live in this city anymore it brings me down.. i donno if its the people or my family or both.. i mean as soon as i get home theres somthing my family is fighting about.. and i just really dont wanna be here anymore.. its so depressing.. this atmosphere is just so bad for me.. i needa get a job.. i have no life.. i stay up all night watching shitty court shows.. and i sleep until 5 in the evening every day.. what a life eh. i mean theres the occasional going outage.. but i dono i dont even wanna do that anymore.. theres not really anyone i can talk to .. im sure my depression and anti socialness isnt to the point where i need phsychiatric help.. all hes gonna say is "your depressed and anti social..here how bout sum anti anxiety drugs and antidepressants that'll do that job" and then he gets paid for telling me sumthing i already knew and putting me on shit that doesnt really fix the problem but masks it.. makes me feel numb.. emotionless.. and most people dont even hafta deal with that kinda shit.. but no i had to be the acception... i mean my life isnt even half bad. my parents are assholes.. my dad and my mom dont have a job.. my little brother doesnt have any friends and doesnt go to school either.. im freakin high school drop out whos lost all her friends.. and i have a brother thats retarded and likes to piss me off.. i live in low income housing.. my parents can barely afford to pay the bills and go grocerie shopping.. wow im livin it up arent i? sum would say so.. like the dying children in africa.. buti donno dude.. considering the place i live in.. this is shit.. compared to everyone else i know whos got all they ever wanted and still complains .. sure i get clothes with my own money and sure my parents dont give a flying fuck about what i do with my life.. but at least u guys have sumone that pushes u to make sumthing of urself.. and doesnt give up on u.. like people have given up on me.. im a hopeless case. theres no hope in me ever becoming sumthing.... sumthing that'll make me money get me married with a huge house and.. 2.5 children.. and a stupid SUV that pollutes the atmosphere and is slowly killing off the human race.. while we sit around all comfy in our little homes with our little familys and our stupid insignificant jobs.. that wont even matter when we're dead and have little worms crawling through the places we never wanted worms to crawl through in our bodies.. but i donno thats just my perspective on life.. its a peice of shit really.. and thats all i hafta say. life sucks.. annnd yah. bye  **LoVe KiRa**  Ranted: Jan.19th 2004 Feeling:coooolldddness.. */*i am cold.. yes i ammmmm omg.. i was just reading my last entry was i on crack when i wrote that!?.. oo yes.. i beleive i was.. GAWD IM SO COLLDD.. make me waaaaaaaarrmm.. i wanna havve another bath fawk.. i came home frum vancouver 2day.. twas fun... cept for.. everyones mad at me.. well then.. i really dont know what to say to that cept for im cold.. cold and hungry i need food im so tempted to eat the god dam ravioli BUT NO i will get mad cow.. i think i shall give it to the homeless instead.. GAH im scared now.. ghosts. their everywhere .. man o man this computer is hurting my brain i think the radiation is starting to give me a brain tumour frum sitting on my ass on this computer for so long... ookiiee.. then.. i just learnt a new word.. FELLATIO say it with me kids FELLLLAAAATTTIIOOO.. *sentence - today i gave fellatio to a male kangaroo sitting on a linen closet in france* ^Definition - Fellatio engaging in oral sex with a male partner^ or maybe.. its both i have no freakin clue all i know is.. i have goosebumps and its 3 37 am and im not sleeping and im hungry and im watching a gay ass infomercial about gay ass politics.. oo today i was reading a bunch of articles on cause and effect it was sooo interesting.. id tell u about it but. im to lazy.. and.. yah..woot i gotta go to vancouver again and stay with sum other people loo doo loo.. okaayy so im acting likkke im on crack again so im just gonna say bye.. becuz.. im a ra tard *narf*  **LoVe KiRa**  Ranted: Jan.16th 2004 Feeling:burningness 

31,July,2004


	 
       Sometimes I get the feeling That I won't be on this planet for very longI really like it here I'm quite attached to it; I hope I'm wrong.      All I really want to say You're the reason I want to stayI loved you before I met you And I met you just in time Because there was nothing left.      I sat here on my suitcase In our empty new apartment 'til the sun went downAnd I walked back down the stairs With all my bags and drove away You must be freaking out.      All I know is I got to be Where my heart says I ought to beIt often makes no sense, in fact I never understand these things I feel.      Don't change your plans for me I won't move to LA The leaves are falling back east That's where I'm going to stay.      You have made me smile again In fact I might be sore from it It's been awhileI know we've been together Many times before I'll see you on the other side      All I really want to say You're the reason I want to stay But destiny is calling And I told them when my time is up I'm out of here      All I know is I got to be Where my heart says I ought to be It often makes no sense, in fact I never understand these things I feel      I love you, good bye   I love you, good bye      
     

    


29,July,2004


	 
      bah.. today was boring and crappy. I did nothing but sit around all day in my pjs watching tv and sitting on the computer... wow .. i'm just so cool.&nbsp; I was supposed to hang out with Jodie today buut that didn't happen which sucks.. so i just got off the phone with sam roberts kid and yeah.. I feel pretty boring at the moment&nbsp; "anywho gotta go bye" right in the middle of my sentence, Damn there's something wrong with me.. Bah men are so mean.. they all think i'm just some kind of slut that they can screw around with.. and when they find out i'm not.. off i go.. and on they go to someone else.. good times eh?&nbsp; I don't know what to do.. no one appreciates me for who i am.. I feel so alone today.. i didn't get outside once.&nbsp; Sometimes i just feel like i wanna be with someone.. i miss cuddles and kisses and all that fun stuff.. I just miss being wanted.&nbsp; It's depressing... the bluenotes people haven't called me yet so i'm a little worried that i probably didnt get hired,&nbsp; Which would probably just make me feel worse.. meh i'm too lazy to write.. im gonna go clean my room and have a shower.. goodbye. -lots of love and saliva, kira 
     

    


28,July,2004


	 
      Well hello my darlings, today was an alright day i guess you could say... all though i was late getting up for school but it didnt really matter.. bah.. i dont even have much to write about i'm just bored. soo yes i went to school i wanted to steal this clash poster for stacey from 1979 from a classroom but sadly the teacher never left and i missed 5 busses already.. sooo yesssss hmm after that i sat around at home made some kraft dinner started feeling very sick.. and then i had a shower and went over to staceys.. we went for a walk and took some loverly pictures and then we watched the sun set underneath the gorge bridge it was so pretty everything was just perfecto except for i almost killed my shoe.. i through it up and then it sorta fell and almost went in the water which sared the bejesus out of me annnd zenn we walked home again and had some tasty chinese food that i couldn't finish because .. i started to feel sick lol i'm all to comfortable with stacey.. it's easy for me to just say "i'm feeling gassy" and i don't get embaressed lol.. yes.. hmm so i gots me some tums because my stomach was so bloated that it looked like i was about to pop out a baby.. and then i went home.. and now.. here i am.. typing on this stupid lap top computer in my room.. someone come visit me.. im bored.. anyways i am off ... to stare more at this lovely screen good day! -lots of love and saliva, kira  P.S. stacey rules my world!!  -le heart!-  
     

    


24,July,2004


	 
      Well today was an alright day.. i got up at around 6:30 to get ready for babysitting ay 7:30.. got to babysitting played Yughio cards most of the time.. the boy i was babysitting was so hardcore when it came to the game when i would ask a question he would flip out at me and tell me i was wrong.. he wouldn't be a very good teacher.. i babysat till around 10.. and was asked to come back later that day ay 7:45 to babysit again because the woman had a dinner to go to with her husband.. soo after that stacey and i decided to hit up the mall haha.. umm yes.. i got a shirt.. woot.. and a job interview.. it was strange stacey and i saw this worker at bluenotes taking this blue plasticy stuff off counters with a blow dryer.. and it was all stuck and hard to pull off so we went up to him and we're like "what are you doing?" he's like oh well we decided we wanted to make it colourful this summer but it didnt really work out.. do you wanna help? we were like okay so we started peeling it off and he walked away for a bit then came back and said.. "are you guys looking for a summer job?"&nbsp; we were like yes sir ree bob.. and he was like well bring in your resumes tomorrow and blah blah.. and then after that when i was changing he came back and told us to just come to the group interview on tuesday at 6.. i'm kinda worried because stacey can't come but whatever i hope i do alright.. the thing is i have no retail experience and i'm only 15 so im going to have to make up all that with lots of out going friendlyness YAY lol yeah i can try i guess .. i just hope i don't freeze up i'm scared of people watching me when someone puts me on the spot.. bah whatever i shall not worry about it.. exams are on tuesday haha wow stressful day.. i finished the study guide the teacher made us make for 7 percent.. it looks perty good it was only supposed to be 4 pages but i made it 9.. i hope that's okay.. anyways.. yes i babysat more gave them baths and such. they made me sing to them the same song 4 times before they fell asleep.. and they said i had a prettty singing voice which made me feel all mushy inside haha well anyways i'm off to bed.. night night -lots of love and saliva, kira 
     

    


23,July,2004


	 
      Aww i love that song.. you should download it.. it's Kimya Dawson - Eleventeen.. she rules.. i just wish it was easier to find songs from her on kazaa its so cute.. so cute i might as well show you the lyrics.. so here they are      eleventeen            silver pink ponies flying over meyou may feel strange, well, you are an angel stuck in tight pants stuck at a high school dance stuck doing people things not knowing you have wings you are my serenade you are my lemonade you are my soul throw it all out the window you are my training wheel you are my chamomile you are my friend come again some other day  you are my pantomime and you are my moonshine you are my sunshine you are my shooting star you are my elbow you are my buttercup spoonful of puppycat bellyful of kittypup pretty pretty baby tin toy maybe X marks the spot and it's not what they expected sing that song again the one that makes me cry when she walks into the room and you don't know what to do  every step of every day i love you every single one of you whenever you get in your own way i love you, you love me too no pain anymore nothing to feel sorry for heaven is right here heaven is every where look at the trees dancing in the breeze feel the raindrops on your knees  silver pink ponies flying over me flying over me they're flying over you too silver pink ponies flying over me flying over me their flying over you toosilver pink ponies flying over me you may feel strange, well, you are an angel stuck in tight pants stuck at a high school dance stuck doing people things not knowing you have wings  you are an angel you are an angel you are an angel.     I guess you might not want to read it all so download it.. anyways today was a great day.. it was scorching hot .. i went down to value village with zea and jodi.. it was alright except for i was dying.. but i guess today was one of those memorable days that really don't mean anything at all.. but for some reason you remember them.. i love leisurely days.. when its scorching hot outside.. and the ground is steaming and all you do is sit there or read.. or sleep.. its great.. my dad bought pizza and popsicles and fudgesicles and juice to cool us all down.. then my little brother and i sat around outside while i read and listened to music.. and we sorta talked.. then we went and played some basketball with all the little kids in my complex.. we did that tfor a couple of hours.. running around giving them plane rides and doing "wash the dishes dry the dishes turn the dishes over!" One girl kept on making me give her plane rides and i got so dizzy and i gave so many horsie rides and piggy back rides.. -phew- i think i sweat quite a bit.. i'm going to go have a luke warm shower in a few minutes and get off to bed because i have to babysit at 7:30 in the morning.. Summer school is almost over.. and i'm somewhat sad.. and somewhat glad.. i will miss certain people and we'll probably never hang out with again.. and some people i won't miss.. for instance.. alex.. because he's not nice to me bah i would have liked to get to know people better but i guess tis too late i have this little project thing to do this weekend.. well not little its worth 7 percent of my grade which i need because.. if i dont get it i will most likely fail this course because i only have 60 percent.. i'm very worried i wont pass.. ugh.. its stressful.. i just wish i were a kid sometimes.. it was all so much easier back then.. running around in bare feet.. swimming in random neighbours pools.. playing with random kids you didnt know.. it was so simple.. getting stung by a bee was the worst part of your day.. it's sad now that i know that soon i have to grow up.. become an "adult" be "mature" have no imagination.. i wish i could go to never never land.. everything would be just grand there and i could live with peter pan.. but i guess i'm too old for that now eh..? yeah its sad.. well anyways.. i am off bye bye all you non existant readers (except for stacey who always read and whom i love dearly -hug-) bye bye!  -lots of love and saliva, kira  
     

    


22,July,2004


	 
      "My stomach hurts, and my shoes rock" I love stacey she is my one and only.. i got new shoes last night and they rule my world.. i might be able to find a picture.. SOo there's about 4 days left of school and i'm somewhat sad and glad.. because i love some people and hate the rest.. yeah.. today i was really pissy because people were angering me.. and i left class and sat outside for a bit then came back for a lovely test.. it made me mad as well.. i think i might be pmsing.. but i really couldn't tell ya.&nbsp; Damn i really love my s hoes.. i want to keep them forever.&nbsp;  urlLink http://www.payless.com/Images/beauty/034428_beauty.gif &nbsp; there are my beautiful shoes.. arent they loverly.. well that picture doesnt show their full goodness. they look grand on me.. one shoe has brown laces and the other has pink laces.. woot ohh man my cat shit in the hall today and pissed in my room last night.. shes being such a meany.. because of the new cat that we got.. she won't accept it.. but yes.. anyways i am off it is darn hot today.. good bye -lots of love and saliva, kira 
     

    


18,July,2004


	 
      WELLLLLLLLLLL HELLO.. i am bored.. as usual so here i am writing.. don't you think im just so darn cool with my last post and all.. i sure think so.. i gave myself a haircut last night lol its shorter now.. and i feel mucho lighter.. annd yess i woke up this morning.. and ate.. then had a shower.. and man o man.. this is a boring post so im just gonna do it later.. bye bye -lots of love and saliva, Kira 
     

    


17,July,2004


	 
       Whoa man.. everything just got very different on this blogger thingy.. now i can.. change the colour of my writing and the size and everything.. its really neato!  hey look i'm writing in red &nbsp;..  and back to black!   And now im writing in a different font..   And another different font.. okay wait thats the same one.. okay anyways.. schools been okay i suppose.. annnd.. i donno  i'm bored today my dad was being a shithead.. by not giving me money.. yesterday i went to Ska fest.. it was pretty fun.. YAY GAY PEOPLE Mike danced with me..&nbsp;  LOOK! this is big writing   and now back to normal.. yeah.. anyways.. that was fun. LOOK ITALIC&nbsp; and now normal.. man im a nerd..&nbsp; anyways.. im sort of ina bad mood.. so im leaving good day.        -lots of love and saliva, kira     
     

    


11,July,2004


	 
      I just realized i say WELL at the beginning of almost every post so I started with i this time.. Its about 9 in the morning and i have no idea why i'm awake but alas i am.  I had a strange dream that there were these falling stars and my dad wouldn't pick me up at school and all the exchange students went back on their bus to china and i was all alone and i died. Um but yes.. today i am seeing anchorman which should be pretty cool i suppose.. and yes.. thats about all i have to say. I must go and get some breakfast good day! -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
      oh my fucking god... i'm so bored.. someone come and amuse me.. i need a life and its friday and i am doing NOTHING nothing at all okay im too lazy to write.. good day -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


08,July,2004


	 
      Well the days have been very much the same.. get up have a shower have breakfast catch a bus.. catch another bus go to school etc etc.. meh it doesnt really bother me.. i need to actually get used to having a schedual all the time. We're supposed to have thunder and lightening tonight so thats pretty darn cool man.. annnd yes.. my jaw is killing me and it keeps cracking it is no FUN! I slept for an hour and a half today i get so tired after school.. and yes.. man i have nothing interesting to say.. there was a fire at the apartment next to my school and on the bus route home all these radio workers were on strike.. i thinkim bad luck because on the bus route i usually take a pass a hotel i've forgotten the name but some woman got pinned between the wheels of a semi truck in the parking lot.. ha.. yah i'm bad luck.. MEH people can die! :( okay no they cant.. anyways i got a new cat her name is Pekoe now.. and my older cat is afraid of her.. but i think they're getting used to eachother.. somewhat.. we're trying to fatten her up because she was  a stray when we found her and shes pretty skinny i gave her a bath the other day and she smelled like wet dog haha.. and then it got all these huge knots in her hair and they keep falling out all over the house anyways.. that is all i must go.. and do some lovely homework JOY!!!! bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


06,July,2004


	 
      Well today was an alright day. I went to school.. the morning was hell because it was raining like death.. i was standing at the bus stop with my hood on screaming "WHY GOD?! WHY!?! WHY DO YOU HATE ME!" i think people were wondering if i was retarded.. meh oh well.. soo i went to school saw the cool hippie with no shoes.. and met some crazies from sooke.. they made me smell trees.. umm i got really good marks in class today so i was proud except for some kid was spitting spit balls at me and some other guy.. it was really angering and i felt like crying .. but umm yes.. then it got really sunny and i bussed home.. and then i played with my new cat.. i named her Peko.. and then i played with Sasha because she was jealous.. and then i feel asleep for about an hour or so.. and stacey called waking me up telling me she was coming over.. we went to the ball park and got some onion rings and candy and the onion rings WERE GOD! Ugh.. im craving some now.. i was just stuffing my face. I love stacey she always makes me feel better.. then we went for a walk on the trail and took some pictures.. and then we went to the park by my house and started digging at some thing we think is a dead body.. we are going back some other day to keep digging.. because we only had sticks. Man we are so easily amused. Anyways.. i should probably hit the sack.. gotta get up early once again.. 17 more days of this hell. Bye bye
     

    


05,July,2004


	 
      Well school turned out alright.. all though i almost fell asleep in the 2nd class.. now im just REALLY hyper.. not so hyper anymore..  but i have my spongebob slippers on and i had some apple turnover.. (which was delicious i must say!) annnd yes.. at school fiona sim is in my first class.. and.. umm i met some people in my 2nd class.. one of which spat a spit ball in my hair.. which was not very nice.. i wanted to punch right in the kissa lol hmm and yes.. i felt pretty ugly but meh! what can ya do.. i was going to bus home but then i realized i had a bunch of textbooks that i could barely carry and i forgot to bring a backpack (stupid me) annnd so i called my parents.. this dude in my class said he would wait with me.. and he carried my books.. which was.. uhh strange. i think his name was matt.. annda zeenn.. yeah we got attacked by a mud wasp! -shakes fist- damn them to heck! and yes that was all... stacey and i are angels meant for eachother.. *bew bew!* anyways good day -lots of lova and saliva, kira
     

    


03,July,2004


	 
      well i'm about to bus to school in a matter of minutes.. for some reason my skin decided to rebel on me on get the first zits in quite some time.. theres 4.. and they are freaking ugly.. ugghh i got an hour of sleep.. i tossed and turned from 10 30 at night until 4 o clock then i fell asleep until my alarm clock screamed at me at 5:30 it was on full blast and i wanted to die.. i got up.. had my shower.. had breakfast got dressed.. went through the oh so hard dilemma of.. putting my hair up or down.. up won. and got dressed.. oh joy.. this day is going to be grand.. (sarcasm) anyways im off.. so wish me luck.. bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


03,July,2004


	 
      Well today was a pretty average day i suppose.. i only got 3 hours of sleep.. and i'm not tired at all.. i think i'm just on my second wind.. i'll pass out sooner or later.. i start summer school on monday and i'm quite nervous because i have to bus all the way out to oak bay high.. which is a wee bit far from my house.. umm hmm so.. this morning i woke up at 9.. and drove down to the clinic to get my lovely shot.. and then i went and got new shoes.. and new spongebob slipper which are pretty sweet.. the shoes are a little different from what i usually wear (skater shoes) they're more sporty.. but i like them.. annd then i helped my little brother find some new clothes and shoes.. and he looks pretty stylin lol zen.. i came home.. and went out again to get hair dye.. and i came home .. dyed my hair.. tis all blonde now.. i'm planning on dying it brown at the end of summer.. but i'm a baby so i dont know.. and yes.. that is all.. now im just sitting on the computer listening to weezer.. being a nerd..  -lots of love and saliva, kira
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
       Narcissistic personality disorder is characterized by self-centeredness. They tend to be choosy about picking friends, since they believe that not just anyone is worthy of being their friend. They tend to make good first impressions, yet have difficulty maintaining long-lasting relationships. They are generally uninterested in the feelings of others and may take advantage of them.   People with schizoid personality disorder avoid relationships and do not show much emotion. They genuinely prefer to be alone and do not secretly wish for popularity. They tend to seek jobs that require little social contact. Their social skills are often weak and they do not show a need for attention or acceptance. They are perceived as humorless and distant and often are termed "loners."    Sounds alot like me now doesnt it?
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Well hello.. i spent most of my night crying in my room.. listening to stupid cheesy love songs and trying to get my parents to stop coming in wondering what was wrong with me.. i think i cried for about 2 hours and my excuse was "I'm pmsing what do you expect" I think i'm becoming a good liar.. I seem to lie alot to my parents now.. it really sucks.. i  am  pmsing.. but normally it doesn't really affect me.. i guess it may have had more of an affect than most night.. Because i haven't cried that much in quite some time.. i'm hurting so bad right now. And i'm so stressed.. i think i need to see a psychiatrist.. maybe get my ass back on some stupid anti depressants.. so i can be "normal" yeah that would be good.. I'd rather be fake and numb then sad.. and dead inside..  I have to get up at 9 tomorrow.. i have an appointment at the clinic to get my fun birth control shot.. I don't even need it.. but i guess its good .. i hate getting my rag anyways.. bah i have a headache goodbye 
     

    


02,July,2004


	 
      Well today was a memorable canada day.. i went over to staceys house this morning to go up island to parksville.. we waited around for a while.. and then we started off on the long drive there.. it took a while because we had to make so many stops.. we stopped at liquidation world.. and i bought some stuff for my room for super cheap and i bought a sweater for $7.99 yeah good buys.. i need to go to Liquidation world more often.. Anyways after that we drove for hours and we finally made it.. Stacey and i walked around a bit.. some stupid guys tried hitting on us but i gave them the finger.. ugh so stupid.. and then we went and walked out to this little island.. but i got scared because the tide was coming in (i have stupid bad experiences with ocean water lol) anyways after that stacey and i just basked in the sun.. and then we realized it was 4 30.. and we had to meet some people downtown at 8.. so we ate quickly.. and went the long drive home.. we came home.. got changed.. and went straight downtown.. it was pretty fun.. we met up with maria meike lea talia.. annd some other people.. and walked around for a bit.. we watched some cool acrobats.. it was fun.. and then stacey chased around emo kids with her camera then i decided to go into the fountain in front of the parliment buildings because stacey said she would give me hot chocolate if i did.. and Leah joined me.. and yes it was cold.. but no problem at all.. annd zen hmm what else.. we umm.. did shtuff.. and then we watched the fire works.. and there were these amusing drunk dudes from ireland.. and we got a picture with them.. then we wandered around downtown after the fireworks.. i saw jem by some bar with people.. so i hid and ran away because i didnt want to embaress him.. and then stacey and i went home.. and that was my day..  -lots of love and saliva, Kira
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
      Hey hey.. i haven't posted in a while. mostly because nothing interesting has happened .. and it still hasn't lol I've been inside for 4 or 5 days now i've only gone out twice and that was too see a doctor for my  ugly wart and get it burned off and to get an ultrasound too see why im oh so sick all the time.. getting the ultrasound was painful because you have to hold your pee.. and drink 4 big glasses of water an hour or so before you go.. and she kept on pressing on my tummy ugh.. but it was sad because a lady there went to get an ultrasound and she found out she had a miscarriage.. and she was all crying and so was her boyfriend/husband..  tis sad..  umm but yes stacey is coming home from lawn bowling tonight!! And i'm excited.. i hope she wins.. because if she does she wins a new set of bowls that she's probably g onna sell for like 500$ which is quite a bit of money.. she says when she gets back that she's gonna "wine and dine me" lol she's my dream date..  oh by the way.. for people reading this.. stacey and i ARE NOT DATING lol silly people.. anyways.. im going to go find some food.. have a nice evening.. bye bye -lots of love and saliva, kira 
     

    



