
30,June,2004


    
       
      Mwah! More quizzes!! Cant get enough!       What Makes You Sexy?  by  urlLink  eva71        Name/NickName           Gender           Sexy Body Part Is    Your Boobs      Special Talents Are    Blow Jobs             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       OMFG! ROFFLE!!       Who were you in a past life?  by  urlLink  Kat007        Name:           Birthdate:           Favorite Color:           Country:           You were most probably:    Yourself, only taller       If not then you were:    Elizabeth Short              Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       HOW FECKING BORING IS THAT!?  
      


28,June,2004


    
       
      BLOODY HELL! Why is it that when you REALLY want someone to reply to an email, they dont???  *cries* I want my email!! 
      


27,June,2004


    
       
         <th colspan=2  bgcolor='#0000>

27,June,2004


    
       
           Your love is... by  urlLink  ChibiMarronchan        Your name is...           Your kiss is...    erotic      Your hugs are...    warm      Your eyes...    twinkle in the moonlight      Your touch is...    awakening my heart      Your smell is...    beautiful      Your smile is...    encouraging      Your love is...    everlasting             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       Kinda very true actually....maybe not so much about the erotic kisses (XD) but about the love. I cant really judge the other ones. Where are my snoggle buddies when I need them online!?
      


27,June,2004


    
       
        You're Exotic Dancer Barbie.  You have some moves, and will do anything for a few bucks.  Take it off girl, but keep it PG-13 please.    urlLink   If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Hee hee hee!! Wow! That sums me up in one little funny picture! ^^   Wish Josh would email me back or else Im gonna have another sleepless night. ;_;
      


27,June,2004


    
       
      Had another crap day, thanks to yesterday night. Yesterday (up until I read my emails) was okay. Purely because my vati was lecturing me and then, after I went back upstairs, I found a green sock and made it into a sock puppet of my father; the great big bogey. I showed Sam and we were both hysterical with laughter, especially when I tried to make it speak (my new talent, making socks talk.) And yesterday evening, i read the email about how brilliant josh is and I was in tears (omg! what a shock...wrote sock then! XD) So, I speant most of yesterday evening wallowing in self pity about how dumb I was to let him go. *hits head* Yesterday night, about half 10, I gave up trying to be all smiley and whatnot and went to bed. But, because I'd wound myself up   really   badly, my mind was like an angry wasp (buzzing too much) and so I was awake til 12 and then I dropped off. Then, i woke up again about half 1 and I was completely awake. So, at first, I tried to close my eyes while praying I'd fall asleep. But that didnt work (as I guessed.) Tried every method and when I realised that I wasnt gonna sleep, I started to pace around the house and freaked mutti out 'cause she thought I was a ghost. Got changed into the clothes i'm wearing now and climbed into bed just after 4, and fell asleep. (one weird thing happened though. I was praying to my buddha for something and the room went REALLY cold..I was like 0_0.) Woke up this morning at 7 and got up. I've spent most of the day feeling like im about to puke up (broken heart warrents nausea...) Went to pizza hut and could only eat 2 slices because I was about to vomit. Came home and went to sleep. Oh wait...this morning, I was gonna email josh but then my mum pulled the plug out cause she needed the phone. So, I wrote him an email offline. I wont talk about what it says cause its ME ME ME business really. I'm praying for something though because I dont want to feel this bad for the next few weeks. Anyway, I've just had another good old cry (oh yes, my tear ducts are practically dried up now.) So...yeah....having the worst time of my life because I was dumb and did something that I regretted badly (regret badly actually...)   I need a big hug. ;_;
      


27,June,2004


    
       
      I know that I should've said something before but I just couldn't...I sat there and was an evil bitch to you but in that email, I never said how it felt like my heart had been plucked out from my ribs. I just let you get away and I want you back, but you wont and so I'm just sitting here feeling sorry for myself...no, that isnt the word to describe. And I know that I was the one who broke up with you but I thought that if you broke up with someone, the feelings would just go away. But they havent. And, I know that you dont believe me but I did say that I'd never say I loved someone unless I meant it and oh god...I mean it. And yeah....we really need to meet up and talk asap or sometihng....I dont give a fuck. And I need to go now (cant explain why but if you find Kat, you'll find out.)
      


26,June,2004


    
       
      I'm so sick of everything at the moment. I thought that breaking up with Josh would stop something but it hasnt. I'm just worse than how I was before and he doesnt know and I'm just so miserable. Been crying most of today because theres nothing I can do about it and...God! Why cant I just get over him and move on. Maybe its cause you dont know what you've got til its gone. And, I'm just wishing I could turn back everything and listen to my heart. The last person I loved messed me up and then the person before that. So, I guess I'm scared of saying anything because he'll just be another statistic to me. Fuck it.   Josh, I love you so much and I cant move on. 
      


26,June,2004


    
       
      Ahhh! Refreshed after my bath (shaved my legs as well! Silky smooth skin now! Mwah!) Feeling quite bored actually so I'll recap the last 2 days of my life!!   Friday  Mutti came home from Great Yarmouth and gave me a bigass hug when I was sitting on this chair, minding my own business. I thought that everything was fine but then around an hour later, she compltely fipped and started to go on about how I hadnt done anything when she was away! I was like "WHAA?!" cause I've done loads when she was away!! Grrr! And this was all because I didnt hoover underneath the Guniea Pig hutch! I dont recall seeing anyone come into our house and inspect the hutch but meh! I hoovered there after the yelling-at-me period and polished the front room, and then I asked my mum a question and she was all like "I dont care what you do anymore!!" ^_~ Could be pretty cool when I use that against her but yeah. And then, the worst thing was that SHES NOT GIVING ME MY ALLOWANCE ANYMORE!! ;_; That means that I'm gonna be £40 down a month!! I need that money in July as well cause Im not working for 3 shifts!! Argh! Blergh! So, I sat in my room for 2 hours, sulking to myself (which was pretty damn funny actually!! XD) Eventually, mutti dear came up and asked if I wanted to go to down so I kinda grumbled yes. We got there and she kept trying to pick fights with me which made me piss myself laughing 'cause I wasnt listening to her!! Roffle!! XP Found a gorgeous skirt though which Im gonna see if she'll buy for me! -_-  Today- Saturday!!  Was awake from 6 this morning because someone flushed the toilet, and it woke me up. Went to work (8.30) and got home again at 3. Told Trish (my bitch of a boss) that I was on holiday for the next 3 weeks and she tried to say that me not telling her was my fault, even though whenever i've tried to tell her, she doesnt listen. -_- Got home and went up to my room, and played on the guitar for aaaages before my fingers started to kill me and so I went downstairs. Listened to some music and had tea. Got in the bath and then I came online again!! I   HAHAHAHAHAHA!   Listening to Black Sabbath- Changes.   I heart you Ozzy Osbourne!! <3
      
>

25,June,2004


    
       
      Blergh! Decided that I'm better off alone (  I'M BETTER OFF ALONE ANYWAY!!    Just downloaded some Coheed and Cambria (Bayley insisted that I did!) and wow! They're really good actually!! They're playing at Reading this year as well so I need to get some piccys or merchandise for her! ;D I call it the belated birthday present!! Fingers are still in agony after playing the guitar for ages yesterday. And I screwed up the stum pattern so I've managed to slice my finger!! How yummy! ^^  My mum comes home today which is sorta good and sorta bad. Sorta good cause I wont have to look after the house anymore. Sorta bad cause she'll moan at me to get offline (blah blah blah!) I dont mind getting off when they ask nicely but constantly moaning in my ear! Gawd! I'm still debating on whether to cut my hair off or not. I want long hair because I'm too stubbourn to change but I want short hair cause its easier to do things with!! It would be quite fun, having short hair again, because...meh! No reason I can post on here without insulting a few people!! ;D  I'll end this log by going...  MWAHAHAHAHAAHAHAHA!!!    
      


24,June,2004


    
       
           urlLink What Cosplay Type Are You?         urlLink What Anime Art Style Are You?    XD So cool!! Sailormoon, I        urlLink What Anime Type Are You?    ^^ Coolio!       urlLink What Anime Stereotype Are You?    omgg! hahahaha!        urlLink What Anime Vampire Are You?    Hi! I'm Rebecca the anime slut. Please have sex with me!! 

23,June,2004


    
       
      I've decided that I hate most men. -_- Except the gorgeous snogging guys in the pictures that Bayray got me!!   Probably gonna have some weird bisexual-esc tendancies now!! Roffle! I'm praying that the guys in my display pictures (everywhere!) are bi so that I stand a chance with them! In the worlds of Bayley:    SEXCELLENT!    Ahahaha!! Why yes they are bloody sexcellent!!   Especially the black and white picture...omg! Pretty damned orgasmic!! XD 
      


23,June,2004


    
       
      Josh is over me already!! Ach!! I wanted to be the girl who the guys never forgot! But Nooooo! -_-  And he never comments on this journal, even tho I comment on his. -_-  I could be a complete and utter bitch now but I'll keep all of my bitterness inside, locked away with a stomach and acid. :P
      


22,June,2004


    
       
        Playful    urlLink   What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      ROMANTIC ONE. The really most most most important for you is that she/he is romantic. You love it to get love letters, red roses and be in a romantic atmosphere. He/She must make you think that you are the most beautiful of all. When he/she is romantic she/he has you got in his hands. When he/she tells you all that he/she feels for you ,you are devoted to him/her. At this point you are easy to be tempt. Your heart is soft and pure and you would never cheat as long as you love your partner. But if he cheats you, you are not hiding your feelings and show how much she/he hurt you because you trusted in him/her and never thought he/she could do this to you.PLEASE VOTE, I want to know what you think about my quiz, I worked hard on it.You can always message me or tell me how I can improve that quiz. Ill sure write back.    urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
      


22,June,2004


    
       
      OMFG! I have just found the spider that freaked me out about a week ago!! I looked up on the door frame when you go into the dining room and there it was! I was very 0_0 because its a nasty looking spider- all legs and teeny body. 

22,June,2004


    
       
      Oh yes. Really depressed myself. ;_; Highlights of my PMs would be:  *Becci's Brothel!! XD Ahhh!  *Talking to Suji loads! *All of the PMS to the people I used to speak to loads  Oh my god. I was such a crap typist then and I couldnt spell or anything. Man...I wish I could go and relive those times. They were the best, when I could get away with nOObism.   *First speaking to Wes (he wanted us to have beautiful babies!)   Omg. Sriously depressed now. :/ 
      


22,June,2004


    
       
      Woke up this morning extremely happy and then I remembered yesterday, and felt miserable again. 
      


22,June,2004


    
       
      I've decided that ending relationships are evil and require heartless people to do it. its funny how you'll think something is so easy and then it just isnt. How can it be? A connection has been broken instantly. Sometimes I really do   wish   that I'd already experienced all of these emotions and feelings so I'd know what they're like. Being older would be better. Being a teenager is SO hard. Everyone expects you to believe in what they want you to believe, and it just isnt like that. ;_; When you're younger, you're idealistic. Naive is a better word, really.  I'm not heartless. No way. I just keep everything inside 'cause if people know how to hurt me, they'll hurt me. Human malice. Also, because I've been broken hearted lots before, it shouldnt hurt this much...its funny how we think things are eternal.   Off to bed now. Friggin knackered. And I need to sleep to think other thoughts rather than "It could be..." Wishful thinking is nice but it wont get me anywhere anymore.   *huggles for you all* 
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      *sigh*  Josh knows now and he took it well...  too   well. ;_; He did also say some things that made me feel so incredibly bad. I just felt awful for ages. I know this probably sounds silly but I wish he'd...yelled at me or something, just so I could feel a bit bad and he could feel a bit better   Anyway, I've got to reply to his email or I wont sleep tonight but josh...please can you reply. I really need to say some things I should've said before. 
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      I really hate myself right now...I tried to do something to stop people from feeling bad and I've made myself feel bad and other people possibly hate me and I want my bubble to fall into and disappear forever. Without me here, peoples lives would be so much easier and no one would get hurt anymore.  *falls into hole*  Thank god I've got the house to myself tomorrow.   I need a hug but...I'm gonna be hugless forever now. 
      


21,June,2004


    
       
        Is it too late to change?  Velvet roses, blinded by the heat  Teenage grownups passing on their painted legacies   Why do we walk backwards down a road that never ends  Not knowing where we're going  Just seeing where we've been  Can't find no direction though we try hard to pretend  That we're not walking backwards but we are, again and again and again  Is it too late to change?  Ivory castles all fall down  False religions being crowned  Politicians tied and bound  We have to make a stand today, the time has come for us to change  Whey do we walk backwards down a road that never ends  Not knowing where we're going  Just seeing where we've been  Can't find no direction though we try hard to pretend  That we're not walking backwards but we are again and again and again    Sorry but I just had to post these lyriscs. They are just so amazing! Kirsty, I need to listen to the song now!! ^_^  
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      Blergh!   Had physics this morning and crikey! What an utterly bizaare exam! I mean, it was really easy in some parts and then you'd turn the page and be 0_0. Quite seriously!! I got the giggles in the middle of it as well because I heard someone's stomach rumble   REALLY   loudly, and then I realised that me and Sophie were sitting in each others seats!! XD Anyways, I'm feeling very WEEE at the moment 'cause I have officially left school for good (never have to wear a uniform again...wow! How coolio!) Gotta go back on the 26th for my results but until then, I am planning on sleeping and watching lots of anime and letting my brain slowly melt away into nothingness...(yes, I   DO   have a brain!  My dad is being really nice to me now because he knows how much stress I've been under, trying to get a job and get into college, and revise! He was being so nice that he got me Kill Bill Volume 1 yesterday because he knows that I'd been wanting it ever since I read about the film! I was like "AAAAAWWWWWWWWW! THANKS! *huggles*"   Blogger has a major fault, thinkin' about it...Why cant we say what music we're listning to?! I might as well start...    METALLICA- THE UNFORGIVEN     So cool!! Better than their new stuff...^_^ Which is still pretty darn good, might I add.   
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      AGHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!    Got your attention! ;-)   Im feeling so sad at the moment. I was looking through all of Dom's baby piccys a little while ago and then I was like "He's growing up so quickly..." and then my mind flashed back to earlier on when I saw a funeral start to take place, and then I was "He's going to die...." and I've just completely depressed myself. ;_; I need a hug...badly. Its just that, even though he was an accident, I cant imagine life without him strutting in (he's 3 and a bit) and going "Oh. Hello Becky." XD He is just so adorable! Yay! Better thoughts in my mind now!  :-D Had my food tech exam today and good god! It was so easy, and I find the subject quite hard. *cringe* But this was more an exam on common sense rather than on food tech! -_-   Anyways, better go and get some sleep! Physics in the morning but then....*dramatic music*   NO MORE EXAMS!!   Sweet beautiful freedom! I can almost taste it!! ^_^
      


20,June,2004


    
       
      Before I start to rant on completely, I'll say that if this update doesnt make any sense, its because I've just been playing the guitar non-stop for half an hour (it doesnt seem long but I havent played properly for years now!) and my fingertips are in complete agony! Thank you for your time!  Anyway, today was fathers day in the UK and so I got my daddy (XD) a new shirt and some alcoholic chocolates! The best thing about the choccies is that it was a BUY ONE GET ONE FREE offer and so earlier on, I was nibbling away at my packet! Haha!   Still typing up my Arcadian Rebellion update! I know what I want to write exactly but its just putting my thoughts down onto paper...grrr. Its so hard for me! ;_; I also needed to wait and see what James was gonna say about my plan for the update because its going to contain some things that people might find disturbing and I wanted to check and see if my idea was okay! Thank god he did or otherwise, I wouldnt really know what else to do with the update!  I wonder what happened at Josh's yesterday...I mean, he mentioned Craig and Liam going round and having some pot (stupid boi) but he hasnt updated since then. Cant really count on his mother to yell at him either cause she doesnt mind him smoking it. -_- He knows that drugs will eventually kill him but all he said, when I pointed out this   very obvious fact   was "Lifes too short." Well, yeah! It will be if you bloodly well go round smoking crap like that, hun!   Spoke to Trent earlier on and said hi. He said hi back and then that was the conversation! I tried to make small talk but no way! He must've been waaay too busy to speak to me! 

19,June,2004


    
       
      Been unusually optimistic at the moment. Although, I know why...    I'M GOING TO CANANDA!!!    We last went to Canada six years ago and that was only to Toronto for a day and the Niagra falls for about 3 days (we were in the US at the time and went up North.) Anyway, in that short time there, I fell in love with the place completely. Seriously, I   So, my mum said yes on the condition that I can afford it and I stay in contact with her!  Now, the hard part is deciding where to go!! I've already decided to go to:  Victoria (I can see my Bayray!!  Vancouver! Kelowna (Kat!! Woohoo! My Ayashi no Ceres sister!)  Any suggestions?   And I need to see where I can stay for the duration of my stay! Havent got the foggiest about that to be honest...
      


18,June,2004


    
       
      Ugh! Worked sucked again today! Had to peel   FOUR   buckets of potatoes! Do you realise how much i wanted to kill them after the first bucket!!  Josh is having a hissy fit because i cant go over his tonight. I told him all he needed to know but no! BLAH BLAH BLOODY BLAH! (wrote BLAG then! Roffle! Gets rid of that effect completely!) Anyway, I'm not drinking anymore because it makes me act like a complete fake, and I dont wanna be like that anymore. I'm going clean baybee! ^_^  Just speaking to Kirsty at this moment in time! Need to have her round mine or vice versa! SINGSTAR!! XD (I   Buying this amazing looking dress soon! Its quite short (OMG! I'll be leik,   SHOWING FLESH!!  ) Haha! Anyway, its short and is black on top but has a thin, burgendy layer underneath! And, the back is completely sheer! It is so nice! Just need to buy it now. I still also need to buy Ayashi no Ceres although, for a while, I didnt really want to buy it because it has lots of nudity (apparently) But then I was like "So what? Its only gonna be a breast! Shock horror!" If it gets TOO graphic, I can just fast forwards it (or hide it! eh eh Kirsty!! ;-))   Two weeks today, Im going to be in Spain! What a weird though! Still need to get Kirstys b/day pressie but I know what I'm gonna get her (and I've only seen it in Spain!)So, I am really sorry for this long delay but I just wanted to wait and get you something that no one else will ever think of getting you!! And, it isnt rude!! XD  Anyhow, I'm in the process of having a brain fart so I'm going to post up my favourite lyrics:    EVANESCENCE- AWAY FROM ME    I hold my breath as this life starts to take its toll I hide behind a smile as this perfect plan unfolds But oh, God, I feel I've been lied to Lost all faith in the things I have achieved And I  I've woken now to find myself In the shadows of all I have created I'm longing to be lost in you (away from this place I have made) Won't you take me away from me?  Crawling through this world as disease flows through my veins I look into myself, but my own heart has been changed I can't go on like this I loathe all I've become  I've woken now to find myself In the shadows of all I have created I'm longing to be lost in you (away from this place I have made) Won't you take me away from me?   Lost in a dying world I reach for something more I have grown so weary of this lie I live  I've woken now to find myself In the shadows of all I have created I'm longing to be lost in you I  I've woken now to find myself I'm lost in shadows of my own I'm longing to be lost in you Away from me  Just in the middle of my Arcadian Rebellion update as well. I have got some pretty dramatic ideas but I need to PM James and ask him if they're okay because they could kinda be a BIT too explicit! Like Utsumi!! (roffle!)  I really fancy watching Battle Royale at this moment in time because I   Which leads me onto my weird dream I had... I was sitting in Sub in Cambridge when this Asian guy came over to me and said "Hi Becks." and I was like "WTF!?" because I didnt know who it was. And then I recognised him and it was James!! XD It was really random because he had quite long hair (Nanahara length! Drool!) Anyway, we just had a random convo about how nice subs are and then I was woken up. Sniffle. I want to know what happens next!!   Maybe tomorrow, we might MIGHT just find out!  XD Ha! Unlikely!! 
      


18,June,2004


    
       
      I really am losing it actually. What a convinent title.  Sadly. ;_;
      


17,June,2004


    
       
      He finally said hi after my intial schizo moment.   And, I've got to go to the doctors because today my mum said something and I just started crying for no reason and couldnt stop, and its been like this for a while now so yeah, she thinks Im suffering with depression (I am.)  So FINALLY! Some bloody relief from that!  Only bad thing on my horizon is work tomorrow. Unless I get "ill" (wink wink) overnight.  -_- Unlikely.  Feck! 
      


17,June,2004


    
       
      Just shouted at Josh because he wouldnt say hi to me on messenger. Too busy speaking to smelly lindsay or whoever.   -_-
      


17,June,2004


    
       
         Trent!! <333333333333 Man, I need to speak to you soon darling! I miss ya! ;_;
      
>

16,June,2004


    
       
      Oh god. I have scared myself again. About a minute ago, I scratched my leg but my leg is completely numb. 0_0 Seriously, I havent been leaning on it or anything. Its just...not there, if you know what I mean.   And, to add to my UGH factor, mother dear might be booking me in with the doctors today for stronger medication. ;_; Its not fair!!   And then, to add to everything, my mother belives I might be sufffering with depression because of these things:  * getting bored easily * regular weepy moments * switching off when people are speaking to me * lack of energy  And then, just being myself really. I told her ages ago that I was depressed but she just said that "teenagers dont get depressed."  WTF!? 

16,June,2004


    
       
      Just washed the dog in the bath! Eech! That was pretty damned nasty IMO. Now, the top of the house has that pleasent odour of wet dog. Yummy.  Found Ayashi no Ceres in dubbed English finally. I was just going to import it from Hong Kong (in Jap) but then I found it on eBay! Woohoo! Pretty damned happy because I'll be able to watch it before I go to Spain as well.   Had a really weird dream yesterday night. I was watching the last Buffy episode (when she dies) and then it was like I was Buffy. 0_0 And then, after I landed, I had to get up and run and find this room. For some reason, there was a timer going in the corner. I went into the room and it was a cooking room. I made some pasta (??) and then someone shouted "There she is!!" and so I had to run off again and then I jumped backwards off this building but held on to a gap. And then this skeleton appeared. Then, I let go and I was just floating there.  Freaky.  I think it was continuing from my other dream but...I dont know. I did have another dream as well but it involves something a bit too close to me.   Oh well. ;_;   Oooh! I finished I Capture the Castle....again and oh golly gosh! Its so sad at the end when you find out what Cassandra really thinks! I was SO close to tears!   Yesterday, me and Sam were messing about in the back garden with the frisbee when we both started to get   REALLY   crap! So, I said we should play discuss and for ages, we were just getting worse and worse when he suddenly did this almighty sweep and it went sailing over the fence, into our neighbours garden!!   XD 
      


16,June,2004


    
       
      Yesterday night, I got   VERY   bored so I looked through the encyclopaedia and took out all the quotes I   He who loses his dreaming is lost- Australian Aboriginal saying.  Separate we come and separate we go And this, be it known, is all that we know- Conrad Aiken, 1969  Anarchism is a game at which the Police can beat you- George Bernard Shaw, 1910  None love the messenger who brings bad news- Sophocles   There is no evil in atoms; only in men’s souls- Adlai Stevenson, 1952  One is not born a woman. One becomes one- Simone de Beauvoir, 1949  A Robin Red breast in a cage Puts all of heaven in a rage- William Blake  The life of a creature passes like the torrent in the mountain and the lightning in the sky- Buddha  In war, whichever side may call itself the victor, there are no winners but all are losers- Neville Chamberlain  Man always dies before he is fully born- Erich Fromm  God is white- Jean Genet  Not to know something is a great part of wisdom- Hugo Groticus  A man can be destroyed but not defeated- Ernest Hemingway  There is no terror in a bang, only in the suspense- Alfred Hitchcock  To be an artist means to never look away- Akira Kurosawa   A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step- Lao Zi    It is fatal to enter any war without the will to win it- Douglas MacArthur, 1952  Marriage is like a cage; one sees the birds outside desperate to get in, and those inside desperate to get out- Michael Montaigne Essays III  We read that we ought to forgive our enemies; but we do not read that we ought to forgive our friends- Cosimo de’ Medici   Whom the Gods love die young- Menander  After all, tomorrow is another day- Margaret Mitchell  The heart has its reasons which reason knows nothing of- Blaine Pascal  The true paradises are paradises we have lost- Marcel Proust  Love is not dumb. The heart speaks many ways- Jean Racine  To love is to give light with inexhaustible oil- Rainer Maria Rilke, 1910  Better by far you should forget and smile Then remember and be sad- Christina Rossetti  We cannot tear out a single page out of our life, but we can throw the whole book in the fire- George Sand  What is beautiful is good, and what is good will soon also be beautiful- Sappho  We fell and know that we are eternal- Benedict Spinoza   The butterfly counts not months but moments, and has time enough- Rabindranath Tagore  The mass of men lead lives of quiet desperation- David Thoreau  He laughs best who laughs last- John Vanbrugh    
      


14,June,2004


    
       
      Ooh my god! I have got the most intensely painful rash over all my legs. When I got in the bath earlier on, it was so sore that I had to bite my bottom lip to stop myself from screaming out. ;_; yes, it was   THAT   painful! Anyway, I had to shave my legs as well which caused it to really kill me. As soon as I got out of the bath, I put this lovely cherry cream all over my legs. Well, smothered the cream over.   Now they dont hurt but are an attractive shade of blushing tomato. < 
      
>

14,June,2004


    
       
        ARGH!   I cannot believe that the profile bit is down on here! I   Just finally done my new messenger profile, which claimed that I was a  street walker!  XD I really should change it though because otherwise I'll have people offering me obsence things. 0_0 That would be quite embarassing.   Gonna wear my red hat tomorrow at school, once I've got changed, so that way there will be a perma-shade over me. I dont know what to get changed into though because I'm more of a winter dresser!!   Right, need some food (nearly called it grub!! < How disgusting!) 
      
>

14,June,2004


    
       
      Just made a new blogger because apprently, my name didn't exist.  -_- Uh huh, righty. Whatever you say deary...  Oh goodness! My chemistry exam was incredibly hard! At first, I was really worried that I was the only one who found it hard but then I found that Josh and Sally Anne also found it hard, and Sophie as well I belive. Although, if we all do really shabbily then they'll bring down the grade boundries. Fingers crossed for that! And then, this afternoon, I had my final English exam which was   pathetically   easy! Seriously. Or, it could be that I'm just amazingly brilliant at English!     Haha! Silly picture of me! Although, my skin looks very clear on it. Jenn commented on my picture (in my private blog) and said that I was very purty! ^_^ Wow, such an ego boost! I'm surprised that my head can fit through doors!  And, here is another silly picture but this time, Kirsty is included in it! Aaah, I remember when we did those wacked out piccys!! And there were loads of fireworks and because I had had a bit to drink, I felt like I was gonna fall out of the window (well, I was sitting with my legs hanging out of it!)     XD I'm so hideous to look at! Like Princess Fiona as an ogre. Although, she has nicer hair than me. <
      
>

30,July,2004


    
       
      Wow! New Blogger settings! wOOt! Been ages since I've been on herein!! ^_~  Lets see what has changed in my life...  1- Dating Josh again 2- Got a tan 3- Dog is sick...;_; 4- Got v.ill myself  Anyhow! Time for food! Typisch!!  XD 
      


01,July,2004


    
       
           Your Sexual Profile (you sexual deviant you...)  by sparkledee      Name           Your Secret Kink Thing    You spank with a wooden spoon       Your Sexual Strength    How hot you look in lingerie.       Your Sexual Weakness    Your freaky noises during sex       Your Likely STD    Syphilis       How Many Partners in Crime?    A few.               Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !             What Are You Most Likely to Utter During Sex  by  urlLink  UMAJohnnie        Name           Sexuality           Age           Most Likely to Say    "Make it snappy, I have a 2 o&#39;clock and a 3:15."              Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       0_0        Your Moulin Rouge Status:  by  urlLink  pinkrobelover        Your Name:           Your deepest secret:    You shot the green fairy      The Bohemian Ideal You hold true to most is:    Truth      Your Job at the Moulin Rouge:    Low-priced Whore      What the customers think:    You should charge more for your services      Favorite Quote:    "The Greatest thing you&#39;ll ever learn is just to love and be loved in return."             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !            What is your tragic death?  by  urlLink  AniMarth        Name           Date of Death    December 5, 2004      Gold In Bank    $-595,268      # of Party Members    0      Death    After finding out that everyone you ever trusted in the world were really just using you, you bought and X Box and bored yourself to death.      Location of Party    At the strip club.             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !        
      


01,July,2004


    
       
           Your love is... by  urlLink  ChibiMarronchan        Your name is...           Your kiss is...    mysterious      Your hugs are...    gentle      Your eyes...    twinkle in the moonlight      Your touch is...    heart warming      Your smell is...    amazing      Your smile is...    amazing      Your love is...    unique             Created with the ORIGINAL  urlLink  MemeGen  !       Its better than my nickname! good god!! Xxx
      


01,July,2004


    
       
      Josh, update your fecking blog! K, thanks darlin'! xxx  Went online this morning and spoke to meh Bayray!! I heart you!!  I was meant to be going to Kirstys today but my stomach is killing and I'm just feeling nasty at the moment! So Im kinda pished off about that. -_- But, it means that I can sleep lots more and not be feeling really sick when im flying! Ugh, that would be nasty!!   Anyways, ran out of things to say but Im gonna update later! Ciao for now!! *kisses*
      


03,August,2004


    
       
      omg! I was just re-reading Joshs blog and man! He sounded like he was happy to get rid of me before! -_- How completely unfair is that!? Ahhh, I'll be quiet before I rant on without getting anywhere...  Party rocked yesterday night! And no hangover today? Wtf is going on with that!! ^_~   
      



