
20,June,2004


	 
        HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MELISSA HAPPY HAPPY I CANT WAIT TIL THURSDAY HAPPY BIRTHDAY UR PREZZIE IS SO DAMN AWESOME AND DIERKS IS SO SEXY. HOTTER THAN CALIFORNIA? HELL YA!  
     

    


18,June,2004


	 
      Me: everything is hotter when the sun goes down... Lissa: no, its hotter when the sun is up! Carolyn: that's not what she was talking about, melissa...  Jennagirl39: STEPHY POOP!  MiSsKiSsY359: that guy is SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO hot Jennagirl39: lol yeah Jennagirl39: you like those weird europeans MiSsKiSsY359: i know! MiSsKiSsY359: oliver james! MiSsKiSsY359: yummy! MiSsKiSsY359: mmmmmm-mmmmmm good  MiSsKiSsY359: where r ur parents? Jennagirl39: thursday  MiSsKiSsY359: i missed u!@ MiSsKiSsY359: lol N0 H0L3: lol N0 H0L3: i missed u 2!!  SeXyPeNgWiNs59: hi snugglepuss!  rel: *holding water pistol* i've got a gun and i'm afraid to use it!  Me: Yeah, there's food in the house because I went grocery shopping. Lizzie: Uh, Steph? Have you even been to the grocery store before?  Me: I love you!! *Brett Farve* Melissa: Steph, he has a wife! Me: So what! Everyone knows that men always want the sexy young thing!  Mom: Johnny Depp is gay! Me: MOM!!! HE IS NOT! Mom: He is! He swishes! Me: Mom, he's a pirate. He's just distrustful. Dad: No, your mother's right. He's gay. Me: HE IS NOT! I LOVE HIM! Mom: What does his wife say about that? Me: I DON'T CARE! Mom: No, Stephanie, he's gay. Me: How do you know? Mom: Everyone knows all the actors are gay nowadays. Me: MOOOM!!  Maggie: We're making babies! Me: It's a girl! Maggie: What should we name it? Me: Yemen! Maggie: Yemen's dead! Me: But she's really cute! Maggie: And pink!  Me: Rocket licked the cheese. And then dad was mad and was like, 'grr' and Rocket was like 'Can I have cheese?' and dad was like, 'Down!' and Rocket was like, 'Cheeeeese...' Mom: Wow...  Me: Mom, can we get a penguin? it could live in the freezer! Mom: Yeah, and then it could shit all over the floor!  Me: I love country music! Justin: People listen to country music when they want to die!  Me: I love you Lizzie. Lizzie: Uh... Me: I love you Lizzie! Lizzie: OK... Me: I LOVE YOU LIZZIE!! Lizzie: I love you, too?  Me: I love you Kelley! Kelley: I love you too. Me: I love you Kris! Kris: I love you too. Me: I love you Nishan! Nishan: I love you too. Me: I love you Danny! Danny: Uh... Nishan: Don't you love Steph? Danny: I love you too, Steph.  Jennagirl39 (8:59:39 PM): steph, you are the nicest, sweetest girl i have ever met. i mean this with all my heart. your honest and true, your definitely not fake or false.. you are so loving and giving and honest and blah im rambling. but i love you to BITS AND PIECES. i know your going through a hard time or whatever.. but just now, ppl look up to you and ppl do LOVE YOU TONS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! !!!! thanks for being there for me. :-)  DeMoNDoDoBiRd: i actually have friends who dont think im psycho DeMoNDoDoBiRd: arent u proud!? anything4949: WOW! anything4949: can i borrow them sometime  anything4949 (8:43:40 PM): ME nd STEPH LIKE FLIRTING iluvbrettsbutt (8:43:43 PM): yes iluvbrettsbutt (8:43:50 PM): we have decided that its flirtalicious  Employee: Would the girls who used lanes five and six please put away there balls!  Pinkkygurl23: so i bet skool is really good cus its with steph Pinkkygurl23: shes awesome  FireSkater07: yea  Mom: I'm scared for when you guys are old enough to drink, because you're crazy as shit already!  anything4949 (8:44:47 PM): YOU GUYS IM GONNA GO START FINDING NEMO  froggirlNG (8:49:25 PM): all i neeed is a hair dryer and some condoms froggirlNG (8:49:27 PM): lol anything4949 (8:49:27 PM): MAKE OUT WITH RANDOM SPANISH GUYS  anything4949 (8:52:35 PM): BOYS IN GENERAL ARE CONFUSEING FireSkater07 (8:52:43 PM): you think we are confusing? FireSkater07 (8:52:51 PM): try to understand women!  iluvbrettsbutt (8:53:57 PM): "is ur dad here?" "i dont know" "go looK!" "i dont wanna! u go!" iluvbrettsbutt (8:54:02 PM): "im not going outside!" iluvbrettsbutt (8:54:06 PM): "me either" iluvbrettsbutt (8:54:07 PM): haha iluvbrettsbutt (8:54:14 PM): *jump in car, duck and lock doors*  anything4949 (8:54:58 PM): STEPH: SHUT UP PLEASAE N-O-W iluvbrettsbutt (8:55:03 PM): HAHAHAHA anything4949 (8:55:05 PM): THAT WAS THE BEST FUCKING THING EVER  iluvbrettsbutt (9:17:21 PM): hey sexy Cooldude8243 (9:17:22 PM): hey anything4949 (9:17:25 PM): hey mike Cooldude8243 (9:17:29 PM): hey iluvbrettsbutt (9:17:35 PM): wuts ur fantasy? Cooldude8243 (9:17:36 PM): who the other peep? anything4949 (9:17:46 PM): shes crazy dont listen to her  iluvbrettsbutt (9:24:28 PM): FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK Super Toast9889 (9:24:33 PM): monkeys iluvbrettsbutt (9:24:38 PM): ezzacly  iluvbrettsbutt (9:26:53 PM): so sexy, when u laugh ur ass off, where does it go? anything4949 (9:27:05 PM): it goes to the sexy bathroom anything4949 (9:27:08 PM): to take a shit Super Toast9889 (9:27:09 PM): i dont have an ass anything4949 (9:27:13 PM): hahaha iluvbrettsbutt (9:27:16 PM): hehe Super Toast9889 (9:27:17 PM): i sold it 4 cheese iluvbrettsbutt (9:27:19 PM): aww iluvbrettsbutt (9:27:25 PM): :-( i bet it feels neglected now anything4949 (9:27:32 PM): thats hilariouse  Super Toast9889 (9:32:55 PM): then what ru? iluvbrettsbutt (9:33:01 PM): im crazy! Super Toast9889 (9:33:43 PM): if u want 2 be iluvbrettsbutt (9:33:47 PM): yep yep Super Toast9889 (9:33:49 PM): i c no problem wit dat iluvbrettsbutt (9:33:55 PM): otherwise life is boring! Super Toast9889 (9:34:18 PM): yes!@ iluvbrettsbutt (9:34:22 PM): hehe Super Toast9889 (9:34:24 PM): that is totally true iluvbrettsbutt (9:34:27 PM): i know! Super Toast9889 (9:34:29 PM): ppl dont understand that iluvbrettsbutt (9:34:33 PM): i know1q iluvbrettsbutt (9:34:34 PM): ! iluvbrettsbutt (9:34:54 PM): every1s like y r u so insane? n im like whats the fun in bein normal?! Super Toast9889 (9:35:05 PM): 4SHO@#!!  anything4949 (8:03:02 PM): ive been mortally wounded!!!! iluvbrettsbutt (8:03:12 PM): y? anything4949 (8:03:50 PM): my razor decided its true calling was to be a crocadile and in the middle of me shaving it turned into a crocadile and bit my leg off and now im going to die from blood loss!!!  anything4949 (8:16:31 PM): i was doing history and this guy named rob was siting there anything4949 (8:16:38 PM): and im like and th answer is....pooop!!!! anything4949 (8:16:42 PM): and he looks at me anything4949 (8:16:50 PM): and hes thinking omfg whats wrong with this person!?!!?  anything4949 (9:12:54 PM): im slipping into love with alex anything4949 (9:12:56 PM): stop me iluvbrettsbutt (9:12:56 PM): aww iluvbrettsbutt (9:12:58 PM): jess! ZeOceanGoddess (9:13:22 PM): eat a cucumber and you'll stop abruptly  iluvbrettsbutt (9:21:45 PM): i love u matt! N0 H0L3 (9:21:49 PM): :-* iluvbrettsbutt (9:21:49 PM): u rock my world! ;-) N0 H0L3 (9:21:54 PM): i luv u to  iluvbrettsbutt (8:26:58 PM): i feel so neglected! :-( anything4949 (8:27:05 PM): i love you baby  iluvbrettsbutt (8:38:29 PM): BOK BOK CHICKEN BOK CHICKEN  Jennagirl39 (8:39:18 PM): guess what Jennagirl39 (8:39:19 PM): my gpa is iluvbrettsbutt (8:39:25 PM): in his pjs?  ANYTHING4949: steph ANYTHING4949: stop cyberin wit charlie ANYTHING4949: i know hes hot ANYTHING4949: but please ANYTHING4949: hes like your bro  ANYTHING4949: 

17,June,2004


	 
        im sick and it sux ass  
     

    


17,June,2004


	 
      hey, u no wut really never occured 2 me b4 rite now? how much i luv my fam. yup, lil annoyin bro included. me and mom r really close, and i really dont think i cant stand bein apart from her for a whole nother 2 weeks, so i think imite go down there for like 4 days or something, at most, cuz i dont wanna miss lessons. and dude...will someone PLEASE tell me wuts da appeal of gardenin? i mean,yeah, turnin da hose on full power and blastin da leafy plants is fun, but thass not really gardenin! haha! and ROSES! yes, they r romantic, but can we please pick a less lethal romantic flower? MY MOMS ROSE BUSH ATTACKED ME TODAY! I HAVE CUTS N BLOOD BLISTERS! FROM DA FREAKIN ROSE BUSH! and keyboards! oi! dotn even get me started on how the keyboard moves the keys around so its impossible for me to type! SHUT UP N-O-W mothman! ELEVATORS R EVIL!  listenin 2: i will survive watchin: eurotrip wearin: my penguin pjs n my mommys shirt thinkin: 2 fast 2 furious or btvs?
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
       Dum de de dum, de de dum, de de dum, de de da da. Dum de de dum, de de dum, de de dum, de da da, la la la.   Well, I walk into the room passin' out hundred dollar bills. An' it kills and it thrills like the horns on my Silverado grille. An' I buy the bar a double round of Crown an' everybody's getting down, An' this town ain't never gonna be the same.   'Cause I saddle up my horse an' I ride into the city. I make a lot of noise 'cause the girls, they are so pretty. Ridin' up an' down Broadway on my old stud, Leroy. And the girls say: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy." Everybody says: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy."   Well, I don't give a dang about nothing: I'm singing an' bling-blanging, While the girls are drinkin' long necks down! An' I wouldn't trade ol' Leroy or my Chevrolet for your Escalade, or your freak parade: I'm the only John Wayne left in this town.   An' I saddle up my horse an' I ride into the city. I make a lot of noise 'cause the girls, they are so pretty. Ridin' up an' down Broadway on my old stud, Leroy. And the girls say: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy." Everybody says: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy."   Instrumental break.   "Well, I'm a thoroughbred." That's what she said in the back of my truck bed, As I was gettin' buzzed on suds, out on some back country road. We where flyin' high, fine as wine, Having ourselves a Big and Rich time An' I was going, just about as far as she'd let me go. But her evaluation of my cowboy reputation Had me beggin' for salvation all night long. So I took her out, gigging frogs, Introduced her to my old bird dog An' sang her every Wilie Nelson song I could think of. An' we made love.   An' I saddle up my horse an' I ride into the city. I make a lot of noise 'cause the girls, they are so pretty. Ridin' up an' down Broadway on my old stud, Leroy. And the girls say: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy." Everybody says: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy."   What? What? "Save a horse, ride a cowboy." Everybody says: "Save a horse, ride a cowboy."  
     

    


15,June,2004


	 
       i wish my mommy wud come home :( i miss her sooo much n while havin jus dad around is great, especially w/ NO BRO! but moms the family member im closest with, pls she hid my book n wont give it back now!!! well...ok...so its her book....and i just wanna borrow it....and she actallly doesnt kno where it is.....so! how 'bout dem pistols?!  listenin 2: me myself n i watchin: da game (GO PISTOLS and jack nicholson is scary!) wearin: red sox wit frogs on em dat  hae a hole (theyr holy sox!!!) jeans, PANTIES! :-P haha my blue cookie monster shirt thinkin: earwax...gross or fancinatin? 
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
       Ploughing these fields in the hot summer sun. An' over by the gate, Lordy, here she comes. With a basket full of chicken, and a big cold jug of sweet tea. I make a little room and she climbs on up. Open up the throttle and stir a little dust. Just look at her face, she ain't a'foolin' me.   She thinks my tractors sexy,  it really turns her on. She's always staring at me, while I'm chugging along. She likes the way it's pulling while we're tilling up the land. She's even kinda crazy, 'bout my farmers tan. She's the only one who really understands what gets me. She thinks my tractors sexy. She thinks my tractors sexy.   We go back and forth till we run out of light, Take it to the barn, put it up for the night. Climb up in the loft, sit and talk with the radio on. She says she's got a dream and I ask what it is. She wants a little farm and a yard full of kids. Then one more teeny, weenie ride before I take her home.   She thinks my tractors sexy,  it really turns her on. She's always staring at me, while I'm chugging along. She likes the way it's pulling while we're tilling up the land. She's even kinda crazy, 'bout my farmers tan. She's the only one who really understands what gets me. She thinks my tractors sexy. She thinks my tractors sexy.   Well she ain't into cars or pick-up trucks, But if it runs like a Deere, man her eyes light up. She thinks my tractors......   She thinks my tractors sexy,  it really turns her on. She's always staring at me, while I'm chugging along. She likes the way it's pulling while we're tilling up the land. She's even kinda crazy, 'bout my farmers tan. She's the only one who really understands what gets me. She thinks my tractors sexy. She thinks my tractors sexy.   She thinks my tractors sexy.  
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
        FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK COMPUTERS SHUD DIE!!!!!!!!!!! MY FUCKING KAZAA WONT WORK SO I CANT FUCKING DOWNLOAD MUSIC FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK FUCK  
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
       y oh y did no one tell me ab jason mraz b4 this? he is my love! im jus playin his cd over and over...of course i dont HAVE da CD, but I HAVE MY IPOD! MWAHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHA!!!!!!! oh man...my ipod. my love, my salvation...plus i bought a pink iskin 4 it and its sooo darn cute! ok on 2 serious stuff: i was talkin 2 my friend 2day n i was thinkin, how many ppl actually kick back n relax over da summer? i mean, last year i totally didnt bc i had horse camp, lessons, n was helpin out at my stable, and this year im relaxin more than most of my friends, but i mean, come on! i go out to my barn 2 or 3 times a week and i just showed my pony, so its not exactly RELAXIN...think on it!  
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
       so...whos lovin summer? me, not so much..my mom went to chicago indefinatly with my bro, so at least not havin him aorund is a plus! but now im stuck wit my dad who works all summer, so basically i get up, make myself food, n then watch tv or go online. not so bad, rite? it isnt wen ur not doin it all day 24/7...  on the plus side, on friday me and charge went to a show and got a 1st palce n a 2nd place! (even though there was only 1 person *me* in the first class and 2 ppl in the 2nd!) but hey! a ribbons a ribbon.  listenin 2: curbside prophet watchin: american weddin wearin: pjs :-P thinkin: wut color shud i paint my nails? 
     

    



