
22,June,2004



       
      Well thay left today. i miss her alredy! well i hope she reads this. send me an email or an im when you get home i mean it i love you get home safe 
     

    


21,June,2004



       
      Well This sucks i will not see my Becky untill next year and i will miss her so much but i never get to bond but i think we will next tome 
     

    


29,June,2004



       
      It is OVER!!!!!! Now i can be Free. Ave Becky Is mine not your's I am willing to fight for her!!! On the other hand I am going to have a great 4th of July. We got a gillin of Fireworks. Becky were are you dont make me call!!
     

    


09,July,2004



       
      i have never been to her house
     

    


08,July,2004



       
      i got an email from som JROTC chick in florida and she want to meet me and see what i am like AVE AND BECKY HELP ME !!!!!!!!! give my some info on this
     

    


06,July,2004



       
      my aunt erin eating nasty stuff&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      my Little Cuz Caitlin&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      Good Pic of becky next to my fishing poles&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      Cowboy Rifle's over my grandpas desk&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      Funny Pic of Becky when She stole my camera for the day&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      One Of My dad's revolvers&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      from my trip to Quantico Virgina&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      i have one of these&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      MY Becky&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      My Uncal Dale&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       urlLink    me at shoot straight&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,July,2004



       
      I may be leaveing in a ambulance but you will leaver in the corners van!!!!!
     

    


14,July,2004



       
      Well he worked and got drunk what a way to spend your b-day and i get cused out because i had to charge my phone and went to do chores and didnt ake it 
     

    


22,July,2004



       
      I shoot every week at least 1000 round's.&nbsp;I am going after school augest second to the police department.&nbsp; To become a registerd sniper. Weapon of choice is a springfiels M1903-A3&nbsp; 30 .06  and a springfield armory M1911-A2 .45.&nbsp;I also have a real big collection of other weapons. i am a sport shooter&nbsp;   
     

    


19,July,2004



       
      five of five&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


19,July,2004



       
      four of five&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


19,July,2004



       
      three of five&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


19,July,2004



       
      two of five&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


19,July,2004



       
      one of five&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      he is also my dart partner and those are the two boards in back thay are reserved for regulars and their is one in the back that you can see in the biker pictuer&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      my dads cooker&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      biker tom and his wife biker peg&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      mayer "max"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      deputy "Mike"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      sheriff "jay"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    


01,August,2004



       
      my dad in in black my uncal bama in white ant tiffay in pink&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    



