
26,June,2004


    
       _I woke up like any other summer morning, but today my maternal parental unit decided that I should clean my room. Although I begrudged the activity, I knew it had to be done. Most of the family's out of the house now, but yeah.... So I started by cleaning up the schoolwork. The recycling bin (the big blue one) is full to the rim, and the trash can is on its way. Lots of memories in some of the papers, but memories come and go. Vaccuumed too; let in some light and fresh air. Then I set to work on my clothes. My drawers were so messy before; now they're all organized; well for the most part, for now. Next, I suppose will be my closet, and then organizing my desk and the shelves that make up the head of my bed. Vaccuum in the area trapped between the bed and the wall. Dust  everything . Set everything straight. Hopefully, I'll be able to breathe more healthily in the nights to come. The goal was to not allow myself to get meningitis (

25,June,2004


    
       _Bored out of my mind as of now. I guess I could do something productive, but that would require effort of which I have not, at least, over summer. We kind of have a flea problem with our pets, and a few of them got into our family room. That last statement kinda seems random, but it's actually a segueway into another random statement. So, anyways, I was hiding on the couch from the fleas, and two jumped on my leg. I caught one and tried to kill it, but when I checked to see if it had died, it jumped away. T_T. _One thing has always been a mystery to me. I thought there might be some authority pertaining to this subject, but I have yet to see a definitive statement. What it is: Are Filipinos considered Asians or Pacific Islanders? ... Okay, so I asked a Filipino friend who is more closely associated with our ethnic background, and he says we think we're Pacific Islanders, while I hear from Margaret Cho that we're Asians. I've added up and balanced all the stereotypes in a mental Venn diagram, but it seems we're stuck in this gray zone. This has plagued my mind on many a standardized test. In any case, I've decided to put that aside for now and just accept whatever labels I receive. Except that being a Pacific Islander might have benefits in scholarships C,C. I've never really associated race with people. It's always just been person and person. Not until recently, in our studies, have such things as racism been brought to the forefront. _For some reason, I've found my muse again. I'm not quite sure what it is exactly, but I've been on a writing spree lately. I've been staying up 'til six in the morning just writing. Actually, on a material basis, I have not made it that far since the beginning of summer, but the fact that the juices are flowing in my mind again makes me glad. I wanted to start a comic just for summer. "Suburbania." I suppose Peanuts already covered that, but I s'pose I could take it a step further. It would just be an exercise in practicing drawing on my tablet, since I cannot scan as of now and still do not have Photoshop when people all around me do. I've had the urge to draw lately, but I'm afraid that if I start it up and fail I won't want to do it anymore. Or worse, I won't want to get my summer work done. _Recently, my self-esteem's been pretty low. I don't really like myself. I can't blame it on media or oppression like other people. It's just my own inner conscience suppressing any ability of mine to accept who I am. I'm not reluctant to be who I am. Or am I? I can never tell. Confusion has always been an integral part of my life, that, at least, I've come to accept. One thing I pride myself on is my honesty, albeit, frank honesty, when it comes to how I feel towards others, but unlike MacBeth, I lie to myself. I don't think I'm quite ready to talk about everything that goes on internally, but I  am  making progress. _With all this free time on my hands, I've been able to take a step back and view the world and people's views. For a long time now, I've wondered what could have possibly made me so bitter and cynical from the once trusting person I was my freshman year. Perhaps, being such a naive person earlier made it that much more difficult to cope later on. eh... but what do I know? Self-examination and self-assessment has never been a strong point of mine. Sometimes, I dunno, it just makes me sick to think of all the horrible things humans do. Sometimes religious zealots too, in the name of "God" or "Allah" or what-have-you. I mean, logic that even a child possesses should tell you that what you are doing is wrong. I don't see how humans can bore that hole into the very essence of what makes humans humane and replace it with the capacity to do such twisted things. Everywhere I look, hate, when there are so many good people in the world too, but their voices just aren't loud enough. They get drowned out by the sensational evil things that people do. *sigh*... It would seem nothing anyone can do will ever fix what humans have wrought upon themselves. _Oh, what? oh yes. You were wondering about the title? Well, we got Cinnamon Toast Crunch, which I have been craving for some time now, and while I was eating it, I read the box (like I always do, to keep myself occupied). And I saw Wendel the baker and wondered, "what happened to the other two bakers?" eh... *researches* AHA! http://www.lavasurfer.com/cereal-generalmills2.html Bob and Quello? huh... I'll bet Wendel ate them. 
    
    


24,June,2004


    
       _UGH! omfg! I don't get it. People think I'm just being petulant when it comes to my grades, and I realize that there are those who are not as well off. But I know I could have done so much better. I've turned into a slacker, and that makes me angry. YES! I realize it's my own fault, and I don't expect pity, and I don't pity myself. I want to incite change! Some people just like to think I'm crying over spilled milk. Well, guess what? this isn't farking spilled milk! Grades might not mean anything one hundred, fifty, or even ten years from now, but right now, grades are the only thing I have and the only thing that can help me make something out of my mess! Everyone has  their  thing. I don't even know what mine is yet, and when I do realize what that "thing" is, I wanna be frickin' prepared. Is that so much to ask? doG almighty! Yeah it sounds selfish, but what of it? I want to lead a regular life, just like and maybe even less than anyone else. There are so many things about me that work to prevent that... Gah! and when people complain to me about my conduct, all they're really doing is feeling sorry for themselves, and it makes me SICK! _I don't normally get angry with anyone, and usually the anger will pass rather quickly. But I can't stand always being angry like this. It shouldn't happen on a weekly basis. Up and Down like I'm on frickin' drugs or estrogen. NO! I really don't need that; it's unnecessary. I shouldn't  have  to explain myself, everytime a person takes what I say out of context. Hell, I say nebulous things all the time. Frankly, I don't give a sh*t anymore. People can kiss my @$$. Every time I try to make an effort to ameliorate something, they just spit it in my face and childishly give me the cold shoulder. I don't mind talking things over, because it gets sh*t done. _So what if I'm self-conscious and worried about my grades? If you think it's wrong of me, then maybe you don't place enough emphasis on them. Yeah, that was bitter! no apologies! You think it's sOOooO easy to be me. You think ALL I do is just sit around and slack off. uh-huh, yeah, sure, you believe what you want. I  do  get things done once in a while, and I make an earnest effort. I may not put out that much, but it's the best I can give. With each year, the tiredness just accumulates. The stress, the anxiety, the frustration. I hate to sound like a stereotypical, angst-filled teen, but people DON'T understand me. And don't think that you do, because you can hardly begin to comprehend. I know myself. Yeah, I'm pretty f***ed up.... 
    
    


23,June,2004


    
       _Today was one of the more uneventful days of summer. I basically sat in front of the computer all day and let the microwaves burn my retinae. I find it incredible just how long I can remain stationary for hours on end. Usually, I have attention deficit disorder-like symptoms, and other times I'm perfectly patient. Funny how it works out that way. Are you wondering about the title? Well, normally, people say, "bless you" when someone sneezes; so, being the good agnostic that I am, decided to go the extra mile and say it in German (because, you know, that makes  so  much sense). What am I doing now, you ask? Nothing, same as all day. I merely figured that since I did not take the time to make an entry yesterday, I ought to make up for it now. _My blog is pretty plain, wouldn't you say? I was thinking of redesigning the template, but I'm far too lazy. Onto another subject: I have a friend, A.J., who is working scientifically to eliminate all contractions from his speech (e.g., "don't," "I'm," etc.). I was thinking of doing the same earlier on, not to seem pompous and stilted, but simply for the sake of being more articulate. However, as I have worked on this ongoing project of mine (a literary work, hardly worth a second-glance), the people have no contractions, and I have stumbled upon situations where the phrasing, no matter the syntax, sounds so awkward that it almost  requires  the contraction to even read correctly. Speaking of that ongoing project. I haven't told you about it, huh? Well, it's sort of this thing I do. I don't know why, the story feeds itself into my mind. I've developed this complex world with intricately-woven stories that I thought I might try to write down, in case I forget it. When I grew older, I became interested in Manga and Anime; so I thought, "Hey! why not try to turn it into a webcomic! :D" How foolish... And yet, I still pursue that whim. In any case, most of the time spent in front of the computer today was for the specific reason of writing. Nothing truly flowed out, but I am now deep into the third chapter, page 98 (1 pg. = a half, landscape 8x10 page). I figure if I write about 15 chapters with 36 pages per chapter, I'll be at 540 pages by the end of ONE of the three major stories. _Now that that's settled, about today? Well, earlier this morning, I woke up around 6:30 AM, turned of the clock/radio, and woke up again at about 8AM. So, I put on my everything, and get ready. My paternal parental unit asked me earlier if our track coach made us sprinters run with weights like dumbells, and although we didn't, I took it into consideration for my summer training. Seeing as I really,  really  want my 400m time to go down, I thought I ought to test the idea. I took my mom's pregnant-lady-but-used-for-physical-therapy dumbells (5 lb. each) and headed out. [One thing that really bugs me: the key doesn't slip into the lock the same as it used to before, and it makes a lot of noise]. I didn't bring my CD player this time because it was jigglin' all over the place the time before. So, I walk down my hill, and start running. OUCH! Even though they were just five pounds each, it slowed me down considerably, made it difficult to breath. I dunno, maybe I'm just a wuss, but it was definitely strenuous. That was the approximate makeup of my day. Not so interesting, ne? So goes the story of my life. Perhaps something amazing, someday, will happen to me like the people in my story. 
    
    


21,June,2004


    
       Okay. I woke up today, fairly late. No time to run, but I managed to eat a decent breakfast. When I get out of the shower, my sister prompts me, telling me that we are going to go somewhere and that I am going to be the driver. (You must understand, I am a relative "late bloomer" when it comes to driving). So this will be the second time for me on the freeway. I assume we are going to take HWY 78 to San Marcos and the Fry's there, but my problem lies in the word "assume." Once we are in the car (Nissan, Sentra, standard), he gives me directions to his favorite gas station on Felicita. This catches my attention (ô_o):  why go out of the way?  I think to myself, only to realize we are heading down the 15 towards the downtown San Diego Fry's. Ahhh!! Thankfully, didn't run into many problems (just a side note: we left at about 11:30 AM). So we drive back to a parking lot in Escondido eventually, and set up some cones so's I can learn me how 'ta parallel parks. After several hours of stepping on the shift, stepping on the gas, stepping on the brakes, shifting gears, we head home. It's 4:30 PM (Xb). I don't know what else to do now; so I think I'll either stay on the computer for a while, then exercise and/or eat, then stay up until I crash on my bed. hahaha. okay. I'm done. 
    
    


20,June,2004


    
       -Okay, so I had a blog elsewhere before, but then I was trying to limit it to this crazy project I was hoping to at least work on during the last year or two. Anyways, I guess this will be my new home *snuggles in as only a whale can*. I just love how the safety valve theory applies to the internet in such a way. Not much happens in my life, and I doubt I will retain the conviction to make entries regularly, especially when the school year starts.  For now, this will simply have to do. Where to start? Well, first off, my summer plans are as follows:......---and that's all. However, I wanted to get my driver's license, do some drawing, work on my summer assignments, volunteer service, improve my 400 meter time, and apply for a summer job. Nice summer, huh? Well, that's the way the penguin plummets. -So yeah, my grades are down the toilet, not that I can help it much now anyways. I got my SAT I scores back a while ago, I tested average. Tim got a 1520 *green-eyed monster* haha... no, I'm happy for him. Didn't get accepted as an NHS officer, but that's to be expected. Even though I say I think it was because it's rigged, and they're all Nazis, I truly believe that I didn't have a sexy-enough résumé or teacher recommendations ('cuz we all know what those would say don't we? ô_o). I'm still directonless in life. Don't know what I want to be, don't know which college I want to go to, don't know anything  about  college. For the past, what?, eight or nine years, about which all my life has revolved is school. and what for? I couldn't tell you. I guess the best thing I thought I could do was appear as good as possible so that when the time came to decide, I wouldn't be a mess. -You know, before, I never considered Track & Field my "thing." Never whole-heartedly dedicated myself to it, but it's given me so much that I thought I ought to see what else it could do for me. This coming school year will be interesting to say the least. The anticipatory anxiety is enough to make me go insane, not to mention that AP exam results are coming in July. Seriously, I don't know why we put ourselves through so much stress. I quit tae kwon do and jazz a while ago. I never appreciated them so much as I do now. Colleges will look at my application and see my junior year: I quit a good deal of extracurriculur activities and STILL didn't make good grades. It's enough to make a cetacean grow tear ducts and cry. That's all for now, not that you were ever interested before in any case. ~SPAMU 
    
    


03,July,2004


    
       _This would be today's entry, only the last entry missed being yesterday's by about ten minutes. So what happened this time around? It was weird (like most all dreams). I was a little bit younger than I am now, maybe early teens. Our class (I'm guessing, though I didn't know anyone) was on some field trip through a building, perhaps, a museum. Its architecture was new-age industrial, but that doesn't matter. Anyways, for some reason, I was an assassin, but my weapon of choice? hefty coins that I chucked at people's heads (¦P). Apparently, my targets were just about anyone; it was completely random. No one else seemed to notice that I was taking out people from behind with those big old coins. So we get near some kind of unisex bathroom (since EVERYONE was going through it and it was part of the tour 

02,July,2004


    
       _It has actually been a while since this has plagued my mind, and I've forgotten what it was that triggered it in my memory. Anyways, I was thinking about leadership positions because I'm still kinda bent out of shape by not getting a position, not even the lowest for which I applied (

29,June,2004


    
       _Hooray! New character design! I finally finished the sketch I started yesterday (took long enough for a sketch 

28,June,2004


    
       _Rude awakening to find out we were going to the beach. The weather along the coast was overcast when we got there, and it was cold and windy. We decided to stick it out until we thought it wouldn't clear up. It didn't. But I  did  start a new sketch. Slowly, I've been picking away at drawing these characters for a story I'm writing (I hesitate to say "book" or "novel," because that would mean I knew what I was doing), and slowly but surely, I've had about six done by now. This one will be the seventh out of an approximate twenty or so characters (main and secondary), not including costume changes. This specific character "Kyron" is the first whole male I'll have drawn seriously. I am so terrible with the male figure. You thought my females were bad... oh man. lol. Anyways, I'm working on him and am currently stuck on what I should have him wear. He was originally slated to be wearing a suit, but that entire character design went to another character. Then I had him as a doctor; so I tried to think of a doctor's uniform. That didn't work. I got so desperate, I started looking to my REALLY old character designs. I managed to resist, but one was really tempting me. Now I'm thinking of placing him in some street clothes, maybe shorts, shoes, t-shirt deal? Who knows. I finally got his face down though. That had been a major barrier before. Wow, it's already 8:30PM 

27,June,2004


    
       _Oohhh my goodness. Here we go again, with the drama. You know, I really do hate feeling negative emotions, but when you subject yourself to them... My friend insists on feeling miserable and seeing the bad side of everything, and whenever she feels badly and I try to listen, she rubs it off on me. I'm  sorry  if I can't always be there for you, but we're just friends. Her definition of a friend extends up and beyond. She wants a  boyfriend  or some kind of higher-level commitment because that's what she's lacking right now. She misses her old boyfriend, and so there's this vaccuum there that she feels her friends need to fill. We just can't fill that position! The best we can do for her is to help her grow out of him and move on, but she doesn't want to move on. And people wonder why I don't like serious relationships. She told me that I was lecturing her, and I  was . I watch her torture herself, and her ex-boyfriend has probably never been driven to such extremes. It's really sad for me to see her bent out of shape over him, and I don't know what to do. I'm no expert on that subject. I recall many people earlier on in life asking me what to do about their friendships, and I could give them a little advice or help. However, I have VERY little experience in romance. My goodness how it boggles the mind. The best I can see it, is a chain reaction of brain-chemical stimulations. But what aroused this entry today (I was originally going to talk about fortune cookies) was the fact that she wanted to go out. _You know, I like spending time with her, but I have to get ready before I go out. I got   out of bed at like 3:30 PM, and suddenly she wants to go out. Normally, if my parents are conscious, I'll just ask them, and maybe they'll take me, maybe not. She just cannot accept an answer of "no." So she insists that I go with her, and gets one of her parents to drive me, which I am hesitant to accept for my own personal reasons (think Cunninghams vs. Ewells + appearance-obsessed parental units = me rocking back and forth in corner). However, there arise complications brought on by the extremity of the spontaneity. Of course, the night before I told her to be more capricious. Whenever I try to help her, it seems, my advice always backfires, even like studying for tests, and it makes me feel bad and not want to help her, ESPECIALLY when she gets angry with me and I can't do anything except to hope for forgiveness. I wish she would just accept my amphetamine-like properties ("uppers") as they are and nothing else. Sometimes, when she gets this agitated by such a small matter, it makes me angry, knowing that there are so many wrong things going on in the world. It's not as if either I or she can do anything about it, but there is more sour milk to be fretting about. (For those of you who read my "reserving my right to be angry," this is different somehow). I don't know why I'm trying to persuade you. You don't even know me. I guess I'm trying to defend myself. Oh well, I give up. _I had always imagined summer as a time to relax, because school was over and so there should be nothing to get in the way. And for the past few summers that has held true, but this summer, oh boy, I can't seem to go a week without something bothering me internally. wha-? sorry I got distracted by this article. I guess I'll talk about fortune cookies now... _So I was cleaning my room, and stumbled upon my old jar of fortune cookie fortunes. -_-.... I have the worst luck with those things. Honest-to-goodness, one of them said, "Listen to a good song everyday." WHAT KIND OF FORTUNE IS THAT? I'll tell you:  it isn't ! It's an advisory statement! I guess that's the backup plan for fortunes when nothing happens in your life. They just tell you what you should do so that maybe you'll actually get a fortune (XP). Now, whenever I go to a Chinese restaurant, I dread the advent of the bill. Those smug little cookies, smiling at me with their crescent shape, taunting me to open it up. I don't even really like them, they're so bland. hey! I am  not  going to let my life be ruled by a cookie, I'll tell you that much! What ever gave little baked morsels the right to command their makers about? Even when I do get the occasional fortune fortune, it'll just be mocking me by dangling words about "romance" or "marriage." Yes, I truly believe there is this old prognosticator with a cutthroat sense of humor writing these for me. Or you know, they could also be randomly generated by computers. But what are the odds? That  every  time I get one of those cookies they order me around? I thought about writing a comic pertaining to them, just to spite it, but... just like "Suburbania," I never got around to it, or it just, slipped through my fingers. *Goes up and edits title*... What else? oh, that's all? okay, well, before I go, I think I should start making my own fortune cookies, except they would be more specific and bitingly sarcastic. Like "Your significant other is cheating on you with the secretary one floor below, because you're right, 'it  is  you...' Oh! and also you will also find ten pennies on the ground face-up this week! :-)" 
    
    


09,July,2004


    
       _I swear I have the worst short term memory. I just went downstairs for something, and I got distracted for if only a minute. Then when I tried to remember why it was I left the computer, I couldn't, for the life of me, recall why it was. (on a side note, I just now remembered why). Earlier, we were having a conversation, my family, and when we paused, I couldn't remember what I wanted to say just a minute or so earlier. I can foresee this as a major problem in my adult life. Also, I'm afraid of spiders. Not deathly so, just don't like 'em. They've bitten me in my sleep, and that I don't mind so much, but if they ever tried that shit while I was awake, I would be all up on that bitch! lol *sad attempt at ebonics*. Anyways, I was going to write about my drawing skill envy problem then cleverly segueway (or, you know, just rant until I ended up on the subject) into how I miss the extinct snacks I used to eat/drink as a child like Squeezits or Gobble Stix, but now I'm tired, so this is officially my shortest blog entry. Funny though. For a lot of people, this is as long as it gets (XP). 
    
    


07,July,2004


    
       _In case I can't think of anything to write later.... I expect this dream came about because I had just watched Vandread and seen a magazine with pictures of space in it, but here goes. The furthest back I can remember, (don't laugh, now, but) there were two girls who looked remarkably like Sailor Neptune and Sailor Uranus (

06,July,2004


    
       _Okay, so I haven't been updating this thing religiously. Actually, I had a couple of things in the back of my mind that I wanted to write about, but there were more pressing matters at hand during the time (i.e., anime, drawing, reading XP). So yeah, I guess I could just play catch up with this entry until I figure out exactly what I want to focus on... or, maybe not. So, what's happened since last I wrote? Eh. well, looking over the last entry didn't help much. OH! July 3rd! So the next day was the Fourth of July (shh. don't say anything). Now I remember. Well, let's start with the personal stuffs: Today, not much happened. Got bored, watched White Chicks the uber pirated version (

15,July,2004


    
       _Hooray! I have two readers (inconsistently): Tisha and Diana! W00t! hahaha... Yeah, I think if too many people read this stuff, which I doubt they do (I keep all the good stuff in the middle, anyways ~_^ ), it might just cause the universe to implode. And we wouldn't want that, now, would we? or  would  we (ô_o)? It's been quiet around here lately. Just birds chirping and me eating. Yes, oh how I do love to eat. Summer reading has been coming along nicely, that is to say, not at all. Do you think I'm antisocial for not wanting to go out much? Maybe a recluse, but not antisocial. Wait. That doesn't make any sense (XD). Anyways, I do love talking to people, but when I'm feeling tired, I don't like to go out. Some times I expend so much energy during the day, the time meant for fun usually gets deposited into the bank of relaxation. I don't think I could go an entire day without talking, even just in my head. I need interaction, though. I feed off of that energy. It's what keeps me going. Otherwise, I don't know... what it is about socializing that I like so much. Perhaps because I can't stand not talking even just idle chit-chat or small talk. Or maybe I just need to get things off my mind sometimes. I know it likes to overflow, as you may have seen, and so letting out the dam a little bit every now and then maintains my sanity.  _It's a beautiful day, today. Too bad it's so damned hot. Is it wrong to wear sweaters on hot days? I have to keep explaining to people that it's not the hot air that bothers me, it's the sun's burning light that I don't like (vampire. lol). I don't care too much for any heat in the first place, but at least with just hot air, I can drink water or something. When the sun's beaming down on you, there's not much you can do except sunscreen or sunblock and shade. Shade isn't exactly available all the time; so, I guess the best thing to do would be to wear something to cover, not necessarily thick, but covering. The people in the desert do it (

14,July,2004


    
       _Damn, transitioning from complete nocturnalism to regular diurnal sleeping hours is a bitch! I feel like shit and probably look like it too (

12,July,2004


    
       _Had another dream I remembered when I woke up. This time it was at school. I don't actually remember a lot of it, just that I eventually headed down to the track. At the track, like... the whole team was there doing stuff, but it wasn't a meet. The weird thing was, Jeff was there(O_o). I was running, but it was so slow. It seemed no matter how hard I pushed, I couldn't get any faster, at least, my normal speed, which isn't even that fast with which to begin (

11,July,2004


    
       _I've decided: today, the laziness dies within me. No more screwing around. Perhaps, before, I've said something similar, and that fact kind of discourages me. But for some reason, I suddenly have this innate desire to be productive. Scary as it may seem. I guess, I don't mean seriously productive, nothing like work-a-mania, just, productivity. Laziness is so.... boring, and outdated. I sat around playing Monster Rancher Three from 1PM to 9PM today. I think I lost a pound or two in the process. To some extent it was interesting, but at some point, I felt my breathing become labored, just from sitting there. Anyways, somehow, I can't see myself doing nothing for so long. I know it will be difficult for me. If there is one thing that I am sure of about myself, it's that I'm one helluva good lazy ass. I want to get better. I want to look, feel, better than a pile of trash. I know currently, even my teachers agree, I look like hell walking in Monday morning after having procrastinated on some project or essay. It's not that I like it, just that's what I've grown accustomed to. Last semester though, after having pushed like the Dickens and a woman experiencing labor to pull my grades up, my body quit at the very end, kinda like my 400m. My body had never done that before, and it scared me. Even before then, I couldn't stay awake past 11PM maybe even earlier. No, I didn't like that. So how to start? First, get organized. Perhaps, follow in suit of Diana's footsteps (Maybe not to her degree of neatness, though o_O, that's more like obessession). When I think back on all that time, that youth, wasted... I guess I just don't have that innate, or perhaps environmental influence even, ability to focus. I've seen those with a keen control over their concentration, and it has served them well. I think I have the capacity for that kind of focus. I've seen myself demonstrate it before, albeit, in insignificant and irrelevant situations (i.e., video games, weddings, etc.). The writing of this blog entry... is not one of those times (XP). Usually, when I write these, the lengthy ones, I tend to get distracted and have to try and remember what it was I was writing about, and, as you may have noticed, I skip around from topic to topic quite often. Ack! Distracted again. I guess that's all for that topic; I've burned it out enough, plus, now I'm biding space until I can think of about what to write in the next paragraph. _Lately, I've been reading a ton of webcomics. Sometimes, when there's a slowdown in the comics I'm currently reading, I start feeling the itch, and I just google and web directory until I find ones I like. I guess, it's because of them, other writers and artists, that I want to be like them. Because I enjoy reading their stories and looking at their art. And when I have all these things stored in my head. Just... people, places, happenings, designs, stories. I feel like writing them down or expressing them any way I can. Not for anyone else (as many of my friends know XP), just for myself. _If you were wondering what the hell the misguided thoughts part has to do with anything in my title. I realized, it just is that I envisioned this pied piper in my head, leading my thoughts off a cliff like lemmings, and sometimes, they wind up in the gutter, or just so brutally mangled, that they're almost not worth sharing. Anyways, that's the story behind that. It wasn't any kind of poetic or artsy thing. When I read the title a while ago, I realized it might come off as something of that nature, but nope, I'm not that deep so as to claim any title of artsiness. _Hmph. This blog entry seems to be lacking in any "straight line." Just kinda goes off into tangents. I wonder what exactly in my mind sparks that, the random surfacing thoughts. The same drive that generates my dreams I suppose. But usually, everything is non-sequitur and irrelated (real word? I don't know, but you get it, right? so that must make it a world, irregardless of Webster. and yes, "irregardless"  is  a real word) oh.... unrelated hahaha wow it's late. _Recently, too, I've seen a ton of Anime. not enough that I would be happy, but more than I'm used to during the school year. *Yawn* I really do want to write more, and probably could. In fact, were it not so late and I not so hungry, I would probably go back and delete a paragraph or two and redo them (XP). It's too late for that now though (so much for adjusting to regular diurnal cercadian rhythms XP). _Oh how I love biology. Not just being able to use words and pretend to look smart (although that can be fun too ;D), I enjoy biology for the sake of knowing how things, life, in particular works. Life is always such a mystery. Baffling and beautiful. Just how everything works out kinda like a symphony of coincidence and right timing. Like sometimes, I wonder at the odds that I ever came into existence or that slim chance life could have ceased to exist. That earth just happened to possess the right conditions at the right time to hold life. I know for a fact, that there are aliens out there. Perhaps, even more like ourselves than we know. Maybe, conditions on the planet have caused different evolutionary outcomes, but I doubt there is much difference. In this universe I can imagine plenty of life forms out there, at all stages, perhaps, unable to communicate with foreign planets. But I can imagine us, looking through our telescopes, not seeing them looking right back at us unknowingly, like that Rocky and Bullwinkle stuff. Anyways, i'd better head out for the night. Signing out, SpAmU 
    
    


20,July,2004


    
       _Where have I been? For three and one half days, it seemed as if I'd just fallen off the face of the earth. So yeah, Final Fantasy X-2 came into my life. I had hoped video games wouldn't be a large part of this summer, but... anyways, when I game, I game straight up. I think my mass atrophied tenfold 

29,July,2004


    
       _I thought I might be able to suppress my desire to play that damned game to the very end. Not the case. The moment I picked up that controller, my fate was sealed. I NEED TO KNOW!!! What happens?! What am I missing?! Oh it's terrible, I've been deteriorating both mentally and physically. I realize this, and yet, I keep playing? WHY?! What is it about those flashing colors and harmonized symphony of sounds that keeps me glued to the couch? Like a moth to the flame (-_-). At first I thought that if I beat the game, I would be through with the damned thing, but it wasn't enough. I thought it was just the suspense relating to the story's ending that kept me planted, and to some extent, it was. However, the true culprit? My need to complete it. This game, unlike others I've played less-than recently (rather, I should say "sequentially prior to"), has seemingly endless sidequests and possible outcomes that keep that 99% from reaching 100%. I'm currently at 99% completion. I'd rather not touch the thing again, but now, I've read that there is a "final" ending (-_-) achievable only via 100% completion. That would mean, another at-least-60 hour session of playing. My eyes are burning. This definitely cannot be healthy. I've even lost contact with the internet. To put it plainly: it's sad. I have been conquered. I never really, truly had a strong will with which to begin (I can foresee overeating a prominent problem in my future ¦B). At least, after I got through the storyline the first time, I began sleeping, eating, and showering on my regular schedule. I wasn't thoroughly absorbed to the brink of death or imagining the world had switched places with the game world (a.k.a., insane). I wish I had that thing inside me, er... inhibition? something to fight my urge to play those games. I know I said laziness was supposed to have died, but this lovely wrench has managed to stick itself betwen my cogs. *sigh* I suppose I am incapable of change. Yes... So the story goes... I want to start over. I know once summer ends, I'll regret having wasted it so carelessly on such a frivolity. But no one ever does anything about it! They just stand on the sidelines and watch. I guess that's really all they can do now. I'm supposed to be all grown-up and mature and responsible and strong enough not to use polysyndeton so often (-_-). This must be one of those tests in life. Perhaps it is not so difficult as one would think or in comparison to others' struggles, but to me, I can't quit. It seems so silly from a distance, but if you could only come inside to the nuthouse, you'd see just how insane I am as well as how hard I'm trying. whine whine whine, complain complain, I know. Next paragraph. _Anyways, I've had much going on in my head (after the second cycle of the storyline, much of the twice-completed game becomes routine and not needing of full attention). It' just too bad I forgot most of it (-_-). I do remember my fortune cookie from Panda Express. It was empty. No fortune. Isn't that terrible? You'd think they'd at least have the common decency to insult me with their psychobabble, but apparently, they'd rather threaten me with the prospect of death (or at least, I think that's how the superstition goes). You know? one of those ancient Chinese folktales-- Oh wait! that's right, the fortune cookie was created here in America (-_-)  _I suddenly remembered one of the things I wanted to talk about! heh. It's actually kinda silly, but if you take my life experiences and add in a few explosions, gun shots, and rippling muscles here and there, my life would be a slo-mo action film (or is that list the entire contingency and standard for an action flick?). Take for instance: we were at the Outback Steakhouse and I couldn't decide. Cyclone chicken or the fried shrimp? I saw the waitress out of the corner of my eye: she was fast-approaching our table. I could feel my palms beginning to perspire. which would it be? my eyes darted back and forth, my mind listing the pros and cons, the consequences of either choice. No! I can think under this pressure! I glanced up from the menu for only an instant, and there before the table's edge was the black apron. I watched as a hand reached into one of the pouches, retrieving a pad of paper and pencil. Time was running out. My paternal parental unit had already begun to order. Then my mind became flooded with questions: which was the better deal? how hungry was I? How could the waitress expect the order of drinks and appetizers warm-up enough for the main course ordering?! This was no time to dwell on off-topic thoughts! I needed to recollect myself, but then, my maternal parental unit had already finished her order! Red wire?! Blue wire?! They both looked equally appetizing, but ordering one meant not having the other. I'd just eaten BBQ chicken on my frozen pizza for lunch, but then again, we had coconut shrimp as appetizers! NOooooO! she had arrived at me. One instant seemed to drag on forever, and I, like a deer in the spotlights, panicked. "Chicken! The cyclone chicken, please."  whew!  the decision had been made, and the world was still spinning. Just when i thought I had cleared the hurdle, the woman had the audacity to throw a curveball. "And would you like soup or salad?" Ahh, but I had prepared for this as I had heard the previous orders. a solid, confident "no, thank you." Now I was in. or so I thought. She bombarded me with options, "french fries, this or that, blah blah blah, or garlic mashed potatoes?" I grew tense, thoroughly unprepared for this surprise and verbal trap she had set. I honed in on the last words she said from my memory. "garlic Mashed potatoes" it was. I'd made it, but only to find out, I had tripped the security defenses and all my spy-buddies had died. The chicken? not so great. The potatoes? lack-luster (no offense to Outback Steakhouse, as I imagined their shrimp as exponentially more scrumptious). The only thing that saved me were the stolen mushrooms marinated in wine. Whoops. hehehee....... You see?! totally riveting. I know  I  was on the edge of my seat, well, more or less because the seats were pretty wide from the table. But yes, indeed, much of my life follows suit with this kind of slow fast-paced action. haha if this is all the action my life holds, I'm at least thankful it's not so much a comedy with me as the center joke. _Okay, gots to go. Physicals are tonight. wanna be in tip-top shape (XP). 50 push-ups, baby. Or else feel the wrath of the doctor's hand (


