
25,June,2004


	 
       mood :  tired but slightly hyper =_= / *_@  listening to :  twitch - bif naked (don't ask why.. I'm searching thru old music)  talking to :   brendan   Yea.... Made it prettier (I think..??). Anyways, made Brendan start his blog back up.. Indeederooo... Anyways.. My lip stud is bugging me.. Meeeeeh~ I should prolly go to bed soon cuz of the moving and such... *cries* I don't think I wanna move really...  Damn.. this is the last night I'm ever going to spend in this house..  ever !! I'm sad now... Depressing house withdrawl... :(
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       mood :  accomplished  listening to :  nothing... cd plat batteries went and died :(  talking to :  Peter... but he's watching Ranma 1/2 so he just keeps on saying "XDXDXDXD" randomly...  I had something here but then the page fucked up and it's gone... And it's all  your  fault!! *shakes fist* Damn you!!!  ...Anyways... Tomorrow until question mark there will be a hiatus cuz we're moving... Once I'm able to, I'll make this page look decent. Until then... eat ice cream or maybe a popsicle? Jesus, I don't know, amuse your self. I'm just pissed cuz I was all ready to post my first entry and then it's all *die*. Wtf?? God.. anwyays... And now for something completely different!   woo~ pirates   ::: moving tomorrow... sadness   says: wooo woo~ pirates   ::: moving tomorrow... sadness   says: created teh blogness peterlicious

31,July,2004


	 
       mood :  longing for goldfish that I've already eatten ;-;  last watched :  Monster (well acted, yet disturbing and cinical)  I told the people at a forum I went to for about 5 days that I would be back about 2 days ago from my trip. Apparently some spam whores fucked up the forum so now all of the threads are passworded. I honesty cannot be bothered to type in a password everytime I enter a thread. No matter how much I like that forum. Maybe I'll leave it for now and then go back after a while and be all "I've returned!" and see if they actually remember me. Fla.. doubtful, though they all seemed to like my name "flamingramen". Heehee.  Damnit, don't you just hate it when friends change? Not necessarily into something that genuinely hurts or offends you. Just conforms to anothers expecations just to make life easier in some way. It's so hard to explain. I love and hate her so much right now. She was one of my bestfriends and now it's like she's dead because when I talk to her now she's not the same. She's not real and I can see right through it, which is what hurts even more.  I know who she really is but it pisses me off to see her supressing that just so fuckheads don't feel like fuckheads.  All of my girl-friends seem to be acting weird. Sometimes some of them hate me, and then others just plain don't understand me. It's like I just can't win with them sometimes.  I shouldn't let it bother me though.  I got a caduceus pendant today from Dreamweaver and a book on Indigo Children. I did that after I left Patty's. I actually cried in front of her . I've never done that before. We were just talking about depressing ex-friend crap and suddenly I was crying. I didn't even notice it was happening for a moment, even tho I was sobbing. It was strange.  But.. I'm gunna go do somemore nothing..  ..mmhmm.. 
     
    


30,July,2004


	 
       mood :  tired and slightly achey  That's right, it's green now. Ha! My old one was being weird and insolent.. so Tada! Green.   ...  I have nothing of value to post *weeps*
     
    


29,July,2004


	 
       mood : &nbsp; pissed off for no real reason   listening to :  the boy who destroyed the world - afi   meh... I feel like a pile. A pile of what? A pile of something  rather unpleasant . *glares*  ;_; I nearly threw up today. I guess I did kinda... and I kinda wanted to.. because the throwie-upie feeling keeps returning. I just want to get it over with! *angst*  I decided to consider making a webcomic... not that I'd really expect anyone to read it, mostly for my own amusement more or less. I already wrote up a rather extensive plot and made character sketches of two of my many mayhaps-future characters. I'm not going to write it out, maybe I'll just scan in what I've already written in me sketch book... I think I will. Wait, I'll go scan now.. but it will seem like not time has past for you. Strange that. Damn you and you're lack of time experience. *shakes fist* ...blerg... scanners being a picky bastard... *kills*  Well, then, that took way more time than it was worth *anguish*    urlLink character sketches   - what are those crazy scribblings you ask? They're their names. That's right. I scribbled them out. Bitches. Well, you'll find out the boy's name if you read the plot line... bah   plotline:   1   - that's right... it's got death and rape. Cry about it.    2   - Ha! I based the siblings on people I hate/have a distaste for! Yay~! *donces* The doodle at the bottom was a pathetic attempt at morbid humour and space filling. Oi.. *badger*   {I changed the names of things so that people can't say that I'm dissing actual things.. I'll just say that I don't know what they're talking about and that I invented those names and that they're just crazy fucks. Clever, no? *turns french*}   ??click for exciting prize??   - that is what happens when you doodle late at night while listening to sexy placebo songs.. well.. it's what happens to me anyways ._.   I have a feeling that if I do go thru with this thinger it'll end up being all gothy. I don't exactly want it to be like that but I'm apathetic enough to let it slide if it does. Well.. I'm done the plot line in my head.. kinda. 12 is gunna be one of them stupid petaphile-bait children and 13 is gunna be a very terrible 2 yr old. It's gunna be possessed-like.. *bug-eyed*   Anyways... Had an interesting conversation with "peat" XD Only a select few will understand that.. Hahe~! Yes... That's right.. *pelvic thrust* 
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       mood :  html coding mode O_O   listeing to :  'at a glace' - afi   doing :  listening to Black Sails in the Sunset, coding my new site which is on tripod *gag* cuz I gots no $$$ T-T and talking to teh Brendan #__%&nbsp; =&nbsp; ???   a little while ago my ickle brother put a metal portable coffee mug thinger in the microwave... it was funny in retrospect. But at the time it was frightening when I kept on seeing the microwave spark and then.. fire. It wasn't too bad, we could just blow it out, but the cup was ruined obviously, and I got plastic ashes on my perogies *shakes fist*.  And our word of the day is "ass-pirate" ...yea, I don't know... 

15,July,2004


	 
       mood :  that stuffed up in a hot garage felling  last watched :  Anchorman [stupid and funny.. but I guess that was intended]  I saw Anchorman last night and it was... very stupid but also quite entertaining so I guess it was okay.  But last night I was playing Prince of Persia in my room and suddenly the screen turned off even tho the tv was still on [it was weird 

13,July,2004


	 
       mood :  delited  eatting :  danone la creme (sex in yogurt form)  watching :  'Rejected' by Don Hertzfeldt ^o^  talking to :  Brendan and Erin, but Erin left cuz I was on 'brb' to long during our checkers match watching the cartoonness 

10,July,2004


	 
      that's right... I changed it to shittles... Because the word shittles kicks so much ass. That and it's the name of my new site that isn't existing at the moment but shall soon. So it's like... Hey! Kill two birds with one stone, eh? Aww.. poor birdies.. damnit. Who ever thought that saying up should be tarred and feathered! *anger*  oh yes..   urlLink      urlLink Which Family Guy character are you?    for some reason I'm Lois... yea.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       mood :  strangely amused  listeing to :   allergic - placebo  Dear god.. I don't want to go to sleep. Eeee~!  I got a placebo cd 'Without you I'm nothing' or something to that effect... Anyways, indeed.  Erm... *long silence due to lack of brain fuction* ...*eyes roll back into head* ... *drool* Yeeesss... Well I finally got some decent 16 gauge earrings for my third lobe... erm "holes"? Should I call them holes or piercings or.. Well yea. Bah! You know what I mean. So cry me a river and I'll build you a cannoe so that you can travel down stream and find someone who cares! o_O Lol! Damn that was fucking random.. I think that's my little singnal that Brinny needs her sleep.. Meeheeee... But yes, now they match my 14's in my 2nd holes and my 12's in my 1st's. Well.. somehow they match.. in some.... way... 

09,July,2004


	 
       mood :  meh  listenging to :  99 luft balloons - nena (I'm trying to cheer myself up) and random old school afi 

07,July,2004


	 
       mood :  meh *shrug*  listening to :  'halloween' - afi  doing :  making a stupid flash music video to 'halloween' - afi, even tho halloween is 4 months away 

03,July,2004


	 
      I hate kazaa *anger* All I want is to hear 99 Luft Balloons and it was 3632KB/3666KB (devil's song apparently 

03,July,2004


	 
       mood :  tired and blah  listening to :  mr. rotobo - styx [I'm  very  sleep deprived @_#]... now it's fly high (saturation mix) - ayumi hamasaki... cuz it's crazy !_!  Yea....... I changed the colours cuz it was too "Ooh looka me I'm black~~!" Or something like that... I cannot think T-T It's like my brain's there but it's all "I'm sorry, I'm not available right now" and it's all like wtf??? o_O I don't understand what I just said.. ah well. I got.. uhm.. 2-3 hours of sleep last night.. It was the most eventful sleep over ever.  First we (me and Nicole.. that it) took Cozmo and Skippy for a walk and this scarey old man was swearing at them. I think he was drunk. Then a bunch of dogs kept on running out of their yards and up to them which was  really  great x_X.  Then we got like food poisoning from the frozen yogert... or yogart?? I can't spell... T-T But then it was all like.. blah.. and then we decided to chat after watching many an anime.. I can't remember exactly what we watched... but it was good... 

07,August,2004


	 
      yep, I'm leaving this place. you can find me at http://fuzzyhandcuffs.blogdrive.com blogspot just pisses me off too much, so ha *leaves and sets blogspot aflame* *cackle*
     
    


01,August,2004


	 
       mood :  content  listening to : ' we die young' - alice in chains [wee]  I watched slim to no amount of tv today... which is stange considering I didn't do much. Woke up at 10:50 to the sound of what seemed like some asshole reving their car. But it just my dad pressure washing the house. Why? I don't know 


