
30,July,2004


     
        &nbsp;  &nbsp;tomorrow i'm going to the beach i think....but i'm with my period which it sucks.....but u don't have nothing with it so just forget.    &nbsp;  &nbsp;no, it's not today yet that i'm going to tell how was my visit to the dentist.............too bored yet.    &nbsp;  &nbsp;WORD OF THE DAY --

27,July,2004


     
        &nbsp;  &nbsp;hum...i was going 2 write about my visit 2 the dentist but it was long and i'm 2 bored 4 that..  .    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  &nbsp;WORD OF THE DAY--

22,July,2004


     
      &nbsp;  &nbsp;I'm going to the dentist at 10am...............................that's all i have 2 say.    &nbsp;  &nbsp;please feel sorry fot me...lolol....    &nbsp;  &nbsp;WORD OF THE DAY --

19,July,2004


     
          &nbsp;2day I've been thinkin bout...secret diaries. i don't have any. i used 2 but i was always afraid that someone could read it and find some  secret  stuff which they weren't supposed 2 know...    &nbsp;how'd u feel if someone reads ur diary? embarraced probably..........i'd feel that 2, i think.    &nbsp;there are those diaries with a lock and a pretty key (still  secret )that actually are useless...i mean, everyone is able to open it just using a pencil or a pen. they're ridiculous.    &nbsp;as i said b4, i don't have any diary but i have this blog. the main difference is that this is a online diary but it doesn't keep anything as real secrets, deep feelings about someone, all that stuff that you keep in a  secret  diary...this blog only keeps useless things...stuff that come to my mind...!    &nbsp;just to finish this....i think that a  secret  diary with a lock and a pretty key or a simple note book are equivalent. the grade of security is the same.     &nbsp;   &nbsp;WORD OF THE DAY --

17,July,2004


     
      &nbsp; &nbsp; My brother's pissing me off......................................................grr!! i'm so mad that i'm able to throw him a chair or a table or something heavier!!! he sucks...................  
     
    


16,July,2004


     
        &nbsp;  &nbsp; check this out... urlLink http://redmusic.com/goths/warning.html . u have to copy and paste it. it's just too stupid too be true. i can't believe that somebody has really believed in that stuff.    &nbsp;i found out i'm a bit goth...weird huh? read it and i think u'll find out that's u're a little bit goth too.   &nbsp;   &nbsp;my internet access is kinda slow 2day...grr. it's frustrating.    &nbsp;  &nbsp;i this this post needs some   c  o  l  o    r    ...that's it...it sucks  .   &nbsp;   &nbsp; *** take care   ***  
     
    


16,July,2004


     
        Yay, this thing has colors now...cool...!!     it seems we can post pictures too....i can't...i tried...damn thing. i'll try later     &nbsp;   i'm bored again .    &nbsp;   (wit colors it's cooler....maybe not.)     &nbsp;     WORD OF THE DAY   --

14,July,2004


     
      Last night I had a nightmare with clowns…nope, not really, I was just kidding.  I'm listening to "Change" by Good Charlotte. Beautiful. This song doesn't mean anything in special for me but I know someone to who this song probably means something…  I'm kinda bored again.   My nick on Msn is kinda suggestive. "Spend ur LaZy…eNdLeSs…cRaZy days inside my bEd…oOpS, inside my hEaD!" It looks like I'm some kind of whore. Spend ur days inside my bed…yeah, it sounds bad. Maybe I should change my nick to another not so…u know. Lol…I only say shit. I must stop with this…right now.  WORD OF THE DAY --

13,July,2004


     
      remember the clowns subject? i think i'm not that bored to talk bout that now... i've been thinkin bout the meaning of the circus...not the word, that whole tent with red and white stripes (lol...like the band, white stripes....ok, forget), a box-office selling tickets to people always followed by their children (ok, not necessarily their children, happy children. noisy children. those kids go to the circus for what? i have to try to think as a child. hum....clowns of course!! i think almost all kids go to the circus to see clowns....almost all  like  clowns. i don't. actually, i really hate clowns. clowns are kinda scary with that perverse, wicked smile they wear. i was trying to get the essence of the circus or just get the essence of cotton candy and popcorn but all i can think of is that diabolic smile clowns wear so i'm gonna stop with this stupid subject before i start getting nightmares with clowns murdering my neighbourhood...   THE WORD OF THE DAY --

12,July,2004


     
       i'm kinda bored....i've nothin to do...   i've been thinkin bout clowns. rich clowns and poor clowns. happy clowns and sad clowns. i know, it's kinda stupid...but i have stupid thoughts. i'll talk bout that later....i'm too bored 4 that now.   THE WORD OF THE DAY --

10,July,2004


     
       Kazza came back 2 normal....uff..   thanks to kazaa i could get together all the songs from GC's 1st album...except "I Heard You"...damn song...grr.    yesterday i built my homepage on my home pc...on microsoft word, i don't think that thing's gonna work..if it does, cool.    i say the movie "jason" 2day...kinda cool...   WORD OF THE DAY --

07,July,2004


     
       Damn Kazaa....yeaterday i installed it on my pc and it worked well but now it's completely stupid...i have a lot of songs i took from Kazza yesterday but i want some more...*hits the computer*   WORD OF THE DAY---

06,July,2004


     
       hi there...!   i want 2 make a website for myself but i don't know how 2 do it...free...!!   my Msn doesn't work...shit...   i don't know what 2 write so i'll pass 2 the...   WORD OF THE DAY---

05,July,2004


     
       last night i dreamt with Benji Madden....it didn't happen nothing special...just the fact that benji had been in my dream makes it special enough...:P i was just walkin' down a street when he passes right by my side...then i woke up...!! maybe i shouldn't have told u anything bc u know what they say...if u don't tell ur dream 2 anyone it may come true so...don't tell anyone i told u that ok?? duh..   starting from today, in every post i'll write i'll promove the word of the day!   WORD OF THE DAY --

03,July,2004


     
       here i am again, not knowing what 2 write.   yesterday i found out the meeting place 2 early, actually, 30m earlier... i took a walk around those streets and i went 2 the meeting place again. then a guy from my school arrived, he was there for the same reason as me...  lots of time later they arrived....we dined and we went to a bar with cool music. there was a guy from my school...really hot!! after that we went 2 a disco, it was cool....   when i came back home i saw a movie ( a little of a movie ) and i slept...oh, and drunk a lot of water...!!   ***take care***
     
    


02,July,2004


     
      My father's going 2 take me there...*sighs*, is that good??  by speaking in "...good", i wanna listen 2 some good charlotte music...it's wonderful......................check this out:  ---------

02,July,2004


     
      i'm gonna hang out with my friends 2night and i don't know how 2 get to the spot where we're going all 2 meet...great shit...:s  this is my 1st post on ---

04,August,2004


     
       yay!  i'm in a dancing mood 2day!           *dances*          *dances more*          WORD OF THE DAY --

03,August,2004


     
       i mysteriously woke up with mysterious murderer feelings.         maybe i should stay at my mysterious home.         WORD OF THE DAY --


