
18,July,2004


     
      Hy everybody! I'm back from the hospital since yesterday! I'm back earlier, I tought I should have stayed for another week, but I'm a strong boy and I could go home after one week. Nice new layout, I like it, it's much better like this &nbsp;   Greetz!   
     
    


08,July,2004


     
      Between 5 and 6 p.m. i should go into hospital.tomorrowmorning i'll have surgery,  hope they don't wake me to soon! With a little luck I'll write something in here again in about 2 or 3 weeks. See you soon!
     
    


07,July,2004


     
      Tomorrow, 1700 local, I'll be in the hospital.  Weather could be better today. It's a lot colder than yesterday. Much more wind. I'm a little hungry, going to have a sandwich.
     
    


06,July,2004


     
      Great day today! Sunny. Did swim in the pool, had a barbecue and played on the computer. An average day. Don't want to go to bed yet, not tired. Hope my dad doesn't get mad because I'm not in bed yet.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      2 days left Went to the shop with my dad. We decided to have a barbecue this evening. I did swim a lot in the pool today, but it was a little cold (20°C). Going to have dinner now, maybe I'll write something later
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Woke op half an hour ago. Need to go to the shop now, my dad's wayting. Can swim in the pool later, it is all filled, little cold though.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Here he is! Blog #30!! Haven't done very much today. Been blogging all day long, did set up the pool, listened to music, chatted with friends. I should do more in life before I'm having surgery, isn't it? Maybe I should stop blobbing now, watch the telly a bit. See ya later!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      2 Profile views already on the first day! People are starting to like me here I think. Thanks!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      The swimming pool is all set now. Hope it will be completely filled within an hour or two, otherwise it will get a little late
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Just read the blog "lust liefde en leed" It is in Dutch, most of you people won't understand that I think. It was a nice blog, allmost like a book. Wish I clould do something like that to. Let's check the swimming pool again.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Those Blog-people told me my message wasn't send, but it was, so change last swimming pool (7) into swimming pool (8) and it will be allright.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Swimming pool is filling op now. I don't think i can swim in it today, maybe tomorrow. Hope the weather will be nice then.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Swimming pool is filling up now, already halfway. Hungry. Going to eat. Dad maked pitta, delicious!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Swimming pool is allmost ready. Only need te fully attach the filter en fill it and it is done!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      We're filling the pool now, allmost attached the filter. Sometimes I just want to be a cat. My cat is sleeping in the sun, just nothing on her mind, nothing to do.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Just the plural of time!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I don't mean the newspaper!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Time zone is GMT +1 in here, so mind that wen you read the times
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      My mum and my little brother left for the sea just a moment ago. I love the silence in here since my brother is away
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Solved the problem, just uploaded entire blog again!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      My most recent messages don't appear on my blogspot. I hope this is normal, that there is a limit on my blogs. If anyone can help me with this problem, please tell.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      My dad has finished inflating the ring, now we need to fill the pool and attach the filter
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Let's see if my dad's finished yet
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      My dad is inflating the upper ring now. My mum took the electrical pump, so we have to inflate it manually. I think setting up the pool will take longer than 10 minutes.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      We bought a nice swimming pool a few weeks ago. But the weather was terrible, although it is summer here in Belgium. Hate the weather here, always cloudy. Last summer was great, though. Anyway, it is al little better now, but still not good enough, and we're trying to set the pool up. The package says it should be ready in 10 minutes. Let's see...
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I used SmartFTP to upload my picture. It looks nice, but it isn't really handy
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I've Added a photo to my current profile, take a look if you want too!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I'll try to put my photo on the internet, but first i'll need an ftp-programme
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Hey, this is a Google site. I noticed it at the bottom of my dashboard! This is good. Google is really the best search engine in the world! we have our own version in Antwerp too ( urlLink www.goegel.be ) Greetz!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I'm going to have surgery next friday, so you people can send an e-mail or an e-card (benneke1989@hotmail.com) that would make me very happy
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I hope you can understand everything I write down in here, I'm only 14 years old (15 in September) and my English isn't very well yet. You can allways correct me, just comment!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I've noticed I'm with the most recent blogs, that's just great! I can use som publicity, so you can react to what I write down here!
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I'm from Belgium I live in Ekeren, a village really close to Antwerp.
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      If you want to know a lot about me, you should check my profile, but I'll tell you something here too
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      I wanted to write what I think here, but before I do that, maybe I should introduce myself
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      This is my first Blog post, hope I can come here often.
     
    



