
08,July,2004


	 
      Summer is half way over for me. It hasn't really felt like summer at all actually.  Working has taken up so much of my time that I can barely make time for much else. It is looking a little bit brighter though. Next week I have off 4 days in a row while my mom sister and I head up to Erie for a little getaway break/ enjoy time together before I leave kinda thing.  I can't wait. Then I have a week...then I leave for Pheonix...and that'll be a blast.  Then 3 weeks after that I leave for college. I can't believe it's coming this fast.  This weekend I go up and plan out all my classes. Yikeso!   Today I had to work at 8-2. That wasn't so bad but I was busy the entire time. I don't so much like cooking like I thought I would.  Then I came home and hung out before I went to youth group. We played that scavenger verse game tonight..and I had to set it all up. I bet I hid like..50 some words. That took FOREVER. It was fun tho. Then I came home and had some of Mom's ham dinner..and then my stomach got worse and was hurting so I tried a hot bath and that did nothing. So thenI got in bed and Jonathan called and made me feel better....:)  Oh well.  I am going to get to bed now before I fall off my chair...g'night world
     

    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Fun times at ATF w/my adopted uncles Bill and Ron...love you guys!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here's my baby...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


08,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I found this guy wandering around in downtown Pittsburgh..hmmmm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    It's so full of LIFE....;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yeah we're not in PA anymore&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Chris and Brian really do have eyes on the back of their heads&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Can we say trouble? ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Cool cat&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    The big light palm tree&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    The cross with our weaknesses on it...that was the most amazing moments&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    The Switch&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Nailing our weaknesses to the cross&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Aw how cute are we three..haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Steph looks ....lol..i dunno &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jonathan...you crack me up kiddo&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    We're real cowgirls...;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    MY CACTUS!! that I never got my picture with..:(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jonathan..*sigh*..;)...and The Queen!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rach and I on that thar wagon&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Brian being the best cowboy up there&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Me and Jonathan...oh he's so cute..:)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rach and Kevin at dinner or lunch..can't remember&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our beautiful work of art that should also be on a city corner..or at least at the center of our table...oh yeah..it was....&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Chris L, Brandon B, and Rachie...er I mean the Queen :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Princess Ariel, The Queen, and Miss America. Yeah can you believe they were there???&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Us before the closing session Saturday night&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    The speaker God used to change my life&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    K lemme just say how gross protien is..no matter what...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Chris looks like that thing is about to fall on him....well I think so anyways...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    We're pretty amazed by this...thing we found...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rach under the weird..big...thing...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Our friend Alvin who we found out was a Christian! He's making our breakfast..mm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rach and Steph at the Waffle House&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    CUTE Greenleaf family at the Waffle House&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    pretty mountains&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    desert and pheonix from sky&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    On zee plane&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    On the way to Phoenix&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    



