
18,July,2004


    
       
       I am so sorry I have not updated the blog for a long time...I have been quite busy these days and I have decided...  &nbsp;  This blog will only be updated for Forrester-linked incidents! Other type of articles will be updated ( if possible ) in time to time... I am very sorry and would like to apologize to everyone...Thank you!    
      


15,July,2004


    
       
      Sigh, today was a very boring day again. Although so, there are lots to tell about today ( There's something about Weng :) read on! )  7.30 am - A Flat Tree Incident It was time for duty. Another boring duty day as class duties have been cut down from checking everyone's attire and giving them summons to keeping their mouths shut. I walked along the corridor and stopped for a chat with Calvin at 3E. Then, a 'flat tree' came ( uhm...believe me... LOL ) and asked us for the directions to 4C. Being an avid ' Anti-Flat Tree Fan Club member, i attempted to tell her that the class was located at the squash complex. Calvin foiled my plan as he told the right location :( ( Nigel, kill Calvin ok?...For the other people reading this, you might know or not know why... )  7.35 am - Physics ( let's shout a pathetic 'yay', shall we? ) The day could not get any worse. The first and second period was Physics! Mr Mah was already writing notes as some prefects and I entered the class. The notes he gave us was uh...brief and looks familiar...from the text book? :P The whole class was  obviously ) very noisy, and I was kinda involved in it too :) I noticed Fluffy...uh, Chia Ern's blue stain on his shirt. I was furious at Ezra as he was still comtinuing to shoot people with liquids, this time it was G2 ink. I was lucky I did not get any stains...  9.00 am - This is so funny, I had to put it differently Weng Loong time! Lol, Mr Mah wanted Niklas, Ian and me to stay back ( yay! no BM! ) to continue to decorate the lab. Weng Loong decided to stay with us ( stop stalking Ian! ) and he was bombarded with so many insults, not only by us, but from Mr Mah! ( yeah, you are da man! ) He showed off his so-called personal katana skills ( which I associated with Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles :P ) and we started to ask him stupid questions like " How are you gonna have the katana? " and " How are you gonna bring it back to Malaysia if you buy it from Japan? " and my personal favourite, " If you get it, could you do a Harakiri? " ( If you do not know, Harakiri is a way to commit suicide :P ) and he still continued to swing Mr Mah's meter ruler and started to bother Ian. Sigh...I really pity Ian. Even Mr Mah could not stand him! Well, once a pathetic loser, always a more pathetic loser in the future...  I am skipping Saravanan's class ( I wasn't there and they got screwed by him lol! ), Add Maths ( relief period ) and recess as there were no interesting stuff that time. Now for...  10.20 am - English is Scary and Tormenting...EST Pn Bhawani was already in class, randomly picking out names to present our inertia projects. Thank goodness we weren't picked, as our raw egg cracked ( it was an experiment thingy... ) and Thinesh's group went first. Their bus experiment was extremely funny, but they stole our notes! 

13,July,2004


    
       
      Today was a very sickening day for me. I woke up, brushed my teeth and was ready for breakfast. Guess what? IT WAS 1 AM!! Ugh, went back to sleep and felt very groggy when i woke up at 6.30 am...  7.40 am - BM Pandemonium... It was obviously my group's turn to present our Anak Laut in front of the class ( Being Group 1 and having Haikal inside, it was SO obvious...) It turned out ok, except for a few minor problems with Abu's voice. Saravanan said our group did well ( which can be good OR bad... ) and the period continued with noise, chaos and havoc.  9.30 am - Additional Math and Additional Problems... Add Maths started late, as Mr Tan hurriedly teached us after collecting our homework. Ezra continued to squirt water to people using a liquid paper pen ( thank goodness i was not involved...) Suddenly, Jia Jen's groin started to glow and blink...( READ ON...IT IS NOT SICK...) Mr Tan then forced JJ to give it to him. At first, JJ refused, but later, he gave Mr Tan the blinking pen ( told ya it wasnt sick...)Add Maths was quite boring, and it could not get any worse when he gave us homework...  10.00 am - Recess... I walked to my cursed duty place...the Herbal Farm. Nothing much to do there, just staring at flowers, seeing red ants, staring at flowers again...And then, Niklas appeared as he made his rounds. With the perverted king around, it was not SO bad...as he spotted dragonflies mating! It was very interesting, as two dragonflies were busily flying as they mated while another kept forcing the male ( or female ) to get off...Must be a 'hubungan sulit-lah!'  12.00 pm - Chemistry...ugh It was Randip and Ridhwan's turn to 'teach' us today. My, was it a bore! They talked about Ikatan Ion, and they made the boring topic even worse. Although so, they were not to blame, as my class was already busy playing since 10.15...Cik Masnira was not happy with our class ( as usual...) and I backed up by helping to tone the class down ( which eventually did not work )  Well, not much interesting things to talk about today, no perverted stories and Weng stories. In the future, for sure! Hehe...
      


13,July,2004


    
       
      Hey there! This is JR @ Inokichi, and this is my first ever post...so nothing muchlah! Thanks to the Einstein of BB, Joel Lim, I am introduced to have a kind of useless but interesting blog to be read by everyone! If you want to remember the wonderful memories which will happen in the future that happens in 4C, the skool or anywhere, remember to look here! I hope I have time to update this... ( Joel, remind me ok? ) and well, that's all for now! See ya again!
      



