
05,August,2004


	 
       Wat's happiness? Actually..i dun realli noes..but i knew tt every1 will definitely find their happiness frm families, frenz n even da loved ones...fer me...i dun realli care or worry too much..coz..it's no use worrying abt things n nv try to solve it...Every1 is searching fer dis happiness..but i noe tt happiness came when i've stp searching fer it...it will come n accompany me..thru all da hardships...thick n thin...ups n downs..   Happiness ish owaes experienced along da way...we had joy ..we had fun...we had happiness!! Our life's were filled wif different colours painted by frenz, families n loved ones...rite?    (:.:~Happiness ish not find in the end of the road, it's experienced along the way. So take not for granted each moment of your life and you'll find a reason to be happy each dae~:.:)   
    


03,August,2004


	 
       Ish LOVE realli tat important?? im toking abt BGR and not family love.. Love ish actually not a feeling...i aso dun how to sae lahz..but if it ish a feeling...it fade away soon ba~ isn't it?? I dun realli blif in true love..but of course, dere r exceptions.. Having sum1 hu loves u lots n load is sumthing gud...but if tt guy has a motive den it's a sad thing..i m speaking up fer ourselves...da gurlz..hehx...guys are after those rich gurlz money...m i rite?? not all ba~ if all guys lidat den da poor gurlz will still b unattached lorz..do loving sum1 haf to do wif their looks?? i dun think sho..looks ish not tat important..as long as u haf inner beauty!! All gurlz out dere...mux haf confidence in yrself...fer those hu thinks u r not v pretty..don't freak..coz..every1 has its own goods n bads...    ( 

02,August,2004


	 
       wat are FRENZ??? to me..they are ppl hu will b by yr side to console u when ur sad..share yr troubles wif...listen to yr probs...blah blah blah but once bitten, twice shy..isn't it?? once ur being cheated, betrayed, hurt..u take a long tym to get over all these sadness n angriness..m i rite?? sumtyms when ur being seriously hurt...u will be afraid of making frenz..or u'll be more aware of them..n not trust them totally le.. try to let go..dun let yrself think too much..things may not be as bad as you think..    ~*~*~Everyone has its own star..whenever you are sad...up on the sky..u will see that there are many stars surrounding yr star...n i m one of these stars...owaes by yr side...~*~*~    
    


02,August,2004


	 
        .*.*.


