
24,July,2004


						
						   Well... this blog is gonna be about all the chicks i've seen or met in my life... I aint got no time to write anything here right now so... ahehehe... til then * transimission end*    

						



25,July,2004


						
						   Julie celebrated her 18th birthday last friday(july 23). :D but she had her party yesterday(july 24), ahahaha... Jocylle, Levi, Carl, John, and I went to their pad and stuffed our bellies ahahaha! Levi and Carl came all the way from  CMU (about 90km from&nbsp;here)&nbsp;just to see julie on her big day.. ahahahaha... wish somebody would do something like that for me. *sigh*... anyway, when we got to julies pad Ichi, who travelled 64km just to see her friend, was already there... *sigh*... Julie is such a lucky girl... ahahahahahaha... the table was pretty small but it had lotsa food, really good food for that matter! ahahahahahhahaaha...&nbsp; i was happy, I spilled about have a bottle of coke on ichi's pants... but she didnt get mad at me. :D lucky me! ahahahahahaha. Jocylle and i listened to this fabulous track by  Maroon 5  entitled  She will be loved. &nbsp; both of us agree that its a very nice song... :D heres a few lines from the song; " I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved".  *sigh* i love this part of the song.... :D then we got to drinking some beer... ahehehe... as usual, Carls skin turned red due to the alcohol. ahahahaha... after a few hours we left for John's place which was like only a few blocks away to drink, talk, and crash for the night. Ahahaha I got as drunk as a skunk and fell asleep.. :D Then i woke up this morning with a slight hangover... :D... Whew! that was fun!  

						



24,July,2004


	 
       WOW! &nbsp; this is great! i can write absolutely anything i want in here! ahahahahahahha! anyway... this blog is gonna be about my art... my progress as an artist... etc. nywayz... I post my art in here ---


