
21,August,2004


	 
      sometimes things strike me the wrong way. sometimes i am blind to things and then when i realize them i feel like a fucker for making these mistakes, but the truth is that every now and then i feel like they werent mistakes. but in reality and in maybe 90% the time i realize they were.  i absolutely despise when things fade away. its like the worst thing that could happen. it proves that things arent as good as we think they are or were and it proves that things arent as valid and strong as previously believed. its horrible really. if youre going to end something you have to end it brutally and in a final sort of manner. fading out is a biatch. like even with summer it just seems as though it fades out instead of having one last great night or moment. its horrible really.  here are some names i like and will potentially name my children if i have some or one. emerson-for the man gabriel- for the angel and the name is a nice one. mary-for the mom, my mom. lucy- lucy in the sky with diamonds ben- for the many famous bens owen-i just like the name fuckers brigid-you know those irish people. grace-thats one of my favorites    sometimes i talk pure and utter bullshit or just make little promises that arent very important but i still dont come through on them. like ill say ill call you back and i never get around to it. i want to stop but its hard. i live a life soaked in bullshit. im a fucking con and sometimes it sucks.   here are some things i would like: id like to actually win at football. theres been a drought. id like to be able to read these books for school. id like to meet someone, anyone who just blows me away in their awesomeness and intellect. id like my best friend who isnt really my best friend to want to be best friends still id like fuckface to realize "hey im a huge fuckface, and im ignorant" id like to have a wonderful sunday id like people to stop acting and beleiving they are in love when they are clearly not. id like everyone to understand me a bit more so that i dont feel like a retard id like to get new shoes id like to get a very nice id. id like to get this id as a birthday present, from my family. id like to see u2 live. id like to be able to put thoughts to action. id like to play under a cork jersey.  but some of these are just fanicful dreams and others like wanting a new pair of shoes are very real and attainable to me. bc people need shoes   you know whatever you feel is valid and you shouldnt feel stupid or retarded for feeling that way, because when it comes down to how you feel you cant be wrong. you cant judge yourself according to what other people do or how other situations are handled. like if you feel a certain way you should be outspoken about it and you shouldnt hide. like if youre hurt you should say fuck you, you fucked up youre a bitch. and if youre happy you should be like fuck you im happy. and whatever else, its true the way you feel. and you cant bullshit people, especially when it matters, or even when they feel like its important. you just cant fuck with people in that way, its just not nice.

20,August,2004


	 
      sometimes things strike me the wrong way. sometimes i am blind to things and then when i realize them i feel like a fucker for making these mistakes, but the truth is that every now and then i feel like they werent mistakes. but in reality and in maybe 90% the time i realize they were.  i absolutely despise when things fade away. its like the worst thing that could happen. it proves that things arent as good as we think they are or were and it proves that things arent as valid and strong as previously believed. its horrible really. if youre going to end something you have to end it brutally and in a final sort of manner. fading out is a biatch. like even with summer it just seems as though it fades out instead of having one last great night or moment. its horrible really.  here are some names i like and will potentially name my children if i have some or one. emerson-for the man gabriel- for the angel and the name is a nice one. mary-for the mom, my mom. lucy- lucy in the sky with diamonds ben- for the many famous bens owen-i just like the name fuckers brigid-you know those irish people. grace-thats one of my favorites    sometimes i talk pure and utter bullshit or just make little promises that arent very important but i still dont come through on them. like ill say ill call you back and i never get around to it. i want to stop but its hard. i live a life soaked in bullshit. im a fucking con and sometimes it sucks.   here are some things i would like: id like to actually win at football. theres been a drought. id like to be able to read these books for school. id like to meet someone, anyone who just blows me away in their awesomeness and intellect. id like my best friend who isnt really my best friend to want to be best friends still id like fuckface to realize "hey im a huge fuckface, and im ignorant" id like to have a wonderful sunday id like people to stop acting and beleiving they are in love when they are clearly not. id like everyone to understand me a bit more so that i dont feel like a retard id like to get new shoes id like to get a very nice id. id like to get this id as a birthday present, from my family. id like to see u2 live. id like to be able to put thoughts to action. id like to play under a cork jersey.  but some of these are just fanicful dreams and others like wanting a new pair of shoes are very real and attainable to me. bc people need shoes   you know whatever you feel is valid and you shouldnt feel stupid or retarded for feeling that way, because when it comes down to how you feel you cant be wrong. you cant judge yourself according to what other people do or how other situations are handled. like if you feel a certain way you should be outspoken about it and you shouldnt hide. like if youre hurt you should say fuck you, you fucked up youre a bitch. and if youre happy you should be like fuck you im happy. and whatever else, its true the way you feel. and you cant bullshit people, especially when it matters, or even when they feel like its important. you just cant fuck with people in that way, its just not nice.   -gooooodnight. watch out for the bedbugs theyre vicious this time of year.         time may change me but i cant trace time ch ch changes    
     

    


19,August,2004


	 
      so phils moving to the back room of the basement. hes got lots of cool posters and hes movin all the good stuff in there so im going to visit him alot. hes got a few decent posters too that i like. so i will admire them like an art gallery. if youre mom works at the hospital sometimes she comes home and smells like it. i kinda like that smell. so anyway we finally got the kazaa (weird pronounciation) back. it was basically bc phil had to hear his fav. song. hes fickle though with his fav. songs like they change all the time. right now its tangerine but the led zep. listen to what my mom just said.  mom: "now you know youre going to have a problem there with altitude" me:     attitdude? mom: "no, altitude"  i found it funny that mom was thinking ahead for her children's health and athletic endevours. (sp). we're goin to boulder from like the 2-5 of sept. ill be there for my birthday! Moms staying at home because she cant take off work too much more bc when you go to IRL you take off lots of work and she doesnt wanna have turf wars at christ hospital. so its me dad and phil. im banking on the hopes that dad will help me celebrate my big 1-8 with some booze. im so old, like adulthood and shit. ah well itll be fun all the same. i love my bday. sept 4th. its such a great bday. right by labour day weekend. i spelled labour the english way. its a great birthday. it keeps me happy at the beginning of school and it makes me one of the older kids in the grade. so SEPT 4th 1986, almost 20 years ago. I SALUTE YOU.   from now on i want everyone to call tampons, tampoons. sounding  like platoons.   and i still have 3 books to read by monday. i want to atleast read one because ive heard its good. i never got around to reading this side of paradise but im lookin forward to that too.  ok so hopefully well play reunion soccer  tonight. id look forward to that. anyway much love. biatch.   -mommy i want a mullet. 
     

    


17,August,2004


	 
      so the other day i just started to doing sit-ups. i did kind of a lot. i figure if youre going to pack heat you might as well make it well defined heat. anyway i stayed up late last night watching queer eye for the straight guy. i wanted to sleep on the couch cooch but it just wasnt comfortable enough. i liked the book a seperate peace. anyway me and the olympics get along well.  so today was orientation aka reason to come to school for a pointless half hour. it was funny though. dallas autographed my stomach, with permenant marker. i dont think its comin out either. it was worth it. then we saw nina and chris lorent and then dal gave me a lift home and on the way we fucked with the walkers, and we saw j mac, which is always always a good laugh. what a crackhead she was walkin through the parkinglot for no reason she said she was come from "xaiver" but i bet she was really smokin pot in her car. shes hot though. i asked if she missed me and she said no, but ill miss you not being in class, and i said well yo jmac im sure therell be someone else with no respect for their elders this year so dont worry" and then we parted ways. jmac was funny because last yr when i pulled shit on her she just ignored it. oh the good times. man jr year was the shit, possibly the best to date, with the exception of freshman yr and the gods.  anyway im back from the little dinner party. it was a great time with a fantastic cuisine made basically from scratch by zulevic. man that kid is awesome. shes way under-rated at basketball too. and well zulevic is a fantastic motherly figure also. much love bro. so anyway tomorrow ill go to training and then see clair again one last time before she leaves. she was way under-rated in the basketball as well, and then thurs ill go to soccer. then sunday is the final and thatll be way rough, but hopefully after ill go out on a high note and finish the summer right at the back to school bash, where you have to bring a school supply to enter maddies casa.  ok im a bit tired ive been taking late nights the past week or so. being sober helps me stay up later. i wish i could get all my memories onto this but thats just not the case. reilly is smart or atleast a great thinker, listen to her. h urlLink ttp://thingthatmayormaynothavehappened.blogspot.com/   in past experience i have found and continue to find it not smart to make plans. when they fall through or go not as expected it could suck.   to sir with love.  thats a song and a movie. the song was made for the movie. sidney poitter. and lulu sang it. its english and older.   yours, murph    ps- listen to xavier rudd.  its good stuff      Same when I left you Now the same upon return As your pages flip over You seem to let them burn You drink from the bottle That stole your friend Your friend Your friend Now the seasons They come and they go I watch the blossoms As the bees take their own I peer through the water That floods my eyes My eyes My eyes I want you in my life I feel I need you in my life But I can't have you Not tonight Not these days Not these days Not these days Not these days I watch our children As they play in the sand Speaking those words That only you can understand I know inside of you You feel that they are gold You know there's time They are not yet old They want you in their lives I feel they need you in their lives But they can't have you Not tonight Not these days Not these days Not these days Not these days I hope these things They come alive inside you And you recognise I hope these things They come alive and bite you In the night I see you standing with each child And laughing As you feed their smiles I hope these things They come alive and bite you In the night Because we We need you In our lives Because we We need you In our lives Because these days are These days are nothing Tell me where do we fit in These days are These days are nothing Tell me where do we fit in  
     

    


16,August,2004


	 
       ive said it before on many occasions. people are fucked up. theyre fucked up because of the people they know, have known, and will know. theyre fucked up because they were fucked around with when they were little and theyre also fucked up because of their families. its the truth, and its not bad to be fucked up. its really not. the people who try to hide the fact that they are way fucked up are just well in plain english cooches. its widespread and its common to be fucked up. like its ok if you get knocked around a little bit by like bullies or youre mom or dad. its ok to have something bad happen to you. having fucked up things happen wont nessesarily make you too badly fucked up. i guess it just matters how much you let it get to you. its like this thing that goes unsaid that everyones family and friends are somewhat fucked up. people try to hide it and when you hide things like that youre just puttin up a front. now im not saying hey tell everyone all the secrets you know about people, no quite the opposite. just admit the fact that you too are completely and utterly fucked up. and i know there are different levels of fuckedupness. but trust me if youre reading this now youre not the most fucked up. trust me. so dont even worry about. laugh about the fucked up ness of the world and the people you know. its funny shit. seriously though who cares, everyone is way cracked out so judging someone else on fuckedupness is a pretty shitty thing to do.       so as a closing statement i will say,      i, stephanie una murphy, am pretty fucked up. im not too fucked up, actually not very much at all because i can handle the fucked up ness. its great. dont hide it. being fucked up is the new yo-yo for the millenium. rock n roll bitches being fucked up isnt a bad thing or a good thing. its just a thing, and we just deal with it however we can and the most you can try to do is not act too much like anyone you know whose fucked you up, mainly your parents, now even though theyre good people and they do shit for you, theyre fucked up too.          holla fo a dolla      yours truly,    -i used the word fuck a little too much in that one didnt i. oh well fuck you.       ps-no really fuck you.  
     

    


15,August,2004


	 
       ill keep it short. basically i had lots o' fun the past few days. buckets o' fun. on friday i went to my best friends homestead which was quite a wonderful time. then on sabado i went to susans homestead and stayed there and before that i went to the flea marketo. it was fun and an adventure. but ive decided ive got a horribly vicious case of drunk dialing. like its sick, like ill call anyone, even people i havent talked to in a while and i wont really have anything to say and then when i get bored i either just hang up or say hey ill call you back in a second. it sucks because most people dont like drunk phone calls. i mean i usually state it right away that im a retard and i dont usually be a crazy SNL drunk girl and say things that dont mean anything, i mean for the most part i make normal conversation or try to reach enlightenment over the telephone wires. nope actually not. but its bad and i shouldnt even bring out the telefono, but i feel bad when i miss drunk calls especially from biros or actually anyone. so from now on im going to try to cut it out. im only going to call a select few. i know its bad and i know i should stop but i guess its like being addicted to online, people just love blind communication because its easy and you dont actually have to give as much of your self or even your real self to a conversation. anyway so im guna stop. and dont feel too special if youve recieved a call. im a self confessed drunken phone call slut. but feel special all the same. ok im tured. thats an nelly accent. herre. thur. you know everywhur. those used to be popular a little while ago. kids these days though, so fickle. oh anyway today i woke my ass up at 10ish and picked myself off of sues hardwood floor and went out to gaelic park, then ate a fry, then went back there and then went home. i chilled there for a while and then called up brian because i really wanted to kick a ball around so then colin and tim came out and we played a little bit and made up this really intense ultimate kickball game. its awesome. and you can play with only like 3 or 4 people. its completely revolutionary to the sport. ok im going to go watch a movie and eat a freeze pop, a yellow one. i feel like i need a really good movie because i like when movies are really good but i have a feeling this one will be came. goodnight on this 15th of august evening.      sincerely, me.   ps- i fear i may have to delete this soon because with school just around the corner you never know who could stumble upon it and there is quite a bit of incriminating evidence on this. so heres a disclaimer  **DISCLAIMER** -The events, people and ideas spoken about on this chronicle are fictional.   and now for a disclaimer for the disclaimer  **Disclaimer for DISCLAIMER** -I lied. Or did I?     pps- i really love watching the olympics. alot.   
     

    


12,August,2004


	 
        ok so its weird how people get obsessed with other people. but it usually is just two people obsessed with each other or even three people all obsessed with each other, or even two people obsessed with one other person. its weird how everyone or atleast people like you arent obsessed completely with the same person or even things. i guess it goes with the whole individuality thing. but like if i ever saw something good in a person id try to get everyone to feel the same way. its weird though how other people never feel the same way about something. and yea that can be taken as a great sense of individuality but its not. its horrible. it could make you feel like you know alone in a way. the isolation that comes from knowing people are never the same or never are on the same page thats crazy shit. that could really fuck you up if you think about it too much. and so what ive learned or rather decided is that with all good or even nice ideas theres a fuckface that ruins it. yes individuality should be asserted and etc etc, but in the end you dont even need to assert your own individuality because its already weighing down on you because in every thing you ever think, say, do, no one will fully understand or appreciate it in the same way as someone else. and yes you can say hey well what if there were 100 so and so's in the world or what if everyone was the same. that wouldnt be good but i mean everyone wishes at some time or another they just had atleast one person to like cling to you know or even someone who would just know fully and i mean people think they have this with certain people and stuff but its not true or real. it would be like having a 100% silent conversation with someone and not having to explain yourself and even though sometimes i like explaining myself it would be like a comfort to know that its all understood. but then a 100% silent conversation wouldnt be so great because youd never learn anything, youd know it all already or atleast youd sympathize with it all already. and its true we all search for an ideal person for us but its a false search because if you were ever to find an ideal person for you itd be a fucking bore after a while. and so yes we try to find our commonplaces and common feelings and understandings but its not the same. i mean settling for someone less than ideal as a friend or even relationship is staking your life in a form of isolation. and not settling is the same acceptance of isolation because the ideal person or persons do not exist. its a false search all of it. and so even with your friends whom you hold very close, i mean i know you dont view them as ideal and for the most part its more of an outer friendship as opposed to telling them everything on your mind. and so in the end its your own fault for not finding an ideal person because youre the   one who stops you from doing, saying, or even thinking. and so we commit ourself to our own isolation. and for the most part it doesnt bother us but who knows you know. i dont even know what the fuck i just wrote and even if i were to make the attempt to not hold myself back from thoughts or actions its still no use because we as individuals dont understand ourselves so how can we expect   anyone else to. who the fuck knows dude, im cracked out. i just got way to into the ADD of that and then that song i am a rock by simon and g. came into my mind. and so whatever. pootie tang is a funny phrase. i always put periods where they are un-needed.        ah we played football in the park and watched spellbound today. it was fun.        sometimes things happen or you look back at yourself and youre just like what the fuck was i thinking. oh man you can really have a good laugh at that kind of stuff.        publicicizing      --i will roll out now. like that ludacris song from 3 yrs ago...seems like just yesterday.    stephanie una murphy      ps-you knew it was coming. suck it fuckers.       pps-when you dont have real music on your computer, you can just listen to aol radio and when youre in your dads work truck you can just listen to 1300 disney a.m. radio because you dont get f.m. hellz yea 10 kinds of nasty  
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
      i need a good belt and clean jeans. everyone hates washing jeans though. who am i kidding, i just wanna dance. marvin gaye just came on aol radio and i was just thinkin about hearing him. so come on, come on ooooh lets get it on. so many people around the world are here because of that song and thats not even an exageration. its just feel good music. how can you not love motown sounds? its just so happy and when they sing they tense up and you can totally tell that they love singing the song. anyway summer is ending and in like a month so is my adolesence. that sucks but shit dude i am nowhere near feeling like a big bad 18yr old, so for me thats mostly all that matters.   ive decided im kind of longwinded, but only sometimes. maybe ill start playing soccer again. i mean i already have all the white shorts and stuff itd be a shame to waste it all on the gaelic. and i mean i do look incredibly attractive in football boots, right reilly. man fresh yr at soccer was the fucking shit. dude i cant even explain it fully, but we were little shits especially to jen. we completely violated all rules of how kids should treat their coach. wed ask her the most personal questions and everything. she probably couldnt stand us. like that little group of kids had the worst ADD ever. ah shit we rocked hard, not so much in actual soccer but the actual team-mate-age. i love those shits. and then with the milos and company last yr. that was funny as hell. everyone on that entire team was fucked up in someway apart from me liz car em and magdawg. after we beat this team and won the league or whatever our goalie got in a fist fight with the other team. shit she was raging. that was funny. and me liz and em are just sittin down takin our socks off and we see this crazy brawl like 50 ft away. oh that was fun stuff.   the eagles are awesome, now i know that makes me a 50 yr old man with facial hair, but i dont mind. if youre ever in a car you could play the eagles and roll the windows down, no matter how hot or cold it is. ok im going to go look for those clean jeans. ill catch up with you later. wow i hope someone reads this otherwise that makes me feel like a very very big stroke. ah well.    squirell is a hard word to spell, i think i spelled it wrong.  LuV yA lOtS. MuAh, KiSsEs. TTYL LYL GTG LOL LMAO   ps-heres a song.   No one I think is in my tree, I mean it must be high or low  That is you can't you know tune in but it's all right,  that is I think it's not too bad 
     

    


10,August,2004


	 
      today i woke from a good sleep at around 3:30 in the am, went online for a bit to look at songs, then went upstairs made myself some cranberry+water juice because its the only thing left in the house, and ten watched tv to about 6am, then i fell back asleep on this small uncomfortable couch until 1. i think i might be scared of my bed.  anyway i saw this on another girls chronicle and i decided that i would do it too because ive got nothing to do right now and im slighted bored.    ~What Is Your Opinion Of The Following~ 271. Eminem: you cant take white rappers with bleach blonde hair seriously.  272. Virgins: bogart that flower  273. God: its good to believe in something 274. The Osbournes: my family on crack and richer 275. Reality TV: i cant help it, i heart it.  276. J.Lo: shes a mack daddy 277. Religion: i guess different ones are pretty cool, but people get far to into religion and they start forgettin about other more important aspects of faith. 278. Emo music: boys with dark rim glasses and tight jeans 279. Valentine's Day: ive never had a romantic one so i cant really say anything about it, but i love eating those hearts that say shit on them.  280. Christina Aguilera's comeback: i can sing like her. i swear.   281. Homosexuals: butt sex. wait sorry i mean i think ppl have problems with groups of ppl when they dont know individuals, i dont think i know and gay people well enough to have an opinion.  282. Abortion: just wrap it up kids. but in cases you have to give people a choice.  283. Inter-racial relationships: if youre asking me if id get naked with a black man, the answer is yes.  284. Murder: thats some fucked up shit 285. Death: kind of sad  286. Obesity: lisa, oops i mean fatty 287. Pre-marital sex: let them make the sweet love if they want to, but if theres babies with no daddys running around shot gun that wedding.  288. Terrorism: thats some pretty crazy shit 289. Pornography: oh so you saw me in that one movie, yes it was a good one wasnt it, nah i dont know. porn is weird and it ruined my computer. fucker 290. Fortune tellers: oh, what was that movie? with the fortune-teller with the third nipple? oh i just thought of the fortune teller from 13dead end drive...i LOVED that game. 291. Threesomes: yea i call it a sandwich.  292. Prostitution: ohhh prostys 293. Politics: i cant even vote.  294. Country music: i think im guna start gettin into it, bc dolly and brian. oh sexy 295. George W. Bush: never met him.  296. Cloning: dolly the sheep, and the flies in bio.  297. Britney's boobs: i love them i think about them everyday, they are so fucking awesome. does she know you guys are talkin about her boobs? 298. Gas prices in America: i think everyone feels the same way about this ~Name Game~ What Do You Think Of When You Hear These Common Names?. 299. Jack: henry, and lil jack.  300. Tiffany: breakfast at 301. Ben:  harper  302. Maria: gaelic, mullet 304. Nicole: ritchie from that show 305. Amy: old school central 306. Adam: and eve  307. Richard:  prior 308. Justin:  timberlake ahah 309. Arnold: ahhh nickelodeon hey arnold 310. Tom: tommy d 311. Melissa: haha molitor 312. Charlotte: 's web 313. Harold: and kumar that movie 314. John: f. kennedy  315. Joel: billy 316. Vanessa: williams 317. Michelle:  sues friend 318. Kevin: my friend 319. Brent: makes me thing of country 320. Jake: idk  321. Billy: idol 322. Sarah: plain and tall 323. Natalie: imbruglia...yes thats right. im torn fuckers  324. Christi: ahh the pothead waterpolo coach 325. Nick:  im just going to pretend it said darren, and now i will saw chowda 326. Linda: ahh from bleekers! 327. Taylor: from hanson 328. Jordan: michael 329. Jamie:  james 330. Adrian: brians padre ~Have You Ever....~ 331. Mooned anyone? yea haha one time in 6thgrade we mooned a cop 332. Been on a diet? nah  333. Been to a foreign country? digo si 334. Broken a bone? nah 335. Swallowed a tooth/cap/filling? i think i might have..not sure  336. Swore at a teacher? yes many times, wed sit in the back of the room and flick them off too.  337. Talked to a lj member via e-mails or instant messages? nope  338. Got in a fight? nah but lets rumble. we used to spar in taekwondo. thast not real though 339. Dated a teacher? yea ruth, jmac, and nina...all at once... 340. Laughed so hard you peed your pants? yes sir.  341. Thought about killing your enemy? idk who my enemy is  342. Gone skinny dipping? nah  but peed in the lake. and got naked at reillys table 343. Met another xanga member in the flesh? yup: no 344. Told a little white lie? yes many over the years 345. Told a secret you swore not to tell? probably 346. Stolen anything? yea  348. Been on TV? yeah, i think.  349. Been on the radio? nah dont think so  350. Been in a mosh pit? nah  351. Been to a concert? yes 352. Dated one of your best friends? no 353. Loved someone so much it makes you cry? yea sure you can love people all the time like that, it doesnt have to be pootie tang love either.  354. Decieved somebody close to you? probably, i dont have any morals 355. Broken the law? on numerous occasions 356. Been to a rodeo? nah but thatd be cool.  357. Been on a talk show? nah  358. Been on a game show? nope, but id rock hardcore on jeopardy i bet.  359. Been on an airplane? hellz yea, 10 kinds of nasty 360. Got to ride on a firetruck? nah thatd be cool thogh 361. Came close to dying? don't think so  362. Cheated on a bf/gf? hahaha  363. Gave someone a piggy back ride? of course, just yesterday  364. Terrorized a babysitter? nah i was a good kid  365. Made a mud pie? of course, and collected worms, lightning bugs too.  366. Had a dream about falling off a cliff? no but i had a dream about falling  367. Snuck out of the house at night? nah i dont think so.  368. Been so drunk you don't remember your name? nah, sometimes im slow to remember though  369. Had an eating disorder? yes tons.   370. Felt like you didn't belong? yea id say so, but id say everyone has that feeling at sometime  371. Felt like the 3rd wheel? haha YES. most definitely, for the past couple months 372. Smoked? yea, but thats stupid 373. Done drugs? yea 374. Been arrested? nah been taken in though 375. Had your tonsils removed? nope, still got them and they fucking stacked..huge 376. Gone to camp? nah, that would be good times  377. Won a bet? yea but i never make them pay.  378. Written a love letter? ahah i wouldnt call those love letters, but i used to write about 5 letters a day. thats another story..  379. Gone out of your way to be with the one you love? nah but ive gone out of the way for pootie tang, but thats just common for everyone 380. Written a love poem? are you trying to get me in bed?  381. Kissed in the rain? nah  382. Slow danced with someone you love? i love timmy in a lil bro kinda way and we danced in the back of gaelic park the other day, but it was old fashion slow dance where you have your arms out on one side and around the hips the other side. oh timmay 383. Participated in cyber sex? oh yea tons and tons of times. nah thats fucking weird.   384. Faked an orgasm? haha again you just want me in the sack.  385. Stolen a kiss? i dont think you can steal a kiss really  386. Asked a friend for relationship advice? haha no dude we dont do that shit. reilly knows the feelings on the whole relationship thing. that shit is fucked up.  387. Had a friend steal your bf/gf? nah  388. Watched the sunset/rise with someone you love? i love the gaelic kids and we usually end up seeing it get bright out.   389. Gotten a speeding ticket? ill get back to you when i can drive 390. Done jail time? nope 391. Had to wear a uniform to work? nah  392. Won a trophy? yeah  393. Thrown up in public? yea 394. Bowled a perfect game? not me but ET has 396. Got perfect attendance in grade school? nah i was always around for most of it though 397. Roasted pumpkin seeds? no  398. Taken ballet lessons? oh you know me, all the time 399. Attempted suicide? definitely not  childhood Stuff~ 401. Did you play with Barbies? not really a few id guess 402. Did you own Treasure Trolls? yes sir 403. Did you watch Beverly Hills 90210? nah not really 404. Did you play Simon? yeah  405. Did you watch Fraggle Rock? who didnt 406. Did you wet the bed? nah i was a pimp 407. Did you believe there were monsters in your closet or under your bed? nah i scared the shit out of my bro with that stuff thogh 408. Did you wear the underwear with the days of the week on them? no...i would wear them now if i had them 409. Were you shy? nah i was a little shit 410. Were you spoiled? probably 411. Were you abused? nah thats a weird question 412. Did you go to the circus? yes yes...twice, i think  413. Did you go to the zoo? yeah  414. Were you in a car accident? a small one  415. Did you build snowmen? oh yea, and in IRL snow was a big deal.  416. Did you cry when you scraped your knee? yea im sure i did 417. Were your older cousins mean to you? nah 418. Did you think slinkies were cool? yes but i always tangled them up 419. Did you think the Ninja Turtles really lived in the sewer? hell fucking yea, that show was the best 420. Were you afraid of the dark? nope 421. Did you have slumber parties? still do, with slumber bags 422. Did you have New Kids On The Block sheets, curtains, sleeping bags, dolls and pajamas? i had dolls maybe and i know i had books  423. Did you tease your hair out like Tiffany? nah we were Irish 424. Did you believe in the Easter Bunny/Santa Claus/ and the Tooth Fairy? nah my mom let me in on the shit when i was about 4. 
     

    


10,August,2004


	 
       when things are short i think they provide for a more dramatic emphasis. so i want to make this short just so you can feel touched but it, the truth is ive got nothing of emphasis to really say. Jesus wasnt born on Christmas. Most people already know that though. today in the shower it smelled like nair the stuff that takes out your hair, that rhymes. and when i got out my hair smelled like nair, that rhymes. but it didnt fall out so i dont think it was nair. only time will tell. im so fucking hilarious, i can barely take it. oh the sarcasm is caustic, isnt it. so that one commerical for i think madden football or ncaa football with the song thats goes "someday somebody's guna ask you the question you should say yes to". well i like that song.       i think we hold people we like to higher standards. like our friends and stuff. this is a picture of some of my friends. its a test to see if i can get images on here. i wear rubberbands sometimes, i end up giving them away though. if i gave you one its because you deserve it because youre probably awesome, or i just want to make out with you and get naked...either way its the same thing.   it didnt work. never mind   see you later. -from me.  ps. heres a bit of a song, It was early Monday morning in the Central Standard Zone You were quiet like the TV, hung up like the telephone You were sleeping next to me, I might as well have been alone  pps-i think a good thing to do is to try and figure out something or atleast think about something important once a day. i burned my index finger on the george foreman grill.  
     

    


09,August,2004


	 
      ive decided i wont finish my autobiography of recent events and trends because i dont really want to. i hate not finishing things but i guess thats what summers for. i wanted to do so much stuff this summer, academically i mean. i coulda wrote tons of essays and shit but i never really got around to it. i really need a voice of reason. and what the fuck am i going to do this year. ive got no one to look up to/stalk/fuck around with during precious learning time.  dallas is too serious and so is kim, but thats better for me because they end up making me get my shit done too. but i want someone who i can just play with. reilly was never in any of my homeboy classes and she is now so hopefully she'll play with me. ill bring in toys and everything. i really want to make a movie. i hate when you dont get around to doing something that before seemed pretty important. i just watched the movie elephant, dont bother with it. it tries to be too artistic and its just slow paced, far too slow paced.  im going to my first waterpark ever with jack the 5yr old, its probably his first time too. and brian possibly aoife too, along with the rental influence of mary and lizdawg. im excited and maybe ill even get tan. haha yea riiight.  i need to figure lots of things out. things are always needing to be figured out. and when i think too much about certain things my brain hurts. your minds a really great thing if you think about it. sometimes i repeat myself entirely too much, im sorry for that. sometimes i wish you, whoever "you" may be, could write back to me and tell me something. it could be anything, it could be like just stupid conversation or it could be important, as deep or shallow as you want. i wouldnt care either way. even if youre mean to me i wouldnt mind much. its just good to have people talk back to you so you dont feel like youre writing to no one. but maybe its better to have no one reading this, thats all very one sided though isnt it.  sometime i think this is too vague for anyone to really understand except me. i leave many things out and details and sometimes whole big parts of my life and shit. i guess you can never really tell someone everything or somethings anything that matters, even if you try. i guess it depends on who your talking to. it may seem like i complain kind of a lot, or maybe it doesnt seem like that. i dont really know.   ok here if you read (present tense) this, then just tell me you did, i will probably only say thank you but it will be an honest and yet somehow still anonymous thank you. unless you know me, which in that case still IM me and tell me you read it. you can instant message me, technology these days is cracked out like that. its murph986. much love fuckers.  sincerely,        bite my butt   ps- in your life there are some things that will never ever happen to you. thats a shame sometimes. some people will never fall in love. other people will never get a pet. and then other people will never go to a funeral. some people will go to too many. its crazy to think about the things that you may never get to do, but its also pretty crazy thinkin about all the shit that you can do. its pretty crazy either way. i guess time plays a big fucker in that whole scheme of things. fuck is a very versatile word, might i add.  pps-anyway i was serious about that IMing thing if you read this little masterpiece. even if i dont know all too well or know you at all or know you well or even very well, do it anyway. it would be appreciated.   
     

    


08,August,2004


	 
       ok so maybe you dont know me or maybe you do, maybe i dont even really know my own self so lets just dive into the mystery. if there are things you may already know, suck it  i go to school. i will be a big bad senior, mostly just senior not so much big or bad. ok fine yes i am both big and bad at once. anyway i go to school in a lovely catholic environment which isnt very "catholic" at all. now i know the word catholic is sometimes supposed to describe a particular type of behavior but i dont even understand that. religion in general is kind of a trap. wow i sound paranoid there. but it is. anything you can do you can do alone or in the midst of a small circle. religion can be a very robotic thing. anyway thats stupid i cant talk about these things for too long because it makes me feel old. anyway i go to mother mcauley high school. people say it sucks, people say its alright. i dont mind it too much on most days. at school there is a plethora of different types of people. there are a good few freaks and also people who lack entrinsic social skills. these people are the ones i usually become obsessed with. oh that too, im kind of obsessive. anyway...theres lots of crazy folk at toolschool and they make me laugh when i watch them or make conversation with them. thats another thing, i dont like making conversation alot, sometimes i do but sometimes i hate it. i dont like saying hi to people you dont know well mainly because im a loser and when things make me feel uncomfortable i shout and turn red and get flustered instead of the normal reaction which would be to shy away. i usually repeat myself too when i get flustered. its funny really. where was i? ok yes, so also at school i have had the pleasure of entertaining the company of basically the same people in all mis clases for a whole 3 years. they stick people together and its not because most of them are particularly smart or anything, although a good few are, its because school has to do that because some kids gota go in honors classes and stuff. who knows really. anyway the kids in these clases with me are unlike any people i have met in well my entire lifetime. theyre a very witty bunch and we can basically own all the teaches we get. its cool to call a teacher a teach. its what the cool kids do. i swear im cool KOO. anyway back to my story, the kids im speaking of are a real group of little shits. i love little shits too by the way, ill get to that later. but anyway these kids in school with whom i spend about 30 something weeks a year with are funny. plainly speaking theyre quirky some of them and you can have a good laugh and a conversation with most of them. we always get shirts too for when we finish a smart kid class. we're freaks like that. fucking elite bitches. anyway thats that. and at school its fun, i have fun when im there for the most part and i have atleast one good hardy laugh everyday. also at school you play sports if you are decent enough at them or if you mom or dad knows the peeps in charge. the mo-co aka mcauley is a very politically enforced community so it kinda does make a difference where your chromies come from. chromies = chromosomes. but the people you meet playin sports make stuff funny too and then you have good times with them. most of the good times relate back to all being on the same team and getting drunk together. but the whole sports thin kinda fell through for me in a way so now i try to play water polo, although im not very good. its refreshing though because me being good at everything has just gotten boring in a way. IM JOKING. wait no im really not..oh yea yea i am. only a joke if you catch the sarcastic undertones. wawawa. anyway thats what i do now. so i think last year in school was a very fun year, i probably did the best i have done since i got in the joint and i guess you could saw i grew up a bit but so did everyone else. all these crazy kids drinking and smoking and making babies that never used to do that before. i just sit back and watch the little catholic school hoards enter full blown alcoholic tendencies with a laugh. anyway that brings me to the social aspects of my life.      well ive got a good crew of friends and acquaintances with whom i have the pleasure of getting naked with. its sad to say but yes at the moment and for the past few months maybe year(s) or so our weekends and once in a while weekdays have been almost solely devoted to the pursuit of alcohol. now its not like most other people or even girls. many people are content with their once in while or maybe every saturday drinking sessions with whatever they can find. we kinda started taking it further than that this year. wed get pissed if we didnt get atleast 2 days every weekend. we were devoted. zack helped us out alot with that beer situation and so he gets some of the credit. so basically from around october to about april/may we'd hang out with the same people all the time. it wasnt too bad of a time at all. i do however find it hard to remember in clear detail all that we did. not entirely because of the berrs, but more because the nights were so much like each other theyre now almost indescribable in a way. our prosty reign consisted of many nights outside in the cold weather. oh yes this year we made up the word prosty...that was fun but it kind of died out in a very symbolic way. i guess that was just a little section of the year and that was what we did. it was fun. so anyway weve got a pretty good record ive only had two po-po run ins in which they fucked themselves and we escaped....unscathed if you will. i just winked at you. and so the spring came and i found out i had a best friend, of whom i will speak of later in a whole category devoted to best friend. ok this is weird best rhymes with breast, but you dont spell breast without an a, like brest. yea thats weird.       movies television and musical adventures   today i went to blockbuster but before that i made out a list of movies i need to see or see again. i like watching movies i know will be good. i think i have trust issues bc i hate getting movies that i dont know much about because if they are bad then its like ive wasted my time. i usually dont dislike movies though. but if i just watch a movie on the crazy cable that i dont know anything about its ok because ididnt plan it and its like fate seeing the movie at the time. catch the drift? anyway here is my list. ghostworld, requiem for a dream, say anything, high fidelity, lost in translation, the emperors club(saw that tonight), donnie darko. etc etc. and i want to see movies that are in the theatres now but i think its the same ones as everyone else so ill just leave it. i like television. i watch it frequently. like gameshows and reality tv and the like. i think gameshows are the grandpas of reality tv, think about it. but me and dal are big on the mtv realworld and roadrules as many other people are. but see were hardcore. we know seriously everything from seattle onward. im a sucker for fake real interactions. i love the canadian phenom degrassi, next generation. i used to watch the first gen. when i was like 5 or 6 haha wow parents way to censor the tv. but i used to watch that. i remember the episode where emmas mom (is it snake they call her)gets pregnant with emma. she used to be in the old one with joey jeremiah and archie simpson. but anyway i love degrassi and its complete unnecessary drama but its good stuff. i encourage everyone to watch it. on noggin. real life now. when i got the letter that said my best friend jack watches degrassi i was almost moved to tears of joy. oh and i listen to music. mostly older music, before your time kid. nah i just end up listening to older stuff because its solid and you can always rely on it because it already happened. its staying power is already validated. and i like geetar. when people play them and also like acoustic music. im a low key kind of kid when it comes to gettin crazy with the drinking and crazy rap music. i usually dont roll like that. some people love listening to rap when they drink, i myself prefer the softer sounds. i sound like im 50yrs old. and so this is me in a very generic nutshell because i havent given too many specifics...this little biographical insight is quite broad because itd get far too long if i went into a lot of detail. i like making lists but i end up wondering about other peoples lists and if mine is ok with them. thats not their fault its mine...so i guess im bad at specifics and lists.       best friend jack henry.      i speak very much of and about my good friend jack. well i dont remember much of how it all really got started or who let it get out of hand obsessive but one day i realized wow thats my boy and the last couple weeks or maybe last month of school was devoted to the strengthening of a completely normal and reciprocated best friendship in which i do not call my best friend every twenty minutes. oh wait, yes thats it, sarcasm. what can i say im needy. jaja. i do however remember when i sat at the end of the stairs with my best friend with no source of entertainment and just stayed there for a while because we must have gotten out of school early and it was most likely a thursday. and it ended up we were late for this thing called practice but kristy or maybe kristi was so stoned she didnt even bring that up. i felt bad making my best friend late for her last practice but i dont think she minded far too much. thats a nice memory i have of jack. another nice memory i have of jack was when wed deliver letters and it looked as though jack enjoyed them so i was happy. and the time when i kicked jacks ass in a race delivering student council papers in theology wing. and in one room she got flustered i guess and couldnt find the desk so she threw it on the ground, yea thats not cheating. flustered is a weird word anyway thinking back to that last like 2 months of school, i have lots of small memories of jack, i think i was scurred i wouldnt have enough memories of my best friend but i got lots. some people would say im fucked up obsessed with my boy but fuck you dude. bite my butt. just read the archives and youll learn enough about my boy jack. ben stiller gets his wife in his movies...what a sugar daddy.         ill have more autobiographical account-age later. for now im tired and cant think of anymore categories. ill be back for more, and you will too. you just cant get enough can you?     
     

    


07,August,2004


	 
       im in the mood for a good old fashion party, tonight i will party with brianna and timothy...my two favorite brothers, and we will head into the great wide open spaces of lemont. hopefully my phone will get much use-age. so i apologize in advance, my apologies dont mean shit. really most of what i say and do doesnt mean shit. sometimes people can tell when im being serious. im usually never serious and so when i start talking from the hizeart you can kind of hear it in my voice. everyone has two voices...school/parent voice and normal voice. its true its true. pop love songs make me laugh, love songs in general make me laugh. when people say baby and girl it makes me laugh. i cant wait to take a shower. sometimes i get in the real mood for a shower...those showers are the best.    sometimes i feel like im just floating through life and i dont like that feeling all the time. you gotta keep your feet on the ground sometimes. i will say that im kinda of anticipatory as to the beginning of school. these next 5 months are big time, in my opinion. but after that, itll be good times in the mother mcauley hallowed corridors.       the degrassi season finale was on last night and i missed it. i will miss it again tonight. that saddens me. i heart degrassi. i heart people who watch degrassi and i heart the drama that ensues in grades 9 and 10 of the degrassi community high school. i heart craig for being a man slut, i heart ash for being a weirdo, i heart paige and spinner for being gay together, i heart manny for being a hooch, i heart jt for being jt, and i heart sean and emma for their troubled history, i heart emma for trying to save the world and sucking at it, i also heart her for pursuing an online relationship that almost got her killed. i heart ash for realizing taking ectasy was a bad decision, and gettin with sean under the influence of XTC was also a bad decision, i heart jimmy for being an african american. i heart hazel for trying to deny her muslim heritage and then realizing shes a hot momma and kissing toby. i heart her also for looking at porn and getting sat. detention for it. i could go on and on and i will but my brother has to go online. suck it         -much love...i just winked at you. you couldnt tell. it doesnt matter      ps-tryin hold back this feeling for so long, and if you feel like i feel baby, then come on come on, lets get it ooooon.....ohh baby....lets get it ooonnon.         pps-you have to love the smooth sensual tunes of motown.             ppps- its van the man      And I will stroll the merry way And jump the hedges first   And I will drink the clear Clean water for to quench my thirst   And I shall watch the ferry-boats And they'll get high   On a bluer ocean Against tomorrow's sky   And I will never grow so old again   And I will walk and talk In gardens all wet with rain    Oh sweet thing, sweet thing My, my, my, my, my sweet thing   And I shall drive my chariot Down your streets and cry   'Hey, it's me, I'm dynamite And I don't know why'   And you shall take me strongly In your arms again   And I will not remember That I even felt the pain.    We shall walk and talk In gardens all misty and wet with rain   And I will never, never, never Grow so old again.  
     

    


06,August,2004


	 
      not a day less will do, from you.  tonight i will write about the gaelic. man i love that shit so much. i even stop drinking for that shit on saturdays, well sometimes. and its not even the gaelic itself its the people surrounding it. all of them are golden, with all faults and whatever else....theyre still all great people. anything i could ever want, i have gotten from them. theyre just a fucking hilarious group of kids who were thrown together through the dysfunction of their families. now i probably talk about them too much but i swear they are great. like michael jackson great. everyone has people like that. i have many. i think the best thing is that we dont usually see each other all the time until summer starts and that makes us even closer bc we never usually fight or anything. i have so much utter love for them all its insane. its sexual and non sexual at the same time. theyre all a bunch of good looking fuckers who make me so happy. and i even forgive theresa for the SF incident. its ok i know we could have beaten those fucker 18yr olds, i dont mind. and i know over the years weve changed and its changed but its probably changed for the best because now its so much funnier and well fucked up. these kids are the main reason why my kids will play sports with the same kids when they are little. i dont really think any of the younger football kids had it like we did. i dont think any of them will rock n roll with each other when they grow up, theyre missing out if they dont. i love them all. i would get naked with any of them. and its good memories...year after year. i love it. i love the gaelic too, the actual game is fantastic. i cant say enough about it.   heres a nick drake song. he was around back in the day but he died. hes got good shit though. im listening to this now: Please give me a second grace. Please give me a second face.I've fallen far down, the first time around, now I just sit on the ground in your way.Now if it's time to recompense for what's done, come, come sit down on the fence in the sun.And the clouds will roll by and we'll never deny- it's really too hard for to fly. Please tell me your second name. Please play me your second game.I've fallen so far for the people you are, I just need your star for a day.So come, come ride in my streetcar by the bayfor now I must know how fine you are in your way.And the sea sure as I, but she won't need to cry for it's really too hard for to fly.  and so i will bid you a goodnight. i know many people may not read this and i wish there was someway i could know if someone was reading this but i guess its a mystery. but to the select few in the world who bare with me...i thank you, in a very anonymous way. so thank you. and SUCK IT.   - gypsies tramps and thieves   -ps- i dig it when you have a smile on your face- van morrison 
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       hellz yea, we're at the maddie, we meaning me and maddie. so i guess once in a while i like to through a little drama into the works. i think the werks is a sandwich at potbelly. i will ask maddie she used to work there. nope she said its called the wreck. oops. crucify me why dont ya. i keed. so anyway last night was weird because we had an online fight. i dont like online fights because theyre such a little shit thing to do. usually im a huge fan of little shit things and acting like a little shit. brian and aoife always remind me of little shits with the shit they pull on everyone aka payge white. i love it. but anyway i think the drama has been sorted but nothing will change. i dont really mind because my summer has been fantastic. mainly due to the gaelic, mainly due to my homeboys. see you cant have 2 things mainly due...it doesnt make sense....but guess what...i dont care.      i wish we had more places to go. i love parties because they are fun. meeting new people is also fun sometimes. actually no, gettin 10 kinds of nasty is fun with new people. im joking its from that commercial. i heart commercials sometimes. but anyway ive decided im a cop out because i cant say what i want to say. especially if its in person especially if its important especially if its to one person. especially if it could have a bad end especially if it could have a good end especially if its trying to find out something you really dont know. most things i learn or see i could already know from somewhere else, but if youre talking to someone and youre trying to find out something you absolutely cant know from anyone else then i guess it makes it way more important. but thats weird and i sound like a freak. but again i could care less because otherwise i would erase it. ive stopped erasing alot of things. i think ive become addicted to writing this shit and getting it off of me and onto the "foggy ruins of time."       i wear green shorts. i wear white shorts. but the white shorts i wear are so much cooler than the gay white shorts that are gay. my white shorts are for athletic purposes. because white shorts are cool, when theyre not gay.      so anyway on friday today i think i will go to zulies for a keg possibly and tomorrow i will go to kyles and get drunk. i might have to drink lots of water today to make up for being dehydrated on sunday....who knows...what a dilhemma....i need a voice of reason. theresa used to be the voice of reason until she took us out drinking in the storm, then my best friend was but i dont talk to her enough for her to be the voice of reason and i wont listen to anyone past the age of 20 so i got to find a new one. if you feel as though you could be the voice of reason, ill interview you but anyway suck it goodbye.          -its me. its only me.       ps- i like rubberbands  
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       i hate being late. rhymes...rapper. it is probably one of the only things i refuse to deal with. like yesterday mary was supposed to drive us out to training and she knew this plenty of time in advance but she was taking her sweet ass time drinkin her coffee and smoking her ciggy-wiggy. what the fuck you baby, she purposely did that to piss me off. what kind of a lazy piece of fat shit cant get up off their fat ass and drive while they smoke/drink their coffee. fuck you mom. thats gay and it pisses me off. we were already 15 min late and then she had to go be an even bigger baby and pretend like she was taking me for a drug test. mom youre fucking stupid. dont even start with me. then she called me a dyke and told me that playing football wasnt normal. that was such a fucked up thing to say. i was pissed at that point so i told her that she should take some responsibility for the things she says and then she got mad. then we all laughed because she called me a dyke. i didnt even know she knew what that word meant. im never going to let her live it down. thinking about it now still pisses me off. the moms can seriously be the biggest fucking 2 yr old ever. i know i can too but atleast i realize it. then she tried to tell me that i should drive and that she shouldnt have to bring us out and she blamed my lack of drive-age on drinking too much but really its because she doesnt know how to DO FUCKING SHIT. shes so fucking unorganized and shes late for everything. get your shit together you fucking retard. wow anger wow.   anyway ive decided im ok with last times. the last time you will do something you know. i just like to know its the last time before i do it or before something happens. its never up to me to decide if its the last time or not because i never really want much of anything to end. so its never up to me its always up to someone else. like i dont even know, i wish things were somewhat normal sometimes. i wish people would say what they think because its not like i know. i dont know anything, im completely oblivious to certain things. many things. i dont fucking know.   today i woke up and i was happy. i only had about 3 hours sleep, but it wasnt too bad. it was a good time. we went to training and then we went out after because we were guna see a film but then we didnt and we went to this arcade and watched this kid play hardcore dance dance revolution. he was like a grandmaster we were amazed. his name was david. he had very little social skills. and i got 2 free dinosaurs because well im hot and we just fucked around in there for a while. then they went to go get tom and then we went to aoifes and we stayed the night and found out the yellow rangers name was trini or maybe triny maybe trina. i dont really remember. i was tired. then we slept. then i got up went to school recieved my physics grade and im here now.  haha my mom just tried to apologize. yea well mom fuck you, and suck it. you fucking cow. haha ouch im so mean. but right now i could fucking care less. wow i swore alot in this oh well.  peace love and fillet o fish.  -theresa and fiona go back today, i will miss them.       -good bye son. it wont be the last time. i promise.   ps-i apologize for the general bad mood of that chronicle i will delete it later. fuckers 
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
        Well i decided to change it up because i forgot both my username and password for the last one. So bitemybutt will live on in the archives of this little blog(hate that word) world. Much has happened to me, but not too much. I guess it depends on how you look at it. Theres alot of things like that. So i picked this address because of the song living life by ben kweller. the first words are...   "the greenest trees" youll ever see are the ones in your mind,    and all the answers and the dreams will come to you in time.      Well its a real good song and you can see some real green trees in your mind. Well anyway Since i last wrote to you the very interested viewer I entered the workforce saving lives one day at a time. i went to new york and had a great time. i contracted some stds, and drank some beers. nothing too out of the ordinary. i saw my best friend whom(is it who or whom) i havent seen in a good while. i played the gaelic. i finished physics and school. my mom came back from IRL. I saw dallas and emma and i saw other people too. i laughed i cried. two thumbs up. fuckers.      ok i dont like when you dont know what other people are thinking. everything would be easier if you silently understood something and didnt need to talk about it to figure it out. a silent understanding between two people is sometimes better than an open agreement. maybe im making it all up. anyway when people came back from new york they were all in love with the people they met there. actually just the canadians, who were good kids. its bizarre. but im not one to hate on the love because well i dont know if you know this, but reilly does. im a supporter of it, like a real supporter of any kind of real love between any group or groups of people. its like a big thing. anyway enough of that shit. ADD always wins in the end.      this summer hasnt exactly lived up to the expectations we had set for it. i dont mind much but when you look back and realize you wasted youre summer on a fat ugly mess of nothing, it kinda sucks.       i still have to buy my books for school. maybe i just wont do it. i went through all of school last yr with my math bio and history book all staying at home. i was too lazy to carry them every day because they were heavy books so eventually i just left them at the homestead. it worked out good. that was such a stupid and useless thing to tell you about. sorry. half the time i say sorry i dont mean it. i just try to get this sorted out as fast as possible when i do something wrong. i hate when things are left open ended. i always tie my shoelaces. even if they are moccasins.       a scummy thing to do is to not make someone aware of certain things that could potentially be gross. it doesnt matter how drunk you are.       ok kyle is going to canadia to visit kdawg who hes obsessed with. hes going by himself and they only met in ny for like 2 days. thats a pretty romantic thing to do. in my opinion.       so anyway ny was a good time. and my best friend goes away to school in a little while. its cool i guess. nah no guessing, its cool. i guess college is a big deal in that sense so its cool to go. ok anyway my best friend well, shes cool and stuff. like really cool. and if you think differently then thats your opinion and i reserve the right jack you in the fucking face. thank you and have a wonderful evening.    -i just call them like i see them. i wear contacts.      ps- "if peeing in your pants is cool, consider me miles davis"    
     

    



