
20,August,2004


	 
       I'm one tenth finished with my Religion Assignment! Woo! Be proud, y'all, be proud. 

18,August,2004


	 
       Yeah...i noe i noe i haven't written in, like...ages!!! but i had sooo many ass's due (damn his and geo) but im back, so yay...i guess. nothing much is new, but we got another person :P hey millie...u smell (mwah).   I tried activating my mms, like..again *rolls eyes*...it still wont work &amp; i have to have my fone off all night so they can fix it, so sorry i anyone *cough..amanda* msgd me and i didnt reply.. :(   k, im off...write back soon (i promise :P) ciao ciao, luv ya luv me, xoxox  
     

    


18,August,2004


	 
       Welcome Millie!! Our blog is growing.. *wipes tear*  Just finished my society assignment!! Have to do the annotated bibliography now.. What the heck am I gonna say? "Ooh, yes this book was very very...good. It told me a lot of things I didn't know before..."?? There really is nothing to say! And we have to write about 150 words for each source! Grrrreat. Well, I'm off like a dirty shirt. Take care, y'all. *does that smooth black guy head nodding thing*  
     

    


12,August,2004


	 
      hey its amanda here i wonder if this will work????/ 
     

    


12,August,2004


	 
       Hey guys...      How's ya? Well, here I am listening to CDs and finishing my 750g jar of  n  utella .. When I'm meant to be starting my S&amp;C assignment.. BTW, Sylv, I haven't got a copy of the Religion assessment, so could you please either photocopy it for me, or give it to me to photocopy? Thankies heaps. Dreading an essay I have to do during English tomorrow.. English has become so gay lately..am I right or am I right? Oh well, at least it's better than being at Technicorp.. *shudders at the thought*      Argh fook... I just wrecked my avatar on a forum... Photobucket resized it twice, so you'll need a frickin' microscope to see it... Fookin' hell!!!      Just wanna say have fun on your Geo excursion tomorrow, Carah, Sylv T and Millie!! And can't wait to see your pierced ears tomorrow, Kaz!!! =oD  
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       So......its the day after i invited cho to the site and made her admin......and all is calm. But wait....augh!!! she' playing "how much is that doggy in the window." ok...now its the beatles, lolz.    well toth and ruello are away...lord bless their souls....i get two frees...then i go home :D    well...i'm still waitng for the reply of kate and kaz...u joing or wat?   k, im off. ciao ciao, luv ya luv me, xoxox  
     

    


11,August,2004


	 
       Hi y'all... ©hö here... How's ya? I'm  finally  part of this blog! Now Sylv T and I are both the Admins for this blog... Should it stay that way? Or shall we all be Admins?      I seriously gotta make a start on my English essay, so I'll blog again later! Be sure to check my own personal blog too, guys ;oP  
     

    


10,August,2004


	 
       Well the Hubbo is away...yeehaa!!! so we have a free. Nothing much is happening, just trying to do some Modern Indochina stuff...Cho is trying to set up our group blog...cant wait :P....while Carah is doing her Biology assignment which is due....fifth period, lolz   well the OC was on last nite...:P i swear, im too obssessed with that show. But its not  my  fault that its such a good show, teehee   well, im off to do some more modern...i swear it takes too much of my time    ciao ciao, luv ya luv me, xoxoxox  
     

    


10,August,2004


	 
       well   hi...got maths next and i dunno wat to write...hmmm   can u ppl join and write stuff, cause i feel kinda stupid writing to meself.....iAM WRITING TO MESELF (cho said imnot)   k, the end, ciaociao, luv ya luv me xoxoxoxoxoxox  
     

    



20,August,2004


    
       
       Ooh yes. It's the weekend once again. And, boy, I am fookin' happy about it.      Just started my Religion assignment- I'm one tenth through! It's meant to be 1200 words, and I've typed 131. 

19,August,2004


    
       
       Yes I'm still bummed that my favouritest forum is on hiatus.. But there's nothing I can do, so nyehh.      My ITS teacher is away again, so I'm on a free again. Teehee. 

19,August,2004


    
       
       My favouritest forum ever is on hiatus!!!! Nooooo! And it's all because of stupid guests attacking my friends. ='o(  It kills me when my friends are upset and there's nothing I can do...      Well, it's 3pm right now... I got home 2 and a bit hours ago.. I'm so glad the Society assignment's out of the way now.. I should've started the Religion assignment when I got home, but nyehh.       OMG, the heats for the talent show are either tomorrow or next Friday.. I'm not prepared!!! I still don't know what to sing!!! *starts hyperventilating* *stops* *goes to make another ham and cheese sandwich*      *comes back* Listening to "A Day In The Sun" by Hilary Duff... I'm just remembering how much I love this album.. Even though Hil's singing ability isn't anything super-stellarly-special, I still love the tracks. *switches to Come Clean*  It's been raining lately, which is good news for those who need rain, but bad news for me. It'd be good if I could go out and dance and splash in puddles like in a movie montage, but no. *ahem*      I know this sounds so totally gross, but the scab on my face came off! I'm so happy because I can see that the wound is getting much better. I'm getting closer to having a normal face again! ("Who said your face was normal before?")      I'm gonna go. 

18,August,2004


    
       
       I finished my S&C assignment yesterday! Woo! Go me. Now onto my Religion assignment... Nyehhh.      I'm in IPT right now...The school computer network system thingo has crashed so the due date of our IPT assignment is postponed. =oD  Convenient. We have an IPT lesson  tomorrow, so I shouldn't get too excited. 

18,August,2004


    
       
       After pissing me off for several days, BlogSpot has let me blog! *raises fist triumphantly*      So what's been going on with me..? Um, I got around to starting my S&C assignment...  yesterday ! I'm gonna go home early today: 1) to get out of the subjects I hate and 2) to finish my S&amp;C assignment, which is due  tomorrow !! I hate procrastinating so much, but I really can't help it.. I'm definitely starting my religion assignment tomorrow.. (Let's see if I keep  that  promise..)  

15,August,2004


    
       
        Just watched the Olympic synchronised swimming finals.. Pretty cool sport actually.. I like it.. Especially when one of them jumps off or lands in the water before the other one/s... LOL, I'm evil.      OMG I should really start my Society assignment.. Okay, start  tomorrow . Geez, I'm hopeless.      LOL how funny are those Police Academy movies?! I love Zed..      Mahoney: "Come on, let's talk."    Zed: "I'm not in the mood! *stops* Okay, I'm in the mood! So..where are ya from??!"  XoD      I found this site bursting with Paul McCartney pics and I was like  this close  to wetting myself. He was so  hot  spankworthy 30-40 years ago... *sigh*       I'm eating the new Cadbury Dairy Milk Malt Crisp block... =o9 I was eating a pack of chocolate pretzels before..I love them because they remind me of my childhood.. ='o( *seriously needs a glass of water*      I deleted 60MB of crap from my computer! *beams with pride* And I deleted lots of stupid pics from my phone too.. But I accidentally deleted a folder full of pics of my buds..Which is a major drag... *goes off to munch on chocolate pretzels*  
      


14,August,2004


    
       
       OMG Beatles Madlibs is friggin' good fun.. XoD      Pink Gardener (sung to the tune of Paperback Writer)     Dear sir or madam will you skip my computer   It took me years to smile will you take a look?   It's based on a plug by a speaker named Kate   And I need a box so I want to be a pink gardener...pink gardener    It's a round button of a round light   And his smooth CD doesn't press   His time is working for the McDonald's   It's a steady job, but he wants to be a pink gardener...pink gardener    It's 64 flowers give or take a few   I'll be crying more in a week or two   I can make it bluer if you like the pumpkin   I can change it 'round and I want to be a pink gardener...pink gardener    If you really like it you can have the dots   It could make a mouse for you overnight   If you must sneeze it, you can spray it here,   But I need a hole and I want to be a pink gardener..pink gardener!    
      


13,August,2004


    
       
       Yup, that's what I'm listening to right now.. But not Macca's version, Roselle Nava's. I'd like to sing this for that talent thingo, but the audience would be asleep by the third note... 

13,August,2004


    
       
       Having one free today is really cool, but it'd be great if it wasn't for a subject like ITS, which is a bludge anyway. It'd be mad if my English teacher was away... But  noooooo  she can't be.      *SIGH* Well, today is Friday the 13th... I've heard that weird things can happen.. Maybe I'll get a boyfriend today? Or be offered a recording contract? 

12,August,2004


    
       
       Try this out, groovy chicks!   urlLink  http://kerrysbeatles.0catch.com/girlmadlib.html       A Girl's Letter To Her Favorite Beatles     Dear Paul,I am your Beautiful fan. I think The Beatles are the Stellarest band ever!My friend Kate thinks that George is the cutest, but I say you are much better blinking than he is. I find your blue eyes and your ugly smile and your cute little eye so attractive. And your voice - ARGH!! Your talent for eating fascinates me. How do you write such pink songs? 'Magical Mystery Tour' is my favorite. Did you write that one?Pardon me for being talk, but do you have a girlfriend? Because, if you don't, I think we'd make a really sweet couple. I know that I live in Sydney and you live all the way in Liverpool, but the magazines say you're tall rich - so you could afford lots of horse rides to come and see me. If you do have a girlfriend, I bet she's not as hard as me. I've enclosed a sexy bracelet of myself. Do you think I'm grey looking?I hope we can meet sometime and maybe have a nice time swimming.      Embarrassingly yours,    Camille   XOXOXO   
      


11,August,2004


    
       
       Listening to the WAV of Michelle... Paul McCartney singing in French... =o9      Quite funny actually- Michelle from my math class is right in front of me! Now I'm listening to And I Love Her... All the Beatles songs were so sweet back in the 60s...      Listening to Boys again.... So suss... OMG, I have nothing to blog about! And I have like 5 minutes left!! I really should be doing my Society essay about Personal Reflection.. But nyehh.      Hold Me Tight... *sigh sigh sigh sigh*      OMG I seriously can't talk about anything... I don't even have any Useless Camille facts! *overdramatic gasp* I'm gonna sign out...  
      


11,August,2004


    
       
       I've got Do You Want To Know A Secret by The Beatles in my head... But it's okay because it's a good song ;o)       Listun...do you wunt to know a seecrit...         *squeal* I love the 60s stuff. I wanna go back in time and scrump Paul McCartney. *goes into daydream mode*      *snaps back* Ah...that was nice. I have a free next! Woohoo! My Math teacher is away... there are like, ten teachers away today.. Must've all been on the same diseased bus or something... 

11,August,2004


    
       
        I am SO pissed off! I had typed up so much before, ready to publish, but then when I highlighted it, all the text disappeared!  GRR...      Oh well, I'll try to make up for it here...      The OC was so good last night! I'm slowly becoming a Summer/Seth 'shipper.. They're not bad together at all..quite cute really. =o/  Next week, Anna Stern comes back and the Summer/Seth/Anna triangle continues... Having to wait one week sucks... OMG Julie Cooper is a cow! I know she's just a character, but if I ever see the actress who plays her on the streets (when I go to the US, nyahh) I'll probably end up whacking her with my handbag or whatever I'm holding.      My bud Jess just showed me some pics of a guy called Blue..yes that's his real name.. My verdict: he is very cute. 

10,August,2004


    
       
       So how does green look? Just waiting for The OC to come on.. I'll be waiting for another half hour, so I thought I might blog for a bit.      Two things are pissing me off: MSN Messenger and BlogSpot. MSN wont let me send IMs, and BlogSpot isn't helping with the group blog that my buds and I want to set up. B-E-A-U-TIFUL.      I'm listening to John Lennon's Imagine ATM... Such a great song. *switches to a different song* Now I'm listening to 'Boys'... Great song too, but why the hell didn't they change it to 'Girls'? Makes Ringo sound...funny.      Guess what I found today? The CD single of Savage Garden's I Knew I Loved You! I can't escape that song! I hear it on the radio and everything  all the time ! 

09,August,2004


    
       
       In Info Tech Support right now... Still glad to be back at school...    I'm pissed because the invitation Sylv sent me (to join her blog) won't work..     (Note to self: ask her to send the invitation  again .)       Kate's behind me trying to set up her own blog, and Anna's on another computer doing...God knows what.      I'm slowly coming to terms with the fact that I don't have a chance with * whisper Mark whisper *. Sad... But I'm training myself to think about him less and less.. It's kinda working.. NOT. ='o{      BlogSpot isn't working for Kate and Anna...for some reason. *gives blogspot.com the evil eye*   This is just  great . Pushes us one more step back from being able to set up our group blog...Grr. 

09,August,2004


    
       
       My religion teacher's away, so I'm in a seminar room in the library ATM... =o

09,August,2004


    
       
       Hm... I'm kinda upset because Ngaiire didn't get through to the next round of Australian Idol.. but it's cool 'cause she'll probably come back for the Wildcard show... =oD      OMG I nearly finished a whole block of Hazelnut Cadbury.. But that's good- it'll bring me closer to 50kilos... 4 more kilos! I hate being 46kilos so much... And my weight is never constant.. Nyehhh.       I have like, 3 assessments.. Religion, Info Processes Tech and Society & Culture... GRRREAT.      For Religion, it's comparing and contrasting bloody religions  again ..just like the last assessment we got. Honestly, where's the variety in things?     For IPT, we have to advertise something (yes I told you about that in my last post)      And for S&amp;C, we gotta compare Vietnam and Australia.  FUN.        The OC's on tomorrow, yay! Adam Brody...spankworthy and spunkilicious. =o9  I dunno, Ben McKenzie (is that his name? Y'know who I mean- the guy who plays Ryan) just doesn't do anything for me... =oP  Especially with that stupid sideways face thing he does! Honestly! Take a drink each time he does it in one episode, and you're drunk by the end. Along with Summer's EWs... And all the bikinis at the parties... And Jimmy Cooper's sighs... I love The OC drinking game! LOL... but no, I don't consume any alcohol, and I doubt I ever will. (There's a useless fact for ya.)      Useless Camille Fact #284:  I always fall for the wrong guys.   
      


08,August,2004


    
       
       In IPT right now... Gonna start an assignment... We have to create some advertising campaign thingo... I want to promote my 'band'... 

08,August,2004


    
       
       I feel like blogging again... I really want to go back to that supermarket to see if  he  is still working there.. I was like, a 5 minute drive away from that supermarket last night... Went to visit my newest cousin.. She's a few months old and she's such a cutie. Very talkative, like her cousin. 

07,August,2004


    
       
       Okay, the last time I saw 'him' was not two years ago!! *gasps overdramatically at what she has just remembered* I remember now! My family and I went to The Philippines last year.. and we bought lots of packets of M&M's and blocks of Cadbury's (as heaps of Filipino-Australians do when they plan to go to The Phils.. quality chocolate and stuff is apparently expensive over there, so we bring 'pasalubong' for our Filipino relatives)... I remember my mom and I went to that supermarket at like, 10PM! And he served us... and he was really nice, I could've melted on the friggin' supermarket floor.. And he wished us well and aahhh... So that was one week before we left for The Phils... October! So the last time I saw him before the party was...*counts on fingers*.. OMG 10 MONTHS AGO?!!  I wish I could remember these things on demand, and not so spontaneously...  
      


07,August,2004


    
       
       My internet connection is being stupid... It's disconnecting me after, like, 18ish minutes. And after that, it takes 4 attempts before it actually connects... I hate dial-up so much. I don't think I'll afford broadband for another five decades. I have a few assignments.. But I can't be bothered doing them now... Can you blame me??      Just listening to some Filipino music now... I miss The Philippines quite a bit. All the great music, food, hot weather... But I don't miss the cold showers. =o  Hot water heaters are quite pricey over there (apparently), so I didn't really have a choice. But at least I saved water. My showers were like, 3 minutes max over there... Here, mine are like, 15 minutes max.. Which is horrible because we have water restrictions. Nyehh.. =oS         Loving you...woah...is such an easy thing to do...No, you never know...it's driving me crazy 'cause it grows and grows..But I won't let it stop, no I'm not giving up..Loving you..just a bit too much..         *double-clicks internet icon*  Wow! I've been connected for 27 minutes! Hope it stays.. If not, then I'm gonna call my ISP and abuse whoever answers. With my singing ;oP         Foolish heart, hear me calling...stop before you start falling... Foolish heart, heed my warning... you've been wrong before, don't be wrong anymore...      
      


07,August,2004


    
       
        Okay... Where do I begin? I got a truckload to write about... So I'll just stick to what's on my mind ATM.      Today was my last day of work placement.. At a place called Technicorp.. Sounds swanky enough, but it was a surprisingly very small office. They had like, what, 4 computers there? But it was alright- if it gets me out of school for a week, it's cool with me. The Manager there hardly gave a rat's ass about me.. I'd just stand there and ask politely- "So what am I going to do today?" or "So what should I do now?" and a couple of times, he'd just grunt and that'd be it. Then I'd go off into the other room ( with a TV, radio and scotch...didn't take advantage of free liquor- DANG ) and just do some 'data entry' ( i.e Copy and Paste ). Well I'm glad it's over: I've missed my friends too much.      I've been thinking about this guy I saw last Saturday... Let me fill you in. I've 'known' him for a couple of years now.. He worked at the supermarket near my Nan's place, and whenever we'd do groceries for her, he'd be there... serving me and my Mom at the counter, or bumping into him at any random aisle... Yet I never knew his name.. I don't know why I never noticed his nametag... Nyeh weird me. Anyhoo, yeah, turns out his mom is like the bestie of this lady my mom used to work with and is great buds with. And that lady's 50th birthday party was last Saturday...and I kinda knew he'd be there, so I kinda tried to make myself look spankworthy, but of course, all I can manage is a decent look. Nyehh. So my family and I got to the venue of the party.. and we just sat, waiting for the party to start. (It was a swanky kinda thing- with performances and stuff, not just an eat and run kinda thing..) and I was fiddling with my nametag on the table- kinda funny really..here's a pic:   Then I looked up, and  there he was . And at that moment, the DJ played "I Knew I Loved You"... I know, I know, it's pathetic as all heck, but to me it was the sweetest.. I gave myself a mission to get his phone number by the end of the party, but I failed miserably. I kept looking at him the whole time to see if we could make eye contact somehow... and we did a few times, but I guess he was just looking at whoever was behind me or next to me at the time. Then at the end, when he got up to leave I smiled and waved at him, and he smiled and waved back. I doubt he even remembers who I am.. He must've been like "Okay..some weird chick is just smiling and waving at me, so I'll just smile and wave back...WHO  IS  SHE?!"   So I'm hoping I come across someone else who knows him.. Like, a degrees-of-separation kinda thing.. Filipinos have a crapload of links to people (especially in the Woodcroft area). I really want to ask the birthday celebrant lady (she's really sweet) for his number, but that'd just be wrong.. And what if he has a girlfriend already? *SIGH* Just so my buds know who I'm talking about... I had a look at his nametag, and his name's Mark. (Forgive me, if you ever read this, Mark.)      Anyways... My voice is getting much better and I'm glad. I've had a cold for about a week, and the Year 11 heats for this school talent quest I'm gonna enter are on next week.. I'm still thinking about what to sing..      My choices:       Only Hope - Mandy Moore       Heaven - Nina       Foolish Heart - Nina       Jealous - Nina (Can you tell that I like Nina's songs?)       Open - Roselle Nava       Breathe - Michelle Branch       Just Believe - Sarah Geronimo       So yeah.. I need something sweet and simple, with just an added high note to impress my poor audience.. Any suggestions??    I'm majorly bummed that my favouritest forum ever is gone... It was called Rubberneckin' Dhani Harrison Forum and the maddest people were on there... We had like, 88 members, and I had nearly 500 posts!! Seriously bummed!! Anyways, we were all pretty strong buds on that forum, so hopefully Rubberneckin's Creator will create a stellar Rubberneckin' Version 2.0?? *wink*    Well I'd better set my profile and stuff... 


