
22,August,2004


     
      Today my eyes pop out leh...OUCH so pain...all my sis(.audrey.) fault hhorrrr? haiz...jkjk  when i am all alone at home for the whole day so most of the time so i will hu si luan xiang(anihow think), haha...i will think of the past where my cousins(only 4 of us at that time) will gathered at my grandma house. when i was in pri 1(i very cute de :

21,August,2004


     
      wa lau...today a math so difficult...then 1hour only how to finish? :c die liao....haha go to sch 4 1hour only...teacher very wu liao leh...haiz...:(  ------

20,August,2004


     
      let me see...  MuMMy: =miss HaizA= =EsTher= =meLisA= =wAn tinG= =sHi hUi= =yIn fOOng= DaDDy: {Han qiNg} {adeLinE (cum naNny)}  LaO gOng: *pOlly* *HarFizAh* *shI Yi*       lAo Po: +WeI qUin(cum penguin)+ +pOh LinG+ +bErniCe+  siStEr: ~auDrey~ ~Jolyne~ ~iVy~ ~cHai tiNg~ ~Lydia~ ~deNiSe~ ~qIu Yu~ ~SeRene~ ~chU er~ ~coNNie~ ~Pei sHi~ ~yUan XuaN~ brother: yEE hoAu . Jun minG . cHe Hao . Jia yI . jEssiCa (she is a girl la...)  dAUghTEtr: -ShErLyn- -aZiZaH- sOn: _hUda_(she oso girl hor)  not forgetting my 2 wonderful grandmother... [cAren] [sHeila] # opps...those who i forgot to write down...sorry lolx #
     
    


19,August,2004


     
      today i hold my lao po(.poh ling.) de hand and purposely let my sis(.audrey.) see...then she so jealous worx...haha...very funny...then must say sorry to my lao ma(.esther.) coz i nv pei her go home and forgot to pass the letter to her..pai seh...dun be angry le la abt both me and her...cool down...first time go home with my sis(.lydia.) today...haha  didn't know my sis(.audrey.) got such good taste...know how to watch the matching making show...the show really very de nice...lolx one day i gonna kill my lao ma(.esther.) for spreading rumour abt me and my father-in-law...wa lau...tml got a-math test...  -breaKing The hAbit- by LINKIN PARK (very nice leh)
     
    


19,August,2004


     
      haha the matching drama very nice and super funny worx...that show make up my 45mins of laughters...lolx :p   lesson learnt today... -people are selfish- -adults alway lie-
     
    


16,August,2004


     
      I pass my A math leh...wat a surprise xia...haha maybe teacher mark wrongly coz i really thought i would fail somemore when teacher collect paper that time i still check answer with my lao po(.poh ling.) then we got different answers...lucky i pass...phew...  today melisa gave me a sweet..haha so sweet and nice of her...lolx unlike someone...saw rachel after sch...she change hairstyle liao...haha esther went mad and piniched her cheek...so ke lian...haiz...nitz   =chemistry suckz=
     
    


13,August,2004


     
      Amongst all my sisters and brothers hor, she is the most nasty one and she is a big bully. Knew her through my lao po(.poh ling.)-dun jealous :p haha ok la...i admit i copy and paste de...aniway whose no. ar? 9008992 u anyhow write one huh?    firstly hor...i know u meh?(this is her favourite line) n hor i NOT les lor...dun get me into trouble...later everyone think i les then i die liao...i will pull u down into the water(read in chi) haiz...dun noe how come i know u...the most bhb and lame sis hor? =) lolx...jk la...this sis very gong one and very nice to bully...haha but she hit ppl...actually only me coz she biased de...very pain lor(i regret letting esther know her, now they 2 gang up and bully me then my sis here still can act victim worx...) then she oso like to act cute and act young...haha though she is a lao ah ma liao...   WARNING: [this paragraph is to praise her or else later she will kill me de so...no choice. =

11,August,2004


     
      haha yesterday saw penguin during recess...then i tickle her but she nv scold me then she laugh...coz she got A2 for chinese...glad for her coz her oral was like...erm...haha not so good la. then i went to find sec 4 de...polly got A1 for chinese and her oral not merit but DISTINCTION leh...sure or not? somemore she said english during oral lor...wa lau, the examiner must be see her cute then forgot to deduct her marks...haha but so happy they got good result. well done worx. i forgot to ask jolyne and the rest(hope they did well too)...oops...nvm then hor i lent my sis the math set then she BEAT me worx...wang en fu yi...haiz... :p   yesterday first time sit with XL in class during chinese EXTRA lesson...she ar really very funny lor...though she always act fierce but she really very scared to offend ppl...haha yoz...me going to kaakyakingg (dun noe how to spell...) on september...is red cross and scout together so esther must be very de happy...hor?   today...not so fun coz i fail chemistry again...haiz i think i wanna drop it liao...someone got B3 for chinese, u can do it de so dun be sad hor...jia you!!! on sunday is my mummy(.miss haiza.) b'dae...haha she ar...coz i nv underline properly female or male in the consent form then she asked if i am boy or girl LOUDLY...nvm suan liao...haha 
     
    


11,August,2004


     
      hmmm..let me see...wa lau...the outcome of not studying is FAIL..haha geog must remember so many thingy de(my brain small)...then the test gave questions thet must think out of the box so....suan liao...zhi yu say that we common test must get about 34 to pass...funny xia...so i must add a lot a lot of oil!  today got assembly, when we sat at the corner then the first thing i saw was penguin (.wei quin.) then she purposely give me that kind of "so unlucky" face -.-'''...wa lau she good...then miss yee talk abt our sec 3 camp...must pay $65??? crazy ar? national camp only $30 then we still go pulau ubin lor and got so many thingy...the sec 3 camp is like dun know go where...erm haha  after school, my sis(.joyne.) drink bubble tea in sch then nv buy one 4 me de...somemore set bad example 4 me...haiz but i will forgive her de coz she shared it with me =)...haha then the other sis(.audrey.) SMOKE leh...haiz...i must tell her to quit smoking, it is bad 4 ur health lor...jk la...that is another person with similar name...phew...got bullied :x by someone(.chai ting.) worx...wa lau...she ar...haiz nothing to say liao...ohhh still got my lao gong(.polly.)...she fever, u better rest more hor...then so ke lian pester by esther k.s.m-i miss esther so much...during the holidays, no one screming tsunnammi(how 2 spell ar?) and all that stuff...oops then hor denise oso not feeling well, must take care...  today so lucky leh got a chance to eat with my father...haha but we still dun talk so much bcoz either he is at work or i am at home so very little time together...becoz i dun have the camp thingy so he showed more concern but i think he is the last person to know that my camp thingy is cancelled...haha me go watch tv liao...the show is super nice and funny... :p        -accidentally in love-
     
    


09,August,2004


     
      HAPPY 39th BIRTHDAY SiNGAPORE!  our pledge:  I, the citizen of singapore, pledge myself to strike regardless of TOTO or 4D, based on quick pick and system 7 so as to achieve car, cash and condo.  haha...lame la~ today is the first time i sang the national anthem and said the pledge so loudly in my secondary school life..haha coz in sch we like sleep through it de lor...then in primary school we sang loudly then we got scolded for shouting...haiya the teachers all so troublesome de...today, the NDP was great! the fireworks were very beautiful and the preformance was splendid! the kallang wave oso very fun! though my ears hurt when we sang songs coz ppl were sccreeaming...i drank too much coffee so like not tired like that but some of the performances were like the SYF...heehee   at nitz, got one bhb and a little bit oso not cute and not nice de ah ma cum piggy "pulled" my leg worx...very pain lor! hor...u noe who u r la...nitz! zzz...
     
    


08,August,2004


     
      suddenly tot of fuhua...haha i oso dun why my mum choose this school so after the PSLE i had to choose btw jurong and fuhua, but jurong too old le and fuhua too young le...haha whatever la but in the end i still went to fuhua.  in fuhua, everything was so different from rulang. maybe bcoz i have different friends, different teachers, different subjects and different CCA.  sec 1...quite boring...i met sheila and caren coz they are in charge of our class during sec 1 orientation...both of them always bullied by us (1C)-me still shy so nv talk much, lolx then other than eng,chi,math and sci the other subjects were all average so my mum forced me to have tution...haiz...and my mum want me to join red cross dun noe for wat so my first choice is rc la...the training was tough lor and i want to quit many many time...the seniors all so fierce during the camp...sobsob but it was very fun and i learnt alot...i nv talk to them before..haha opps i forgot to say...mr loh is our form teacher he ar...a good teacher. at the end of the year, one of the teacher treated us pizza but i forgot who liao =

07,August,2004


     
      yoz! coz my sis (audrey) want me to practise engalissh (english) so here i am lor...but hor i dun know wat to write leh..today not very good mood la, coz cannot go to the camp quite pity but at least i found out that surprisingly some people who alway bully me actually an wei me leh...can't believe it...haha jk la... :p  then today me n abigail met at kembegan then we go explore the shopping centre...very quiet de so eerie..haha then we went to the campsite n everything went so smoothly...want bus got bus, want train got train...then we reached the campsite le hor, we saw abt 3 ppl waiting then the gate is locked...i got a bad feeling but we still wait then more ppl came...then so suai we really came to the wrong place for briefing...wa lau!!! so we were told to fly to "dobby got"...  when one is unlucky ar...want train miss train then suddenly the train move so slow...then the traffic light all red de...haiz...when we reached there then they told us we are reserve and this briefing we dun need to come then she took our attendence...huh, for wat? me and abigail cursed mrs kim :x...but realli very fun lor...run there run here just bcoz we got a blur teacher in charge...damm it. :C
     
    



