
20,August,2004


	 
      arr me harties eat drink and be merry for tomarrow you may  be chased into a ditch and stabbed to death by angry hobbos  damn those hobbos DAAAAMMN THEEEMMMM *shakes his fist in rightous fury* now lets watch them fight for small amounts of cash  urlLink www.bumfight.com  haha silly hobbos 
    


14,August,2004


	 
      Destiny is a game, is it not? And now you await my latest move ~kain 
    


13,August,2004


	 
      Ok I don't understand why people like this movie so much.  It's about a poor dude who meets this stuck up bitch on a boat and he winds up smashin her.  For some strange reason, she dumps her future million dollar husband to try and get with some poor guy who plays violin and draws pictures of naked chicks.  In the end, he just dies.  Now she is stuck with nothing but a shitty old necklace which she winds up tossing in the ocean after about 60 years lata.  I find this movie to be quite gay and the picture is a good way to describe my thoughts on it, and the boat itself. .  .  .  .  .  urlLink      urlLink   urlLink   urlLink   
    


12,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    here ill add to the fuckin kiss stuff lol&nbsp; urlLink   
    


12,August,2004


	 
      Now i bet u didnt know he was a fan eh?&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


12,August,2004


	 
      Wow Kiss make up really can do wonders! &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


12,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    this one goes out to the doctor  urlLink    
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    WHAT IS A JUGGALO?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yum.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    He-He! It's Dykey-Poo! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
    


11,August,2004


	 
       Hand of fate is moving and finger points to you  He knocks you to your feet and so what are you gonna do  Your tongue has frozen now you've got something to say  The piper at the gates of dawn is calling you his way  You watch the world exploding every single night   Dancing in the sun a new born in the light  Say goodbye to gravity and say goodbye to death  Hello to eternity and live for every breath  Your time will come Your time will come  The ferryman wants his money you ain't going to give it back  He can push his own boat as you set up off the track  Nothing you can contemplate will ever be the same  Every second is a new spark, sets the universe aflame  You watch the world exploding every night  Dancing in the sun a new born in the light  Brothers and their fathers joining hands and make a chain  The shadow of the Wicker Man is rising up again  Your time will come Your time will come   ~Iron Maiden Wicker man~ 
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    he he he.... boobies
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    my god balsac  urlLink     a pic from GWAR.net 
    


11,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    love metal  just testing this pic post shit, seems to work. and just for morons and copy write shit this is HIM His, Infernal, Majesty 
    


11,August,2004


	 
      Testng TwiztedMajik is a queerbait 
    


11,August,2004


	 
      yo yo yooooo... this is just a test so see if this shit works!!! 
    


11,August,2004


	 
       welcome to our nightmare you can only veiw this  because we dont give a shit and neither should you so read comment and enjoy         p.s. zeromancer rocks  
    



