
23,August,2004


	 
       Phewwwww... back to school again! in the morning, i felt kinda frustrated! especially to those heavy stuffs! i just could not understand why students have to carry such heavy load! :( anyway, today in school, i seldom talk. it's kinda lazy to talk. The amazing thing was that i didin't eat in recess time... hehehe.. see??? how lazy i am until i have no appetite to eat. Prelim is just this coming friday and i haven't really do an important thing, which is to revise! ohhhwwwww man! i can't imagine what will happen to me... hope miracles come again!    In da evening around 8pm +++ i went out to have dinner with my bro! drian! hehe.. he seemed to be quite moody as that bastard came and joined us.. his name is *e*** (tooottttt e toooootttt) hehe... and my bro seemed to me recalling his past. his bad mamories with that bitch that he used to like! what a sad thing to remember! it's ok.. i will always be there for u bro! cheer up ok? hehe. and hopefully by this thursday. u can start a new chapter with ya lovely ex-gf. i will pray for ya success! u really rox my day today.. u told me a love story.. it's between u and her.. it's kinda cool! u are such a faithful dude! keep it up.. try to make "the notebook 2" (but leave the sex part behind ok? huahuahuahua) hehe.. all da best! hehe.. and for me.. i will wait..... till the one show up! ;)   
    


22,August,2004


	 
      Woke up this morning at 7 am man! I am deadly tired! All for my CrUzAdErZ! hehe.. it's my team's game today against OrLeAnDeR! hehe. da score was.... 4:2 CrUZ won! yeah baby.. hehe... and after that.. i went to eat with some of my team players in da foodcourt located in KK hospital. The place is very lovely.. i mean the scenery. i like it a lot.. but the food.. it's moderate and the drinks... SUkX.. especially the home made barly.. it's so sweet and made me felt yuKkIe! hehe.. after that i went to MiLcHeL 

20,August,2004


	 
       Yo.. this morning gotta wake up early as i was having a maths DRP ( from 8 - 10 ) & english course... but i didin't attend it! i was in da bad mood all of a sudden and with no reason! wad a stupid me! hehe.. went home after that and guess wad? i went to sleep? oh man.. it was really very rare that i sleep in the afternoon.. hehe..    after that i woke up and i went to catch movie with : Andrian, Randy, Alvet, Banet, Fendy, Firman, Botakx, Richard, Andy, Andrew, Eric, Aditz. It was Alien VS Predators (did i sleep wrongly???) hehe.. and it's kinda funny in the end... People said that the movie sukx to da corner but i will give it 6.5/10 for da rating.. hehe.. not that bad.. ;)    after that i went to Anita's birthday party (just next to United Square  ) hehe.. and it's kinda quiet at first but.. after that.. people start to come in.. the party was quite fun but i am sad about one thing.. i realised that **************** let's forget about it.. i just wanna forget bout bad memories and remember the good ones.. hehe.. so after that i moved on to watch soccer match at U.S. with Randy, Alvet, Fendy, Banet, Shin Shuo and another guy whom i don't really know him.. hehehe.. and after that i went home..       Tomorrow, I believe, will be a great day too.. good nite honey... ^o^ cup cup cuit cuit muackz!   
    


20,August,2004


	 
       Wuah.. today is a very freaking cool day for me! I'm Lovin It.. huahuahua.. ok let's start.. ;)    In school, in da morning.. i wrote an essay.. a short one actually.. hehe.. i don't know why i am suddenly changing... i like english a lot now.. hehe.. after that.. a maths.. i am so in love with that subject! i am begining to get a live in a maths lessons.. hehe.. and after that. the boring phys lesson.. making me ill and sleepy.. don't know why... wad can i do about it? hehe.. who cares... hehe... and e maths lessons.. it's always like a free lesson.. hehe.. after that.. there was a short monitor's meeting.. opzz i remembered that i have to buy things for teachers.. a pile of colourful pieces of paper.. it's to wipe my ass.. huahuahua.. jkjk... no offence.. neway... after that... my teeth... DI BOR TAU GA! NGILU

19,August,2004


	 
       Yo.. today.. erm in school... as usual... but when i was in ava room.. someone played the piano.. owwwww man.... suddenly i thought of my TF.. hehe... the way she play that damn thing! i like the tune of piano a lot! hee.. by the way.. the maths test.. i hope i can get a good mark for it! ;) hehe.. when comes to math DRP - the first hour.. i am so serius.. after that.. huahuahua.. u know me lahhhhhhh hehe... i can't concentrate anymore.. and u know wad? my class made a really stupid list and guess wad i am? i am the mayor in the powerpuff girls.. isn't that awful? huahuahua. but.. it's damn funny.. i laugh till bloated! hehe..    neway... i didin't go da night study as i was having my eng tuition.. hehe.. guess wad? the whole eng tuition.. i was chit chatting.. but not learning.. wad the hell man? hehehe.. i was chit chatting about the riot.. the indonesian-chinese riot that went on a few years back.. it's kinda sad to recall those memories.. if not that riot.. by now.. i can't speak english and i will not be in s'pore.. but.. bcoz of that riot.. it brought me here.. to a place where i am new to everyone... hehe.. but in da same time.. it's kinda cool.. hehe.. at last.. i am speaking english right now.. hehe.. cool eh? from... 'apple' , 'chair' , 'milk' to... NOW ... huahuahua..    Oppzz i almost forget.. on da 9 of August.. it's my lilo's bday... i forget about it.. wad a shame of myself.. feel like slapping my face.. throwing myself down from 12th floor and kissing my own ass... huahuahua.. how can i do that? hehe.. neway.. in my heart.. i wanna wish her.. HaPPy BeLaTeD BiRtHdAy.. HoPeFuLLy I CaN ChEEr HeR Up By ******** let's see wad will i do later on then.. hehe..     Neway.. after talking to my half best bud just now.. i am abit cheerful.. at last.. the year before this.. we were so close together.. until this year where i have my own world and she has hers.. but.. right now i try to combine our worlds together again.. hope it works.. it's been suck a long time seem i spoke to my TF.. where are u my TF? wad are u doing? i wonder.. hehe.. neway.. all of ya will always be in my heart.. forever ok? hehe. promise! hehe..     I WaNNa SLeeP.. NiTe NiTe My CuTiE PiE DiArY... MuAcKx ^o^      
    


18,August,2004


	 
       Today.. it's just an ordinary day to me.. i felt no unique things happened to me.. hehe.. neway... i knew one thing that change.. which is the countdown to my prelim.. i am such a freak! i haven't even start revising.. and all i can do is to wait.. wad the hell man?????? I can't let this happen to me.. i don't wanna make the same mistake again.. which is to regret over wad i had done.. so.. MikeL... buck up biatch! hehe.. neway.. i am so sleepy, but still have homeworks... wad shall i do????? i don't care.. i just wanna sleep.. 3... 2... 1... ZzZzZzZ ;)  
    


17,August,2004


	 
       Yo... todae i just created this thing.. hehehe.. i got the inspiration from tRaCeS.. all thank's to her.. hehe.. today... lotsa people grow old.. hehe... Alvet (17 yr old), Daisy (18 yr old), Anita (16 yr old), amoz (16 yr old)... SO MANY! hehe... cool.. wish all of ya heppie!!!      Neway, today was a long day for me.. but, i have fun.. In P.E lesson today.. my class played baseball again! hehe.. it was a very exciting game indeed.. hehe.. i hit the ball as far as i can and the ball flew quite a distance.. hehe.. which is close to homerun.. hehe.. feeling happy to have the ability to hit so far.. all thankz to my primary school in jakarta, for teaching me such game! and.. today i had 3 tests all together.. 2 school tests and 1 O'LeVeL' one... it's so scary... ieuwwwwwww.... hehehe ( note : i like to say the word 'ieuwwwwwwwwwwww' ) my geo test was ok but my chem test 


