

21,May,2004


     
      This is going to be the last post for at least a couple weeks. The reason being is that we are going on a cruise to alaska for around 12 days.
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Im getting all packed up for the trip tommorow!
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      I just got back a hour ago!
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      I just woke up today!
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      this is it   Disgruntled-with-Tech-Support asks: "Let's face it: At some point or another, we've had to deal with some form of tech support. Quite often, it's a hit-or-miss experience depending on the level of support required. Occasionally, strange, bizarre, or nonsensical explanations result from the problems reported, such as this one: I had just had DSL installed, only to find it much slower than the 56K line I was looking to get rid of. On calling the provider, I was told (by someone who likely reading off cue cards) to visit one of their internal websites for measuring bandwidth. While there, I observed that they had both bytes per second and bits per second listed, and that the number of bytes/sec != bits/sec * 8, rather a factor around 13 or 14. I pointed this out as a possible problem, and the guy's reasoning: 'Uh, it looks like the bytes are getting through to you ok, but the bits are getting stuck someplace.' What was your worst explanation from tech support?"Disgruntled-with-Tech-Support asks: "Let's face it: At some point or another, we've had to deal with some form of tech support. Quite often, it's a hit-or-miss experience depending on the level of support required. Occasionally, strange, bizarre, or nonsensical explanations result from the problems reported, such as this one: I had just had DSL installed, only to find it much slower than the 56K line I was looking to get rid of. On calling the provider, I was told (by someone who likely reading off cue cards) to visit one of their internal websites for measuring bandwidth. While there, I observed that they had both bytes per second and bits per second listed, and that the number of bytes/sec != bits/sec * 8, rather a factor around 13 or 14. I pointed this out as a possible problem, and the guy's reasoning: 'Uh, it looks like the bytes are getting through to you ok, but the bits are getting stuck someplace.' What was your worst explanation from tech support?"
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Wind does this thing not work?
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Disgruntled-with-Tech-Support asks: "Let's face it: At some point or another, we've had to deal with some form of tech support. Quite often, it's a hit-or-miss experience depending on the level of support required. Occasionally, strange, bizarre, or nonsensical explanations result from the problems reported, such as this one: I had just had DSL installed, only to find it much slower than the 56K line I was looking to get rid of. On calling the provider, I was told (by someone who likely reading off cue cards) to visit one of their internal websites for measuring bandwidth. While there, I observed that they had both bytes per second and bits per second listed, and that the number of bytes/sec != bits/sec * 8, rather a factor around 13 or 14. I pointed this out as a possible problem, and the guy's reasoning: 'Uh, it looks like the bytes are getting through to you ok, but the bits are getting stuck someplace.' What was your worst explanation from tech support?"
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Im trying to post some more information on the windows section of this page!
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Like i said a few posts back, this is the "Last" post for tonight, i dont know why....
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      This is a post for sure!
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      Just another post before I goto bed for the night.
     
    


20,May,2004


     
      This is the first post in my new blog! I hope i can get it now!
     
    


16,June,2004


     
      : "I'm tired of HD failures. I've suffered through a few of them. Even with backups, they are still a pain to recover from. I've got all fairly inexpensive but reliable hardware picked out, but I'm just not sure which RAID level to implement. My goals are to build a file server that can live through a drive failure with no loss of data, and will be easy to rebuild. Ideally, in the event of a failure, I'd just like to remove the bad hard drive and install a new one and be done with it. Is this possible? How many drives to I need to get this done, 2,4 or 5? What size should they be? I know when you implementddddd RAID, your usable drive space is N% of the total drive space depending on the RAID level."
     
    


06,June,2004


     
      hi, this is it for now.
     
    


05,June,2004


     
      pops popss popsss
     
    


04,June,2004


     
      asdasdasd
     
    


04,June,2004


     
      We just got back!
     
    



