
30,June,2004


	 
       urlLink     Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince ?!?
     
    


29,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Katie Holmes knows how to make that detective sing!
     
    


29,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Robert Downey, Jnr: An amazing actor, even if the  Singing Detective  film was all it could be!
     
    


29,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Opens June 30th.  Looks kewl.
     
    


27,June,2004


	 
       urlLink     A Page of Madness  - Japanese Film, 1926.  A special event at Revelation, Sat. 10th July 2004: 9pm.
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Revelation - Perth International Film Festival - http://www.revelationfilmfest.org/
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Touching the Void ... one hell of a docudrama!
     
    


24,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Joss Whedon's first feature film is blogging!
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    the fabulous duo, new batchannel, new battime!
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    a new look, a new team
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    An oldie, but a goodie.
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Drinksafe warning: you'll be burping for days.
     
    


20,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    For Australians, releases July 29th.  (In the US June 25th.)
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    http://www.fahrenheit911.com/
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    So animated ...
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    So fierce ...
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    So cute...
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yeti Sports 5 ...
     
    


17,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Has Keira been watching too much Braveheart??
     
    


16,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    0.9 is so slick, so pretty, so STABLE! :)
     
    


14,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    When photoshop goes wrong!
     
    


14,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hermione ... bad boys always get punished!
     
    


12,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Firefly on DVD in Australia ... finally.
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Laser 
     
    


07,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Best 404 ever.
     
    


06,June,2004


	 
      I've been playing with the new  urlLink Hello PhotoBlogging Tool  which allows those of us using Blogger to post  and host  pictures (albeit within in fairly specific size parameters).  Here's a quick test, capturing the storm-tossed Sunday I can see from my back window:  urlLink    Although  urlLink Blogger  still doesn't officially host files other than the text and templates of blogs, this new service has no obvious limits in terms of photos, so it's certainly a step toward Blogger freely hosting more than just text! 
     
    


06,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    28 Days Later
     
    


06,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Nietzsche: Sip on these ideas!
     
    


06,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    The cover to LIMINA volume 10.    
     
    


31,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    dannybot?!?
     
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Will makes a new friend.
     
    


24,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    more than meets the eye
     
    


22,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    William Gibson, bridging the future, living the interstitial.  Chronicle Photo by Sam Deaner.
     
    


20,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    cray like a rupert?
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    it's here!
     
    


17,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ... with no Camelot, no affair, no Holy Grail, but with lots and lots of nasty Saxons! :P
     
    


14,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The Invisible Woman ... perhaps Sarah Michelle Gellar?
     
    


11,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Think about it.
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink     A Page of Madess , so far ahead of its time! ( urlLink Details )
     
    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The world wide web told me so:  urlLink http://www.johnhowardlies.com/ .
     
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Movie posters are always edited, but this one seems to be  urlLink raising a few eyebrows .
     
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Topical: http://www.theaustralian.news.com.au/common/story_page/0,5744,10042844%255E12332,00.html
     
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Sometimes, I wonder how serious things can be on the set of a moiton picture ...  the  FireFly  filming looks fun!
     
    


05,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jennifer Garner's new look for the Elektra film (spunoff from the very average DareDevil feature) looks very promising.  More like the look from the Frank Miller comics... 
     
    


03,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Spider-Man 2 - cool, complex and compelling!
     
    


05,August,2004


	 
       urlLink     urlLink Guess who's back? 
     
    


03,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Who said political satire couldn't have big explosions?
     
    




