
25,August,2003


     
      Am back in Reading...  Joy of joys...  Scott and Christine's wedding went well and it was fairly baking weather.  I wasn't quite all there there though and spent a while on the phone to Graça.  Today I've been bored stupid.  Tidyed room a bit, watched athletics on TV etc.  Boring, boring, boring...  Tomorrow should be better have an MOT on my car and then Kathryn arrives in the afternoon, ready to come to BXL with me.  Sorry not really with it tonight!  More soon!
     
    


22,August,2003


     
       urlLink Times Online   Look Richard's famous!  In the print version I took the photo of him!
     
    


19,August,2003


     
      Last day!  I'm out of here!  Unemployment here I come...  So, successful night with Mónica last night and tomorrow is Scott and Christine's wedding!  Back to BXL with Physics Kathryn next Wednesday...  A+
     
    


19,August,2003


     
      So Rickytó has returned to the land paved with shite.  Well to be honest it's not even properly paved is it?  You trip over every five metres due to missing cobbles.  Frickin' Brussels...
     
    


18,August,2003


     
      Frickin' french, frickin' subsidies...  Good old Guardian!  urlLink kickAAS 
     
    


15,August,2003


     
      People on my  blacklist :  Daniel "Jahman" Dadson  Liam "Loves the Wimmin" Cahill  Richard "Dirty Dick" Freedman - Get's double points for dodgy  Double Dating  shenanigans Ricardo "Randy Rick" Ribeiro  Paul "El Konko del Amor" Anthony   Removed from  Blacklist : Graça Sousa - She phoned me and moaned, so I have to or I'm "in big trouble"... Oonagh Sands - She been ill and is too nice to be on a blacklist to begin with...
     
    


15,August,2003


     
       urlLink BBC NEWS | UK | England | Hampshire/Dorset | Inquiry into sunbather's death   Poor bloke!  You couldn't make it up...  I pay tribute to him.
     
    


15,August,2003


     
      COOL!  Our office has water pouring from the roof - it's drenched our office and is starting a torrent down the road.  Qualité!  Ag, ag, ag!
     
    


15,August,2003


     
      People on my  blacklist : Daniel "Jahman" Dadson Liam "Loves the Wimmin" Cahill Richard "Dirty Dick" Freedman Ricardo "Randy Rick" Ribeiro Paul "El Konko del Amor" Anthony Graça "Can you do all my work for me?" Sousa Oonagh "Is she dead?" Sands
     
    


15,August,2003


     
       urlLink West Midlands in Europe   This is where I work, this is where I live.  I no work here in one week time, I join unemployment scrapheap...
     
    


15,August,2003


     
      Hola!  Welcome to Mikey Bee's/Miguelito Abeja's/Chantry Bee's first attempt at a blog.  As you can see it's dull as.  Nevermind.    It's a bank holiday here in the Land-of-Belges so I'm wasting some time doing this...  Contact me at mailto:chantrybee@netscape.net  A+ M.Bee
     
    


18,September,2003


     
      Hello, hello.  Am pissed off with being unemployed...  Really starting to chaff my winkle.  There's just nowt interesting around, I have big debts and no way to pay rent etc.  All in all, it's a right pile of arse.  Cooked for WMiE people last night.  Had a great weekend in London with the newly casados last week.  No romance in my life...  Going to become a hermit.  I'm cheerful aren't I?  Well the weather's nice at least - 27° in September, can't complain.  GET ME A JOB
     
    


28,May,2004


     
       urlLink ATVEA Home Page 
     
    


02,July,2004


     
      Have been in Portugal for Euro 2004 - it was amazing...  Week in Porto, week in Lisbon.  saw some of the most amazing places... Will wrtite more later... 
     
    


12,August,2004


     
       urlLink  Guardian Unlimited  Guardian daily comment  A Harry Potter politics        Sorry, is it me or does Denis MacShane come out with some slanted codswallop? I'm glad he's pro-European and all but Jesus he talks some nonsense. People in Europe look at the UK and say 'I wish our country had the low unemployment of the UK' of course, but equally they see a place of little culture, failing infrastructure (the only reason our investment's rising is because of 50 years of underinvestment...), and xenophobia. The UK is becoming more and more intolerent and this is a reason I'm abroad - I cannot stand the Little Englander mentality...   
     
    


11,August,2004


     
      The greatest road sign in France, other than Condom of course!!!  &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    


11,August,2004


     
        Let's blog a bit...         So, I'll write a bit on my blog for once...      Last night I met my Portuguese mate Ricardo and some other Iberians for a pitta and beer.  Randy Ricky's been in Porto for 2 weeks so was good to catch-up - turns out his Grandpa died the day he got home while he was on a bus...  Not nice.  But he seemed in fine fettle, randy as ever - prattling on about this Spanish bird's eyes!      Anywhos, today the rain's returned to Brussels - I shouldn't be surprised but arg!      Time to get on with some work!      A+  
     
    


11,August,2004


     
        Bored in Brussels         So, it's that time of the year where continental Europe shuts down... BXL is a ghost-town I tell you... 2 people in my office... I'm struggling to achieve anything so I'm playing around on this instead... It's one of the few times I think the British consumer-driven, capitalism is all attitude has its value... Jesus, how can these European states not go bankrupt when everyone on hols??? Imagine if peeps worked in August - Europe might catch the UK up and stop being so economically sluggish...        Gah!        Leeds lost last night - arg! Hope we get to the ruddy play-offs...  
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    I think this is a wicked photoid!  Lots of Dutch peeps outside the Estádio do Dragão after the Germany vs Holland game...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Toulouse - ah, how I wish I was there and not in Bruxhelles&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Graça and I at the Kite festival near Lisbon.  urlLink    
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Ricardo scoring at Luz to beat England :(&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


08,August,2004


     
       urlLink    It's me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


08,August,2004


     
       urlLink    Too Close for Comfort!!!  urlLink    
     
    



