
30,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       Time:  Earlier today.  Place:  the red line train at Wilson Ave.  Incident:  As I was leaving the car, I passed a rather rotund gentleman who was singing at the top of his lungs, "pass the chicken!" in a very melodic fashion. He repeated this little ditty as long as I was in earshot.   This immediately recalled another experience I have had with random chicken-stuff. Last year when I was walking to work, I was approached by a man with a bag, who got very close to me and said, "I have chicken for sale. Real good chicken. Any piece you want." He opened a scummy looking bag to reveal an assortment of fried chicken. I said no thanks and went on my merry way. He called after me, "You're missing out! I have good chicken!!"   So, yeah, not much else is going on in my life right now, so chicken is the highlight of my day (that and eating really good spaghetti.)   Over and Out.  &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,September,2003


	 
      Hello from the land of justin timberlake and way way too much web surfing.  I got rid of my cable tv last week which in turn has led to a lack of TV.  period.  I dont get local channels either.  I think its best this way.  Im going to the clinic outpatient now, so things are looking up.  Im reading, listening to the radio; Im finally cleaning the house.  I'm happier.  That stills leaves me with plenty of time to surf the web endlessly as i am doing right now.  I really do need to wind down after the rousing game of mini golf i had with jeremy and paul and john. ...and peter paul and mary.  Its pretty cold here.  If only i had a bob evans that i could duck into for a warm, breaded oriental chicken salad, since thats what i crave in the winter.  Alas there is no bob evans in colorado.  I've only seen ONE waffle house and it was near the airport so thats sort of nonmansland type territory and can't really be considered colorado.  There was a perkins, but it was torn down.  In its place was built an eating establishment with a leprechan as mascot.  or maybe it was a denny's.  either way, why did they bother?   &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,September,2003


	 
      Whenever someone else uses the word  frosty  it deserves attention ( I also enjoy the assorted mischief): "Autumn leaves, pumpkins, and chrysanthemums—not to mention Halloween costumes and assorted mischief—will help ease us into the inevitable frosty climes of winter."  &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,September,2003


	 
      Word to yo motha.  I trust that all the ladies had a lovely weekend...I was in Kansas City with the fam.  Mary is SO TALL!  She comes up to my chest and she is only 7.  It's off the hizzle fo shizzle.    Tonight is a big one, what with pottery class and all.  Who's to say what will go down after class.   I started "researching" grad schools yesterday (aka surfing the net and ending up frustrated b/c I can't seem to find the info I need).  Shan how is school going now?  Still feeling like it may not be your thing???  Give it time...  I'm off to the mall with Gracie to get her some educational toys.  Yesterday we went to this Gymboree class where I swear the teacher was on uppers or something.  She was hopping around the room like a damn kangaroo (but looked more like a woodpecker); she had way more energy than any of the kids.  Then we sang such classics as "Where is Gymbo?" and "Bubbles in the Air."  I tell you, I challenge myself and learn something new every day with this job.  
     

    


22,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,September,2003


	 
      So, here's the latest... On Thursday I went to the Green Mill, a Chicago favorite, with some classmates from the English program. It is an old jazz/swing club, which reportedly was owned by Al Capone back in the day. It is great on Thursday nights, because they have a 15 piece swing orchestra. Now, as many of you know, Shan does not dance. What, you may ask, does she find enjoyable at this place, then? Well, I enjoy the decor, which has not changed since its opening back in the 30's, love the music, and like watching good swing dancers. This is I think the third time the new English people have gotten together for fun and drinks, and I have to say, it's still a little awkward. Some of these people are a little kooky and goofy, as English majors can be. But, not me! Oh yes, get a new beers in me and I am by usual obnoxious self. I think I seriously kept the conversation going at some points by just being an idiot. But, you can't talk about Chaucer and Milton all the time. Come on, people! Some of them would, I think... So anyway, the night hit a high point when a nattily dressed dancer spilled his drink down the back of my pants (not while he was dancing, though). How, you may ask, did this incident occur? Well, friends, all of you are familiar with the trouser styles of today, which sit pretty low on the rear. Mind you, I'm no Britney Spears, but I do sport the pants, now!! So, as I was sitting in said pants, having a nice chat with my fellow students, dancer guy accidentally pours almost a whole drink down my pants. I was wearing khakis, but all was well, as he was drinking something clear. Matt was none too amused with these shenanigans, but I let it go.   Also on Thursday, I checked out the new H & M store that opened on Michigan Avenue. Have to say, I was a little scared. Not only were there about 300 people in the place, but the 80's wear was abundant!! We're talking oversized, off the shoulder sweatshirts. I am not ready for that, and I hope most other people aren't either. A lot of their clothes did look cute -- and reasonably priced-- but I could not handle the madness. Teens everywhere, grabbing tapered jeans and  other bad items had me running for cover. The lines to the dressing rooms snaked all the way through the stores, also making me not want to try anything on. I will be back, though, hopefully when the 80's have left... With much relief I headed next door to Filene's Basement (aka TJ Maxx) and felt safe and comfortable shopping there amid the J. Lo sweats and FuBu Ladies gear.   Ok, that's all I can blog for now. I went to the Lincoln Park Zoo today and hopefully here is a picture of my favorite animal, whose stuffed friend was left at La Quinta on SB '98! Sniffle...   &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,September,2003


	 
      Hey ladies... So the delinquent blogger is finally getting on the ball.  Or I was going to until I realized I have to pick Mary up at the bus stop...hold on.  Such is living on the edge as a nanny.    And I'm back.  I apologize for taking forever to get on this blogger thang (by the way, a couple days ago Jon and I were getting some household items-goodtimes, I know-and out of nowhere I said, "What if Linens 'n Things changed their name to Linens 'n Thangs to appeal to a thuggish ruggish clientele?  And maybe got Fubu and P Diddy of Sean John to design some stuff for them?").  So I guess I have some catching up to do, and here I go!  I am working as a nanny for 4 kids.  3 are in school all day so I spend my days with a 2 year old...for a good mental image of this kid, picture Cindy Loo Hoo from Dr. Seuss.  That's Gracie; she's a great kid to take care of...very easygoing and fun.  It has taken some adjustment, but I'm starting to really like it.  I am still applying for grad school for next fall; being a nanny doesn't exactly have career path written all over it.    I'm living in Newton, which is about 15 minutes outside of Boston.  It's a sweet area (what I've seen of it, anyway) and I LOVE my apt.  Although I felt like such a mom having to buy floor guards for every piece of furniture so nothing scratches up the wood floors, which are new.  And gorgeous.  Also I'm sleeping in my very own big-girl bed (aka, a queen size) for pretty much the first time, and I love that too.    Hmm now on to extracurricular activities.  *wink wink* (Right, I wish my life was that exciting.)  I am taking a beginning wheel-throwing class on Tuesdays and had my first class last week.  The class is cool so far and has a good teacher.  There are two gals around our age so I'm HOPING to make some friends.  Gee I hope they like me. ;) And Alison, you'd love this...Jon and I go to a trivia night at this bar called innerlimits every Thursday with some of his friends.  The questions are mostly geared towards the older folks, so we haven't exactly cleaned up, but we have racked up $25 in gift certificates.  And hey, more than the prizes, it gives me a good kick in the head to think, maybe I'm not as smart as I once thought.  I have had a couple moments of glory, however.  I haven't let CHS down; I got the kalamata olive question AND a Don Quixote question fast as lightnin', I say.    This weekend, I jet off to Kansas City for my great aunt's memorial service.  I get to see my siblings, which will be great, but I would like to stay around here and kick it.  Plenty of time for that soon enough, though...Oh, and I'm coming back to Indy Oct. 24; my friend Kristin (from DePauw) is getting married on the 25th.  So I hope to see some of the crew out and about that weekend!  Wicked.  How B-town am I.    Peace, love, and leather pants,  Jenny  
     

    


18,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,September,2003


	 
      Tuesday's a Good Day for Irony...  Just finished working this morning as a "career counselor" for immigrants in Uptown. I am just sitting here thinking about the fact that my job is to help people find jobs and get their lives together, I am currently having a professional crisis. I do not, right now, find grad studies in English to be my life calling. At this point, if I was really serious about the whole thing, I would not procrastinate on doing my homework and dread going to class. Right? Or would I still procrastinate because that's what we all do? I guess no job or school is what it's cracked up to be- oh well.   I too have been sniffling into a hanky about the fate of Ben and Jen. Maybe I just have a cold from all the yucky kids I've been around lately... Must go to Einstein's Bagels and also get ice cream. Without a doubt, it will be snacktacular!  &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,September,2003


	 
      Shan, a.k.a. Chicago, has finally arrived to rock the boat!    Actually, the weather has been sucking so much here lately that I think quite a few boats were rocking over yonder in the harbors. Since the theme seems to be "what I'm up to," I have to say that you all sound like your weekends are tons better than mine! Not that reading, reading, reading, and staring at rain clouds doesn't hold a certain amount of charm, you know. Let's see... I joined some new fellow grad-mates on Friday night for a rousing evening of chat, noodles  urlLink (Noodles and Co.)  , and beer (at  urlLink Prairie Moon -- a good locale for beers other than Bud Light)  in Evanston. Just so all noodle-eaters have a clear understanding: Noodles and Co. serves Asian, Italian, and other "American" (?) dishes. There is a virtual smorgasbord of options! Laughed until I practically peed my pants at Robin Williams in an HBO special (I am a little upset by the fact that he is vulgar-- Mrs. Doubtfire never really got that point across)! I also viewed Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers... I wish the books could hold my attention, but I hate to say that I like these movies better than the 'ol written word.   I did manage to venture out of my apartment today for some tasty brunch at  urlLink Benedict's  on Lincoln (in Lincoln Square) and then for some jigging at the  urlLink Chicago Celtic Festival  downtown at Grant Park. While rain clouds loomed overhead, I enjoyed a harpist, some cute Irish dancer children with scary wigs, and crafty artwork.   I can't wait for all of our respective cities to be up and running! &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,September,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,September,2003


	 
      Greetings from sunny So-Cal.  I'm jealous of those on the East coast, whose weekends have begun, as I'm dying to get out of here.  On tap for the weekend:  A bunch of us movie nerds are headed to see Sofia Coppola's latest film,  urlLink "Lost in Translation ", which opens tonight in select theaters.  Bill Murray with Tokyo as his backdrop, unable to speak the language is sure to be some visually and comically arresting stuff.    I'm getting the hair cut tomorrow at  urlLink The Standard Hotel on Sunset .  There's a hip salon there that's dirt cheap called Rudy's Barbershop, and they have free valet with validation!  The coolest thing is that you can't book appointments in advance there.  So you just go in, put your name on the list, and then go wait in one of the hotel lounge or pool areas where some eurotrash dj is spinning some tunes.  It's a great place to spy on celebs and beautiful people while sitting in a big furry white chair, sipping on a $12 martini.  It's almost worth the price of a plane ticket to take part in this fun little afternoon.   Last time I was there, John, Leah, and I spotted Jessica Simpson (of recent  urlLink MTV "Newlyweds " fame) and two of her pals laying out by the pool that overlooks the city.  They were drinking Amstel Lights and getting even orangy-browner by the L.A. minute.  Leah also commented when J.S. was getting up to put her clothes on, that she hadn't ever seen a skirt that short.  Oh, and those boobs have to be fake.  If you haven't caught any of her MTV reality show, you must, as it's horrrrible.  She asks her 98degree husband, Nick Lachey, if Chicken of the Sea is tuna or chicken.  This goes on for five + minutes.  It's so bad it's good!    Have a great weekend everyone.  Happy blogging!
     

    


31,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,October,2003


	 
         yesterday i went to walgreens for some juice and while in line to check out, i noticed the selection of snacks that bombards you at most store registers.  what was profound about this display was the signage that said "need a snack?" and was right below a box of super glue.  so apparently, at walgreens, they are encouraging the practice many people attempt to leave in kindergarten, eating paste.  along with snickers, twizzlers, and reese's, one can also snack on glue.....yummy! 
     

    


28,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,October,2003


	 
      ...     whilst driving to work today, i was flipping through morning radio and came across a familiar song "now taaaake these broken wings and learn to fly again, learn to live so freeeee!".  now this song always has made me laugh, along with some other choice songs.  but this time i was listening, really listening and i found some of the lyrics disturbing "you are half of the flesh and blood that makes me whoooole".  then it made me remember the time that faye took me to her christian bible study/convert jennie before she goes to hell!  and how her friend jackie was telling me i will go to hell unless i allow the Lord into my life the way she wants me to, all along referencing particular passages (the good old "i am the vine, you are the branches" and " you are the clay, i am the potter").  she even used the word "saved", not in refernce to me, mind you!   so i think mr. mister is trying to start a cult.....and i used to sing along.  the evidence is all right here:  Baby, I don't understand, why we can't just hold on to each others' hands This time might be the last, I fear, unless I make it all too clear I need you so, ohh  Chorus: Take these broken wings, and learn to fly again, learn to live so free And when we hear the voices sing, the book of love will open up and let us in  Take these broken wings  Baby, I think tonight, we can take what was wrong and make it right, mmm Baby, it's all I know, that you're half of the flesh And blood that makes me whole, I need you so, so  (chorus)  Take these broken wings, you've got to learn to fly Learn to live life so free And when we hear the voices sing, the book of love will open up and let us in Yeah yeah, let us in, let us in  (Solo)  Baby, it's all I know, that you're half of the flesh And blood that makes me whole, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, so  (chorus)  Take these broken wings, you've got to learn to fly Learn to live your life so free And when we hear the voices sing The book of love will open up for us and let us in, yeah yeah Yeah yeah, oooh  so i am sticking with shaking my tail feather....
     

    


27,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,October,2003


	 
      due to my lack of work at the restaurant this week, i am finding myself with more evenings to plop on the couch and entertain myself with random shows.....my favorite being "the 80's strikes back" on vh1.  on most all topics, there is an interview with hal sparks (alison's previous loverboy!) and that guy from ed, who really is funny, but where did he come from?  juliette lewis also pipes in a bit, but what i really love is being reminded of the time when trapper keepers were HOT and ocean pacific rivaled dolce and gabbana for cool points.  of course, the biggies stick out: mr. t, who shot jr, culture club.....but where would i be now without scratch and sniff stickers?  no matter that you knew it would stink, you still scrated and sniffed the skunk with as much enthusiasm as the root beer mug.  damn, i think i can credit my good grades to scratch and sniff since without that check plus, there was no sticker.  and then trapper keepers were banned, yes banned, in fourth grade at christ the king grade school....but being the rebel that i am, i stuck with it and carried a polar bear trapper, risking detention and sentencing to hell.  if only that was still the case, trapper keepers being contraband instead of guns......tear, tear.  try this wee match up game at  urlLink 80s Strikes Back . who knew ronald was a jelly belly fan?
     

    


23,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,October,2003


	 
      ...it's snowing in Boston.  The leaves haven't even fallen off of the trees-and some of them are still green!-but sure enough, it's snowing big fat fluffy flakes, and over an inch has accumulated already.  The first snow always gives me a nice warm fuzzy feeling and for a second or two, I think that I actually like the winter...until the first time I soak my shoes and the bottom half of my jeans walking to the car and then numb up my hands scraping the ice off of the windshield.  Then I wise up and spend the drive to work with one hand on the steering wheel (or in my pocket) and the other raised high in the air, flipping old man weather the bird (or playing the piano).  I've got to migrate to a warmer climate asap.    urlLink Fall Bird Migration - All Info About Science for Families.htm 
     

    


22,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,October,2003


	 
      so yes it is monday in case you haven;t noticed and i decided to start my week off right.  at the center this morn, as i am zipping up my pants (after taking a wiz, not rolling in the hay), i zip my scarf into my zipper.  not so bad if i can get the damn thing out, but no, the world doesn;t work that way, as i have learned from the cubs and sox.  so i am destined to spend the rest of the day at half mast, scarf entwined with zipper, and tug at my sweater to hide said atrocity.  but at least when i stand next to attractive fellows in a barski, i avoid camel toe.  (hee hee, shall i sent that bit to jean?....you KNOW it had to be said!)  anyhoot, in response to such lovely blogs, what's not to like?....literary club: GOOD!, watching jessica simpson go camping with louis vuitton bag and bear bin: GOOD!, dogs lead a cheer: GOOD!  and, jenny, may i suggest kevin bacon and lady in red boots from footloose, or if going for the man on man theme, kevin and jack his stalker from will and grace.  OR jessica and nick ;)  but why be constricted with people, think washer and dryer, ketchup and mustard, pot and kettle?  seriously, why not jesse and chester from "dude where's my car" complete with track suits and "dude" and "sweet" tats?  and i'm spent......   
     

    


19,October,2003


	 
      I'm devastated to say that I think New England has better foliage than Indiana, even than Brown County.  There goes that claim to fame (I say claim to fame because I have witnessed busloads of Japanese tourists diggin the leaves at Turkey Run and in Brown County)...but at least we still have the Indy 500.  I was in New Hampshire over the weekend, and they just have some great leaves.  Mountains too.  Exciting stuff...  I am looking for couples' costumes suggestions if you bloggers out there happen to have any.  Jon came up with a gem of an idea...being Harry and Lloyd from Dumb and Dumber when they're wearing the orange and white suits...but I'm a little concerned about how we're going to acquire the necessary props to really pull it off.  But damn it, I'll try.
     

    


19,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,October,2003


	 
      well, i too am going along with the national passtime that was never really personal or family favorite.....my grandpas both passed on prior to my birth so it was never an wgn for me; it was the 700 club and golf with grandma.  but alas, i have found a boyfriend, much like tbox, with a fondness for baseball that has delighted me the past couple weeks.  "hey jennie, instead of going to a movie or something, how about we watch the cubs at my house!"  WAHOO, sign me up!  unfortunately, i am not as devoted and have not really learned the players and their stats, but i did witness the famous sosa hit a homer about eight games ago :)  so sean has uncovered the inner baseball fanatic in me.....GO CUBS!  no subway rides or home games on the horizon, but you better believe my ass will be plopped on the couch tonight, beer in hand and chips ready to throw at the tv for bad calls....right after we attend a speaker for domestic violence that i am required to see.  so it's even steven.....but he still sang the beginning lyrics to elvis' song, suspicious minds, "i'm caught in a trap, and i can;t get out, because i love you too much baby" to make me laugh.    so here's hoping that the sox and cubbies pull on through tonight, for grandpa t, grandpa b, boo, seannessy, mariah, and all of us that love them :)   
     

    


14,October,2003


	 
      Sad times for baseball last night...is there really a curse over the Cubs and the Red Sox?  I went to the Red Sox game and had a great time despite getting a little chilly.  I successfully took public transportation into Boston by myself for the first time, meeting interesting characters like a diehard Mariah Carey fan wearing a Rainbow t-shirt who thought Glitter was the best thing to happen to the box office sinceTitanic.  And we all know how touching Titanic is.  I even got there early for batting practice (Jon got a ball from Andy Pettite, pitcher for the Yankees...I shouldn't say "got" so much as "got in a brawl over;" he had his hand on the ball and was pulled into right field of Fenway Park by this Yankees fan trying to steal it from him!)...we sat in the bleachers and I was fortunate enough to overhear some exchanges between Yankees and Red Sox fans; the basic gist of all those being, "You suck!!!" "Yankees suck!" and "Mr. October (Derek Jeter) sucks!"  It's a good time.  At any rate, despite all this excitement, the Red Sox were the ones that sucked it up and blew the game.  Clowns.  And then later on in the evening, the Cubs followed suite and blew a 4-0 lead to lose to the Marlins.  And Katie, I feel your Grandpa Bob's devotion to the Cubs.  My Grandpa Tarbox may just be the guy to rival his love for the Cubs.  He too is closing in on 80 but is still willing to cruise the streets of Chicago scalping tickets for another Cubs game.  It's amazing how they never give up on these teams, despite failures and disappointments galore (yes, Ali, as in the Cure).  I'm nervous to email him today as I think last night's game may just have broken my poor Grandpa's heart.  Get it together, Cubs!  Here's hoping tonight goes better for the Cubs and the Red Sox!  PS Nyebag: I mentioned to Brett this weekend how I occasionally enjoy throwing up the peace sign while driving, i.e. when letting someone in.  He claims that this is all he, too, uses for hand gestures.  Right.  
     

    


14,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,October,2003


	 
      so there are many a thang that i love about working at the julian center (fyi, this is my americorps site).....i can call my site a "center for kids who cannot read good" since i am the literacy coordinator, we watch the young and the restless during lunch (so shan, i feel the daytime bondage, uh, bonding), and snoop dogg is one of our custodians...seriously, we are talking contest winning impersonator, in like, 20 yrs and without braids.  i still haven't mustered enough courage to ask for an autograph, but i will.    and one more thing, i hate soaps.  i am not a big fan of reality series either since the main premise is to imitate real life, but hey, who really lives with 20 other women competing for one man, or on a deserted island eating bugs, or who marries their sister's third husband who has survived a killer bee attack AND given birth?  but here i am each day at lunch, seemingly enthralled in this show simply because everyone else is and who really wants to hear "your show is crap!" from the new girl?  it's like saying "yeah, i eat here all of the time, and i love the ribeye" when waiting tables at sullivan;s despite my being a vegetarian; no one wants to hear it!  so this is what confuses me: we are told to be individuals, but one still makes more friends with honey that vinegar......  at least snoop and i can still roll down the street, sippin' on gin and juice.  
     

    


13,October,2003


	 
      Saddle up, partners...I'm going to the Red Sox game today!  One of their chants is "Cowboy Up," which I get a real kick out of.  Like all of sudden we're not in Boston, we're in the wild wild west.  Anyway...the game on Sunday was rained out and moved to today, so I get to leave work early to go.  Goodtimes.  For those of you who don't have a boyfriend who is obsessed with baseball and has passed the bug onto you, the Red Sox are playing the Yankees for the American League Division Championship, and they're tied 2-2.  Here is an idea of just how knowledgable I have become about baseball: Me, after the game was rained out: "So now Burkett's not pitching?  Nice!"  (this guy sucks) Jon: "No, Wakefield's pitching tonight (Monday) and then Lowe on Tuesday." Me: "Sweet...Lowe's MUCH better at home." and Jon gives me the old double-take, how did you know that look.  Welp, considering I have watched more baseball in the past few weeks than ever before in my life, these things aren't hard to pick up.    So go Red Sox.  Cowboy up!   urlLink    Nyebag, glad to see you're hopping on the bloggin' wagon.  Shan and Alison, thanks for your help in telling me how to post!  
     

    


13,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,October,2003


	 
      okay, so i am new :)  and i uh, my name is jennie (echo with me, "hi jennie"), and this is my first time blogging.  but i was encouraged by my friend, alison, to join, so here i am.    welp, since i have now joined pseudo corporate america and now have a cubicle and a low paying job (GO AMERICORPS!), i also have time to do menial tasks to make the day go by.  one of which was checking my old depauw email account to see who doesn;t talk to me anymore, but likes to email my old account.  so i scan all of the spam and pat myself on the back for getting spam protection at yahoo and what do i find?  but a message from the women and science that i have been removed from their distribution list.  WHAT?!  you people PLAGUED me from the moment i was woman and took a science class to come to those damn luncheons and speakers!  (which i sometimes thought of going to for the free food :)...so basically it took GRADUATING and another year+ for you to get the hint.....didn;t you go to high school?  i am too cool for science.    and i found an invite from stacy to try a new hand held lie detector.    
     

    


08,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,October,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,November,2003


	 
           My little sister Mary wrote and sent me this story.  It's really cute...but maybe she's watching too many Disney movies.    "Once open a time there was a peses (princess) she was very pretty.  Her name was Law Law.  Bet like nomol (normal) girl she had a problem?  Bet why?  She didn't have any friends.  She was very very sad.  She started to kriy.  Then she had a cockes (cookies ;) and milk.  She falt better.  She whached some tv.  Then went on a walk.  Then she met a boy.  Then they played.  Thay had a good time.  Then they got to now each other.  Then when she was 29 and he was 29 and a half they got maryeyd."
     

    


25,November,2003


	 
          People ask me all the time what I do with a two-year-old all day.  Actually, I even ask myself that.  So I thought I would post something about it every now and then, and perhaps one of you will be around a 2 y.o. and utilize (Alison, remember how much Mrs. Fitzgerald loved that word?!) this information.  Grace is an unusually easygoing kid, being the fourth child, so maybe all of this won't apply to the average 2 y.o.; I don't know many others.    The first thing I caught on to is that 2 year olds are big imitators, so if you're laughing, then they will be too.  Whenever Grace gets upset or kind of bored, I do something like yell out "Hee hee!" (like Michael Jackson...one day she'll hear his songs and wonder why that hee hee thing is so familiar); Grace is very responsive and loves to yell it out too, and she's getting disturbingly good at it.  Or we sing selections from "I'm sorry Ms. Jackson" or "Giddyup 409."  My personal favorite is saying "And den" like in "Dude, Where's My Car," something she also loves to say.  The best times are when she is really worked up and doesn't feel like playing these games, she'll yell "No and den!!!"  Seriously, without any prompting from me.  It is so funny, I have to hold in my laughter because she is genuinely upset.  I must admit, you can't spend a whole day singing or yelling out random comments, so we also do things like painting, swinging, and cooking.  Today Grace took it upon herself to color the legs of the table with her orange marker...luckily for me, it was a washable marker...I worry at times that I may not be the most convincing parent when trying to discipline a kid because I really find things like that so funny.  Hopefully I wouldn't have laughed had the marker not been washable.    So there's a little peek into kickin' it with a two year old, which reminds me, I never explained the title.  Grace looks like Cindy Lou Hoo, so I started calling her Gracie Lou, and then, following the natural progression of things, Gracie Loudicrous, then just Loudicrous.  Only on special occasions, though.  I certainly wouldn't want her to start repeating that one as her parents may not see the humor in it.          
     

    


24,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,November,2003


	 
         I got such a kick out of Leah's website with the tampon doll and it made me think of pearl river.  This store is fabulous and I shopped there many a time while up in NYC.  It's owned by a Chinese family that brings goodies from home to the USA and sells them for reasonable prices.  I frequent this website for unique gifts and it has a Chinese wedding sections for all your betrothed ladies out there.  Enjoy!  Okay, the website is  urlLink www,pearlriver.com .....I still need my lesson on posting links, Alison!
     

    


20,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,November,2003


	 
      I once was a good writer.  Back in my college days, anyway.  Even my professors seemed to think so...after all, they made me a writing tutor (which, I will admit, was at times no more than trying to explain the complexities of the comma to yet another frat guy).  Perhaps "making it" in such a big way at old DePauw has given me a big head, because now, when it matters most, I am stuck.  I am in the middle of my personal statement for graduate schools, which appears to be a simple enough task.  Don't be fooled (Shan, I'm sure you feel this).  It's a doozy, one of those way-too-general things that's impossible to pin down and write about.  So I putz around while at work, scribble out a few things, and then bring it home and get Jon (also a writing tutor, lucky for me) to help me structure it.  Now I know how to do all of these things too, it's just that I don't want to (perhaps I'm spending too much time with my 2 year old friend Gracie?).  Perhaps what I'll end up doing is taking highlights of my blogs-maybe some of yours too, because I just don't have that many-, pasting them together, and turning that in as my statement.    To be honest, the personal statement doesn't worry me all that much.  I'll buckle down and get it done this weekend because I have to.  What does worry me is actually getting in to grad school and having to write again on a regular basis.  What am I doing when I decided to go to grad school, you may wonder?  Putting off the real world, that's what...doing exactly what I do best.  
     

    


19,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,November,2003


	 
      Sunday was perhaps my most fun night ever at Sullivan's steakhouse....not b/c of the dough, but b/c of the people I worked with and the way the evening went.  First off, Sundays are notoriously slow and usually the crew consists of the newest kids on the block.  I am now the oldest of the newest kids, wahoo!  Anyway, so it's low key and fun....what was especially lovely about this night was we had certain sections of the restaurant blocked off b/c we have fewer servers (8 as compared to 16)....but the hostess could NOT figure it out.  She kept seating the wrong sections and being like, "Yeah, that might not be your section, but that's your table," and seating people in one person's section and giving that table to another person.  While some people were beyond irritated with her stupidity, I just laughed and got a kick out it!  I mean, there were MAYBE 10 tables in the restaurant.  To her discredit, she also had a seating chart, like map of who was where and the blocked sections were blacked out.        Anyway, I am leaving with my whopping $40 for the night and who do I RUN into on my way out?  Kato Kaelin, the world's most infamous houseguest.  Yup, definitely bumped into him and was like, " Uh, sorry."  Did a double take and asked the valet guy if that was Kato.  And it was.....in Indianapolis, on a Sunday, at my crazy restaurant.  I only wonder where he sat.
     

    


17,November,2003


	 
      So once again, the delinquent blogger is back.  This time I am armed with a somewhat acceptable reason: I realized a few weeks ago that I was really behind on my grad school apps (which are taking a ridiculously long time to finish...every school has a slightly different angle on the same old question and they all have random, weird things to do.  I applaud ASU and IU for the simplicity of their applications; every other school could learn a few things from them.)  The most exciting part about the application process is the prospect of moving somewhere WARM (CA, AZ, or FL).  I hate old man weather and jack frost and the rest of the crew; I am already dealing with my first cold of the year.  I'm just not cut out for cold weather, I tell you what.       Since I last blogged, I have realized a couple things: 1), I don't know why there's so much hype about the Blue Man Group.  I liked STOMP better (and let's face it, that's just more fun to say); I loved the parts in BMG when they're drumming or playing the pipes (that sounds gross but how else do I put it???), but then there's parts like when they are spewing cereal everywhere during which I sat and wondered, is the 40+ crew sitting behind us only laughing because they're all drunk?  Or do they actually find this funny?  I'm gonna go out on a limb and say that if any of their kids were to "get creative" like the Blue Men and spew cereal all over the kitchen table at breakfast, they wouldn't find it quite so entertaining.  Hmm.  2), I like parties with beer and doritos (Ali, are you drooling yet?)  much, much better than ones with champagne and silly snacks like "baked apples drizzled with cherries stewing in brandy all day."  You're probably wondering, why the hell were you doing at the latter party?!  Rolling my eyes, that's what.  Jon's friend Adam had a party in his swanky North End apt; Adam is very cool, but one of Adam's friends Monica (who pranced around all night in a pink shirt with a big bow on it and a chain belt with a pink rhinestone M on it) wants to be an event coordinator and insisted on making this party very "adult."  Now when has anything adult added up to big fun?  Never yet, and it hasn't started.  I hope I never become the kind of person that genuinely thinks I'm having fun at such a function.  Instead, I hope I become a prankster at such parties who adds a little Everclear to the cherries or replaces Monica's M with a gorilla pendant or something along those lines.    I have a couple recommendations for the blogging crew and our avid readers: the book "The Essential Difference" by Simon Baron-Cohen and online dvd rental services like Netflix.  "The Essential Difference" is this really cool book that addresses the differences between the typical male and female brains and how hormones present prenatally (like testosterone) affect brain development.  Very cool, and it's not as psycho-babbly as you might expect.  The online dvd thing is just really convenient for anyone who likes to kick it on occasion (or, perhaps nightly) with a video and a box of junior mints (sorry, I am really hungry right now)...we tried walmart's but they take awhile to ship so I'd recommend Netflix.  Also, if anyone has any movie suggestions, please let me know!  
     

    


17,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,November,2003


	 
      i love the olympics....next year, summertime, olympics.  today, nadia comaneci, olympic gold medalist in gymnastics turned 42.  tonya harding, olympic gold medalist in scandal and hilarious debauchery turned 33.   
     

    


10,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,November,2003


	 
      this weekend i had an epiphany.  something funny, disturbing, but true.  my boyfriend, sean, and jessica simpson are birds of a feather....perhaps that is why i am obsessed with her antics.  i have compiled a list of reasons why:  *i don't think sean could name a brand of tuna, not even chicken of the sea.  i also don't think jessica could either until that incident.    *sean and jessica both love shopping more than humanly possible and sported the "trucker hat" with much enthusiasm. plus, nothing is too expensive for their tastes ($700 underwear?)  *this past wednesday, when sean was leaving the gas station, he forgot to remove the pump from his car before driving off.  common mistake....if you're jessica or sean.  *sean's mother still does his laundry (sometimes) and ironing....does jessica know what a lint trap is?  *in a conversation about children (not ours, in general), sean remarks that he will trade his car for a minivan when expecting his first child.  why?  b/c kids need "a lot of metal surrounding them to protect them in an accident" and because "babies are important!".  apparently my toyota corolla is not safe for children, but jessica's suv will do the trick!  *i had a cold last week, cough, whatnot.  sean asks me is i could be pregnant and i respond with something like a "wha?" and he replies that women get sick before they find out they are pregnant and i am sick, so could i be pregnant?  i calmed him by telling him that morning sickness is defined by symptoms of barfing and nausea, not sniffling and coughing.  i bet jessica would have already peed on the stick.  *sean and jessica still love and admire 98 degrees, okay i made that one up :)    there are more, but i will not bore you.  overall, i am not dating a complete nutball, he just has his "jessica" moments that make me laugh.  if nothing else, i do respect nick lachey for taking the plunge with jess and having an idea of what he had to deal with to hit it with that hottie! 
     

    


09,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,November,2003


	 
          This morning I was doing my usual jackaround activities to start my day at work: check messages, check my work email, check personal email, read blog, read online news....what have you.  And I stumbled across this beauty of an article  urlLink   that reminded me of my encounter with a canadian goose a couple of years back.  I was driving to work and   this goose bolts out of nowhere and jumps beneath my car.  I hit the tricky bastard and was so upset that I stopped to check on the fella.  He was shitty, as you would be, but lively.  I called information get a hold of animal control and bandage up the squaking bird and later came to find that he only suffered a broken wing.  Good for the goose.  But what baffles me about the article is how does a Canadian Goose damage an airplane?   urlLink   urlLink    side note: i cannot figure out how to link this since i am blogging illiterate, but it's in the editorials at indystar.com
     

    


05,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,November,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

31,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,December,2003


	 
      and I don't mean Queen Latifa!  The Queen of England's fave dog is the Corgi.  I too adore the Corgi and for those of you who have never met one, they are precious.  Their ears are longer than their legs and they have such a wonderful demeanor....precious.  Well, I came upon  urlLink this story  in the indy star today which talks about the death of one of the Queen's corgis.  Apparently there was question as to which of Princess Anne's dogs attacked, but a culrpit has been determined.  Never trust a terrier (and for those who know, I abhor terriers, especially after living with Gretchen's friend's Boston Terrier, Renfield!)!     
     

    


29,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,December,2003


	 
         I went to the Simon and Garfunkel concert Saturday night, and wow, it was incredible.  The best thing about it was the crowd...mostly in their 50s and 60s, some still tokin', and so excited to be there.  I kept thinking how psyched I would be if in 30 years DMB had a reunion tour.  I guess that's what Sat. night was like for those grown-up hippies.  There were some noteworthy outbursts of enthusiasm: two times, when the entire crowd was seated, there would be one individual in one of the first few rows standing up busting a move all by him/herself (probably secretly hoping to be invited up on stage).  The first time, no one else joined in, but during "Mrs. Robinson," pretty much everybody got up to shake their tailfeathers.  I just have to say, Paul Simon does write some absolutely incredible songs, but he certainly isn't very nice to Art.  Poor brillopad-hair Art kept going on about their friendship and how great Paul and his songs were, and Paul would be like, "Yeah I know.  I am pretty cool.  You on the other hand..."  That may not be verbatim, but that was the general feeling I got, which was disappointing.  At any rate, it was one of the coolest concerts I've ever seen.  
     

    


12,December,2003


	 
      To aid Alison in the presentation of her award-worthy blog, I will use caps :)  HOW'S THAT FOR YOU?  Just kidding.....Anyway, today's selection for excellent children's book is  Diary of a Wombat  by Jackie French, illustrated by Bruce Whatley.  I find this book exceptional because it informs children of other animals of the world, namely Australia, and is just adorable.       Here is brief decription:  What, exactly, do wombats do all day? One enterprising wombat answers that question and a few others in diary form in French's (No Such Thing) tongue-in-cheek picture book. After explaining his unique Australian heritage, the star of this volume paints a funny, if rather dull, picture of his daily routine. "Monday Morning: Slept./Afternoon: Slept./ Evening: Ate grass./ Scratched./ Night: Ate grass." Things begin to perk up, however, when the wombat discovers its new human neighbors. Before long, the always-hungry creature is at their door begging for food (preferably carrots or oats), digging in their garden ("Began new hole in soft dirt") and turning his neighbors' belongings into scratching posts. Happily, the human family appears to take the antics of their adopted wild "pet" in stride (though the wombat sees things a bit differently "Have decided that humans are easily trained and make quite good pets").   Thank you amazon.com....the illustrations are fabulous and cute and I found myself rooting for this pesky creature and his quest for carrots, something I might not say if it was entitled "Diary of a Possum".  Check this out next time you are visiting Borders or Barnes and Noble.   
     

    


11,December,2003


	 
      There are two acceptable spellings of gre/ay, and in my mind, they are completely different colors (colours, if you will).  I'm just wondering if this is just something I've dreamed up out of nowhere or if anyone else is feeling me on this.  Someone can have grey eyes, but not gray eyes.  You can have a gray car, but not a grey one.  I picture grey as a soft, watercolor color but gray as a harsh, marker color (once again, I do spend a lot of time with a toddler).  Grey is clearly the more poetic of the two colors; gray is the one with the more negative connotation.  So you can't have a grey day, but you can have a gray day.  *side note: I just looked down and realized I have a gray shirt on!*  Here are some examples just so you can see I'm not crazy:       "Brunette hair, Grey Blue eyes and is dressed to Thrill, in a beautiful Peach Gown with White Lace."  "I can see through the mist of your gray blue eyes. You have a hidden feeling, and you don't know what to say." some fine online poetry by J.J. Anne Marie Loeffler (could this be Jill "Birthday Song" Loeffler?)  P.S. Who gets their "thrills" from porcelain dolls?!  I looked up "grey blue eyes" and this is one thing that came up.    
     

    


11,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

11,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,December,2003


	 
       I see a trend of year-end top 10s of this year, so I am going with the flow and creating my "book of the week", hopefully day, but we shall see how busy I am pretending to be at work (actually, I am quite busy these days, so I have shed my wolf costume!).  As you may know, I am a children's literacy coordinator, so I will be reporting on children's books.  perhaps this will only provide immediate assistance to Jenny, but the rest of you can refer to this when you have your own bundle of joy (to babysit, raise, whatever).        Week/day one: I Love Guinea Pigs  by Dick King-Smith (hee hee Dick King) and illustrated by Anita Jeram I find this book especially poignant since, while in New Zealand, Brett and I were doing what we do best one night: sitting around with a doobie chatting about nonsense while Jenny and John hid from us.  Now you might know the silliness that comes from these kinds of conversations, but this is classic.  we are talking about guinea pigs and I suggested that somewhere, there is a wild guinea pig.  The Good Lord did not just create the guinea pig in an aquarium lined with wood chips and an annoyingly loud water bottle, no, there are wild guinea pigs.  Can you imagine hiking along and hearing the rustling of bushes by your feet and out runs a wild guinea pig?  So we had many a laugh and were sharing our joy with Jenny and John the next day at dinner.  The icing on the cake was Jenny getting all serious and saying, "Well yes, there are wild guinea pigs.  I had to write a report for Joyce and John Tarbox about guinea pigs before I could own one."  Ah, the Tarbox family....      At a recent book sale, I spotted "I Love Guinea Pigs" and had to buy it.  In case you were wondering, there  are  wild guinea pigs.  They were first introduced to North America by Spanish sailors about 400 years ago.  Their origin was from a country in South America called Dutch Auiana, hence "Guiana Pigs."  Also, guinea pigs do not have tails and are not actually pigs.   some other interesting guinea pigs facts: • The latin name for guinea pig is  cavia porcellus  (it means piggy-looking cavy)  • Guinea pigs enjoy a variety in their diet, so include cabbage, carrots, apples, and clover as well as pellets • If you "handle them regularly, and carry them around, stroke them, talk to them....they bcome really fond of you"  • Some things a guinea pig might say: "putt", "chut", "tweet", and "drr" • Baby guinea pigs are born fully furred, eyes open, and with teeth!  If you would like to find out more, read "I Love Guinea Pigs."  It includes little references about guinea pigs previously owned by the author.  His two favorites were King Arthur and Beach Boy, both Abyssinians.  Touching stories, I tell you.  You should already own this book!   
     

    


09,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,December,2003


	 
          This picture could have been me this past Sunday afternoon.  Boston had a crazy "noreaster" (if I hear that cheesy word one more time I'm going to call in and complain to all of the news stations!) this past weekend, and being the intelligent kids we are, both Jon and I had our cars in the city Friday night when the storm started.  Hey, we wanted to go out, and a little snow wasn't going to hold us back.  Weatherfolk always exaggerate anyway, right?  Not this time.  Saturday morning rolls around and lucky for us Hornet (aka Dancing Brian...smiles from Jennie...I saw his dance troupe Sat. night!  The BDE!) had an SUV and was able to take us home.  We came back on Sunday armed with shovels when the snow finally let up to unearth our cars...I actually thought the wrong car was mine, initially.  It took over an hour to get them out.  Goodtimes, I tell you.  Everyone walking along the street (and there were plenty of them, heading to the grocery store or trolling *thank you Tish* about on snowshoes or cross-country skis) feels compelled to dispense advice on the best way to get the cars out.  I say, if you have a better way to do it, grab the shovel and demonstrate!  The point of this story is, snow is fun but shoveling is not.  Also, I have strong arms from all that shoveling so don't mess with me.  Mmmm hmm.  
     

    


08,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,December,2003


	 
      At  urlLink Grossface , you can choose a topic, make a video about it and send it in to the site. The administrators will make their own movie about the same topic, then viewers vote to decide which one is funnier. 
     

    


04,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,December,2003


	 
      Putnam Goes Ape For Service Animals       Don't be surprised to see monkeys in local supermarkets in Putnam County reaching for things off the shelves and giving them people in wheelchairs. The Putnam Legislature last night went on record supporting a section of the Americans with Disabilities Act, that says service animals must be allowed in all commercial establishments.  Most people are familiar with seeing eye dogs for the blind. But some people in wheelchairs use monkeys, that are trained to fetch things from shelves in stores.  Putnam Legislator Sam Oliverio doesn't know of any disabled person in Putnam having a service monkey. But he wants the county's laws to be ready in case someone goes into a store with a monkey. 
     

    


03,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,December,2003


	 
         my latest project at work, besides actually working, is to find this photography book on one of my most favorite photographers, francesca woodman.  i have wanted this book for about five years now, never had the money to buy it when i was thinking about it, and have recently been salivating over it online, since it is so rare that most bookstores do not carry it.  what is so frustrating about this is this book is now out of print and it was just released in 1999 or something.  so now the price has gone from $45 new to $300 used and my mission is to find that one bookseller that has not yet received the memo and scam them!  what is so wonderful about this photographer is that her career was so short lived and tragic, but she created a body of work comparable to cindy sherman and nan goldin in about four years.  two articles about her, one in the urlLink  village voice  and another that somewhat compares her to  urlLink sylvia plath  (and shannon perks up!), are worth a read.  maybe i am biased, but i admire how perplexing, yet beautiful her work is and i actually referenced it when creating one of my projects that included self portraiture.    so if you find this book for less that $300, you have made an investment!       
     

    


02,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,December,2003


	 
       Last night, on a very frosty and windy Tuesday in Boston, Jon and I had dinner in the North End, the coolest part of Boston.  It's the Italian 'hood and a very snazzy place to go.  As soon as you drive in, you smell lots of garlicy goodness...there are probably more Italian restaurants in those 5 or so blocks than there are in all of Italy.  It's off the hizzle fo shizzle.  Anyway I love love love it (even though it was a pretty quiet night and we still had to park far away, pay $9 for it, and freeze our asses off on the walk) and I wish I were heading to Italy SOON.  I need to get myself a piggy bank and start saving up.     On another note, when people tell you the traffic out here sucks, they aren't kidding or exaggerating.  Yesterday was one of the worst traffic days in Boston's history...luckily for me, I drive in the opposite direction of everybody else (west away from Boston instead of east into it) and I didn't have to deal with it.  What would be a 20 minute commute for Jon if there weren't any traffic was 2 1/2 hours yesterday.  Nuts.  Hopefully the Big Dig will be finished in this decade.    And that's the way the cookie crumbles.     
     

    


02,December,2003


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,December,2003


	 
         this is for all of you english lovers out there and i KNOW you exist!    urlLink plain english  is classic, let me tell you.  they are all about ensuring that the english stays plain and simple and, you know what, so am i....and what's better is this is serious business.  the whole organisation was founded b/c of these two older lasses that died b/c they could not understand their housing laws!  so this really is a life and death situation.  personally, i am all about it b/c damnit, if you are going to say something, then say it looooud (say it loud).....say it clearrrrrr (ah, say it clear).  so enjoy.  this is an english (as in the country) site, so of course they poke fun at us yankees.  personally, i feel they should, especially when arnold swartzenegger says "i believe gay marriage is something to be shared between a man and a woman".  did they not address gay issues in 'total recall' or 'twins'?      p.s. this is a blogging first for jennie.....i have made a link!  hats off to alison for adjusting my blogs up until now, but finally i figured it out!  gold star for me :)       urlLink  
     

    


02,December,2003


	 
      I have nothing to blog about at this moment, other than I am really tired, stressed out because my semester ends next week and guess what? I'm a procrastinator! So, somebody, blog for us! I hope everyone had a good Thanksgiving and I guess one item of interest is that I ate Thanksgiving dinner 4 times over the break. Anyone top that?   &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,January,2004


	 
         Sean and I went to see the movie Monster the other day starring Charlize Theron in her Oscar nominated, Golden Globe winning role.  To say the least, this movie will challenge your view of "cold-hearted killer".  I read a review before I went and the critic said that the movie was named "Monster" to provoke the viewer to decide, after seeing the movie, is the character truely a monster?    A brief synopsis....(This is based on a true story) Charlize Theron plays a serial killer named, Lee, who is abused and molested as a child, has her first child when she is 13, and results to prostitution in Florida as a means of living.  During the nine months between 1989 and 1990 that the film portrays, she then meets Selby, played by Christina Ricci, and they engage in a lesbian relationship.  Without giving too much of the plot away, this is about the only true friend Lee has ever had in her life.  During this time, Lee also has rough encounter with a "client" where she is tied up and raped and ends up killing the bastard.  This starts her killing spree of men that solicit her, leaving 6 men dead by the time she is caught.   She was excecuted in 2002.  Now what is most facinating about this movie is the evolution of Lee.  Not only does Charlize gain 30 pounds and wear contact lens and heaps of makeup (seriously the only times you can see a glimpse of the actress is when she smiles), but she also portrays the inner struggle of her character with passion and ease.    I highly recommend this movie, as does Sean.  Like Mystic River, you just want to die after you leave the theater, but it sparks conversation about social deviance.  I just cannot say enough good things about this flick!
     

    


29,January,2004


	 
      I had quite an experience at the doctor's office today.  Somehow a simple checkup turned into getting blood tests and a preliminary diagnosis of asthma.  Asthma?  I am a shallow breather but never thought anything of it until Dr. Paterson informed me that she thought I had asthma.  Now I have to get a series of breathing tests called PFTs and a chest X-ray.  All I have to say is, my insurance better cover this; if not, my "asthma" may continue to go untreated.  If it does, great, I'm finally getting something out of my $244.02 monthly insurance payments.  I have felt quite ripped off until my new plethora of illnesses showed up.    Now, the asthma diagnosis I could handle-I don't mind toting an inhaler around-but what really sucked about this particular visit was Dr. P's veiled criticism of my (apparently) bad health habits.  When she asked me if I exercise, I was proud to finally be able to say yes, usually 5 times a week.  Dr. P thinks I should step it up to 6.  I guess I should quit patting myself on the back for taking the initiative to exercise (and mind you, Dr. P is no picture of fitness herself!).  Then she asked me if I smoked, drank, or did drugs; I said I drink only once a week (usually true these days) and fibbed a bit by saying in that one sitting, I'd have 5 or 6 drinks (in reality, maybe 8).  She gave me a disapproving look and said, "That's a lot for a woman."  What would she have thought of me a few years ago?!  She closed our visit by slyly mentioning that I or my boyfriend could have herpes or genital warts and not know it.  Whoa.  The whole time all I could think about was how much I wanted some water, as I had a couple glasses of wine last night and was kind of dehydrated.  I am not quite sure how I gave her the impression that I'm an idiot, especially because now I have some proof that I'm not...I was invited to Berkeley for an interview (wahoo!...that's why I had some wine).        This could be where I spend the next 6 years, Tolman Hall at Berkeley.
     

    


29,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,January,2004


	 
      This was too funny to pass up...I was doing some homework on the democratic candidates to educate myself and came across this quote from Al Sharpton.  I think he's got this election in the bag.    "I do believe the [Democratic] party has moved far to the right. I do believe that the party has a bunch of elephants running around in donkey clothes."  Right on, Al.  They're wolves in sheep's clothing.    Here's a trivia tidbit for you: Who was Al Sharpton's wife a back-up singer for?  
     

    


26,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,January,2004


	 
      So much to blog, so little time :)  I have some pics to post, but am not familiar with computers enough to know where a USB port is off hand, so I must get my "manual for dummies" for using my digital camera.  Seriously, I received this stick that one can save info on and then transfer that info from one computer, ipod, etc to another via the USB port.  I had to ask what it was because I had no idea what I had just unwrapped.  Those of you who are computer savvy, happy laughing!    Anyway, I read this  urlLink article  today on the good old Indy Star website that I find intriguing.  It talks about Gen X and how they work in the workplace (apparently there are books on how to manage Gen Xers.).  It discusses a trend in members of Gen X of simplifying and focusing more on life and happiness than on corporate success.  Now, we are not considered Gen X.  We are grouped in with those Britney worshipping, Prada toting, what are salt and pepper jeans? Gen Ys.  Byron has posted about this internal confusion and displacement before and I enjoyed hearing his argument.  While I never attended prom in taffeta, I still feel that owning a hair crimper, wearing fifty pairs of socks at once, being injured with a slap bracelet, and knowing Johnny Depp prior to Pirates of the Caribbean earns me the right to be in Gen X.  Sure, when I watch "The 80s Strike Back" on VH1, I can only really relate to years 85-89, but who cares?  I want to be part of the "cool" generation!  Also, I saw Chris Rock at the Murat this past Friday and laughed myself silly.  I recommend snagging some seats (if still available) at a venue near you!
     

    


23,January,2004


	 
      It boggles my mind the way media aimed at children has gone so downhill.  Since I am currently spending most of my time with a 2 year old, I am subjected to listen to this crap.  First, there is way too much of it out there; all kids really need are some pots and pans to bang around and a big empty box (preferably a refreigerator box) to make a fort out of.  Mud and sticks are key too.  Somehow there is this whole crazy toy industry that manages to dupe both parents and kids into spending billions of dollars on plastic melded into various shapes and forms that kids play with for like 10 minutes and then either lose interest or lose all the little pieces that go with the toy, rendering it worthless.  I definitely had some toys growing up that I loved...my Cabbage Patch dolls, my Barbies (all of which I lent to a cousin who then sold them off!  oh well, better to be rid of them I guess), and Legos.  Toys have just been taken to a new level now...who really wants a battery-operated plastic dog that won't stop barking until you put its bone in its mouth, only to have it spit the bone right back out and continue the barking?  Some toys now are straight up creepy, like "Fur Real Friends."      They move around very mechanically, make weird faux-animal noises, and have creepy glassy eyes.    I just can't applaud this stuff.  Perhaps the worst of all is the stuff aimed at kids 3 and under, like Gymboree products.  Grace (who's 2) is watching a Gymboree video right now, and it's pretty appalling.  I think it probably stunts children's growth, but somehow Grace's mom thinks it's the greatest thing ever.  This is what Gymbo the Clown      (a grown man masquerading as a clown...this is the stuffed animal version so imagine a grown man dressed up as such, including face makeup) sings little diddies like "I have a little bicycle, I ride it to and fro, and when I see a green light I know it's time to GO!" while pretending to pedal his legs in a circle.  Another old naptime favorite (which I think would have scared the crap out of me) is this song about being a grizzly bear and growling when you wake up.  What?  Where do they come up with these things?  I wonder if Gymbo the Clown admits to his family what he does.  Does he call up his ladyfriend and tell her he has a slammin' new video out where he acts like various farm animals?  Or does he make up a fake job that no one really gets, like Chandler Bing's job, and never admit his true identity?  I wouldn't.    P.S. For the record, I'm proud to say that Grace has spent more time banging on the pots I set out for her than watching the video.  She's a smart one...ignore that crazy clown!
     

    


23,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,January,2004


	 
      In the craziness that was last and is this week, it has always nice to have the blog.  Actually, as of today, I can slack a wee bit more at work....no more programming!  I just want to thank y'all for the great stories, insights, comment, etc.  Anyway, tissues aside, I must share the glory that is  urlLink Dansko .      One Saturday, my work shoes broke.  Bummer for this server, who has little time to shop this week and needs shoes to work.  Gretchen (my roomie) to the rescue!  She let me borrow a pair of her shoes, the heavenly Dansko clog.  Now I admit I enjoy and seek out infomercials, BUT I do not get sucked in and purchase (Tish does enough QVC shopping for one family).  So when Gretchen raved about the unending pleasures of owning a pair of Danskos, I scoffed at spending so much money for work shoes.  Then I wore them, the soft pillows of shoes that my feet floated in for an entire shift.  I had to spread the word.  These are cute, comfy, non-uggish shoes that are well worth the dough.  Think Doc Marten's Mary Janes, with some cousins.....they also make some yuppie sandals, but no one is perfect.   I purchased the pictured pair, the Kyra shoe, in black.  On a final note, when leaving the store (good old Goodman's in Nora), my salesman suggested a pair of Ugg Boots for my next selection in footwear.  I politely laughed and thought to myself, "I might not be couture, but I am not a yeti!".      
     

    


21,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,January,2004


	 
      I think enough time has passed now that I can write about how much the Colts sucked it up on Sunday without pouring salt on open wounds...or maybe I'm just reopening them.  What have you, I don't think any of the C.P. gals are too into football so I'll take the risk.  At any rate, I watched the game with Patriots fans (at this guy called Fat Boy's house), and they realized pretty quickly that I was not one of them.  I should have kept my mouth shut because I got a lot of shit during that game.  I haven't been a Peyton Manning fan ever since Jon informed me that he was accused of sexual harrassment during college, and after that game...hmm.  The expressions on his face were almost comical..."Did I, PEYTON, just throw that?!  What the f**K?!"       I got some skis in New Zealand last year and finally broke them in on Monday at this place in New Hampshire called Tenney Mountain; it was pretty cold and windy, but they had some great runs.  They ain't got nothin' on Swiss Valley, Michigan.  ;)  It was a great time, and I only fell once (although I had several close calls).  I sort of gimped my way down a couple black diamonds, but hey, at least I gave it a shot.  That about sums up my ghetto-fabulous weekend, and now it's back to work.  ooooooooooh yeah.
     

    


20,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,January,2004


	 
      I have now lived in Boston for approximately 4 1/2 months.  And lucky me...I get to be here to experience the coldest day Massachusetts has seen since 1957.  That's right...me, who hates cold weather, gets to be here for one of the coldest days in history (here are the stats: -10 F without wind chill; in some places, up to -50 F with wind chill).  Nearly every school has cancelled school (from an article in the Boston Globe: "I can't remember ever closing school for the temperature," said Frederick Foresteire, Everett school superintendent, who has worked in the city's school system for 38 years. "It is out of the ordinary.").  In these temperatures, you can get frostbite after just a few minutes of exposure to the cold.  I just don't understand why people are willing to live in such a climate.  Take a tip from our fine feathered friends: migrate south!  Old people do it, due to their long years of experiencing how much cold weather sucks.  I personally will be migrating south or west come July...I just can't believe it's taken me this long.  
     

    


15,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,January,2004


	 
         Now that my grad school applications are in (yip, yip, oooooooh yeah), I have found a new activity to fill my afternoons while Grace naps.  While snooping around the Rousseau household, I happened upon some Kathy Smith workout DVDs that Susan does (she's my boss, the family's mama-and I must say, I applaud her for staying in such great shape after popping out fo' chillins).  So I decided to venture into the world of working out, not only for my health but also for the great quotes ("and lift it, and stretch it, and pump it, and pulse it, you're doing FANTASTIC" *if I ever made a workout tape, I'd substitute snacktastic*).  At any rate, Kathy Smith is full of enthusiasm for fitness and at first, I found myself wanting to thank her for her encouraging words.  But after doing "Timesaver: Lift Weights to Lost Weight" a few times, I find them to be ridiculous.  For all Kathy knows, I am sitting on the couch with a bag of Doritos, laughing at her antics and comments (to a big black guy who's part of her weight-lifting crew: "How come your bicep's bigger than mine?"..."Pump it!").  So far, my efforts have left me with a sore back and shoulders but no muscles; I may have to turn to steroids for the hardcore woman weightlifter's body I've always coveted.  Bottom line, kickin' it with Kathy is an okay way to pass some time in the afternoon; now, next time I see any of you, I'll expect comments on my scuplted arms and calves.  Thank you, thank you.   
     

    


06,January,2004


	 
      Howdy folks.  My apologies for being delinquent in my blogging for awhile now.  With my show going on hiatus and me being unemployed to going home to just now getting a laptop and hooked up to the Internet, it's been a crazy few months.  So I'm back with little to report, except that I'm knee deep in temporary Job Search 2004, until I find out if/when our show got picked up for Season Three.  I thought I'd keep you up to speed with my interview progress (if there is any), and just how hard it is to get a shitty job in L.A. even with a college degree!   For those of you who haven't checked it out,  urlLink Craigslist  has proven to be a great resource when searching for a job in a big city.  Just click on your city on the menu, and you'll be privy to tons of apartments for rent, jobs for grabs, and my personal fave, the barter section.  Man, if I only had my degree in "massage therapy."    I've sent, faxed, and emailed out about 50 resumes to various businesses, and I've gotten three calls.  That seems to be the trend when doing these mass mailings.  It's extra hard to get a waitressing position as you have to submit a headshot along with your resume just to be considered (yes, it's an audition), and usually 1,000 women audition for the coveted one waitressing position.  So you tell me, is a funny, quirky, unconventionally cute brunette gonna get the position over nose and jug-job Jill?  Apparently boobs sell booze out here.  I interviewed for the position of hostess at a place that holds kids' parties for stinking rich families in Santa Monica.  Upon entering the facility, I was told to take off my shoes and grab a mat and join the circle.  I kid you not!  So basically, I'd be helping frazzled underworked mothers set up their one year old's birthday party with thirty of the one year old's closest friends!  Apparently the tips are great.  They liked me, and said they'd call me to set up a trial runthrough of a typical party day for this weekend.  They still haven't called.  It's not like I even want the job that badly, but out here, even if they say you have the job, it doesn't mean you have the job.    I'm *holding my thumb and index finger an inch from each other* this close to doing some weird performance act for spare change at the Santa Monica Pier.  Any suggestions as to what my talent should be?    &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,January,2004


	 
        Okay, so New Year's Eve, abbreviated is NYE, my last name.  You'd think that I'd be destined to rock New Year's for that simple reason, but the stars were not given that memo and year after year, I wait to see what might occur.  Now this seems to be a common complaint; "yeah, New Year's is my least favorite holiday; it always sucks" or "it's overrated".  Well, I feel like it's my RIGHT to have a good New Year's since it spells my name, much like the Irish MUST party on Patty's Day.  Last year, I managed a quick get away by leaving the country and time zone and am proud to say that January first never happened for me (thanks for that International Date Line!).  But let me tell you about this year......  I worked....at Sullivan's.  I was there at 2 blowing up balloons and was greeting my first table around 4:30.  Two lesbians who wanted nothing to do with my perky ass and were only there b/c they had a gift certificate that expired on January 1, 2004.  They were on a date and set up camp at my table for two hours.  UGH!  We were running a package that started around 5:30.  $75 a person and that included appetizer, salad, entree, side, dessert.  Later in the evening, I get double sat (two tables at once) with a NINE TOP and an EIGHT TOP!!  Craziness ensued.  Each person at the table of eight is wearing enough diamonds/couture to buy all of our houses and living spaces.  They order a bottle of Cristal, the ONLY bottle in the house. This costs about $380.  But at this point, he could have ordered a bottle of house wine and I would have reacted the same, BUSY!     Anyway, turns out this cat is none other than Kenny Anderson, famed point guard for the Pacers.  I had no clue.  Turns out he is also on the injured list.....mmmhmmm.  So that's work.  Made some money, out by 1:00, ready for a beer.  I attend this house party with Sean, despite just wanting to chill.  Drunk people at 1:00am + Me after work= Annoyed.  Small party, not so bad.  I actually went to grade school with the house owner and his girlfriend is one of my reading coaches at the Julian Center.  I am there for about 45 mins when chaos ensues.  Sean's friend, Tommy, falls over on another friend, Dave, and splits his head open on the door frame.  I, along with Emily and Preston (the only other sober folks) get to drive his drunk, barfing, bleeding ass to the hospital for stiches.  It's 4:00am before he emerges with 10 staples in his head.  I was alone in the waiting room, almost asleep and cursing New Year's.   So that was New Year's Eve 2003.  Anyone want to hang out next year?     
     

    


04,January,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,February,2004


	 
       Okay, so one of my life dreams is to be a backup singer.  I mean, come on, they get to wear the snazzy costumes and chime in with some "ooo"s and "ahhh"s to complement the lead singer, plus there is the added microphone dance that must be perfected (and we all know how well I can cut a rug!).  Some of the artists that I would most like to backup sing with are Elton John (he practically writes his songs for the backup singer!), Billy Joel, and Paul Simon.  Oldies but goodies....if only I could carry a tune.  So, going along with the proposals of late, I propose this:  what ditty would you be belting if appearing on Star Search, American Idol, the Miss/Mr./Mrs. American pagent, or the Grammys?  I would have to go with "Ray of Light" by Madonna.  Despite my current irritation with her shenanigans and fake British accent, that song never fails to put me in a dancing mood.    Check out this site to test your knowledge of  urlLink backup singers .
     

    


26,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,February,2004


	 
       Jon and I eat the same basic meals every week: tacos (my personal favorite), ravioli, salad and bread, frozen pizza, pasta...or we go out.  So I'm wondering what everybody else eats that is quick and easy...especially Jennie and Leah, since I know there won't be meat in your suggestions.  Not to get all Martha on you gals, but I could use some meal ideas.  I have a righteous bean dip recipe that's sure to snackisfy if anyone's interested.    
     

    


25,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,February,2004


	 
          This past Friday, my mom, Tish, and I went to see the traveling Broadway musical, The Lion King.  We actually got to attend a pre-screening of the show courtesy of United Way, so I felt important.  Anyway, I must say that all of the hype was well worth it.  I did enjoy the original cartoon flick, but this blew me away.  The story line is the same, but they have added a couple new songs for the production.  In my opinion (and the Tonys agree as well), the costumes are what make this production so spectacular.  They create a giraffe from a person balancing all fours on stilts and them wearing a long giraffe neck and head.  These creatures come on stage teetering and anbling around, much like a real giraffe.  The opening number (the good old "Circle of Life") brings all the animals of the sahara out to celebrate Simba's brith, including an elephant, a cheetah, gazelles, soaring birds, and zebra.  Just fantastic.    I must also comment on the music, since it is a musical.  It is rich with African influence and Rafiki, the crazy monkey, takes on the role of almost an ancient African healer.  Not that he wasn't in the movie, but it is exaggerated in the live show.  But the new songs, the scenery, the costumes all keep it real with the African theme.  Loved it!  Just in case I've piqued your interest, the show will remain in Indy until the end of March and then goes to Columbus, San Fran, Boston, and Detroit (not in that order), and is always playing up in NYC.  
     

    


24,February,2004


	 
       I am not generally a fan of skunks, nor do I know anyone who is.  But, they do have a one-up on just about every other species because when they die (well, at least when they die as roadkill), they get the last laugh.  They make a stink, if you will.  You may not notice every animal that's a victim of careless drivers, but skunks make you notice their fate with that last blast.  There's a dead skunk on my drive to work that has been stinking up Route 9 for the past couple days and shows no sign of letting up.  I just like the idea of the skunk getting to give a big 'fuck you' to whomever built a highway in thier hood that ultimately led to their death.  Also, I hope that whoever nailed the skunk feels guilty every time they drive by-there's no forgetting what went down with that stench.  Maybe it will help people pay a little more attention to the critters in the road (not to dog anyone who has unwittingly hit an animal-say, a goose-I know sometimes it's unavoidable). 
     

    


23,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,February,2004


	 
       On my drive to work this afternoon, I stopped at Panera to grab some grub and then headed off to the Julian Center.  I took Michigan Road which brings me past a Lowe's hardware store.  Outside of Lowe's was this gentleman dressed as Uncle Sam and clutching a fistfull of cash.  I looked around for some promotion or something to allude to why this man is dressed like this in the rain in front of a hardware store and realized that he was panhandling!     This reminded me of a recent Simpson's episode where Homer falls into panhandling after a drunken night and realizes that he too can panhandle and then buy Marge the diamond jewelry she has always wanted.    Since Sean is currently between jobs, I suggested he dress up as a Leprechan or something and give Uncle Sam a run for his money!
     

    


19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,February,2004


	 
       I have seen "The Apprentice" a few times now, and I find it really irritating that Donald Trump is now being referred to as "The Donald."  No kidding.  How about "The Hairpiece" or "The Toupee?"  Much more suitable if you ask me.  Perhaps worse is how "The Donald" views his lifestyle; it bothers me that he assumes he has what everyone else wants.  Not at all, Hairpiece.  If I ever turned into a person remotely similar to who he is, I'd want one of you guys to hunt me down and kick my ass.  Along the same lines is this new Range Rover commercial I just saw.  It shows these two guys walking alongside a road in the snow in France, backpackin' it.  One guy is telling the other that he wants to major in ceramics.  Then this Range Rover pulls over and gives them a lift, and they get in the car and start drooling all over  themselves at how cool it is.  They look at each other and one tells the other, "Maybe you could minor in ceramics."  And major in something that will enable you to make enough money to buy a fine piece of machinery like this.  I hate that kind of crap and all the assumptions that go along with it; as though everyone who isn't living that type of lifestyle desparately wishes that they were.  Ridiculous.  The happiest person I know is my sister, who works as a therapeutic horseback riding instructor at a non-for-profit organization and makes maybe $25,000 a year.  As far as I'm concerned, Donald can take his hairpiece and Range Rover and shove it.    
     

    


19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,February,2004


	 
      Welp, I'm back from the big interview.  Whew!  Crazy times, ladies, crazy times.  We stayed in a seedy little hotel called the Berkeley Travelodge-good thing Jon was with me or it may not have been a safe option.  The weather wasn't the best-pretty rainy- but that didn't hold Jon and I back from exploring San Francisco on Monday.  It's a great city, especially when you just want to throw some pervs (look around) and not drop much cash.  We kicked it on Fisherman's Wharf and watched the sea lions that have a fine colony there, saw Alcatraz (but didn't take the tour), and ate a great sundae at the Ghiradelli Restaurant (nothing wrong with a "restaurant" that only has chocolate treats on the menu).  Mostly we just walked our asses off, which is some feat with all the hills up in there.  All in all, I give this city the thumbs-up: great public transportation (if I can figure it out, any fool can), clean, good views, and friendly folks.    AND DEN, on Tuesday, the big interview...I put my costume on and cabbed it over to the university.  The other interviewees were pretty friendly, mostly girls finishing up their college degrees (ha! the innocent fools...ain't got shit on me), and the atmosphere wasn't at all competitive, which you might expect.  Basically, how it works is, they have selected 20 folks to interview out of the 90+ that applied.  From those 20, they'll take up to 10, but if they only find 4 that they really want, then they'll only take 4.  The best thing about the day was the professor that's becoming the program director; we'll call him Seamus.  Seamus had a propensity for saying "and stuff," which is something you just don't expect from a really smart guy.  Here are some examples: "Welcome to Berkeley, everybody.  Hope you all have a great day, and stuff...we have a lot in store for you today.  Here's a schedule of what we'll be doing today.  And stuff.  Uh, let me know if you have any questions *3 second pause* and stuff."  I got such a kick out of this guy!  Luckily for me, he cut out the "and stuffs" during the interview; I don't know if I could have held in all my chuckles.    Anywho, after taking the redeye cross-country to NYC and then driving back to Boston, we got home this morning and were pooped like Mr. Hanky.  I have 3 more interviews coming up that I need to saddle up for; Alison, hopefully we can kick it in B-town when I come to check out IU.   
     

    


17,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,February,2004


	 
      Going along with the sing song headlines, I must share with you all about my lunch yesterday.  Now, on Mondays, I don't go to work until 12, which is just lovely.  So I go to Wild Oats on my way to work and create a salad at their incredible salad bar.  Yesterday I was having some trouble selecting a beverage until I spotted it...Dr. Wild, Wild Oats version of the fine Dr. Pepper.  What a find!  I have seen many generic names for the cola, but none quite as fun (Dr. Thunder comes in a close second).  So next time you find yourself at Wild Oats, try Dr. Wild, you won't be disappointed.    Sorry about the failure to include a pic, hope it doesn't spoil the fineness of our blog.  Kudos to Mike and Alison for coming up with a flashy color scheme!
     

    


16,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,February,2004


	 
         Katie, I'll be joining you in California on Sunday!  Not that I'll actually be anywhere close to L.A., but what have you, much closer than I am now.  The big Berkeley interview is on Tuesday; I am sort of forgetting about Valentine's Day because I just want the day after to come.  I really hope California doesn't turn out to suck because I've put all my eggs in its basket (can I say Arnold's basket since he's the governor now?) and wanted to live there for years although I've only been inside the LAX airport.  I think characters in movies like "Dude, Where's My Car?" and the proximity (how's that for a sly plug?) to Mexico (and Mexican food) are the big selling points for me.  This from the girl who based her college choice partly on the fact that a Dave Matthews song was playing on the student radio station while driving around campus...    
     

    


12,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,February,2004


	 
         Were someone to invent a keyboard that gave the same satisfying clackety-clack of the old school typewriter, I'd surely invest in one.  I used to love pounding away on my mom's old typewriter (with or without paper rolled in) just to hear that sound.  Even if you're typing a lot of nonsense, that sound makes you feel like you're working ridiculously hard and should be winded after finishing your assignment.  I guess typewriter-computers wouldn't go over well in offices as all that noise would be enough to drive one a bit crazy, but for personal use, sign me up.    
     

    


10,February,2004


	 
      After driving 30 minutes to work for 5 1/2 months, I have come to recognize a few cars on that drive.  The timing has to really be on for me to get to see these folks, and we only cross paths a couple times a week.  The first one I started to notice based on a license plate which reads "67A POO."  I'm guessing this is not a vanity plate.  I'd love to say this plate resides on a Range Rover or a hideous Hummer, for extra laughs, but no, it's fixed to a Mercury Sable.  How unlucky can you be...I wonder if when they first got the plate, they went along with it hoping no one would notice.  Come on!  Poo?!  I get a nice morning chuckle out of it, that's for sure.     The other guy is quite mysterious in nature.  He drives a shiny blue Beetle (a new one), and up until mid-December, the Beetle has a squiggly pride sticker fixed to the back right window.  Then suddenly, one day, the sticker was missing.  Luckily I can say with a great deal of certainty that it's the same car as I had memorized the plate number.  This incident has led me to many mornings of wondering what happened...why remove the sticker?  In my opinion, it made that car worth noticing.  Did he switch teams?  Was he visiting his mother and had to remove it because she wouldn't approve?  Did someone else take the liberty of removing it in an act of vandalism (or was it stuck on the inside?)?  Perhaps I'll never know.  I've been tempted to follow him to work, but who knows much further he has to drive than I do, and then I'd be really late to work.  Plus he might be a little freaked out.  Or maybe he'd be like, "Hey Indiana (as I still have Indiana plates), I've been wondering what brought you to Massachusetts!"  If some morning he were to pull over and get gas, I'd be tempted to pull over as well and strike up a conversation to get to the bottom of this.  Should I ever crack this mystery, I'll let you folks know.  
     

    


10,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,February,2004


	 
         I have been meaning to post this for a while, but have not been in the office (I had a wee Americorps retreat and then went to Depauw on Friday to check out this exhibit they have in their new gallery about social stratification.  Very sweet!  They even had pieces of two of my fave lady photographers, Nan Goldin and Barbara Krueger...Sean was also a fan).    So back to my original postie.  Last Monday, my roommate, Gretchen, invited me to attend an event called "porneoke" with her at Birdy's.  Now this was actually the same week Birdy's was featuring Jordan Knight, but this was different.  The way she described it was that these bands go up on stage and play familiar songs but change the words to make them dirrty.  Hey why not, plus her psuedo-boyfriend is in one of the bands.  So we go and find out that she was wrong....very wrong.  Porneoke is, in fact, where they play muted porn tapes and call upon two brave folks to come up and narrate these scenes.  There were two bands that opened, but the fun was yet to begin!  I made up my mind that there was no way that I could be funny on the spot and would not be porneoking....I would much rather belt out "I will always love you" on stage.  But the crowd was small and the lady population was smaller.  Gretchen was recuited first and actually did well (but her partner was a lady, so it eased the tension).  Then they called Scott (the psuedo-boyf) and the blonde sitting next to him....I looked around, searching for another "the blonde", but to no avail.  So we go up there and I already told him the chances of me being funny were nill.  Then what do we get?  We get a cartoon scene with a witch who has a man eating vagina!  "What the....?" was about all I was capable of....and it just kept getting better.  The next scene we were dealt was a western with a pig and a cat all wooing this naked lady.  The pig was violent and shot the cat's penis THREE times (there was even a cartoon dramatization of the holes).  This was too much and had me in stiches......needless to say, we did not win the Princess Lea (?) pez dispenser that was the grand prize.    If any one is interested in attending, I believe it will be a monthly ordeal.  I would be up for going, but participating is another story :)     
     

    


09,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,February,2004


	 
      Ain't got nothin new to contribute in particular, but here are some random facts in the spirit of keepin' on with the blog.  1.  Have I mentioned that the street I work on is called Lovers Lane?  Cute, yes, but impossible to keep the street sign safe from thieves (next one they put up has my name on it), making it a tough street to find. 2.  They played "Flip Fantasia" as background music on NPR this morning around 10. 3.  One of my fish died two nights ago of mysterious causes; the two babies, however, are still maxin' out relaxin' in their special netted off area (aka, nursery...that's really what the box said). 4.  Rev. Al Sharpton is standing strong as ever in the Democratic primaries and got 3rd place in South Carolina (he received more votes than Howard Dean!).  Go Big Al! 5.  I can't take credit for this random fact since Jon came up with it but, nonetheless, here it its: Joe Lieberman sounds like the guy from Alf.  Too bad he dropped out of the race; I'm surprised he didn't make a bigger point of that, perhaps by having signs made that said "Vote for Lieberman" with Alf's picture on them.   6.  The premiere of the new season of Crank Yankers is next Tuesday, Feb. 10, so don't go making any plans for that night.      7.  I really hate reality tv but still watch it out of boredom and laziness occasionally.  The new season of the Real World looks terrible. 8.  Saturday is Jon's and my one year anniversary; cheers to that, and a good ol' fashioned salute to Jon.  Wahoo! 9.  Today at Subway there was a hair in Grace's sandwich, but the lady who works there is so nice I didn't have the heart to say anything.  I don't want any bad blood between us as I frequent this location for their righteous sandwiches, plus she looked clean. 10.  Also at Subway...the same hairnet-less woman put up a sign requesting people not to talk on their cell phones whilst ordering.  I wholeheartedly applaud that and told her so.  This earned me a couple extra tomato slices.  
     

    


01,February,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,February,2004


	 
      I thought of each and every one of you in the world of Close Proximity yesterday when I got my hair cut.  Needless to say, awkward conversations ensued.  I tried the tactic Katie mentioned of giving quick answers after awhile, but that didn't not deter this friendly gal.  She asked me how I came to this hair salon and I told her I picked it randomly because I liked the name.  REALLY?!?!  WOW!  Like that was a super-bold move on my part.  Then she asked me how long I had lived around here and I said 5 months.  "Don't you just love the area?"  I explained that I thought Boston was great but the weather sucked.  "Can't have it all," she said, disappointed in my reaction.  Oh yes you can, I thought to myself.  It's called California.  I kept this thought to myself as she was from here (which I felt obligated to ask, even thought she had a thick, unmistakably Boston accent) and quite protective of her native parts.  Then we chatted about football for a little bit, and it hit home to her that I was from the same Indinanapolis that the Indianapolis Colts are.  "Whoa...how 'bout that game?   Pats really showed 'em!" she said.  I supposed so, not really wanting to get into this as I couldn't care less whether the Colts made it to the Super Bowl.  She didn't want to drop it, and I must say I got a bit defensive of the Colts.  It's not like they suck and had no chance.  I told her my thoughts on the game and all she had to say was, "Well...Peyton Manning..." as though it were obvious what she meant.  What, that he played two perfect games before sucking it up in New England?  I just had that feeling that she was parroting comments made by other folks (yes, probably guys) and had no idea what they meant.  We moved on, and the discussion began to center around my hair...not my favorite topic.  "It looks GREAT!  This cut is just such a good LOOK for you!"  I'm glad she thought so but am also wise to the fact that your hairdresser has to make these comments.  She just wouldn't let it go.  Even when I was nearly finished and sitting peacefully under these weird heat-lamp things they had to dry my hair, she'd pop around the corner armed with another hair care product and slap some more crap on my hair to get it nice 'n stiff, just the way any helmet-head loving gal likes.  "Wow-don't you love the color?!  You have such beautiful HAIR!"  You can only enthusiastically say "YES!!!"  so many times before it fades into a dull, "whatever, fine by me."  Whew!  Glad that's over with.  And my hair's nice and short so hopefully I can avoid going back for quite some time.  
     

    


26,March,2004


	 
       Last night, Jon and I went to see Bob Dylan play at this little club in Boston.  The show was pretty cool (from what I could hear, anyway...my ears are all plugged up from a cold), and we managed to finagle our way to a spot where we could actually see Bobby D himself.  Anyway, the funniest thing happened: two 40ish guys squeezed right in front of Jon and I and lit up a joint.  They were all hunched over it and thought they were supersmooth, until the security guard (who was, mind you, about 5 feet away) busted them.  It was great watching these clowns' reaction; I have this whole storyline in my head that they were both probably tokers when they were younger.  A few days ago one of them busted his son for weed, decides to confiscate the weed and then relive his glory days by smoking up at a Dylan concert (keep in mind that you can't smoke cigarettes in bars here).  Riiiiiiiiight.  Furthermore the joint was about half the size of my pinkie and definitely not worth getting busted over.  Lucky for these guys, security was laid-back and let them stay at the show.  
     

    


24,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,March,2004


	 
         On my way to the doc's office today (yes, the biannual sinus infection is here and I want a sinusectomy), I passed a car with the bumber sticker "A hamburger stops a beating heart".  Just like anyone who knows Alison knows she sleeps in her makeup, anyone who knows me knows I have a soft spot for bumber stickers (exhibit A: the perkster).  This one takes the cake or shall I say hay?   
     

    


17,March,2004


	 
          Yes, today is St. Patrick's Day and I, being the Cathedral grad I am, am going to pay homage to this hoppin' holiday.  It seems like this is the day of the year that everyone claims their Irish heritage, even if it means that their fourth uncle twice removed is married to a gal whose cousins are Irish.  Hey, why not?  Shout out to the Irish who are celebrating their patron saint today :)  Oh yeah and here is a link to a fun  urlLink Patty's Day activity .    It's great to be back to the blog!  I have been away from work (aka my computer time) for a while now, but attended some great conferences and got to hang with some fellow Americorps members for a couple days in Bloomington for a retreat.  It was an educational time to learn more about the presidential platforms on community service, different diversity issues, and other things during our sessions as well as kick it with my peers.  Shannon, I also met Matt's twin!  Seriously, I did a double take thinking "uh, does Mr. Hautman have a double life?".  You know how everyone is supposed to have an identical twin out there?  Well, Matt's lives in South Bend and his name is Ben.  I wish I could have taken a photo, but I think he may have found that intrusive!  Anyway, that's all for now.....
     

    


16,March,2004


	 
         "I'm gonna buy a gun and start a war If you can tell me something worth fighting for..."  I'll tell you what I want to fight for.  Naps.  I could use a daily siesta between the hours of 2 and 3.  Not only would workers be happier, I think they'd perform their jobs more effectively.  I'll also advocate for the distribution of adult-sized carpet samples on which to sleep, and perhaps pillows.  Another thing I'd like to see is nap rooms at restaurants; after a big meal, all you really want to do is lay it down for awhile.  While I realize this isn't practical, I still think it'd be nice.  Here's a  urlLink poem  for napping inspiration.    
     

    


16,March,2004


	 
          Take a gander at this  urlLink video clip  when you're bored.  It depicts Donald Rumsfeld blatantly contradicting himself as he tries to save face about pushing for war in Iraq.   
     

    


16,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,March,2004


	 
         Did anyone catch the Simpsons on Sunday?  I watched part of it, and it was a really funny one about Raffi, a popular children's singer.  In the episode his name was Roofi.  Most of you have probably heard Raffi's classic "Baby Beluga," but I'd like to share some tidbits from other Raffi songs.  These verses pop into my head at random times and I can't get them out, so be careful not to start singing them to yourself, comforting as they are.  1.  "I may not know their lingo, but I can say by jingo.  No matter where you live, we can shake hands." 2.  "Biscuits in the oven, gonna watch 'em rise.  Right before my very eyes, hey hey." 3.  "All I really need is a song in my heart and love in my family." (this is the refrain, and the verses list other things Raffi also needs: food in his belly, clean air for breathing, pure grain alcohol for drinking...I must say, the refrain is pretty misleading.) 4.  "You may see a baboon basking in the balcony...a lion licking a lemon..." 5.  "This old man, he plays five, he plays five with his friend Clive.  Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, uh-huh."  (Let's face it, Raffi has an edge to him most rock musicians would kill for.)  The whole point of this blog, and it was also the point of the Simpsons episode, is how ridiculous it is that a grown man can make a ton of money singing these lame tunes for kids who don't know any better.  Sure, they're clean-cut and soothing, but so are a lot of other songs.  It's the same thing that shocks me about someone's career being dressing up like the Gymboree clown and doing videos; what are they thinking?  Oh well.  I'll probably end up buying all of his cds for my own kids and he'll have the last laugh.     
     

    


11,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

11,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,March,2004


	 
       Today has been a fun music day for me because I'm having an 80s revival.  There's nothing better than some 80s classics to get you revved up on the drive to work.  And I must admit, I like to rock out in my Camry; it can be odd at times to be sitting at a light and singing away, but what have you.  You get used to it, and hopefully it gives the folks around me a good morning chuckle.  Everyone can use a laugh at 7:30 am, and I'm happy to be the supplier.  At any rate, here's a top ten list of some of my favorite 80s tunes, and perhaps you all would like to add some of yours.  10.  If You Leave -O.M.D. 9.   Waiting For a Star to Fall -Boy Meet Girl 8.   Miss You Much -Janet Jackson 7.   Never Tear Us Apart -INXS 6.  Invisible Touch -Genesis 5.  Hangin' Tough -NKOTB (I had a fort in my closet dedicated to this band called "NKOTB and Me") 4.  P.Y.T. -Michael Jackson 3.  Melt with You -Modern English 2.  Don't Dream It's Over -Crowded House 1.  Blame it on the Rain -Milli Vanilli (I celebrate Rob and Fab's entire catalogue and yearn for a comeback)  
     

    


09,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

08,March,2004


	 
        +    Perhaps is the clouds, perhaps it's the day of Mon, but for some reason, I have been quite comtemplative and observant today.  While driving to work, I was behind this sport beheamoth vehicle that was sporting an environmental license plate and was struck by the irony of a gas guzzling monstrosity supporting the natural wilderness it's destroying.  hmmm....  Since Mondays are my late days at the Julian Center (I don't arrive until 12!), I go to the gym in the morning because then I feel like I have had a productive morning.  Since I have been doing this for the better part of five months now, I have some regulars that I swear with: the Washington Fire Dept makes an appearance if I get there early enough, the extremely skinny lady who runs like a ostrich, and these gals who once gave me some lip for using the very treadmill they ALWAYS use.  Anyway, today I was especially intrigued with some randon folks who came to join my workout sess.  First there was the man who was dressed in a navy turtleneck, khakis, and brown loafers going for a brisk walk on the treadmill (I was waiting for him to start jogging, but no such luck).  Then there were two adolescent boys lifting weights in their school uniforms and yahmechas (sp? and btw, I belong to the Jewish Community Center's gym, despite being a gentile).  So now it's cool to skip school and head to the gym?  Lastly, as I was leaving, I overheard these ladies discussing eggplant.  One was apparently pissed at some chef who did not make the eggplant soft enough and was complaining that "eggplant should be like butter, melt in your mouth"  (I was really tickled by the "like butter" being uttered at the JCC) and she was going to have words with this poor chef.    All in all, I had a great workout and threw some great pervs! 
     

    


03,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,March,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,April,2004


	 
                                         Welp, going along with the asking Alison to arrange some pics theme, here are some photos of when my mom, Tish, and I went to the  urlLink Exotic Feline Rescue  the other weekend.  She loves big cats like lions and tigers and, once she caught word of this rescue (and that it was only an hour outside Indy), she had to go!  We had a great time and really enjoyed getting to see the animals all up close and personal.  I also appreciate that they rescue these animals from people that are mistreating them or from the circus!  When you go, you have a guide that leads you around the rescue (which houses 132 big cats) along these paths that lead right next to their "exhibits" (I am not a fan of that reference, so I called them pens).  You can snap pics and observe, but steer clear of getting too close or else you might loose a finger or get sprayed (as this one fellow did in our tour group!).  It is a mere $10 to tour and all of the proceeds are used for the rescue.  The tour guides are all volunteer, as well as most of the workers.  All in all, it's a great place and I highly recommend going.  I think the highlight for Tish was seeing that there was a lion named after her!  Personally, I liked the wee cubs (they had 9 6mo old tiger cubs) and the scrap between two tigers (one in a water bin, the other being slapped!).  Grrrrrr......  
     

    


26,April,2004


	 
      Here are some of my pictures from this weekend (Alison, I trust you'll fix these photos!).  My sister Natasha came out to visit and we had a rockin' good time.  The first couple are from the Cape and the others from downtown Boston...ohhhh goodtimes.  You'll notice that Natasha and I have on matching Boston sweatshirts...it got a little brisk out on Sunday so we had to invest in sweatshirts before walking the Freedom Trail.  Between the sweatshirts and the constant snapshots (Tash had 2 cameras, a black and white and color, plus my digital), I'm sure folks got a good chuckle at us crazy tourists.  Little do they know...                
     

    


26,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,April,2004


	 
       I just finished reading "Dude, Where's My Country" by  urlLink Michael Moore  (and I would highly recommend it to anybody!), and towards the end of the book he talks about the upcoming election and who he thinks would be able to beat Bush.  Moore proposes that America's favorite talk show host,  urlLink Oprah Winfrey , run for president.  President Oprah!  I love it.  Vote Oprah!  Can you imagine the army of women out there campaigning for Oprah?  And if Dr. Phil got in on the action, oh man...he could counsel people about voting.  "Still considering voting for Bush?  Are you a masochist?  Self-destructive?  Come on now!  Do you want positive change in your life?"  That Southern twang always gets the crowd going.  In all seriousness, I would totally vote for Oprah (maybe partly just so I could say things like "Did you catch President Oprah's State of the Union address last night?").  I know Boots said that watching her show raises people's stress levels, but still...she gets things done and she is actually "in touch" with America.  Would you vote Oprah if you could?    
     

    


26,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,April,2004


	 
         Some of you may be familiar with the street Meridian in Indy.  You know that this is a main highway/road in Indy and is quite populated with automotive traffic at all times of day.  As I was driving to work yesterday, I spotted a lady riding her horse donning a whitle bicycle helmet along Kessler Blvd towards the Meridian intersection.  I was fascinated and rummaged through my purse to locate my digital camera because this had to be documented!  When the light turned green, she and Mr. Ed trotted across the road and continued on their way.....it was awesome.  I did snag a quick photo, but my computer skills are nill and I have yet to download it from my camera.  It just goes to show that nice weather merits all sorts of tomfoolery in Naptown! 
     

    


14,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,April,2004


	 
         Today is blue day for me.  I broke up with Sean, my (ex) boyfriend, last night and it was not fun.  It's almost 3:00pm and I am bored, so I have been thinking my favorite things to cheer myself up.  Here is what I have come up with:    Root beer floats        I gave up soda for Lent and have just started getting back into the swing of  carbonated bevs since Easter, so the root beer float is a perfect way to fuse soda with my fave food, ice cream!     Drumsticks         Not the chicken kind, the ice cream novelty kind.  They used to be standards at my dad's house when I was a youth and I have just rediscovered the goodness.    Yoga        Something I stongly recommend for anyone.  I have a weekly class that I attend on Tuesdays (for FREE!) at my gym.  Very relaxing and soothing.      Fella          My little black cat is the best!  He does funny things that make me laugh and has quite a personality.  Recently, each time he goes outside, he lifts his front left paw and hops/limps like he was three legs until he get to the grass.  It gets me every time!     The Apprentice        I don't kick it with reality shows all that much, but this one has me hooked.  I tape it every Thursday so that I can watch it after work.  Tomorrow is the season finale, so the world with know if Kwame or Bill makes the cut.    Nalgene         I drink water like it's going out of style and without my Nalgene water bottle, I would be one thirsty girl.  It ensures that I drink the necessary 64 oz of water daily (usually more) and is a billboard for my favorite free music stickers.  I recently added a Basement Jaxx one that is super fly.  So there are some of my favorite things.....I know Oprah has hers, but what are some of yours?  
     

    


13,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,April,2004


	 
       So, Arizona it is!  Jon and I just got back from visiting Arizona last night and made the decision to move there.  We had such a good time...we flew into Phoenix on Friday, and Friday afternoon went to ASU where I met with a few of the professors that I'll be learning from/working with next semester (all very cool).  But I won't try to fool you into thinking the professors impacted this decision at all...once I saw the plethora of Mexican restaurants, I was sold.  My brother John showed us around the area; everything is so new and clean and, most importantly, WARM.  Then Sat. we took a road trip up to Sedona, which is just a couple hours away.     It's a really beautiful area with all these mountains and red rocks.  We did a little mountain biking, checked out an art fair (it's a really artsy place), and drove to a winery (yeah, a winery in Arizona...not bad, though).   We stayed in Flagstaff Sat. night at this great hotel where you get FREE DRINKS from 5:30-7:30, free massages, and free breakfast the next am (Embassy Suites...and yes it is a national thing, we asked!).  What's amazing about AZ is you pass through a different ecosystem like every 20 min. you drive; Flagstaff is just 2 hours away from Phoenix and still had snow in the mountains.  I'm really jazzed about all the trips we can take from Phoenix...Mexico, Vegas, Southern Cali...all not too far at all.  Good times...and all visitors welcome.       
     

    


12,April,2004


	 
      I believe that all y'all except Katie and Leah have seem my roommate's cat, Jupiter.  He is a grey tabby cat with white paws and what I call tan "squirrel fur" on his tummy.  His is also a husky cat, living up to the name Jupiter.  Most visitors comment on Jupiter's size and weight, but he doesn't seem to mind.     Anyway, this cat, Mikesch, has Jupiter out weighed by at least a couple kilos....      If you'd like to read how this fine German cat got so cubby, check out this  urlLink article  from yahoo.  
     

    


06,April,2004


	 
       Okay, so out of the whole Proximity crew, I probably score a 2/10 when it comes to hair issues.  I have purchased and experimented with perhaps eight hair products in my entire life and never really felt like I needed any of it.  But, before you shoot me, I have finally found a product that I can endorse:  urlLink Garnier Fructis' Fiber Gum Putty  (or something like that).  It's this wicked stuff that is like pomade mixed with hair gel mixed with cotton.  It claims the "no stick" factor and lives up to it, but trust me, I doubted at first.  I tend to use mine prior to blow drying, but it can also be used on dry hair.  All it does is help my hair fall into place without much styling (because if my daily beauty regimen starts taking more than 10 mins, I need help!), but also allow me to tweek when necessary.  All in all, I cannot do enough to describe the glory that is this product.  Since my hair isn't curly (Shan, Alison, and Jenny), I cannot test that market, but I have faith.  So go and buy this, $2.99 at any Target!
     

    


06,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,April,2004


	 
         Okay, so last night my roommate, Gretchen, and I decided to ditch working at Sully's (it was nauseatingly slow!) and go out for dinner.  We went to a little cafe in Broad Ripple and ordered dinner; I got the vegetarian lasagna.  While we are waiting for our food, we sit and chat for a while and then start digging in once our chow arrives.  Now I knew that the lasagna was made with fake meat, according to the waitress, and figured it was worth giving a whirl.  It was awesome!  Now I have never been a big fan of the whole fake meat thing, having only tried the "not dog" hot dog, but this was like turning over a whole new leaf.  So our waitress comes with our check and is acting awkward and uncomfortable.  She begins to explain how she accidentally gave me the real meat lasagna and hopes it wasn't a problem.  Ordinarily, I would be annoyed, but not this time since I enjoyed the lasagna so much.  It lead me to an epiphany: I like meat and am swearing off vegetarianism.  It's been a great ride and I figure, if I like the stuff, why not?  Teddy will be proud, no more grazing in the yard.  By the way, April Fool's!  On a serious note, I got a 23% on the whole Emo-quiz as well....I guess I need to tap into my emotional core.  
     

    


01,April,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

27,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,May,2004


	 
       I'm always looking for some fresh new jives to get the party started (aka, jolt myself into reality) on my way to work, and I thought you gals might be as well.  So here's a band that I was introduced to by a British friend while in New Zealand (I still feel like I owe her one, that's how great they are!).  They're called Groove Armada.  I'd recommend "Goodbye Country, Hello Nightclub" or "Lovebox."  If you guys have some suggestions, that'd be great.  It's too bad mixed tapes are no longer hip...I'd totally throw a Groove Armada tune on there in the #1 spot!    
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
       Last night I went to this club Kameleon with my neighbor, Amber, and some pals from  Sully's to dance dance dance to some fine 80's tunes (the new wave kind, not so much Starship).  Of course some of it sucked, but once the DJs got their groove, it was The Cure, Interpol, New Order, James, Blur etc. all the way.  Goodtimes....  Anyway, one of our convos was about how the Catholic Church had recently proclaimed that they will not distribute Communion to any parishoner who is involved with abortion practices(aka a doc who performs them, etc.).  Now is my church, just this past Sunday, our priest gave us a lecture about leaving early and coming late and then dropped the bomb: apparently some people in our church have not been eating their host at Communion and have been leaving it in the pews and song books instead.  Of course for a devout Catholic who believes that the host is actually the body of Christ, this is a tragedy.  As for me, I was just waiting for him to say "The body of Christ does not belong in the pews or the song books, it needs to get in your belly!".   Oh and btw, The Cure, Interpol, Mogwai and others will be touring this summer, according to the Cure's website.  Looks like Cincy, Chi-town, and Detroit are all on the list, but no Indy....     
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
        and a happy day for me!!!! im not sure why I am taking such delight in the news that jam band extrordinaire  urlLink Phish is finally breaking up !!!  I'm not sure what makes me so happy about it really.  I guess it's because I really hate them.  I also really hate faux hippies, which make up Phish's core audience.  I mean, COME ON!!  Those stupid ass stickers and patches that their devotees manage to put everywhere, and act as a mating call to each other.  Driving around you see Jesus fish, and Phish fish on people's cars and I think, what's the difference?  Either way the driver is devoted to something equally generic and also feels the need to tell the world about it.  I'll apologize to anyone on this blog that happens to like them,  oh hell, no I won't.  I'm going to relish this for at least an hour. 
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,May,2004


	 
         Get what's yours by going to  urlLink this link.   If you sign this World Wildlife petition to cut global warming emissions, you'll be e-mailed a coupon for a free scoop of Ben and Jerry's ice cream.  No, it's not one of those scams, I've already signed the petition and got my coupon.  You can also e-mail the petition to any of your environment friendly/ice-cream loving (Jennie, you're the first one I sent this to!) friends.  Thanks guys! 
     

    


24,May,2004


	 
       It's 3:00 and I am bored at work, so why not post again?  I read  urlLink this article  on Indy Star online today and it piqued my interest.  Apparently Muncie, IN is banning people from displaying the Confederate Flag while staying at this public park/campsite.  This also appears to be mainly a trailer park inhabited by people from a low socio-economic class.  But it made me think of a larger issue, why the Confederate Flag?  Now, according to people I have met from the South, the Confederate Flag is a symbol of "Southern Pride".  Others view the flag as having a latent meaning of hatred for African-Americans or minorities in general.  I asked some of the ladies at The Julian Center about their opinions and most of them agree with the latter, but they were also all African-American.  Personally, I am very intrigued with how people view symbols and I often find that most symbolic objects are not given just one, face value, meaning.  What is your take on this?      Also, while I searched Google for this photo, I came across a book that you might like to read if you are interested in the evolution of the Confederate Flag.  It's called "The Damned Red Flags of Rebellion" by Richard Rollins.    
     

    


21,May,2004


	 
         So after a kickin' start with The Stills and crew show on Friday and a fine breaky with Al, Mike, and Aaron on Sat, my weekend took a turn for the worse: I had to attend my cousin's graduation from Cathedral on Sunday (bummer I had to work on Sat and miss the Open House....free drinks!).  Now I have suffered through two graduations myself, but they were my OWN graduations, so it never occured to me that I was putting my beloved family members through ulitmate hell by asking them to attend.  Now parents are one thing, but I had my brother, grandmother, and uncle at my high school graduation....how mean!  So yes, Allison's graduation was not fun since I didn't know any of her classmates, stupid Mr. Rhoades was the speaker AGAIN, and it took almost three hours.  Of course it was nice to see her prance across the stage and accept her diploma holder, sans diploma, from the second balcony of Clowes.  Had they not announced her name, I wouldn't have been able to distinguish her from the rest of the crowd.  About the only bonus was getting to hit up Steak and Shake with her sibs, Phil and Rachel afterwards....mmmmm, chocolate chip shakes alive.         
     

    


21,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,May,2004


	 
          In all my years of having people mispronounce my last name in Indiana, little did I know that some distant Tarbox relatives have been whooping it up on the East Coast.  Here are some things I have learned: 1.  There is a town in Massachusetts-a very small one-called Tarbox. 2.  There's another town in Rhode Island called Tarbox Corner. 3.  There is a Tarbox car dealership in Rhode Island (Toyota...I happen to own a Camry!).  It was quite a shock to my system the first time I saw the license plate "frame" with Tarbox in big block letters.  I'm just not used to seeing my last name anywhere other than in relation to me or someone in my immediate family.   4.  This is the best one of all.  There is a band called the Tarbox Ramblers from Cambridge, Mass that plays weekly at this bar in Cambridge.  Oh yes, I'll be checking them out.  I just checked out their website ( urlLink www.tarboxramblers.com ), and get this, they opened for Van Morrison when he was out here in April!  Holy mackerel, I waited too long to investigate this one...imagine me meeting Michael Tarbox at a Tarbox Ramblers show, getting friendly, and then him hooking me and Jon up with some sweet seats to the Tarbox Ramblers/Van Morrison show.  I'm not sure how much I'll dig the Ramblers-they're country/folksy-but how often do you see a band with your last name in the title?!  For me, this'll be a first.    P.S. I accidentally went to spell check just now instead of upload file, and it suggested I replace Tarbox with Throbs.  ???  Maybe it's not as popular as I thought! 
     

    


21,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,May,2004


	 
         Okay.  Let's face it, I could pass for 16 at times.  I still get carded for cigarettes and even the occasional R-rated movie.  Most of the time this doesn't bother me, but when I'm hitting the town with Gracie (the 2 year old I take care of, pictured above), my youthful looks lead to lots of disapproving looks.  It's now easier for me to imagine what is would be like to be in a wheelchair and constantly have people looking at you and then either quickly looking the other way or giving a warm, supportive "wheelchairs are okay by me" smile.  I mostly get a more menacing, "the likes of you shouldn't be in THIS mall" kind of look from bitchy, Talbots-wearing, Audi station wagon-driving suburban moms.  Part of me wants to yell that I'm 23, she's not even mine, hey I'm studying for my PhD next year, and if she were mine, I'd be proud as hell and you can shove it up your ass!  Another part gets some satisfaction from how mad it makes these crazy women that I'd have the gall to have a baby.  Pop a Zanax, lady.    But the looks from these ladies aren't the worst part of shopping.  Abercrombie and Fitch has that covered.  I have this $75 gift card for that awful store that I received as a Christmas gift, and it's been a thorn in my side ever since.  Every time Grace and I go to the mall (and yes, I only go with Grace: she's a fantastic, opinionated shopping partner, and I'd never step foot in a mall around here on the weekend), I buck up and go into A&F in the hopes of using the gift card.  I hear the techno grooves thumping at least 8 stores away and usually cower in fear and run the other direction.  But a couple weeks ago, I forced myself to go in and picked up a couple "women's" shirts.  More like pre-pubescent shirts.  They seemed small, and no way was I trying them on, so I got larges and darted out of there.  I tried them on at home to find they ended a few inches shy of my belly button.  Hell no!  I may have rocked that look in high school and early college (I can't believe that!  Midriff-baring and bareback shirts?!  What was I thinking!!!), but I'm a little too old lady for that now.  Anyway, I exchanged those scraps of fabric today for a fairly normal button-down shirt for Jon as nothing in the women's department would cover my ass or belly.  The sales-wench kindly balled up Jon's shirt and thrust it into a naked-woman bag and requested an additional 72 cents as my gift card didn't cover the entire amount.  Ha!  At least I can rest easy knowing that I got what was mine from A&F (formerly known as Abercrombie and Snatch) back in the day.  In my opinion, A&F represents the worst of America (but the guy pictued below...not so bad).       
     

    


20,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,May,2004


	 
         Today I went to lunch with my eighteen year old cousin, Alison.  Now those of you who know her, know her and her escapades.  Those of you who don't, let's just say, her last day of school was last Friday and she was sent home for wearing a "provactive" outfit for senior dress up day.  Black eyeliner should just be tattooed on her eyes.  So today she expresses a deep need to chat with me....so off to the Bakehouse in Broad Ripple we go (yum yummy, btw).  After about 15 mins of mindless chatter, she pops the question "can you go to the BMV and get me a copy of your driver's license before I go to Florida; I lost my fake ID?". I politely explain that I have straight blondish hair in my pic, am wearing overalls, and it looks like I am missing a tooth...aka, we look nothing alike!  Then it occurs to me, what kind of prude am I being?  What's the worst that could happen?  It's confiscated and I just deny knowing her.  Why am I being so anal?  So I guess somewhere between turning 21 and graduating from college, I lost the screw the man attitude and gained the I can go to jail for that attitude.  Is this one more brick in the wall of becoming an adult?  Should I start buying things that beep, ring, and hum and hang out at Starbucks?   
     

    


19,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

19,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

18,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

17,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,May,2004


	 
      Hi guys! its good to be bloggin again.  I was in new york for the last week doing stuff for the One Show festival and receiving my award.  We got the bronze pencil which was a bit dissapointing but honestly i can't be dissapointed as this is the highest honor one can receive at this stage in the career and even a bronze is way more than i had ever dreamed i'd get.  the portfolio review went well.  there were people from lots of agencies, mostly from new york that were all sitting at separate tables and you could go sit down and have them look through your book and give you advice.  all the advice pretty much cancelled each other out though which was kind of funny.  if one person had a favorite ad, it was another persons least favorite ad.  this just proves again that this is such a subjective business that i guess i should just stay my course and hope that someone wants to hire me in LA before i make massive changes to my book. one guy who i really admire actually said he "loved my book" which floored me.  So all in alll, it was an ego booster which i needed desparately.    Since john has been laid off (YEAH!!!!! severence pay and the whole summer before grad school, wedding, honeymoon, moving OFF!!) we are going to work on some more ads for my book together.  he is good at the computer and i have lots of ideas that need to be translated from paper to real ads.  He is also taking LOTS of picturs and im hoping hell set up a photo blog soon so you can see them.    So, I think ill go to the agency to get advice from my boss about how to proceed from here.  Ill also take my 2.5 years of work off their broke ass computers so i can have it all on my home computer and safe!  We're wrapping up all the wedding details slowly but surely and i cant believe its only like 3 weeks away!!! thats very exciting but nerve wracking as I feel like there are details im forgetting, but that's what i have a wedding coordinator for.  Thank god for her!!    ill blog something better soon once i get some shit done.  love ya ladies! 
     

    


14,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

13,May,2004


	 
       Wahoo!  I just registered for my fall classes for next semester.  I'm getting so excited...not for school, but for school supplies shopping!  Only partly kidding...that's obviously the best part of going to school.  Shan, you'll have to give me tips on any new must-haves for my educational needs (but you better not suggest one of those creepy baskets as a backpack alternative).  Anyway, these are the classes I'll be taking: Pro-Seminar in School Psychology, School Psych Ethics and Practice, Multiple Regression/Correlation Methods (ahh, stats...hope this teacher doesn't hate me like my last big witch of a stats teacher did...Jennie can vouch for that!), Theoretical Issues & Research in Human Development, and Applied Behavior Analyses.  I'll let any of you borrow the books when I'm done on these fascinating topics, just let me know.  I'll even tape-record the lectures for ya on topics of particular interest.  At any rate...the whole registering for classes thing makes going back to school feel so real and I'm so jazzed for that!!!  Best of all was looking at my schedule...my earliest day is an 8:30 on Wed.  But then that's before I get my internship so we'll see if this blissful-looking schedule lasts.  I don't mind doing a crapload of work as long as I can do it on my own time.  Ooh and I can't wait to start talking in terms of semesters and breaks again!  Yip yip ooooh yeah.  
     

    


13,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

12,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

11,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,May,2004


	 
          There's no place like Boston for baseball.  If there's one place that can compete with Boston baseball, it's gotta be Chicago.  But I grew up going to Cubs games and maybe I wasn't old enough to appreciate the atmosphere then, but this just seems like another league (which is literally is, I guess).  Jon scored some awesome Red Sox tickets from work last night-7th row, between home plate and first base-and by the bottom of the 7th inning, we snuck into 2nd row (too bad I didn't have my camera).  My personal favorite players are Jason Varitek, the catcher, Johnny Damon, and of course Pedro Martinez, the pitcher who'll start nailing batters in the head (intentionally) when he gets pissed off.  But I think what really makes the game is the crowd...last night, some older guys start teaching this little boy (who they earlier spilled beer on) the "no batta no batta...swiiiiiiiiiiing" chant, a stunt that ended with the little boy (probably just shy of 7) yelling at the batter, "you SUCK!"  Then you've got the classy Boston accents all around, either ripping players to shreds or defending them ("I don't care what you say, he's got hahrt"...that's heart, by the way).  And when you leave you're bombarded with locals peddling t-shirts with slogans like "Anyone can have a bad century" (the seller of these shirts commented that if we'd get the Bambino up out his grave, he'd drill him in the ass) and "Jeter blows A-Rod" (those are a couple Yankees players).  Last year during the playoffs against New York, fans altered "Reverse Curve" road signs to say "Reverse the Curse."  Enthusiasm isn't exactly the word for the Boston crowd...maybe more like obsession.  But if nothing else, you've gotta admire them for never giving up on their team.   
     

    


07,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,May,2004


	 
        Now I know some of you ladies moonlight as a waitress/hostess or have at one point in time.  For those of you that went to college more than 100 miles away from your hometown and do not currently reside in said hometown, I doubt you frequently run into people you know from high school or college at your restaurant.  I do....and it sucks!  Last night I waited on Alex Yates, a fella I went to college with, and his family.  When the family asked how we know each other, he said from DePauw.  They hid their surprise and promptly asked me if I graduated!!  Pardon?  Did you say you wanted your ribeye in your lap?  Will do!  Here in lies the worst part of waiting tables, no matter where you work; your "guests" will often presume you are an idiot because you are waiting tables.  I have found this at PF Chang's and Sullivan's, so it is not the restaurant.  I also find myself eager to share that "YES, I did graduate!  Right now I have two jobs, one that serves my community, not my checking account, and one that takes your order...what do you want?".   I often find myself remembering that in New Zealand, I cleaned hotel bathrooms for a buck and no one flinched!  My flatmates did it, my friends did it; it was almost a right of passage into a new town.  So yeah, I will deal with John Selbourne, John Cavanaugh, and Alex and I will get all of the free steaks I want!  
     

    


05,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

05,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,May,2004


	 
       &em ailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,May,2004


	 
      While shopping at Half Price Books this weekend, it occured to me that there are certain constants, or givens, in this world.  As dear old Cathedral football coach, Rick Streiff would put it, "all you gotta do is stay white and die".  I would add get a job, but that's me.  In the world of used music, I have found that there are always certain cds that flood the used cd racks.  It seems that no matter what store, in what city, in what country I go to, I will always find these cds.     Anything by Belly, usually King, but sometimes Star.     Not that Bush is my fave band, but this album must be their worst!     Usually there is a selection by Madonna, and I would venture to say that this one gets resold the most.     I KNOW you have all seen this while searching for Republica or some other band that begins with R.     Perhaps this was right next to the 50 copies of "One Hot Minute".   What is some of the junk you always have to sift through when used cd shopping? 
     

    


04,May,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,May,2004


	 
         It's time for me to let the cat out of the bag.  I've been hiding out in Boston all this time because...Jon and I have a child.  That's right, a child.  His name is Dinh Van Tuan, he's 7 years old, and he lives in Vietnam.  How does all this add up, you're wondering?  Well, we adopted him through an organization called Pearl S. Buck several months ago, and it's been a really cool thing to do.  So I wanted to suggest it to any of you who may have a little extra cash floating around (it's $25 a month).  You can either adopt a child (that's what we're doing-you give your $25 a month and also exchange letters with your adopted child; with Pearl S. Buck, the average length of a sponsorship is ~13 years, and lots of sponsors end up visiting their child at some point), become a CHAMPion for a child (which I just learned they prefer; you still give your $25 a month, but you don't get individual letters from the child, nor do you write them...this saves money on translation and postage), or of course you can just donate some money if you don't want the monthly commitment.  If you're interested in checking this out, go to  urlLink Pearl S. Buck's website .     
     

    


30,June,2004


	 
       Hey ladies!  It's been awhile...and now I'm happy to say I'm back in Indianapolis to kick it for awhile before moving to Arizona.  Jennie and I had a great time in NYC getting what's ours (we didn't pay for parking once, very thrifty girls!!!) and then some more good times at the New Zealand reunion in New Hampshire.  But then Jennie left around 6 on Sunday and that's when the real fun of packing/cleaning the apt. started.  What a pain in the ass!!!!!!!!!!!  I never think things are going to take as long as they are.  It doesn't help that I tend to be a schizophrenic packer, darting around the apt. doing little things here and there instead of focusing on one thing.  Here are some of the highlights of packing: 1.  We didn't take the couch and wanted to donate it and have it picked up, but you have to organize that jazz a couple months in advance! (oops!)  So we pushed the couch out onto our sidewalk Sunday night, and it was gone Monday morning!  That's when we first realized that the people living around us are hip to snatching random goods from the trash (which I applaud...I'd much rather have someone use it then throw it out).  Other things that were taken: a bureau, a mattress, a magazine rack, a SpongeBob trashcan, a lamp... 2.  We were in the midst of moving our desk when we realized it wasn't exactly holding up (it was a $40 purchase from the Christmas Tree Shop), so we kicked that to the curb, and yes, it was taken. 3.  We had to tie the mattress to the top of an SUV to move it to the storage place.  The first time around, our tying job wasn't adequate and a few minutes into the drive, I look up and yell "The mattress is gone!"  Luckily for us, it hadn't fallen off completely, just flipped backwards.   That's enough reliving the move for now.  It's too soon to go into more detail...I may start having flashbacks!  Now I am on my way to see a baby miniature horse (yes, there is such thing as a miniature horse...those are the size of a large dog...so imagine what a baby mini will look like!) at the stable my sister works at.  Pictures will follow!  
     

    


28,June,2004


	 
      Hi Ladies The next time I post it may be from the city of light! Since we have just switched realtors in an effort to get our house sold faster we are going to be trying to check email every other day while in France.  So, I figure that I'll be able to post a few times and let you know what we're up to.  Whether I can read the blog is another story as it sometimes doesn't like to load on slow connections and computers.  Anyway, we are leaving tomorrow around 3:30pm here to go to the airport so I'll be doing a little blogging and emailing in the morning if anyone cares to comment on this post.  I'm posting my packing.  Here is what I'll be reading while on my honeymoon.  I may catch something else at the airport as im known to buy a book when I have three others with me that I haven't even started.  I think Jennie's book recommendation post "Sex Drugs and Cocoa Puffs" might be too hard to resist if I see it at the airport bookstore...we'll see!     Sarah Vowell is a regular contributor to This American Life and like Sedaris has a voice that is unforgettable and I assume it'll be impossible to not read the book with her voice in my head.  But thats a good thing I guess; it's more personal.  This book (The Partly Cloudy Patriot) is her first (she has a second that came out last year) and is a collection of short stories and essays etc.       Another proximity recommendation and a book that I've eyed at the bookstore probably since its publication but never purchased.  Now I have!     Subtitled: The Paris Review Book for Planes, Trains, Elevators, and Waiting Rooms. The description on amazon says: It's theme is the reader. Everyday we must live through moments of waiting--to get from one place to the next, from one appointment to another, for something to happen. This ingeniously useful compendium offers reading material to fill those gray moments with beauty, wonder, insight, and emotion. Organized by the time that the reader has available at that moment, the anthology provides a poem for that elevator ride to the lawyer's office; a short story for the thirty-minute commute; a novella for the three-hour plane ride. As ever, The Paris Review provides work from only the best writers of the last three generations.     Lastly, a new blank journal to write in.  It's small and grey with a little pocket in the front to put a picture in.  I have a picture of the empty Sears store at night focused in on the lone escalator.  John and I went to the abandoned mall a few block from our apartment and took pics at night as the empty stores inside are all lit up.  We both have an obsession with old department stores etc; so called suburban ruins.  I typically can't write in a journal so small but this will fit so nicely in my purse I had to have it.    A la prochaine.....   
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
      It's quite lovely to be back to the Prox after a wee hiatus!  I had such fun with Jenny in NYC and my fine flatmates(minus one) in the Hampshire.  So many stories, such little time!  I will be sure to post a link to my pics once I get them uploaded (as well as the pics from The Stills show a loooong time ago).    I must mention the funniest night we had in NYC and that was the night of the Keane (pronounced Keen) show.  We came to find out that it was sold out, but the door guy mentioned a slight chance of some tiks being available come showtime.  So we kicked it in the barski, waiting for some news.  In the mean time, this fella perched on a stool and started strumming his guitar...but the shocking part was his voice.  Seriously, he sounded like Joni Mitchell, enough that I looked around to see where the gal with the microphone was!  I missed the first ditty, but Jenny said that the refrain was a repetition of "tiny" sung like "tiiiiiny, tinnnnyyyyy".  Hee hee, so we started singing "hold me closer tiny eunuch!" We ended up getting into the Keane show for free and it was sweet, but not as enjoyable as tiny eunuch.  Oh yes, and Jenny and I had a thought.  Now I know most of us read  urlLink 1.21 Gigs  on occasion and one predominant theme (aside from musical thoughts and whinings and the occasional political piece) is the use of vulgar nicknames!  Seriously, they can refer to one another as shit stain and dildo and everyone seems to know the suspect in question by that nickname.   Perhaps Proximity can trump them with vulgar nicknames of our own.....?   Finally, this book called  urlLink Sex, Drugs, and Cocoa Puffs  by Chuck Klosterman looks hilarious!  He is apparently a senior writer or editor for Spin Mag and this is his second novel.  I read the exerpt on borders.com and laughed about his emo bit!  Teddy would be a fan....he talks about how there is no true love in the world anymore because of Coldplay and John Cusack.  Very funny and it could be next on my reading list.     
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

25,June,2004


	 
       I read  urlLink this article  on Salon this morning and it really just struck a chord in me.  Why has middle america, the blue collar workers, the farmers etc gone republican when none of the policies they help the bastards enact benefit them in any way?  In the article he says:   "Nobody thinks it's strange that Nebraska and Nevada and Arizona and Montana vote for right-wing Republicans in election after election, consumed with tax-cutting fervor and a passion to shrink the government, even though it's the massive federal programs of the 20th century -- dams and aqueducts, agricultural subsidies, public lands thrown open to ranching and mining and lumbering -- that supports those states' economies to this day."  Middle america is so jaded to the politics of economics (and rightfully so) that they base their decisions soley on cultural issues.  Anti-abortion, anti-evolution and the like.  And the republicans are slimey and perceptive and they mobilize the masses on these issues.  It's easy to point the finger at republicans but the article also takes aim at the Democratic party for its part in this debaucle:  "There are two different errors that were made, and both of them have amounted to jettisoning the working class, so that the working class is no longer the central focus of the party. In the McGovern era they described this as the "new politics." The error of that was apparent at the time, because McGovern went down in flames. The idea was, we'll build a new coalition around students, feminists, environmentalists and so on."  The author mentions that both John Edwards and Howard Dean talked old-school populist politics early in this election and now John Kerry attempts to echo them but seems insincere.  I will vote for Kerry of course.  I have no choice.  I want someone other than Bush in the white house.  But I still have the Howard Dean sticker in the back window of my car.  Lots of people have told me to give it up; take it down.  I was lazy at first but finally I tried and found that the tape I used had melted to the window or something.  I can't get it off.  But maybe that's a good thing.   
     

    


25,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

24,June,2004


	 
       John sometimes does because I like caffeine a little too much.  In fact I'm typing this post at about 300 wpm.  These pots are so awesome.  I got one for my wedding (when I returned a few towels!) because I love espresso and have been looking for a way to make it at home that doesn't require a really expensive machine.  These things make espresso better than I've tasted at many coffee shops and for about 1/8 of the price of a home machine.  I drink it in the new espresso demitasse and saucer that I got at Crate and Barrel or use one shot of espresso and one shot of vanilla soymilk (heated in a pan on the stove until it foams) in a coffee cup and saucer.  It is simply divine.  I highly recommend it to anyone that likes espresso.  It's so cheap to drink at home instead of spending like 3 dollars on an espresso drink at a coffee place.   urlLink Here  is a place online to get them.  
     

    


24,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,June,2004


	 
         Hey laaaaaadies!  Welp, I about to leave for Beantown, known to the outer world as Boston, to visit Ms. Box for her birthday.  So jazzed, so jazzed...but I wanted to leave you with a wee post about this amazing band called Keane.  They are a fine British find and actually, Steve posted about this band on 1.21 Gigs last week.  According to Spin, they have held the #1 spot in the UK for a few weeks since the the release of  urlLink Hopes and Fears  , their first album (I believe).  Anyway, these guys are a must for your collection, sounding a bit like Travis, Coldplay, and one critic said Radiohead in the Kid A days.  Jen and I are going to check them out in NYC at the Knitting Factory on Thursday, so a review will be in order.  In the mean time, Target is selling this gem for $8.99, a steal if I've ever seen one.  Lata! 
     

    


21,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

21,June,2004


	 
         Coffee and Cigarettes was perhaps the worst movie i have ever seen in my entire life.  So annoying and boring that it actually made me angry.  I spent the whole movie just boiling for it to be over.  Some of the user reviews on IMDB put it perfectly:  Summary: boredom disguised as art      if you can't write clever dialogue but only meaningless and boring droning from empty people, then dress it up as an art film, maybe no one will notice or, better still, they'll read some "cool" cachet into the dreck that will give it meaning. there is simply not one person in this film that you would listen to for more than 40 seconds if you were trapped bedside them in a bar.do we need a film on the emptiness of human communication when we can experience it firsthand everyday? so why pay money for it? I would see only if they paid a standard therapy fee to me ( about $135.00 per hour).Jim Jarmisch should have quit after Down by Law, his only good film. Quentin Tarantino, pay attention, here lies your future and it ain't pretty.   Summary: Throw away your time and money here!      Don't you wish that every time you scribbled with a crayon on a piece of paper that you could pick it up, hang it in a museum, and people would pay to see it? That's kind of what this film is like. Don't you think it's great that Jim Jarmusch has cool friends like Tom Waits and Cate Blanchett? So do I. But do I need to pay $10 to see Jim's cool friends ramble their insipid thoughts in pretentious and moronic vignettes? Well, obviously I do, because I did. But I'm really glad I did, because now I know for sure: Jim Jarmusch has REALLY COOL friends. That is about the sum total of what I came away from this movie with.      The vignettes vary from the medium-okay to the suicide-inducing. The worst one is the first one, with Stephen Wright and Roberto Begnini. The best one (and the only one featuring anything approaching a performance) is Cate Blanchett's conversation with herself. It's not that great, but at least you're watching some talent, and not JJ's cool friends just be themselves with the assurance that THAT IS ENOUGH. The other bearable one features Alfred Molina and Jim Coogan, but even this is a one-sentence joke stretched out to five minutes. The White Stripes, Pop/Waits, RZA/GZA/Bill Murray, and a number of others that I have already completely forgotten, are not worth watching. Unless of course, you are one of JJ's cool friends, or aspire to be. Or maybe if you're his mother.      If you do end up going, please note that the opening credits represent the order that the "personalities" (can't really describe them as actors in this case) appear. This will prove an invaluable guide to how much longer you're going to have to sit through this crap.      Be sure to keep an ear open for the world's longest version of "Crimson & Clover."   Summary: Worthless, pretentious, and over-rated      Coffee and Cigarettes was worthless, which is why I'm glad someone else paid for me to see it. If you actually liked this movie, I would love to talk to you, because you are just kidding yourself. You think it's cool to like movies that you don't understand, when really you don't understand them because they are crap and there's nothing there to understand.  The  urlLink New York Times  however gave this movie an "A" according it Yahoo movies.  Wow NY Times, you're a real bunch of fuckin losers. 
     

    


17,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,June,2004


	 
         Shannon's post about feminism intrigued me and recently I have been rather creative and began working on a new collage and taking some abstract photos (I also took six rolls of B&W film from who knows when to be developed, can't wait to see what comes out!).  So I wanted to share with you one of my fave photographers,  urlLink Nan Goldin .  She is amazing and her work has been grouped with Cindy Sherman, Diane Arbus, and Barbara Krueger.  She began taking pics after her sister died tragically when she was 16 so that she could have a photographic memory of her friends, experiences, relationships etc., a documentation of her life.  All of her images are in color and often use what some believe is a "harsh" light with a flash, but I find the flash quite complementary to the image, not distracting.  She came about in the 70s and has been an active photographer ever since, documenting her violent relationship with her boyfriend, the 80s club scene, and the beginning of the AIDS epidemic that has claimed the lives of many of her friends.  This is what I consider her most poignant and universal work.  A show I saw of hers in NYC contained a 16 photo or so sequence that begins with her friend and his boyfriend, their happier times together, and follows the both of them through her friends eventual death, concluding with his empty hospital bed surrounded by all of the cards, balloons, etc that decorated his room.  You can read more in the article I linked to!            
     

    


16,June,2004


	 
         I love games, plain and simple....board games, game shows, sporting games, card games, mind games :), you name it.  Surprisingly, I don't find myself too competitive and hopefully you guys don't view me as that either, I just love to play games.  The good old days of Scattergories at Dave Roger's house still ring clear in my memory.    Now for the reason for my post:  This week, and actually last week, on Jeopardy, this guy, Ken Jennings, has won a record 11 times (since they got rid of the five wins and you're out rule last year) and made over $350,000!!  This is an accomplishment as far as I can see.  While I love trivia, there are always those categories that I have a snowball's chance in hell with and if the whole board is filled with such categories, I am bummed.  But this guy is swift with the clicker and actually knows most of the answers....his guesses are also usually right.  So I give mad props to Ken for his knowledge, speed, and cash flow, as well as for finding a different way to present his name on his booth for the last 11 days.    
     

    


16,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

16,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,June,2004


	 
      The 11 year old girl I take care of has this shocking t-shirt that I had to post about.  It's from Hollister (think Abercrombie and Fitch), and there's a picture of a cow on the front of it.  Above the cow, it says "Why buy the cow?" and then there's a bubble coming from the cow's mouth that says "The milk is free!"  Inappropriate much?  Now Maggie does have an obsession with cows, but still.  No kid of mine would ever don that shirt!  It's not like it's a hip new saying that her parents may not know the meaning of; it's common knowledge.  It's like wearing a t-shirt that says, "Hey!  I'm slutty and like to hook up with no worries of commitment!  Anyone interested?"  I tried to find a picture on their website, but there wasn't one...maybe it's been discontinued due to disgruntled consumers like me.  
     

    


14,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

11,June,2004


	 
         Two words:  Shitford Wives       
     

    


11,June,2004


	 
      When I arrived at the theater in denver to see Coffee and Cigarettes, the doors were locked.  Bastards!! on the website it never said that the matinees are only friday through sunday.  I was pissed but we wrote some thank you notes, went to a great middle eastern restaurant and went to see a different movie at a big movie theater which i will be reviewing....now.
     

    


11,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

11,June,2004


	 
      Hi Guys, Today ill be going to denver with john to see "Coffee and Cigarettes" a little movie about caffeine and nicotine which stars a lot of famous people.  They are just vingettes of people sitting around cafes etc and talking.  Ill do a review of it later today.  
     

    


11,June,2004


	 
        
     

    


10,June,2004


	 
      Guys, I almost hate to do this to you, but I couldn't pass this up.  My Grandpa sent me this forward which is apparently floating amongst the Republican-minded, Bush-loving members of the population.  I always wondered what their mass e-mails and e-mail distribution letters look like, and now I know.  And what a load of crap it is.  Anything that starts off with a kid hesitant to miss school is obviously the beginning of a tall tale.  And frankly I don't find the picture below to be endearing, I find it frightening.  Take a gander for yourselves...     Editorial by CK Rairden May 10, 2004  It started out as a fluke.  Lynn Faulkner had been offered an extra ticket to a Bush campaign event by his neighbor Linda Prince.  Mr. Faulkner decided to offer it to his 15-year old daughter Ashley who he expected would decline, as she would have to miss some school to attend.  But his daughter surprised him.  Ashley reminded her dad how four years ago they attended a similar event when then Texas Governor George W. Bush visited the same spot on the campaign trail.  Ashley remembered attending that event with both her father and her mother Wendy Faulkner.  It was raining that day and they all stood in the rain awaiting Governor Bush "eating Triscuit crackers" enjoying the time together and hoping to get a glimpse of the would-be president.  Ashley recalled holding her mothers hand as they waited. So she decided to go again this year, but this time her mother could not attend.  Wendy Faulkner was murdered on 9/11/01 in the south tower of the World Trade Center.  She was there on the 104th floor for a one-day meeting.  Ashley decided to miss school in honor and remembrance of her mother and attend the event.  So the trip was on.  Linda Prince, along with Lynn and Ashley Faulkner, were off to the Golden Lamb Inn in Lebanon, Ohio for the event.  The group arrived early and got a spot close to the front.  As the event wound down, the president worked the line in full campaign mode shaking hands and signing autographs.  As the president passed the group, Mr. Faulkner got an autograph, and the president continued on until Linda Prince spoke up, "This girl lost her mother on 9/11," Prince told the president.    Then everything changed.  "The president's entire _expression transformed," Mr. Faulkner told me on Sunday.  "He turned and came back against the flow and his eyes locked on Ashley's.  His face showed a man who was no longer the president, he was a father and a husband."  President Bush made his way back to Ashley and he embraced the 15-yeal old young woman.  "She snuggled in with the president just like she did when she was a little girl with her dad," Mr. Faulkner said.  "I know it's hard," Mr. Faulkner heard the president tell his daughter.  "I'm okay," Ashley told the president.  The embrace continued.  Mr. Faulkner had his Kodak digital camera with him and debated on invading this very private moment between his daughter and the leader of the free world.  "For 20-30 seconds the president belonged exclusively to Ashley," Lynn Faulkner told me.  So he decided to capture the moment without invading Ashley and the president's privacy.  He held up his digital camera, not even aiming with his eye and with one click snapped just one picture.  It showed in detail the face of a compassionate man who just happens to be the president comforting a young woman who lost her mother in the 9/11 attacks on America.  Mr. Faulkner told me that he saw tears in his daughter's eyes, and saw emotion that he hadn't seen from his daughter in 2 ½ years.  Ashley told her dad, "The way he was holding me, with my head against his chest, it felt like he was trying to protect me, he wanted to make sure that I was safe."  That feeling is captured in a very clear way in this moving unscripted photo.  It's the only photo of this special embrace as the press corps had already been ushered back on the bus.  And the photo was never meant for publication.  All Mr. Faulkner did when he returned home from the event was e-mail it to 15 friends and family.  But by the middle of last week, I had received the photo from eight different people.  Others were also receiving the photo and forwarding it along.  It became an Internet phenomenon, as it was e-mailed around America.  Mr. Faulkner called the embrace "President Bush's precious gift to my daughter."  And with his small act of e-mailing that photo to friends and family, the picture can now become a gift to the American people.   And as sad as the story is the release and publication is a good thing.  Disgusting photos coming out of Iraq for the past 10 days have shocked Americans, as they should have.  But no longer are the terrible images of 9/11 shown.  While the Iraq prison photos have been picked up by the elite media and shown time and again, this touching photo has gone largely ignored by the mainstream media.  But the alternative media has made this touching powerful photo one of the most e-mailed photos of last week.  The Internet once again took over where the elite media failed.  Matt Drudge ran it on May 7th, as did the Page 2 Politics journal, and hundreds of other blogs.  Millions have now seen it, but millions more need to.  It gives a stark reminder why America is at war with radical Islam and other terrorists around the world that are determined to cause this kind of pain to other American families.   The images of 9/11 have faded in the minds of far too many Americans.  This picture and this family's riveting story give a stark reminder of why America is at war.  Each day around the globe our soldiers are fighting in an attempt to prevent any other event as terrible as the murders that took place on 9/11.  Look hard at this picture.  See the compassion and sadness on the president's face.  Look at this young woman, see her grief and listen her father's words.  Ashley and her sister Loren just spent their third Mother's Day without their mother, as did thousands of other children who lost their mothers on 9/11 at the hands of ruthless uncaring terrorists.  Imagine yourself in that position.  Then remember why America is at war, and consider the type of person America should have leading that war.  CK Rairden is the Editor of The Washington Dispatch.
     

    


10,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,June,2004


	 
         This is a pic of what I just had for lunch, a vegetarian naked burrito from Qdoba.  Yes, I am posting about my love for  urlLink Qdoba Mexican Grill  and I am not ashamed.  When they offered a card where you buy 10 burritos or entrees and receive the 11th free, I picked up five because I knew I would use them all up in about a month.     I found this pic of a burrito eating contest and it made me laugh!  You KNOW I would have won (unless Tarbox was in the competition, then it would have been tough to call!)! While in NZ, Jenny and I would have conversations recalling this one time, when we went to Qdoba (since Mexican food is a delicacy there!).  We would recant how they first put the chips in the bowl (for nachos), then top it with queso, add rice and your choice of beans, etc.....Today, when I went, it was magical.  But I did make my cashier laugh when I said "And can I have a frosty beverage with my meal?" Goodtimes.  
     

    


09,June,2004


	 
       Hi ladies.  This is a picture of me and john doing what our dance teacher liked to call "a basket" at the wedding.  John is laughing because we tried to go different directions once we arrived in said basket position.  I think it was still pretty cute.  The whole wedding was one big blur so im glad that i have at least one picture (care of my sis) to remind me that it actually happened.  Katie or Alison, if you have any that are good will you email me a couple?  I dont get to see proofs for the professional pics until i get back from my honeymoon.  Which reminds me...Im going to have to find a place to blog when im in France!!!!   For those of you who weren't at my wedding, I couldnt stop talking with a dull southern accent and calling it "Ma Weddin' "  
     

    


09,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

09,June,2004


	 
         So, Michael Moore's new film "Fahrenheit 9/11" will be hitting theatres June 25.  Check out the  urlLink trailer  (even though I couldn't on this computer!).     
     

    


09,June,2004


	 
       Guys!  I just encountered the rodent that's been crashing at my place (it could at least chip in on the rent and food costs, come on).  The story of my little mouse buddy goes back a ways.  A month ago, my friend Heidi was here and she and I started throwing around Hershey's Kisses after we got back from the bars.  Then a couple weeks later, Jon and I were looking behind the couch for something and discovered a pile of mouse poop and Hershey's Kisses wrappings.  So after that we tried to be really careful with the snacks, but I'd often hear some scampering around late at night.  And JUST NOW, I'm sitting here kicking back with a Veggie Delite sub and a Coke (with the TV on, not being quiet at all), and who comes boldly strutting out but the mouse!  I guess it was about time we became acquainted.  I sort of want to leave him some snacks and see if they're gone in the morning.  He looks pretty skinny...it'll be like leaving cookies for Santa!  Anyway, he's much cuter than the gerbils and hamsters I had growing up, and maintenance-free.  I hope he pops out again soon...I'll keep you abreast of any new developments!    
     

    


07,June,2004


	 
       Okay, as I was driving back to work after my doc's appt today, I noticed the marquee at the local McD's/BP combo station said "Free Song with Purchase of a Big Mac".  Seriously!  Now most of you know about my rule to never eat food from gas stations (unless prepackaged) and I considered breaking that rule just to get the free song...but alas, I declined.  What I want to know is, can I request a tune, perhaps something by Stevie Wonder or Prince?  Could Shan request a Smokey Robinson ditty? I may have to investigate on my way home.   This reminds me of the line that Taco Bell used to use that claimed "You like it or we'll eat it!".  I got many a laugh from imagining my cashier actually having to eat my chalupa if I did't enjoy it!    Also, while at the gym this morning, I was people watching (as you do) and saw a youngster doing lat pulls with a SIDE rat tail!!!  I kid you not....his whole head was buzz cut except for a curly puff behind his ear.  Of course I wanted a closer look and sure enough, it was what can best be described as a side rat tail.  Teddy should have got a hold of that one! 
     

    


07,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,June,2004


	 
         Remember being a kid and having your grandparents tell you what life was like when they were kids and being shocked at how much they had to suck it up?  I can remember some of my Grandma's farm stories about 4 am wake-up calls and 8 mile hikes to school so clearly, listening intently and thinking "glad I wasn't born yet."  And then as I got older I started wondering if my future kids and grandkids would think the same thing when I told them about growing up in the 80s and 90s (that is, if people are even still talking at that point...maybe all communication will be reduced to IMing and emails and cell phone calls).  I thought we had swift travel covered pretty well with the availability of flying, but I just read this article in  urlLink Discover  magazine that mentions hypersonic vehicles ("scramjets") that are now being tested and could become passenger vehicles in the next decade or two, depending on funding (sorry, they don't have the article online, but still a cool website).  It says you could fly from NY to Tokyo in just a few hours on one of these babies.  Not bad...especially since every time I think about going back to Australia or NZ, the next thought in my head is "how will I possibly handle that plane ride again?"  I don't think I've got it in me, but with this snazzy new jet, maybe I (and my kids) won't have to.    
     

    


07,June,2004


	 
       Yes, David Sedaris is back to his old tricks in his new book "Dress Your Family in Corduroy and Denim".  He remains an outsider looking in and continues his humorous commentary on his family members, his North Carolina neighborhood, and social expectations.  Apparently, we also get an update on his brother, Paul, better known as The Rooster, who drops the f-bomb like it's going out of style.  Check out this link for a sample from this  urlLink fine novel .  Personally, my fave vignette is the one where his sister, Amy, dons a fat suit for Christmas with the family (from Me Talk Pretty), much to her father's dismay.  She eats mayonnaise by the spoonful from the jar as he encourages her to go for a walk, run up the stairs, do anything to shed the pounds.  The best part is that she could only afford the bottom half, so she's little on top with some junk in her trunk!  I swear I laughed for days off that one....What are some of your faves?      
     

    


03,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,June,2004


	 
       Jesus christ!! It is only like 3 days until my wedding!  Im starting to feel a little bit crazy because my mom and sis are here and the only thing we can talk about is the wedding.  I can't believe that it'll all be over soon. Its been a whole year since we started planning it and it's going to be soooooo great not to have to deal with caterers, florists, bands, photographers and stupid site managers from now on.  I know more than ever that I never want to be an event planner.  I really hate that shit!!! But what I am excited about is being able to see all the people I love so much all here in one of my favorite places in the world.  I cannot wait for that!!!! I also can't wait to have the ceremony as I am obviously excited to marry john.  It's just all the other nonsense that tends to make you want to kill something.  Sorry I've been absent a bit from the blog but i've been insane!  Love ya ladies
     

    


02,June,2004


	 
          Hey all!  I'd like to wish Miss Coogman a hip hop happy birthday!  Here's to your last b'day as a non-married lady :)      To go along with the birthday theme, be sure to check out a Cold Stone Creamery (a yummy ice cream store)near you on June 28th from 5-8pm.  They are giving away a free slice of their Oreo ice cream cake to each patron in exchange for a donation to the Make a Wish Foundation.  Goodtimes! 
     

    


01,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,June,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

30,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

29,July,2004


	 
         My eight-year-old sister and Mary and I were at Target the other day perusing the goods (did anyone see Oprah's bargains yesterday?&nbsp; She's all about Target, apparently...I'm sure she does tons of shopping there), and Mary found a steal: these little tubes of plastic animals for 24 cents each.&nbsp; There were three varieties: jungle, farm, and sea creatures, all very exciting for her.&nbsp; So of course she wants to bust right into them in the car, and in her excitement she commented to me "Isn't it cool all the stuff that China people can make?"&nbsp; I guess she noticed the "Made in China" emblem on those plastic animals and lots of other stuff too.&nbsp; I agreed with her that they were a talented nation, but also mentioned that they weren't paid very well for their work.&nbsp; I have this tendency to tell Mary way too much for someone her age (Bush is evil!&nbsp; Go Kerry!), so I shut it pretty quickly, but I thought it was crazy that an 8 year old has already noticed how many of the toys she plays with are made in China.&nbsp;   In other news, Jon's here!&nbsp; Wahoo!&nbsp; He got in around 4 am and is of course sleeping right now, but I really want to wake him up.&nbsp; I'm trying to hold back; we'll see how long that lasts.&nbsp;    
     

    


29,July,2004


	 
       &nbsp;I was watching The Today Show this morning as I ate my nutritional breakfast of chocolate chip cookies and I got to wondering...Why do all of those people wave like fools?&nbsp; So, as a normal person I turn on the TV in the morning wanting a little info about the news, weather, and traffic, but instead I get about 10 minutes of people waving and putting signs in the camera about how they are just married or from Topeka, Kansas.&nbsp; Seriously, do they realize how they look?&nbsp; I would appreciate if a news show was actually a news show and not a crowd show.   
     

    


29,July,2004


	 
      Hey all, this is my first post and I just want to make sure I do it right, so it will not be very interesting.&nbsp; I promise more intellectual and entertaining thoughts in the future, but for now, aren't we all glad tomorrow is Friday? 
     

    


28,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

28,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

26,July,2004


	 
      Well, were packing up our whole apartment which we've been accumulating things in for almost 4 years now.  Its really  not too bad but I still need to procrastinate and whine about it a little bit.  We're going to be staying at John's parents house until we move to LA. First we need a place to live out there which we're working on. The married housing at UCLA may be our best option as it is month to month  and since I don't know where I'll be working yet I don't have an idea of what location I'd like to reside in.  The married housing claims it's in Mar Vista/Palms.  Katie, I know you said that  those are not place you'd want to live but do you think it'll be reall unsafe?  I suppose it will just have to do if we get a place there as we could even move out after a month with no penalty and find a better place to live.  Anyways, sorry for the rant directed at Katie everyone.  Again, I'm just trying to procrastinate .  How are all your days??
     

    


23,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

23,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

22,July,2004


	 
       &nbsp;&nbsp; Hey now, so today is Keith Sweat's 43rd year on this earth.&nbsp; Happy birthday to the man that gets all the ladies twisted over him!&nbsp; Feel me, baby?&nbsp; Yeah, that's right. 
     

    


21,July,2004


	 
         In honor of the first television show ever to be brought back from the dead due to staggering DVD sales, find out which  urlLink Family Guy  character you are.  I'm Brian, and that makes me happy.  Martini anyone?
     

    


20,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

20,July,2004


	 
      Hey Friends! As if this week couldn't get any more insane for me,  urlLink Beacon Street Gallery  (my current part time job and one time AmeriCorps assignment) called yesterday to say that I have a full time job! I am soooo jazzed. We were waiting to hear if we would recieve a grant from the good old government to start an arts-integrated cirriculum program in a janky school in Uptown. The money came through yesterday and this means that I can have this job for up to 5 years! In this position, I will be in charge of running the tutoring component of the program. This will include hiring and training the tutors, working with the teachers to make sure the kids' needs are being met, and so forth. Then we will have some good time arts enrichment that will help enforce academic lessons. So, basically, I will just be Jennie Nye (we totally need to conference so you can teach me what you know, Jen!) This is the kind of job I have always wanted, so I feel super lucky.  &nbsp;  All right, kiddos, I guess I'll check in with you after the wedding. I will, for once, use my camera so I can post pics of my tropical vacation! Love ya~&nbsp;  &nbsp;    
     

    


19,July,2004


	 
       I know that a few of you are MoveOn.org members and already got this email, but for anyone who didn't, check out  urlLink this clip  of Bill O'Reilly telling everyone to shut it.&nbsp; "Shut up!&nbsp; Shut up if you don't support the war, just shut up!"&nbsp; You know how the saying goes...if you don't have anything nice to say, don't say anything at all.&nbsp; Apparently this applies to Americans during a war...if you don't like it, shut up!&nbsp; Cause Billy doesn't want to hear it!&nbsp;&nbsp; And here's a&nbsp;link to a  urlLink petition to complain  to the FTC about Fox News'&nbsp;one-sided&nbsp; reporting.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;     
     

    


19,July,2004


	 
      Ok, so maybe  urlLink this story  from the Women's Wall Street Journal is over-the-top and a hunk of bologna, but it scared the piss out of me.&nbsp;&nbsp; It makes you wonder if the airlines, and&nbsp;the government for that matter are truly looking out for us with all of the loopholes&nbsp;which still exist.  &nbsp;  Insert short, sappy monologue:  &nbsp;  I guess&nbsp;this article&nbsp;just pounds into my head once again, that we must be alert, because airline employees are only allowed to do so much.&nbsp; It's frustrating that something actually has to happen before they can do something about it.&nbsp;&nbsp;We must also say proper I love yous and goodbyes when leaving a loved one even for a day, because true friendships and loves are really what make even a short life, worth living.  &nbsp;  Let me know what you think of the article.&nbsp; Were the 14 gentlemen really in a band?&nbsp;   
     

    


16,July,2004


	 
        ...I was just rolling around naked in $7 worth of nacho cheese, while running away with $40 in tortilla chips.&nbsp; Ooooh, almost.  &nbsp;  I'd love to be the person who calculates JUST how much chip'n'cheese was lost.&nbsp; &nbsp;  Read  urlLink here  for the entire cheesy story.   
     

    


16,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

15,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,July,2004


	 
      Hey all!  I feel bad for not posting, so I figured that I might take a cue from Shan and post about my current annoyances.     1.  Biology      So most of you know that I am taking a Biology class this summer at IUPUI because I never took one at DePauw and it's a prereq for my masters in social work.  UGH!!  There is reason I never took Bio and I feel like sending my advisor from DPU a hate letter for not telling me about this wee prereq when he knew I was interested in an MSW....but I have to ask him for a recommendation, so I might not do that!  So I am sorry, but IUPUI sucks.  I know there are other people out there who attend that hellish academy, some may enjoy it, and I just cannot understand.  Perhaps I am being a whiny, private school bitch, but I LIKE my prof knowing my name and not having a technologically advanced uni (they post class notes online!  I had not idea that even existed; why not just pass them out in class?  Oh yeah, people would have to attend!).  I also like my profs without an Egyptian accent b/c Bio is pretty much a foreign language to me, so having it taught with an accent just compounds that problem.  Why I need to know what hormones the pancreas secretes and where the superior vena cava drops off its blood to tell moms to get a job to get their kids back, I will never know.     2.  Hoobastank      HoobaSUCKS!!!  I hear that stupid song "The Reason" on the radio all of the time.  Actually, one day it was on three radio stations simultaneously!  They are awful....nuf' said.    Okay, I was going to write more, but now I have to work...annoyance #3?  Perhaps....
     

    


14,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

14,July,2004


	 
         To me, the most important part of getting new digs is finding new places to snack.  NZ had so-so snacks, and Boston just didn't cut it in the Mexican or sandwich department.  So while Jon and I were out in Phoenix last week apartment-hunting, hitting up all the new fast food places was right up there on the priority list...maybe even as the #1 priority.  We were like little kids checking these places out.  When I noticed a sign proclaiming "Sub Factory," we got so excited that we turned that car right around and scooted in straightaway for a snack; another time we saw a later movie so that Jon could have his first In and Out burger.  But for me, the pièce de résistance was none other than Del Taco.  Ahh, Del Taco; my only consolation in writing this is knowing that I'll be back in a few short weeks to get what's mine.  What I get there is a fine Veggie Works burrito.  The burrito shell is superior to Taco Bell's by far, and they also top 'er off with some guac to sweeten the deal.  They serve Coke products instead of Pepsi and have some great hot sauce too.  I don't know how far reaching Del Taco is, but  urlLink make it a part of your next road trip  and locate one nearest you!    
     

    


12,July,2004


	 
       Hi Ladies    For the next day or so ill be checking my email lots as we have internet access at our hotel in Arles.  So far we were in Paris for 10 nights and now we've been in Arles for 2 nights.  We have 2 more nights here and then we go to Nice for 6 nights (yeah beach!!! and Chagall and Matisse Museums) and then we will fly to London and stay for 4 nights before returning to the states from London.  So far weve seen EVERYTHING there is to see in both Paris and Arles and have been having so much fun.  Its been nice and relaxing too to read every night and just hang out.  Here is my other news, our condo has a contract on it and someone will be purchasing it from us 6 days after we get home on July 30th!! so we are going to be home on the 23rd and then have 6 days to move out before the closing on the house.  Then we'll live at john's parents house until we go visit LA on august 9th for a week to find a place to live and hopefully have some job interviews for me.  Well, ill leave you at that.  Love you ladies!
     

    


10,July,2004


	 
      hey!  so after much ado, you can check out the  urlLink pics of my life  since may.  hip hop happy peering!  
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

07,July,2004


	 
       Gals, I am feeling so very youth of the nation right now.  I'm posting from one of the ASU computer labs.  Ahh, college.  I love this campus; it's gorgeous!  Anyway I have to let you in on this anomaly I just witnessed and see if any of you have been privy to such a thing.  I was in the women's restroom and noticed that the handicapped stall is equipped with not only a toilet but also a urinal.  Urinal?  In the women's, you say?  Yes, I do.  I even double-checked.  My best guess is it's some kind of mother and son's potty break package.  Which makes a little sense, but who wants to see a urinal in the ladies' bathroom?  Certainly not me.  I'd never use the handicapped stall because of it.  Weird.  Any of you ever see the likes of this in your stomping grounds?  
     

    


05,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

02,July,2004


	 
         Okay, I am sick of "Extreme" this and "Xtreme" that!  Seriously, everytime I turn around there is another extreme product, whether it be Gatorade, Road Rules, or Trojans.  This has just got to end!  I mean, is EXTREME fruit punch really that different than regular fruit punch (and would anyone prefer a Hawaiian Punch?)?    Today I received an email from "Your Soulmate"....I was extremely excited that Prince Charming had finally found my email address until I opened some spam mail.       Jenny and I were chatting about this in NYC and I wanted to open it up for convo: When you go to Victoria's Secret (or Gap or wherever) and purchase 5 panites for $25 (not $9.99), do you have trouble selecting that fifth pair?  Like you have four cute pairs and then you have that blasted fifth one and just pick a random print or color?  Then it ends up being your LEAST fave pair to wear and you wonder "why did I get grey and not black?".  Yeah, I am a victim of the ugly print...     This is Snow Patrol.  They are great.  You should have a wee listen!
     

    


01,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,July,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

10,August,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

06,August,2004


	 
      The past 2 nights in our apartment have been interesting, to say the least. A new gal has moved in upstairs and let me tell you, we are in crazy land! Since I officially start working next week (thank god) I am kickin it at home and around town this week. This gal upstairs is apparently home all day but hardly makes a peep. We can hear people walking around-- virutally every step, so it is more than obvious when someone is in the apartment upstairs. So, this person makes virutally no noise all day long, but at night-- the freaks come out! Starting around 11 (usually when Matt and I go to bed) she and some other person (we guess to be a guy) are apparently moving large pieces of furniture across the floors and dropping them right above our heads. So, I've hooked it up with the earplugs and have been sleeping ok, only to wake up for the extra loud noises. It's par for the course when you live in an apartment. But, the real treat was last night. We thought the guy that used to live upstairs was loud- apparently he was not getting laid! At the start of the very loud 12:30am s-e-x (bed squeaking like you wouldn't believe) Matt and I flicked on the light and uttered the profanity of our choice, only to find that the roll in the hay only lasted for about 2 minutes! Tee hee. At least we can count that kind of noise to be minimal! 
     

    


05,August,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,August,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

04,August,2004


	 
      I have finally put digital pictures online. This is a big deal for me...so, after you pat me on the back, check out the  urlLink honeymoon photos ! I think I set up the link right, but if not, tell me how to hook it up all smart-like. 
     

    


04,August,2004


	 
       Ok, so as most of you know I am a social worker, not by training, but by default...and I have an observation. The population I work with is what they call "involuntary" meaning they don't want to work with myself and my co-workers, but it is court ordered. So, needless to say they are not too pleased when I prance on up to their doors all day and knock and then make them talk about the most stressful thing in their lives.  Well, to get to the point of this blog, it has been really hot lately here in humidville, USA and I have noticed that not only are my clients acting strange, but their neighbors are as well. I was at an apartment complex in a lovely area at 38th and Post road when a young man ran up to me and yelled "Hey Lady" in my face and then ran off. Now, as a young social worker, how am I to interpret this behavior. Not really knowing what to say to this young man, I yelled back "Hey" as he ran away. I have been doing this job a year and that is the first time I have had that happened, maybe the heat got to him? I didn't really think much of it, but I went to another clients house at 10th and Rural and was walking towards their house when this random woman came up to me and asked me what time it was, so I told her. When she heard the time she then told me to "get a life and leave her alone" Ok, seriously what is wrong with people...?? My only explanation is the heat!  
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
       Hey! Now I know it's been a while since I posted and I bet you all have been counting the days until I rejoined the blog, so rejoice, the fasting is over!  I am now finished with Americorps Year 1 (save a couple hours to keep my health insurance kickin'), so I no longer clock 40+ hours a week at the Julian Center. While I did enjoy my time there, I am stoked to begin Americorps Year 2 with Peace Camp at the end of this month. What am I doing with my time now that I no longer have a day job?      Ahhhh....but never fear, I still am waiting away at Sully's, finishing Bio-hell (one more day!!!), and getting prepped for my LSAT class.  If you fancy, check out my pics from the  urlLink Coogman nuptuals . A few are pretty dark, but there are some shining stars! BTW, that wedding was the BEST!  On a final note, one of my friends from NZ, Brett, has retaliated against me for signing him up for an email company that harasses him (actually he is confusing me with someone else, but long story). So he is now forwarding me porn...what an interesting way to get back at people that send/sign you up for crap emails. If anyone needs some new sights, I've got the hook up!  
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

03,August,2004


	 
       A contributor to Idealist.org's August 1 article, "Women Criticize Vatican Document on Feminism" states that "no religion is a great friend of women." This is in response to the Vatican's statements concerning feminism's role in the decline of the traditional family and family value system. Do you agree with this statement? I have to admit that I have very conflicted feelings on this issue (just got married at a catholic church). I think some religions could be pals of the gals, but I don't know enough to say which ones. Thoughts? Sometimes I think that my Catholic upbringing has transferred and transformed itself into a belief in the principle of Karma, but I'm just not willing to admit it and research the whole thing. How do my fellow IHM/CHS-ers feel? 
     

    


03,August,2004


	 
      and it sucked! Kidding. Hi Gals! I'm so happy to be back in Chicago and the world of blogging. To start with the most obvious news, the wedding and honeymoon are now wonderful memories. Yes, that's right, the Coogman family has officially come forth. I had an awesome time at the wedding and reception (hope you all did too) and the honeymoon was incredibly beautiful (the vest ensemble greatly enhanced the experience!). It is amazing how relaxed I became once we were in Turks and Caicos. I don't think I had let myself slow down that much in a long time!  In terms of the H-Moon, we didn't do too much. Our resort had a fab beach, so Matt and I logged the majority of our time in the beach chairs. The water was amazingly clear- I had never seen anything like it in my life. We did go horseback riding on the beach, which was cool, and not nearly as movie-glamorous as I expected. Lots of horses pooping and inexperienced riders like myself screaming when the horses all decided to gallop. We also went on a snorkeling trip that was quite fun. As a first timer, I was a little frightened but soon buddied up with a 9 year old British lass who also wanted to wear a life preserver whilst snorkeling in 10ft. of water. Thank god dorks love company! The trip included diving for conch shells, which the boat driver then prepared into conch salad on the beach. I have to admit that I was not skeptical in terms of eating the snack because a shell just doesn't seem, well, alive. We were able to take home the shells and the one we have is pretty smelly.  One good story for Alison: Matt and I were eathing dinner pooliside at some resort when a super friendly cat just sauntered up to our table and sat at my feet for the entire meal. He tried to jump into my lap a few times to snag a bite of my crab legs, but Matt was not a fan. It just sat there and stared at us. Very bizarro to see a cat kickin it at the beach.  So, I'm home...happily remembering all the good times had in these past few weeks and enjoying getting back to my life. It has never felt so good to shower in my own shower, sleep in my own bed, and just live in my apartment. I am starting a new job position today so I can't wait to get to work. More about that later and I will post beach pics soon as well. I'm reading 2 selections from my bachelorette party: The Good Girl's Guide to Bad Girl Sex and How to Be a Great Lover. So far it's safe to say that I am not failing by these author's standards. In the Guide, the "good girl" is actually typecast as a gingam-wearing, puffy sleeved Laura Ashley dresser! Gads. I'll let you know how they turn out. 
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
       &emailalert=no&email=adgrant@indiana.edu&url=http://closeproximity.blogspot.com&name=Proximity&bgcolor=003399&fcolor=FFFFFF&link=FFFFCC&words=comments&title=Comments &width=350&height=350"

01,August,2004


	 
       The other day on my endless drives around the lovely Marion County I was listening to NPR, because the rest of radio sucks and I heard a very interesting news bite. They stated that Eukenuba had come up with a type of dog food to feed your dog when they are puppies to make them smarter. The point of this is that the leading cause of death for dogs is being put to sleep in a shelter, so Eukenuba is thinking that by having smarter dogs, people will be able to train their dogs eaiser and therefore, not get annoyed with their dogs and give them to shelters.  I have a few problems with this one serious, one not so serious...  First of all, all dogs are trainable and a dog making mistakes is the owners fault. Most dog owners have to spend a lot of time training and playing with their dogs to make sure they are good dogs, not just one time and then give up  Secondly, I wonder would feeding my dog Juno dog food to make her smarter prevent her from doing all of the annoying this dogs do, like rolling in horse poo? I think not! A dog is a dog for a reason, they aren't always the most brillant creatures, but they love us and thats why we love them! 
     

    



