
06,January,2004



       
       urlLink    TIME's local address.
     

    


06,January,2004



       
      Welcome to Anand's Blogs
     

    


30,January,2004



       
       urlLink Hutton Inquiry - Report by Lord Hutton  Report of the Inquiry into the Circumstances Surrounding the Death of Dr David Kelly C.M.G.  by Lord Hutton  
     

    


30,January,2004



       
       urlLink Global Ideas Bank - most socially innovative ideas and projects plus awards   Leads you to Natural Death and Befriending website
     

    


30,January,2004



       
       urlLink The Natural Death Centre 
     

    


30,January,2004



       
       urlLink Befriending - Website for the terminally ill 
     

    


16,February,2004



       
       urlLink Mukul Sharma's Mindsportal 
     

    


19,February,2004



       
       urlLink totse.com | Temple Of The Screaming Electron 
     

    


23,February,2004



       
       urlLink Reason: A Week of Eating Dangerously: Searching for detente between man and beast  A meat eater's day out !!!
     

    


25,February,2004



       
       urlLink The TO KILL A MOCKINGBIRD Student Survival Guide 
     

    


25,February,2004



       
       urlLink Meme Central - Memes, Memetics, and Mind Virus Resource 
     

    


29,February,2004



       
       urlLink Urban Legends Reference Pages 
     

    


03,March,2004



       
       urlLink MBA Institutes in India, Admission Deadlines, Placements, Jobs, Seminars & MDPs 
     

    


03,March,2004



       
       urlLink Wired Magazine 
     

    


03,March,2004



       
       urlLink IIM B Student Community 
     

    


10,March,2004



       
       urlLink quoteland.com - Quotations on every topic, by every author, and in every fashion possible 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink The Ketan Parekh Saga 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink List of finance topics -- USEFUL. 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink Free Dictionary 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink The Short Run 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink Economist.com | Business encyclopedia 
     

    


17,March,2004



       
       urlLink Online Glossary of Research Economics 
     

    


24,May,2004



       
      Title Test
     

    


24,May,2004



       
      Got my GMail account !!! Anand.Swaminathan@gmail.com
     

    


24,May,2004



       
      Hi
     

    


25,May,2004



       
       urlLink EAC - Exact Audio Copy  
     

    


03,June,2004



       
       urlLink Short stories at east of the web 
     

    



25,May,2004


	 
      Puneet Dalmia - IIT D and IIM B Alok Mittal      - IIT D and UCB   JobsAhead  started off at the peak of dot com boom in September  1999 , with angle funding from the Dalmia group. ChrysCapital came in for two rounds of funding. The operations broke-even in 2002-03 with a turnover of around Rs 8 crore, and subsequently closed FY '04 with net profit of Rs 3 crore, riding over billing worth Rs 15 crore.   urlLink Crorepatis at 32, as of Tuesday - The Economic Times 
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
      A simple story of a IT Project Manager. Just wondering what is Anand going to be. A Rishi or a Gaurav ?  urlLink 'I hired him, now he is my boss' - The Economic Times 
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
       urlLink Lessons in Excellence 
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
      IIM Calcutta creates a comprehensive web presence, building a community of alumni, faculty and students. urlLink Click 
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
      Looks like a good site. My CEO reads this site ;-)   urlLink AlwaysOn Home 
     
    


01,June,2004


	 
      Anand and Srinath complete two years at Trilogy.  These are the few things I remember of these two years (chronological) :  Anand and Srinath have a boring 1 month of training  A and S celebrate their first month salary at Gongura (with a full meals ;-))!!  When life was getting boring, with just two of us, the modellers joined us and we never felt the need for more people again.  Honestly, not much of challenging work in the two years. But was succesful in making my managers happy with my work and Anand did become a dependable team member.  Thinking back, office would have been boring without the tons of hours spent theorizing, agonizing, celebrating, philosophising about stock markets !! And of course, making some money too !!  Anand wants to try something different. He had dreamt from kiddo days of attending corporate meetings in a suit and strategising. Decides to go to B-School. Just hoping for some romance in life.   Taking CAT was painful. The postponement of CAT was a blessing. His theories on fate/destiny get some more confirmation. B-School would have not been possible with the cancelled CAT. The final CAT on Feb 25 2004, was the best CAT paper he wrote and rest is history. Somehow, he never had the full heart to do well in CAT, although he wanted to get into a B-School.  And the future ?  Kolkata beckons !! I have no idea what will Anand be in 2006.                            Somehow I have really enjoyed the brutal (Im looking for an equivalent word for surprisingly surprising) turns in life when I had not expected them.  So, what he wants to do now is make tons of money or atleast be in the middle of money !! Not only for himself, but for others who still have no idea how to make money. He wants to make India a land of money makers.  Ahh, come on shut up Anand, remember people who create history, have no hope of a personal destiny !!  ( How was that for an ending ? Of course, I stole that line from somewhere !! )
     
    



