
29,May,2004


    
       
      We wanted to go out of town for the weekend, but we decided to stay in instead. Chris is with his Dad this weekend, so we're on our own. I thought I'd turn the house a little bit more "hotelish" for us. I went out and got some fresh flowers, candles and wine. We had a very romantic dinner last night. Tried out some Yellow Tail Chardonnay. It was OK. I don't think it's worth getting again, but it hasn't turned me off to Chardonnay yet. We've got some more Aussie wine to try out tonight.  Dennis took me to see Shreck 2. It was pretty cute - very silly. I want to check out The Day After Tomorrow as well.  Our plan for today is to go to the Soulard Farmers Market with the cooler this morning, then head over to Belleville to pick our own strawberries. :-D
      


21,May,2004


    
       
      The picnic worked out wonderfully. I grabbed a new basket, a citronella candle, a pre-made turkey club sandwich on wheat, some bottled water, some grape tomatoes, some yummy crackers, and some nectarines at the store. I took along our goat cheese, cranberry curd, a white wine, and the chocolate chip cookies.  We went to Sandy Creek Covered Bridge and ate - everything! Then I walked up and down the creek a little. Should have gotten Dennis to wear his slip-on shoes so he'd come in with me. The baby bluegill were picking at my toes :-D  (The wine made me giddy followed by sleepy!)  It was so nice to get out and just spend time with Dennis and not worry about anything at all. Something to do more often for sure!
      


20,May,2004


    
       
      I want to take a romantic picnic in the park this evening.  We're celebrating the two year anniversary of something this month.  It isn't when we met, when we started dating, when we fell in love, or when we moved in together.  It's just some random time between meeting and dating when our contact started to increase beyond "some person I see at various events around town from time to time."  I'm taking some goat cheese - we have that already, I'm going to go make some chocolate covered strawberries in a few minutes.  I don't know what else to take, but I'll settle on something as I stroll through the grocery store after a bit.  Always dangerous to do with the debit card in hand :)  I'm tired.  It's been a hard week at work.  I can't even count the number of tiny things I've been criticized for, and I was in the office by myself all day Monday.  Of course accepting criticism is not one of my strong points as it is, but come on already!  It just wears you out after a while, to have everything picked over like that.
      


30,June,2004


    
       
      Well, date day and night with my son that is :)  Dennis is gone to Wisconsin, so Chris and I headed up to Forest Park.  We rode the Giant Wheel that is there to celebrate the 1904 World's Fair.  Chris had to keep me safe cause I got a little scared :)   Big Scary Wheel:     View of downtown you don't usually see:    After the wheel, we went to picnic by the boathouse.  We fed some lettuce to ducks.  They didn't really like it.  Snobby ducks!  Then we rented a peddle boat.  We made it all the way to Post-Dispatch lake at the bottom of Art Hill.  Oh, it was fun.  Chris was a good peddler too.  He never really did stop or get too tired.  Good thing, cause I would have worn myself out without help!  We ran back home for a while to rest up, then headed back out for the Muny's production of Meet Me in St. Louis.  Chris liked the real trolley and the fireworks at the end, but I don't think he was totally thrilled by the rest of the show.  I can't really say that I was either, except watching a play about the 1904 World's Fair in Forest Park where it actually took place was pretty spectacular!  We got home very late and found Dennis already here!  Yea!
      


28,June,2004


    
       
      We were at the Sears Craftsman Nationals Friday night.  Here's what I wrote then: (from  urlLink Neons.org )  "Top Fuel wasn't running as hot as Funny Car. In between rounds we went back to the pits and watched Darrell Russell's crew for the entire rebuild. Darrell is very nice, not at all like stupid John Force  He packs his own chute and pours his own gas too. (And did I mention he's quite cute on top of all that?  ) Anyhoo, we must have been good luck, cause he came out in the last run of the night and busted a 4.511 @ 328.54, for the #1 spot and obliterated the track record. This was the quickest run I've ever seen. Awesome!"  I was so impressed with Darrell Russell.  He was going to be my new favorite race car driver.  I even dragged Dennis out of our way to pass by his pit one last time after he put down that amazing run!  I checked up on the results last night on the NHRA website.  I saw that Russell had had a crash, but there were no more details at that time.  Dennis left for Wisconsin with his Dad first thing this morning.  I came back in from seeing them off and flipped on the TV.  The first thing I heard was, "Stay tuned for details of the fatal crash at Gateway last night."  Oh crap!  I knew exactly what that meant.  I was stunned and shocked and upset much more than I probably should have been by the news that he had died in that wreck.  I had a very upsetting day at work because of it.  Just cast such a pall over everything.  Strange how that happens sometimes at the news of death.  Maybe it's just my birthday yesterday has got me more in touch with mortality in general right now.  I just know that Darrell Russell was absolutely NOT dead Friday night.  Everything was so normal, so routine.  Nobody had any idea what was coming.  Of course Dennis and his Dad just left to go drag racing too, which isn't helping matters any!  Rest in Peace, Mr. Darrell Russell 
      


27,June,2004


    
       
      Well, I'm 27.  Just about time to quit telling!  As promised, text from Dennis's card:  "A Promise of Love for Your Birthday"  I wish I could buy you A thousand beautiful gifts For your birthday - Fancy things, luxuries, Suprises to delight you - But I know the things That make life happy Can't be bought  ...like love, And the closeness Two people share  Time - Days spent together When we're happy No matter what we're doing...  Kindness - The little things we do For one another...  These things can't be bought, And yet They're the best gifts of all...  And so, For your birthday, I'm giving you this promise As part of my gift - To love you even more And make you Even happier, To make all our days Together Days to remember Always.  Happy Birthday All my love always  Dennis   Yes, vomit :)  It made me cry when I got it.  He makes me such a girly-girl.  *sigh*    For my birthday gift, Dennis, Chris and I went to Litchfield.  We stopped by my folk's house and picked up Mom.  We all four went to the lake to play at the playground.  There is a "pizza pan" spinning thing that I almost made Dennis sick on!  Then we went to  urlLink The Ariston , which is an old cafe on Route 66.  I just love the place!  I had a french dip, which was excellent as always.  The suprise of the evening was an ENTIRE two layer red velvet cake.  This place has the best desserts.  Oh, it was heavenly!     I love the way Dennis listens to me and goes out of his way to please me.  This was such a special birthday because I got something so simple, but so me.  It's so nice to be loved!  If you ever go, though, you really should get a horseshoe sandwich.  It's the central Illinois thing to do.   From cooking.com:  The signature food of Springfield, Illinois is a sandwich known as a horseshoe. It has been credited to a chef that worked at the Leland Hotel in 1928 and has become Springfield's most famous contribution to the world of food. It consists of two hamburgers on two slices of toast, covered with cheddar cheese sauce and buried beneath a mound of French fries.   For the Welsh Rarebit Sauce: 2 tablespoons salted butter 1/2 cup beer 2 egg yolks 3 cups grated Old English or other sharp white cheddar 1 teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 1/4 teaspoon dry mustard Salt  For the Sandwich: 1 1/2 pounds ground beef Salt and freshly ground pepper 8 slices toasted thick white bread 2 pounds cooked French fries   TO MAKE THE SAUCE: Set up a double boiler or set a medium-sized stainless-steel bowl over a pot of simmering water. Check to make sure the bottom of the bowl is not touching the water. Melt the butter in the double boiler and then add the beer. While constantly whisking, slowly incorporate the egg yolks. Add the cheese and stir constantly until melted and the sauce is thick enough to coat the back of a spoon: this should take 5 to 8 minutes. Add the Worcestershire and mustard. Season the sauce with salt to taste. To avoid a stringy sauce, it is important to constantly stir the cheese and be sure that the water is not boiling, but rather simmering.   TO COOK THE BEEF: Season the beef with the salt and pepper and form it into eight 6-ounce patties. Heat a large non-stick skillet over medium-high heat or set up an electric grill, and cook the patties, a few at a time, 5 minutes per side for medium.   TO ASSEMBLE THE DISH: For each serving, place two slices of the toast on a large plate and top each with a patty. Pour the rarebit sauce over the beef and top the sauce with French fries. Serve immediately.   Recipe courtesy the Leland Hotel, Springfield, Illinois   Of course you can always get your horseshoe with ham instead of beef.  I actually like the ham better.
      


26,June,2004


    
       
      Tomorrow is my 27th birthday.  Dennis and Chris made a run to Target to get my gifts.  Dennis got Austin Powers on DVD and Chris got Bruce Almighty on VHS.  We took Chris to see Bruce Almighty at the theater.  I did like it, probably not enough to own it, but it's really very sweet that he remembered.  :)  What a cutie I have!  Dennis's card was disgustingly sappy!  I'll have to type it out when I've got a bit more time.  (Wordy...)
      


22,June,2004


    
       
      I made it to the library to pick up Henry James's The Ambassadors this morning.  Here goes!
      


21,June,2004


    
       
      Chris got himself dressed before I was even done brewing coffee this morning!  My goodness, he must have been very excited about soccer camp!  What a relief.  Back still hurts a lot!
      


20,June,2004


    
       
      I finally have time to read again!  I used to read voraciously, but school reading really cuts into leisure reading.  I'm graduated, so it's time to start up again in earnest.  I think I missed too much literature during my science & math heavy college career, so I clipped the Cliff's Notes list as a "summer" reading list.  Of course it's going to take much more than summer to do it, but you always have to force yourself into reading the "classics."   I cut what I had read within a reasonable amount of time.  I cut a whole slew of Dickens.  I cut randomly.  I had Dennis shout "delete" at whatever interval he felt like.  The list is still too long.  Yes, I have missed quite a bit!  No, I honestly haven't read any of these except for Pearl Buck's The Good Earth, which I believe we tackled in 10th grade?  I'm sure I'll gain new appreciation to re-read it.  Ambassadors, Henry James Anna Karenina, Leo Tolstoy As I Lay Dying, Faulkner Bean Trees, Barbara Kingsolver  Black Like Me, John Howard Griffin    Canterbury Tales, Geoffrey Chaucer Death of a Salesman, Arthur Miller Different Drummer, William Melvin Kelley  Dubliners, Joyce Ethan Frome, Wharton Farewell to Arms, Ernest Hemingway Frankenstein, Mary Shelley  Giver, Lois Lowry Good Earth, Pearl Buck   Idiot, Fyodor Dostoevsky Inherit the Wind, Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee Jane Eyre, Charlotte Bronte Killer Angels, Michael Shaara Light in August, William Faulkner Madame Bovary, Gustave Flaubert Man and Superman & Caesar and Cleopatra,  George Bernard Shaw Miss Lonelyhearts & The Day of the Locust, Nathanael West Moll Flanders, Daniel Defoe   Nana, Emile Zola Narrative of the Life of Frederick Douglass Notes from Underground, Fyodor Dostoevsky  Old Man and the Sea, Hemingway   One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, Kesey Outsiders, S.E. Hinton's Pearl, John Steinbeck Pickwick Papers, Charles Dickens Picture of Dorian Gray, Oscar Wilde   Raisin in the Sun, Vivian Hansberry Red and the Black, Robert Stendhal Red Badge of Courage, Crane Rivals & School for Scandal, Richard Brinsley Sheridan Sense and Sensibility, Jane Austen Sound and the Fury, William Faulkner Steppenwolf & Siddhartha, Herman Hesse Stranger, Albert Camus Sun Also Rises, Ernest Hemingway  Tender Is the Night, F. Scott Fitzgerald Tess of the d'Urbervilles, Hardy Three Musketeers, Alexandre Dumas Victory, Joseph Conrad Way of the World, William Congreve Winesburg, Ohio, Sherwood Anderson Winter's Tale, William Shakespeare Wuthering Heights, Emily Bronte Yellow Raft in Blue Water, Michael Dorris  I have every intention of picking up more from the Cliff's Notes list at a later date.  This is more than enough, no?
      


20,June,2004


    
       
      Oh boy, I really hurt my back!  I have no idea what I did, but I know that every possible position I can put my body into hurts.  A lot.  I hope I didn't do anything serious to myself!  Dennis has been quite a help.  I can't do much but lay in bed.  Sheesh!  I have to work this week.  I wonder how that's going to be?  We needed to get the apartment ready.  Chris is coming back from his grandparent's house this evening.  He's starting summer camp at the Y tomorrow morning.  *fingers crossed* for smooth sailing getting ready!
      


14,June,2004


    
       
      I took my sister to her first good rock n roll concert Saturday night.  We saw  urlLink The Wildhearts  and  urlLink The Darkness  at  urlLink The Pageant  in the Loop.  I'd never been there before, but it is a huge improvement over Mississippi Nights.  Excellent club, excellent crowd, excellent show, amazingly LOUD!  I had a great time, reminded me of good old rock n roll shows that I used to drag my poor mom to.  Apparently Ginger of The Wildhearts wasn't fibbing when he said St. Louis was great...   urlLink Tour Diary Page .
      


03,June,2004


    
       
      Oh wonderous!  I got bumped to part time at work.  How annoying.  I know I'm on my way out anyway.  I believe my boss is incapable of being pleased with anything - ever!  Hopefully they'll fund my job search.  Part time with no benefits is just too much to take.  Shame, I honestly do like the work.
      


30,July,2004


    
       
      Not the metal band, but the book.  I got it. I read it. I didn't hate it. I just can't  love  it. This is a great American writer, and a great American book from the last century. I see the richness, but it rang a little empty for me. I was instantly reminded of Edgar Lee Master's  Spoon River Anthology , which was written 15 years earlier and is much prettier, at least as full, and just as biting and ironic, and hits just as sharp a chord of "America" as Faulkner does, not to mention the close connection with death and dying. Of course poets (seeds in a dry pod) can always brave new territory first, but let's be honest. Faulkner wasn't pioneering stream-of-consciousness. It'd been going in poetry for - ever? And Ulysses, king of the genre, was published about 10 years earlier. Anti-Victorianism had been going on since the 1870s. Heck,  Anna Karenina  had some serious stream-of-consciousness sections in it and it was published starting in 1873. Did catch an  urlLink interesting paper  someone wrote about Faulkner and cubism and surrealism. Maybe I'm just reading it so late that the freshness isn't fresh anymore?  Beyond all of that, I did like the book. I like the fact that I can say "I've read that" if it ever comes up in conversation for some reason. I like the fact that I've been to Yoknapatawpha County, even if I could never spell that without looking, and I'm not 100% sure I can pronounce it :)   My favorite passages are when Faulkner breaks through his characters and slaps down a big hefty chunk of prose.  WOW!  Now if I can get  that  in larger doses, please?  I will read more of him just because I saw what's hiding behind all of those darn ourns and tothers. 
      


29,July,2004


    
       
      I spent some time this morning adding text to my footer, moving my Blogger and Site Meter buttons down there, and adding a Links section to the sidebar.&nbsp; I even managed to make it look like the other sidebar lists.&nbsp; Wow!  After that, I realized that I don't have much to link to.&nbsp; My email and homepage are listed in my Profile, and everything else I've got up as a link right now is already accessible from my homepage.&nbsp; I guess I ought to think of some more interesting links, and work on adding those this afternoon.  *yawn*&nbsp; I don't really enjoy my days off.&nbsp; I wish I was working five days a week because staying home is not too much fun.&nbsp; I know it is stressing me out, and stressing Dennis out too.&nbsp; Blah.&nbsp; Maybe I should volunteer for something? 
      


27,July,2004


    
       
      I'm going to finish reading Tolstoy's Anna Karenina today.&nbsp; It reads very quickly for such&nbsp;a long book (my copy is 817 pages.)&nbsp; I just found out that The Penguin Classics version of it is the current selection for  urlLink Oprah's Book Club . I feel like such a joiner! I didn't know until I saw it on display on an endcap at K-Mart with a big banner announcing it as "Oprah's Summer Pick!"   Now I know why it was so darn hard to get my hands on one of the 20-something copies the library keeps.&nbsp; I think I may sign up for Oprah's book club just to see what other people are saying about it.&nbsp; I may have a bit of an unique view of it since I have been through leaving my husband for another man.&nbsp; Maybe I'll even have something meaningful to contribute.   I'm so glad I've started reading!&nbsp; It makes me really happy.&nbsp; Anna Karenina is not a happy book, but it is so beautifully written.&nbsp; I think this was an excellent choice to follow Henry James's The Ambassadors.&nbsp; They were both writing inner monologue, they both handled their novels in a similar fashion.&nbsp; But where James is nearly impossible to read sometimes, Tolstoy shines.&nbsp; There are difficult passages, the characters go through exceptionally complex trains of thought, and the whole time you can't help but understand everything.&nbsp; I personally think James went too far in the academic sense of what he was doing.&nbsp; So far that the story almost disappears.&nbsp; The things he left out were almost too big to make anything of it.&nbsp; Tolstoy is a much better read.&nbsp; It seems that  this  is what James should have done.&nbsp; The sense of accomplishment I had after I finished The Ambassadors was mostly "whew, I made it through that!"&nbsp; I am honestly enjoying this one though.   Oh, got the bug to go read.&nbsp; Sitting here typing isn't getting me to the end of the book any quicker :)  
      


21,July,2004


    
       
      We went drag racing last night.&nbsp; Not much exciting happened, but Dennis's new car is  slow !&nbsp; As in 16.6 @ 82.&nbsp; Much slower than it should be.&nbsp; I ran two 15.6s at 89 and 88.&nbsp; Both on high 2.3 60' times.&nbsp; Bleh.&nbsp; The air was heavy and the track wasn't great, but I expected more MPH out of the car since I changed the computer.&nbsp; I know I short shifted the first run because I forgot the how high the new rev limiter is.&nbsp; Hehe!  Right as we were getting ready to leave, Chris got bit / stung on the ear lobe by something.&nbsp; Poor thing :( 
      


20,July,2004


    
       
      Yesterday&nbsp;was Dennis's dad's 52nd birthday.&nbsp; Dennis called  urlLink The Pasta House  and ordered Chicken Flamingo, a dozen rolls&nbsp;and their famous salad from the bulk carry-out menu.&nbsp; We stopped by the grocery and grabbed a&nbsp;triple chocolate layer cake and a quart of Neopolitan ice cream, then&nbsp;picked&nbsp;up our chicken and took it all down to his parents' house. &nbsp; It was a nice dinner, but Romeo (their&nbsp;Yorkie) and Chris don't get along very well.&nbsp; They were both very wound up and both very noisy!&nbsp; Neither one of them listened to us either ;)&nbsp;    
      


19,July,2004


    
       
      Dennis bought himself a new car Saturday afternoon.&nbsp; Yea, now we've got two Neons! &nbsp;      It's a 1995 ACR, the same color as my R/T minus the stripes. 
      


17,July,2004


    
       
      These are the states of the union that I've seen. Add a chunk of Canada to it, because I've been about 115 miles in from Sault Ste. Marie on a train.       urlLink create your own personalized map of the USA   &nbsp;  Now don't take this to mean that I don't travel.&nbsp; I've seen any number of places here in the Midwest, and within easy striking distance of home.&nbsp; There are so many things to do!&nbsp; Everyone should stop flying over the fly-overs and take a look around.&nbsp; Yes, we have the Ozarks, but we've also got Chicago - and everything in between!&nbsp; There isn't a lack of culture.&nbsp; It isn't even boring.&nbsp; Vast fields of corn on clear summer days can be just as beautiful as other vista in the world.&nbsp; It just takes being able to appreciate what you've got!  &nbsp;  I want to see the American West.&nbsp; I want to see New England.&nbsp; I love the historical aspects of both places, as well as the visual impact.&nbsp; I want to see real mountains.&nbsp; I want to see Washington D.C. just once.&nbsp; I want to see the Pacific Northwest.&nbsp; I want to see the desert Southwest.&nbsp; I think we've got more travel destinations right here at home than I can ever possibly visit.&nbsp; I have quite a list of things within a day's drive of St. Louis that I haven't done yet to keep me busy for a long time.&nbsp; For instance, I've never actually stopped in Kansas City and looked around.&nbsp; I've never seen the sights in Memphis.  &nbsp;  I want to take Dennis to a lot of the wonderful places I've seen in the past.&nbsp; He just has to see New Orleans.&nbsp; I want to take him all over the UP of Michigan and Minnesota.&nbsp; I want him to see  urlLink The House on the Rock  and visit a cheese factory with me.&nbsp; He's never had good fresh curds, let alone deep-fried curds!  &nbsp;  My obsession lately has been driving to a nearby small town - like  urlLink Vandalia, Illinois  or  urlLink Washington, Missouri  - staying in a bed and breakfast, and just taking in whatever there is to see.&nbsp; Just for the weekend.&nbsp; I'm happy with simple trips like that.  &nbsp;  Heck, there are things in St. Louis itself that I haven't done, and other things that I'll never get tired of doing.&nbsp; The view from the Arch, the Botanical Garden, going to see the Cardinals - these are things I'll never pass up an opportunity to go do.  &nbsp;  Just look at the pretty city I live in!   &nbsp; 
      


15,July,2004


    
       
      Everyone was cranky after dinner this evening.&nbsp; Summer cabin fever?&nbsp; We all got in the car and randomly drove up Lemay Ferry into south St. Louis.&nbsp; We wound up going past the Chippewa  urlLink Ted Drewes  and thought it sounded really good.&nbsp; But we only had about 30 minutes to get back in time to close the pool, and the line was typically long, so we swung over to the South Grand location.&nbsp; No line!&nbsp;&nbsp;      &nbsp;  Chocolate chip concretes were the daily special, so we got three and ate them in the car on the rushed drive home.&nbsp; Yes, it is hard to drive a 5 speed in the city when you're eating Ted Drewes :)  
      


14,July,2004


    
       
      I had a job interview once that included a personality test.  It is lame because you can easily defeat these quick-hit versions.  They are doubled up to catch you in lies, but if you keep with your story and keep in mind what your boss would want to hear, it is pretty easy.  I just did this with no intentions behind my answers.  So if you believe in these things, this is me:                     Introverted (I) 58.33% Extroverted (E) 41.67%  Imaginative (N) 53.49% Realistic (S) 46.51%  Intellectual (T) 50% Emotional (F) 50%  Organized (J) 52.63% Easygoing (P) 47.37%  


14,July,2004


    
       
      This song cracks me up!  I hear it at work and almost laugh out loud because it reminds me so much of the summer Dennis and I met.  Liz Phair - Why Can't I?  Get a load of me, get a load of you Walkin' down the street, and I hardly know you It's just like we were meant to be  Holding hands with you when we're out at night Got a girlfriend, you say it isn't right And I've got someone waiting too  What if this is just the beginning We're already wet, and we're gonna go swimming  Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you Why can't I speak whenever I talk about you It's inevitable, it's a fact that we're gonna get down to it So tell me Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you  Isn't this the best part of breakin' up Finding someone else you can't get enough of Someone who wants to be with you too  It's an itch we know we are gonna scratch Gonna take a while for this egg to hatch But wouldn't it be beautiful  Here we go, we're at the beginning We haven't fucked yet, but my heads spinning  Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you Why can't I speak whenever I talk about you It's inevitable, it's a fact that we're gonna get down to it So tell me Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you  High enough for you to make me wonder Where it's goin' High enough for you to pull me under Somethin's growin' out of this that we can control Baby I am dyin'  Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you Why can't I speak whenever I talk about you  Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you Why can't I speak whenever I talk about you It's inevitable, it's a fact that we're gonna get down to it So tell me Why can't I breathe whenever I think about you
      


14,July,2004


    
       
      My summer reading list is going very slowly.  It took me a long time to finish Henry James's  The Ambassadors.   It was a different kind of read.  Lots of internal dialogue and ramblingly beautiful sentence structure.  There are very few people I would recommend it to, because it takes a special kind of patience and a very quiet room to get much from James's classic "late James" style.  I know a lot of people who would give up after the second paragraph though :)  Dennis gave this one a whirl:  "The principle I have just mentioned as operating had been, with the most newly disembarked of the two men, wholly instinctive - the fruit of a sharp sense that, delightful as it would be to find himself looking, after so much separation, into his comrade's face, his business would be a trifle bungled should he simply arrange for this countenance to present itself to the nearing steamer as the first 'note' of Europe."  It slows you down a lot :)  The library has lost the copy of Anna Karenina that I put on hold Monday.  I hope it shows up soon.  They'll get me another copy, but still, it sucks to lose a book like that.
      


12,July,2004


    
       
      The  urlLink St. Louis Cardinals  are heading into the All Star Break 7 games ahead of the second place Cubs!  They're the second best team in all of baseball with a silly record of 54 - 33.  Get ready folks, we're going to have some rough losing streaks in the second half.  At least there will be Olympics to distract us for a while...
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      Finally got around to scanning this:     It's from our  urlLink trip to Six Flags on the 4th .  I know it says that right on the picture :)  We watched the alligator show, then paid $5 for this horrible Polaroid.  Chris is holding a three-year-old alligator, and I'm holding Chris.  Apologies for the terrible over-exposure of the print.
      


09,July,2004


    
       
      Work annoyance:  This morning one of the things left on my desk was a pile of fax cover sheets.  Here's why: My boss rarely uses a computer, so they're already copied and you have to *gasp* use a typewriter to fill them out when you need them.  I am not good at hitting lines with a typewriter.  So I decided last Friday to make my own fax cover sheet on the computer.  I printed it out on letterhead and everything.  I thought it looked quite nice, plus it is now a template like all of the other forms we use.  Apparently that was bad and wrong, and I must be too stupid to make my own copies from the stack of 58 fax cover sheets I already have.  Oh well.  Gotta concentrate more on the job search.  I don't know how I'm supposed to develop loyalty to this :)  Yeah, if you could just take care of the covers for the TPS reports, that'd be great...   Apartment annoyance:  Somebody doesn't like us closing the pool.  In their very best impression of second graders, they called the landlady and tattled that we were, "at the pool till 10:00 after we made everyone else leave at 9:00," and that my son was, "in the pool all by himself, with nobody watching him."  Neither was true.  We were at the pool later than anyone else, but we locked up at 9:00 by the watch we took down there with us so we wouldn't be late.  It's pitch black at 10:00.  Wouldn't we have noticed???  Chris got to the pool before we did by about 45 seconds.  I had a shoe delay :)  I was irritated that he went straight in, but we could see him the whole time and the pool was full of people.  He did get spoken to about it last night though, and again today after we found out we're living with a mole!  Landlady called with a long message today.  Later found out who was responsible for the call, that the landlady knows it is all crap, and that my neighbor is even more of a drama queen that I had figured.  And I had figured her for a BIG one all along!   Moral of the story:  WHO CARES!  IT'S FRIDAY!!!
      


08,July,2004


    
       
      Just got back from the cookout at Chris's day camp.  There was only one other parent there today.  I hope that makes him feel special :)  Especially after all of the things I could have gone to if Paul would have only bothered to tell me about them.  The Circle Y Ranch is pretty cute.  It's back in those Jefferson County hills I want so badly to move into.  Or on top of, I should say.  There's a beautiful little creek that runs through the middle.  It's got a rock bottom, of course, as all of the creeks in the hills seem to have.  There's also a nice weathered section of limestone bluff along one side for a while.  It was exceptionally humid, since it had just finished raining when I arrived.  Steam was rising off of everything around.  It had rained very hard on my way down, so that I almost missed a turn because it was hard to see, and my brakes were really soggy so I almost missed it again after I'd finally found it.  The kids had caught about 10 frogs and toads and the cutest little red / orange salamander!  I'm not sure what species it was since our little field guide only has about 5 types altogether.  Hrm, I should invest in better field guides.  I do wish I had one every so often, and they'd make great bedtime stories for Chris.  Didn't bring the camera again.  I need to velcro it to myself!  I'll try to remember next week.
      


06,July,2004


    
       
      Edited pictures of last night's storms.  My degree in meteorology was't an accident.  I love bad weather.  I was excited to have gotten two lightning pictures.  It's hard to do.  Just lucky, I should say.  The volume of strikes last night made it a lot easier!         
      


05,July,2004


    
       
      It's our last day off together.  Dennis's last day of an eleven day vacation!  We're being vegetables.  I think I'd like to be celery.  Maybe Dennis is an eggplant?  We were going to go downtown to Fair St. Louis Saturday night to see the big fireworks, but after it got rained out Friday and there was a good chance of rain Saturday, we opted for another trip to Festus.  This time we took Chris with us and got another $30 worth of fireworks.  Chris is taken with sparklers this year.  Forgot to take the digital camera though.  Darn, there would have been some cute pictures!  Yesterday I got my birthday present from my parents.  We all went to Six Flags.  Oh, my dad was in fine form.  :x  Dennis tried really hard to keep him entertained and distracted.  It was a nice try, but it didn't work.  He wound up going to sit by the entrance for the rest of the day.  Weeine.  It gave Dennis a good glimpse behind the scenes.  Not sure that's exactly what I wanted him to see :)  I didn't let it ruin my day.  We tried really hard to have fun.  As always, the 4th of July was HOT and MUGGY.  Blah.  I didn't get to ride The Boss, Mr. Freeze, or the Screamin' Eagle.  For some reason they shut some of the coasters down for the day?  We didn't make it to the water park either, which was fine by me!
      


03,July,2004


    
       
      Due to a schedule conflict with Paul, Dennis and I wound up going to Festus to shoot fireworks by ourselves last night.  We bought about $80 worth.  I'm still very childlike about fireworks, since we had a very limited selection in Illinois when I was a kid.  Oh, and blowing stuff up is cool too!  We had a lot of fun.  We almost always have fun.  He's a fun guy.  Being in love is fun!  Being in love and shooting fireworks is even more fun!  *yawn* we were out late, for a couple of old fogies...
      


05,August,2004


    
       
      Chris and I spent the day at the  urlLink City Museum  today. We did so much climbing and crawling and sliding! I'm worn out!  I got scared when we were way up in this airplane. It's higher than it looks up there, and it's just built over the parking lot...     The new caves are really cool too. They used the old lightwell of the building for part of it. It's very neat!    It was so fun!  It's really tiring though.  I came home and took a nap :) 
      


02,August,2004


    
       
      Dennis took me out to the Bella Sera Italian Grill on Gravois Friday night. We just had sandwiches. I got a grilled chicken club, and he got a steak and cheese. They were both very good. Not as good as the fish tacos at the same location when it was a mexican grill though :) Sandwiches came with fries, which they graciously substituted with sauteed spinach. The spinach was excellent! Neither of us felt up to a $5 glass of wine. I didn't see until we were leaving that they had Schlafly on tap, or I would have had some of that with my sandwich. If they stay open longer than the mexican place did, we will go back.  Then we went to  urlLink Oberweis  for desert. He had a very fancy waffle cone with brownie ice cream. I had a hot fudge sundae. He liked it better than Ted Drewes, but I didn't. It was  very  good though.  We rented three movies, watched one each day over the weekend: Bad Santa (hated it!), The Butterfly Effect (liked it a lot, and it didn't creep me out), and Secondhand Lions (liked it, very cute).  For all of that, it was a very boring weekend.
      



07,July,2004


    
       
      Dennis and I met before the Gateway Neons meeting at Clydesdale Park.  We talked and cuddled and talked.  Then he tried to kiss me!  I ducked a little bit.  We decided to skip the meeting and head for the fireworks instead.  We stopped by Mobil to get some gas.  I suprised him with a quick kiss on the lips.  Awww, our first kiss!  And nobody died either...  After the fireworks, we went back to south county and ate at Steak N Shake.  We kissed again in the parking lot - with feeling :)
      


09,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:   Whaaaaa! Date:   Tue 07/09/02 11:21 PM     

09,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   Who me? Victim? Nope! Date:   Tue 07/09/02 09:45 PM        **I know this reply is late(lost the 1st attempt! DAMMIT!), and a lot of the things in this email have been resolved, disolved, and covered in real life, so I'll keep this reply brief so I can get to the others ;-) It's harder to reply to these now, because I have been seeing you so much in real life, and I would much rather do this for real than in email!!   LOL - hahahahaha, you are officially a victim of the drunk dial!  I wouldn't say drunk, maybe, but it sure was the "been drinking" dial ;)  I was drinking by myself :'''''(  **If you ever need to call. Call. If I'm here, I will pick up. If not, I will get to you as soon as I get the message.   Paul was out until 1:30 (in the morning)  I got scared - a lot!  Then I tried to get him to talk - he still won't talk so much.  He did say DENNIS a few times.  He doesn't think he deserves to be happy.  :'''''''(  I hate hurting people.  It is hard to *get tough* when he gets like that - I know he hurts, but I don't know how much he's acting out - pressing my button - every other time I've almost gone, all he had to do was cry and I lost all confidence.  This time, if he can't be a big boy, I'm going to have to just buckle down and get "mean" with him, I guess.  *sigh*  Why do we have to make things harder than they need to be?  *ouch*  **It looks like things are going OK now in this respect, or at least have improved since I received this email. I'm glad that he is at least trying to be civil with me in real life, even if when I leave he hates me.   I had to force myself to stop thinking about you.  I got close to "run away to Dennis" thinking - when I was trying to have Paul hold me - trying to hold him - he just can't do it right anymore...  It was hard - I really had to THINK --- concentrate on the moment instead of dreaming it away with you in my head.  I know I need to feel all of this - I can't lean you thoughts of you too much - this is for me, afterall.  What's the point if I don't get anything out of it?    **I'm glad you see that. I'm glad you are trying to do that. I want you to be done with that (as much as you can be) before you start this. Ha! Who am I kidding...we've already STARTED this....  What's the point if I build you up to some superhuman mystical creature that you can't possibly live up to in real life anyway?  **I know. That's what I was concerned that we were doing all along by doing all of this email/aim stuff and not seeing each other in person so much. But now that we've spent time together in real life, I realize that the aim/email showed us the TRUE us, the us that we are in real life without the distractions, without the filters that are required in order to live day to day. It allows us to be oursleves without fear when we're together. It accelerated our "getting to know each other" process tremendously, and was a positive thing. I know it has brought us closer than we would have been otherwise. I can't imagine our history being any other way.   Paul sees how much I love you - he saw it Thursday night.  He felt like a third wheel.  I told him that THAT is the REAL me - the me I can't be around him, the me that comes out when I'm at work, with friends, home alone - the me that runs away when Paul comes home, the me that he has hurt so many times.  I guess we really can't stay married if he's not married to ME, can we?  **And I know you've told him a lot more since then(just got off the phone w/you;-) and I'm glad that he's taking it as well as he is. I'm actually GLAD that he was there today. I got to look him face to face and be honest with him. To see that he CAN deal with me.....if he has to.  **The only thing that worries me is what is happening with his command of you not to see me....  I cried last night.  :''''''(  **I'm sorry to hear that.  ^^^Doh, thought I wasn't going to involve you :)  I suck at not  involving!  **You are doing OK. I am very curious as to what is going on, because I'm part of it. I can't NOT be part of it if I'm with you. AND DAMMIT I'M GOING TO BE WITH YOU!  Well you ARE a little scary...  :)  **What about me is scary to you???  God, I'm so sorry...  I mean sorry that we have bad timing :(  Sorry that I can't promise you there won't be some measure of OUCH involved...  Sorry that you have to experience it like this instead of under perfect conditions.  Sorry sorry sorry.  **I know what I'm doing here. I know the possible outcomes, including the bad ones. Don't be sorry. The fact that you are always telling me you're sorry kind of worries me... :-/  But I'm HAPPY too :-D  You make me happy.  Making you happy makes me happy.  Being with you makes me happy.  Getting email from you makes me happy.  Getting IMs from you makes me happy.  Reading your website makes me happy.  Reading you silly screen name makes me happy.  Thinking about you makes me happy.  I'm just one big ball of happiness :)  **:-) I'm happy and can ecco all of those things :-) But my fingers have a long night ahead of them, so I won't retype ;-)   I'm just scared today and sad.  I HATE hurting people.  I won't be able to handle hurting you...  "What have I become, my sweetest friend?  Everyone I know goes away in the end.  You could have it all...  My empire of dirt.  I will let you down,  I will make you hurt..."  You know, that song scares the shit out of me... except the last two lines!!!  "If I could start again, a million miles away... I would keep myself, I would find a way."  **I know that song is HURT. We can only be us. We can only play out these cards we've been so absolutely lucky to get dealt. Let's enjoy winning this round of cards, even if we don't end up going home with all of the money. You can have a lot of fun gambling, even if you don't win. Although I think we've got a steady supply of aces up our sleeves, and I KNOW we're both smart enough to play this game without losing it all.  There's always a little tiny piece of hope somewhere, isn't there?  **LITTLE TINY PIECE??? HOW ABOUT FRICKING HUGE!!!???!!! Shit, if I didn't beleive in my heart that this would turn out well I wouldn't have come this far with you!!! Do you think I would? With everything on the line? Do you think I'd throw you this rope if I wasn't going to pull you up with it? Do you think I'd give this much of my heart to you if I didn't truly beleive the risk was worth taking? That the odds were beatable?  **And that last line. That's bullshit. I wouldn't change a thing I've done since I met you. I would not keep myself a million miles away. Would you?  

09,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   "Shannon Yevcak"   Subject:   Re: Quickie :) Date:   Tue 07/09/02 04:09 PM      You're probably gone already, but I am ok :-) Will talk more tonight for sure, but busy at the moment. Just popped on to read, no real time to reply.   :-D :-D :-D You make me grin like an idiot with simple text, yet you doubt I'm in love with you? Sheesh! ;-)  Cautious. That's all I'm trying to be. This IS so wonderful, so special, I want to make sure we do it right. I want to avoid any regrets because I don't have any yet. I would do everything over, just as I did it. I want to be able to say that about ALL of this :-) So I'm being careful, cautious. I know you are too. More reply later! Boss is still walking around!  Dennis
      


09,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:   Quickie :) Date:   Tue 07/09/02 03:18 PM      I've only got about 15 more minutes to sit here, but if you get this in time, could you please hit me back real quick to let me know you're cool?  I sent a longer email, kinda freaking.  I'm cool now - but worried about you *worry wart*  :-D  Besides, I just like to pester you :)  Shannon
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      I had been honest with my husband.  It finally got to him enough to email Dennis about it.  I can't really say how I felt about it at the time.  I was selfish.  If you don't take a stand for yourself at times like these, you don't make it through; you don't make it out.  I did what I felt I had to do.  I never got to reply to this to Paul.  Dennis didn't want Paul to know I'd seen it.  Oh! did I ever have things to say about it!  I still do, with a few years' perspecitve on it now.  Hurting someone you love (or loved) is not easy.  I wish Paul could have told me he wanted to make me happy.  I never got that impression from him - NEVER.  I had come to believe that he truely wanted to make me miserable.  That's the way he acted - almost as long as we were together, except for the six months or so when we got on really well right around our wedding.  From:   Paul Yevcak   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   This is Paul!! Date:   Wed 07/10/02 09:10 AM      Hey Dennis,  Don't know if you're at work now, or at home.  Doesn't really matter though, I guess.  At any rate, I just wanted to get some stuff of my mind, and clear up a few things with you.  First, and most important, I'M NOT MAD AT YOU FOR ANY OF THIS.  Like I said yesterday, I like hanging out with you, talking to you, BS'ing with you; whatever the case may be.  I don't blame you for anything that's happened.  I'm sure that for you, as it is for me, parts of this situation are entirely too "weird".  I get upset when I see you and Shannon together, goofing off, or joking around.  NOT because it pisses me off, or that I think you guys are going to go around the corner and have sex or something.  But I see the way Shannon looks at you, and I see the smile on her face that never diminishes.  I hear the way she laughs with you.  That's what hurts most of the time.  It's  just another nail in the "Shannon and I aren't meant for each other" coffin.  I wanted to be the "Dennis", I wanted to be the one that can make her laugh, I wanted to be the one who can always put a smile on her face.  But in all honestly, I can't.  I have to literally WORK to accomplish those things. You do it with ease.  So yes, it gets uncomfortable, and it gets discouraging, and it hurts me to no end.  I'm the husband!!  I should be the one who makes her feel like that!!  But I'm not, and never will be.  As  I said, that is THE only reason I get quiet.  I feel like the 3rd wheel when the 3 of us are doing anything.  And I'm sure that you've noticed that same thing.  And I know this is NOT your fault by any means, that you never set out to do anything will ill intent.  And at home, I DO use you as an excuse often, or use you as a "stick" to poke at Shannon.  Deep down I know that's wrong, but a lot of times I'm just grasping at straws, so to speak.  I'll write more later, but I was in a 3-car accident this morning on my way to work, and I have another insurance company to call. But I just wanted to let you know that I DO NOT blame you for any of this. Not one part.  I'm just trying to figure out how to deal with it. Perhaps once Chris and I move it may be easier for me?  Not 100% sure.  But I'm envious, and jealous.  Shannon has never acted, around me, the way she acts around you.  And that's what hurts.  I never realize how bad it is until she's around someone else.  And at that point I realize, "Gosh, have I ever been dragging her down."  Anyway, I've said it before, and I DO mean when I say that you're a pretty cool guy.  I could hang out with you all the time and never get bored.  But right now, it's just kinda weird.  Hopefully though, when this is all said and done, we'll still come out friends in the end?  I'm shooting for that.  Gotta run.  Paul Yevcak  P.S.  I got that Blackdog fuel rail installed.  And I did it right!!  No leaks at all!!
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   It's early :) Date:   Wed 07/10/02 07:24 AM      I know I just sent you an email, I can't remember for the life of me if I said this or not - if I hadn't sent it, I'd edit it, but too late :)   Let me know what I need to do - to do this the right way - a way that we're all comfortabe with.  That's what I want.  Ok?  You say things to me that indicate that you're ready, then you back off.  I'm doing the same thing, I suppose.  I'm ready now, not going to recant that.  You can only dance so long before your legs get tired :)   Dang, hehe, I wish I was even close to being awake :)  I'd be more understandable that way.   Sorry if I'm not being CLEAR.  I feel clear, but damn words...  You know.   Hehe, I'm laughing at myself, I'm a dork, a silly tired in love dork.  :-D   I can back off - give you time?  Is that what you want?  Or do you want me to work on convincing you?  I'm not sure how I'm supposed to be  - the only thing I'm going on here is feeling.  My brain is getting fried, now that I know what I want, I can't really fight anymore to try to get myself talked out of it.   I still want to do things RIGHT, Dennis, I never said I was willing to fuck it all up.  Ok?   I just feel very strongly that right may not mean waiting for ever?  It's also not pressuring you.  YOU need to tell me what YOU need - whatever you say is what I'll do.  I want you to be as comfortable as I am, to not be scared anymore.  I'll still wait, don't ever take it to mean that I won't.   Hehe, talk to me after I've slept for a few hours ;)   Ugh, maybe between these last two emails I've managed to make a lick of sense?  I hope so - I know what I mean anyway :)   STILL in love with you :)   Shannon   BTW - call me if you want to talk today - or don't if you want time to think about stuff... whatever, I'm easy :)  And don't feel like you have to stay up all night chatting with me - I can't help but feel like a loser with a shitty job sometimes.  (Uh, cause I have a shitty job???)  Let me know if you still want to hang out Saturday - I'm thinking I'd love to catch a movie with you... 
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   What you need? Date:   Wed 07/10/02 06:43 AM      Let me know what you need, ok?   I still mean it, I'm still in 100% - come what may, when it may, as it wishes - whatever.   I don't know what to say to you - so much of me wants to convince you, but that's wrong.  So I'm a little stuck...  I don't want to back down either, I won't change my mind about you.     I'm just done being scared.   I feel like I faught the good fight, did everything I could and I *still* love you more than I've ever loved anyone, anything ever.  And I know you love me too.   I wish I could give you my not-scared brain for a day :)   When you're ready, let me know...  I'm waiting, I'll wait as long as you need me too, until you're ok with everything.  I'd never, ever, ever want to force anything on you.  I don't mean I'm ready to do anything wrong.  I'm just ready to be yours.   I'm IN, Dennis, as of this moment, for good.  You've got me.   Call me, IM me, email me, whatever - when you're ready - before you're ready - as soon as possible - whatever.  :)  I'm yours.  I love you. 
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      This is a chunk of IM between our mutual friend Jeff and I.  Jeff saved it and sent it to Dennis.  Dennis forwarded it to me.   From:   WhiteHonkey66@aol.com To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   stuff Date:   Wed 07/10/02 12:28 AM     WhiteHonkey66:  so what do you guys talk about  akatornado6:  Everything.  akatornado6:  He's really smart :)  WhiteHonkey66:  i know  akatornado6:  And cool, and nice and just a good person.  akatornado6:  I need a good person right now.  WhiteHonkey66:  i know what you mean..... theres times when you just need the right kind of person or thing to help deal with others  akatornado6:  Yeah.    
      


10,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   "Shannon Yevcak"   Subject:   Re: Whaaaaa! Date:   Wed 07/10/02 12:22 AM     I'm glad Blaise is good for something ;-) Have you mentioned me to him? Just wondering....  I had to stay late at work, so I didn't get to leave until 11:45, then I had to stop for gas, and well, here I am :-)  Dennis
      


11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   I forget who this is now! Date:   Thu 07/11/02 03:28 PM      Thanks for sending that to Paul.   I forget that he doesn't ge my jokes, so I asked him, "Did Dennis reply to your email yet?"  "Yeah, just a little bit ago."  "Well, can I go see him or what???"  I was just being a smartass - forgot myself for a minute, oops :o  He didn't like that too much.  I'll fix it - laugh it off, no worries :-D   Hehe, well, as you can see, here I am *again* checking my email at odd times of the day...   Thought it'd be a great time to sneak in a few *kisses* and a great big *HUG*   TTFN, will find out about the movies Saturday @ some point - ok?  It is still a "maybe / maybe not."  Whatever, I'm easy :)  
      


11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   Paul Yevcak   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   RE: This is Dennis Date:   Thu 07/11/02 01:50 PM     -----Original Message----- From: dennis [spoolboy@autospeed.com] Sent: Thursday, July 11, 2002 1:27 PM To: Paul Yevcak Subject: This is Dennis   **I was at home when I got this this morning, but didn't have time to start on a quality reply until tonight at work. It has been a slow night tonight ;-) I work from 3-11:30.   **I'm adding this paragraph last before I send this. I was really  reluctant to send this. I'm opening up my armor to you big time here. A part of me was concerned that this email would get kept, dwelled on, and possibly used against me or Shannon. Please respect what I've done here and don't do that. It will not be for the good of anyone involved if you do that.  @@I fully realize that.  And I give you my word, no bull-shitting that I will NOT be printing these, saving these, or dwelling on these e-mails.  I am also opening up, and discussing things with you that would cut me to the bone.  I know that you won't use any of this against me, and rest assured that I have ABSOLUTELY NO intentions of doing that to you, either.  **Yeah, I like hanging with you too Paul :-) This *IS* very weird, especially since the 4th of July.... I felt very bad for you that night. I have tried very hard to think of you, to put myself in your shoes, and treat you how I'd want to be treated if I was in your place. It is very hard as it is. I don't want to make this any harder than it has to be for anyone. I WILL NOT disrespect you or your marriage by doing things with your wife that I shouldn't do.  @@I've known for some time know that you never actually WOULD do  anything that you shouldn't do; but I will admit, there are many times that I have to remind myself of that.  I'm still working through all of my feelings about all of this, and there is SO much going through my head that sometimes I just can't keep it all straight.  I REALLY hit rock bottom Sunday night; and Monday morning I took it upon myself to contact my friend Cindy.  She  used to work here at SSI, and Shannon may have mentioned her already.  This past Saturday and Sunday, I didn't eat much.  I had a bowl of oatmeal on Sunday, and that was it if I recall.  Still, I wasn't eating, I literally got sick twice Sunday night, and spent at least 45 minutes literally crying my eyes out.  I knew then and there, that I would NOT make it through this without having at least one person to talk to.  Cindy was the only one.  During her time here at SSI, I helped her through some incredibly traumatic things in her life.  Sometimes I was an open ear; sometimes I was a "shoulder to cry on"; and yet other times, I was just a wall for her to bounce ideas off of, for the sole purpose of letting her maintain her sanity, and reassuring her that she WAS NOT crazy for thinking the things she was thinking.  And I can tell you right now that it feels so very good to have someone to talk to.  My apetite has come back, my stomach aches are gone, and so are my headaches. So now Cindy and I have switched places.  I'm the one in dire need of help, and she's taken the role I once had. And I know that you didn't come in and steal anything from me.  I've been pushing Shannon away for so long...again, I DO NOT BLAME you.  And I mean that.  **I know. And I have tried to avoid putting you in that situation. I hope you can see that I have. Sometimes though, it just seems like I'm trying to stop a train by holding it with my bare hands. If there is anything I can do to minimize your pain, I will do my best to do it. If you don't want me to be with Shannon until the divorce is final, I will do it at your request, out of respect for you. But it won't be without dificulty. She and I have become very close friends and I want to be there for her to talk to and be there to support her through this rough time. And I also want to be with her because I genuinely enjoy her company very much.  @@I competely understand what you're saying.  And yes, I HAVE noticed you trying to stop the train.  Or at least get it to slow down some.  But as it is in real life, it's DAMN hard to stop a train.  I'm still not 100% sure about how I feel about you guys going out to eat, and to a movie and such.  I honestly don't know about that.  I guess it wouldn't be so hard if it wasn't every weekend and such??  I need help getting the house ready to sell.  I MUST have help with all of that.    **As I've said elsewhere in this email, I respect you and your marriage and will not do anything with Shannon that I shouldn't do with a friend's wife. I hope you can see that from the times you've been around.  @@Yes, I understand.  And honestly, I DO believe you.  BUT it's taking a long time for me to get used to that.  Deep down I know that you mean it; but for some reason, it's just not soaking in as fast as other things do. My apologies.  **I don't want you to be hurt Paul. I don't want to hurt you.  @@And likewise.  I know that I've said things to Shannon that I don't mean, or that I wish I could retract.  Again, there are so many thoughts running through my head that occasionally I have mental traffic jam, and end up saying things I don't mean.  **I do know where you're coming from, if not exactly. I spent 4 years loving a woman that, although she loved me back, did not love me as much or in the same way as I loved her. I wanted to be with her very badly, but no matter what I wanted, no matter how hard I tried, I just couldn't make it work. It felt so right to me for so long.... but it just never was. I am still friends with her. I have had the experience of seeing her with several men since I've known her. Even had to endure her confessions and stories of her love and sex life. Talk about pain! I've been over her for about 3-4 years, but it still hurts to hear her talk about being with someone else.   @@EXACTLY!!!!!  That's EXACTLY what I'm feeling!!  And don't ask me how to explain that!  ;)  **I don't think you ever truly stop loving someone once you start, you only learn how to deal with it and understand that concentrating on the pain only makes it worse.   @@And unfortunately, I'm not dealing with it too well yet, am I??  Takes time I guess....  

11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis    To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   This is Dennis Date:   Thu 07/11/02 12:36 PM     Shannon, I tweaked this a tiny bit again. I didn't BCC because I figured sep emails were safer. There, the armor's off now. Lets see if he puts his sword down.  Dennis  --- Paul Yevcak   wrote: 

11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   Paul Yevcak   Subject:   Re: Haven't heard from you. Date:   Thu 07/11/02 12:12 PM    I understand. I worked on your reply a lot yesterday. I'll send it next.   Thank you for contacting me.  Dennis  --- Paul Yevcak   wrote: 

11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   It's going to be ok Date:   Thu 07/11/02 06:53 AM      I've got to remember to leave these emails open for a little while longer, I always think of something to add to the end.  Silly me :)  It's going to be OK.  All of it.  This calm is not leaving me!  I read the email from Paul to you back to Paul again - thank you - gee, it sounds like you guys are about ready to smooch    I get pictures :-D  What you wrote back will help me out a lot.  You're outside, you're very intelligent, you're level-headed about all of this.  I know Paul needs someone to talk to.  I need someone to talk to too.  You're really helping out with everything.  I didn't plan on putting you in that situation.  You've got some kind of grace.  And I mean definitions #2 and #3:  2.  politeness:  dignified, polite, and decent behavior  She fended off queries with her usual grace.   3.  generosity of spirit:  a capacity to tolerate, accommodate, or forgive people  You've got it in great quantities.  I'm learning!  Will you teach me that?  Among the million other things I want to learn from you, can you slip that in somewhere along the line?  Please?  You never cease to amaze me!  I think I'm unserstanding something new!  "Growing old with someone" is about GROWING, not getting wrinkles...
      


11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   I totally nailed 'em! Date:   Thu 07/11/02 06:19 AM      I just knocked out the 10 best radios of my life!  I totally rocked - I mean they were perfect!  Damn, and I didn't even think about saving the tapes...  Tapes?  Hehe, they're digital now anyway...  I though for sure that you'd have me all screwed up and my voice would waver / crack.  But no, not in the least!  I'm so fucking happy that it just shines through in my voice - the whole world is hearing me smiling :-D  You did this to me :-D  I thought they would suck big time this morning because I did them about 30 minutes after you went *poof*  I wasn't sure how I was feeling after that - I sorta 1/2 way freaked myself out for a little bit - about 10 minutes?  Sent you a little email right then, and yeah, I tried to call you :)  Hehe so sue me :p  But then this lovely calm feeling came over me - the same feeling I have when I'm in your arms.  I know you're coming back, I'm not scared anymore.  (Hehe, watch my karma - now that I'm sure you're coming back, I've scared you off for good!!!  :-D  )  You finally got through my thick head the last little bit.  I guess I let go of whatever I had keeping you out?  I don't know - I haven't cried for joy in a good long while, thanks for that!  Thank you a million times - I mean it from the bottom of my heart, the deepest part of my soul - just thank you!  Ok, so on to replying!  

11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Uh? Date:   Thu 07/11/02 03:11 AM       Uh, was it something I said?   Come back, please?!?!?   *heart attack*
      


11,July,2004


    
       
      This is Dennis's reply to Paul's email from the day before:  From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   This is Dennis Date:   Thu 07/11/02 02:24 AM       

11,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   Today, Paul, etc. Date:   Thu 07/11/02 12:48 AM      Awww, man, no email from Dennis :(   Waaaait, yes there is!   And it's about trench mouth!     Great!   :)  **LOL! You would have had that last email already, but it got lost on the first attempt! DOH! The trenchmouth thing was a copy/paste of a fwd that I got from someone. I thought it was kind of interesting.    I feel bad right now.   Really really bad.   Dang it, I'm sorry 1000 times over.  **If you say you're sorry again I'm going to tickly you with a feather until you scream!!! :-D Especially if it's about something that you didn't cause!!!  **Now, if you had a PLAN for us to get caught.... that's a different story....   I suppose Paul had to come home, had to force the issue, don't think he knew at the time, but someone (something) sent him, I'm sure of it.  **Yes, I knew it was only a matter of time before we got "caught". I felt very strongly that today was the day, and that's why I didn't want to come out. But I figured that if we got caught, oh well, WTF... once I was there, my "fuck-it" attitude quickly retreated. I realized that Paul is a human being too. And how much it would hurt him to see us together. I'm just glad that he showed up right when I did, not after I'd been there a while. I know we'd have been together on the couch in one  way or another... and that would have been VERY BAD for him to find us there. Even if all we were doing was laying there spooning....yeah, right....that's all we'd have been doing....:-/   Now I'm feeling all wonkey.  **What does wonkey feel like? :-)   I don't ever want to put you into uncomfortable positions (unless we're naked, or course...)     **:-D I understand. Beleive me, I wanted to be there. I will not go somewhere that I know I don't want to go.   **And what kind of uncomfortable position would you like to put me into naked? Remember that us fat guys don't look so hot all contorted up like those skinny fuckers do! ;-) And we're not as limber either!! But we snuggle and hug MUCH better!! And you can always use a fat guy to stop a car with if you're downtown together ;-)   I am really really trying to find the brakes that worked so well about 10 days ago.  They're not working so much for me anymore, DAMMIT!  I see what I want, I can touch it, taste it, smell it, hold it in my hands.  So fucking close!!!    **I am trying to find a reason why I should use the brakes.... I know the thing you said about Chris is a good reason.... but Paul already thinks we're fucking.... and it's so easy to "give them something to talk about".  And I'm finding that this "girly" part of me you bring out (you know, being physically naked in front of you is not an issue, because I feel naked around you anyway!) is not such a strong person.  This girly part of me is even more impulsive than what I'm used to!  You don't know how long I've waited, how many nights I've dreamed --- yes, yes you do know -- you've been there too.  When I close my eyes, it's to fight off the girly needy part - the part that just can't wait.  To force myself to take it for what it is, to take what I'm getting and be damn grateful  for it.  (It's not bad - I'm not complaining!!!)  **Well, if being physically naked in front of me is not an issue....;-)  **And I find it very entertaining that I bring out your "girly" side, lol. I figured all of the talk about cars and stuff like that would stimulate your "male" side, lol! But I guess we do talk more about sex and romantic things than cars anymore... and I think I like your girly side :-) But I like the other side of you too! Hmm... don't think to hard about that.... there's a dirty joke there somewhere! ;-)   *sigh*   I told you once you said YES you were saying YES, didn't I?  I tried like hell to convince you otherwise.  **YES. I still say YES. Yeah, you SO tried to convince me otherwise, but all you really convinced me of was that you cared about me enough to discourage me, which made me want you even more. Plus there's my "prove you wrong" and "argue" side that you stimulated by telling me that I didn't want to say yes...   I guess this feeling is what I was worried about - now that I'm standing here all alone...  I feel super exposed - and I'm terrified that I'm going to lose you!  **You're not going to loose me. I'm here. Not going anywhere. What do I need to do to prove it? I would like to see you being independent a bit, but only just as badly as I want to be with you.   Damn, I want to rush things.   I have to work.  This is some of the hardest work I've ever had to do.  **I'll help you. I will keep us going slow. I know I can, at least until I feel that it's right to speed up.   The consequences scare me --- and the scariest ones all have to do with YOU!  You leaving, you getting hurt, you not being satisfied - GAH!  It's girl stuff!  **Damn girly side! ;-) I'm not going to leave. I won't let you hurt me, I can only hurt myself. And I can't imagine anyone that I would be more satisfied with than you...unless maybe I met a woman with multiple vaginas?   God, are you still sure?    **YES!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  I want to know, I know I'm a loser for asking!    **You're not a loser. This is still so new and I worry about losing you too. I know you're real tho. I have accepted it. I guess it's easier for me because I was the pursuer, not the one being pursued from the begining.  Of course I know, but I've got such a track record of scaring people away...  Hence the lyrics to "Hurt" - everyone I know goes away in the end - I can't shake that last bit of insecurity.  Maybe that is a good thing, it's keeping me in line?  I'm not sure, maybe that insecurity is hiting me in the ass - that's what is causing me to want to rush rush rush - like I want to somehow find a way to pin you down or something???  No, not pin you down.  I just want some type of security blanket, I guess.  Some type of concrete evidence that you're not going to run away? And yet, if I look, it's all around me.  You've done everything but  hit me over the head to let me know how you feel.  And damn it all if there isn't a part of me that probably wouldn't get the message if you did hit me over the head.  I'm stubborn, did I bother to mention that?  :)  **  There, you happy now?! lol! :-D If you'd just look into my damn eyes you'll see your security blanket! I'm goofy, silly, stupid in love with you. How could I not be and be acting like this? I've never felt like this before. You make me deleriously happy just by being in the same area as me!!! What do you need??? I'd do anything for you, except hurt you, lie to you, or something that would jeopardize our future together.   I'm blabbing, I hope you see that I'm working things out in my head as I sit here and type - so if something sounds shocking at first, just hang on, I'm trying to get back to a comfortable place.  **Yes, I understand. NP! :-)    I was not ready to tell Paul everything yet.  But I guess I had to.    **Yes, I knew you weren't. Thank you so much for telling him. He knew it already and lying to him would only make things worse. How long could we keep up the lie anyway?  I wasn't going to do it - until I saw you, and pratically threw myself at you damn the consequences... Yes, I do like you that much!  How the hell did this happen again???    **I don't fucking know!! I ask myself that all the time. What makes Shannon love me so much? What makes me love her so much? I have no answer really, other than "I just do". There are a thousand good reasons why I love you, like the fact that you're loving, kind, smart, caring, sexy, beautiful, and about 10000x more stuff that my fingers are saving themselves from typing.  I saw that there was no way to hide it anymore, really no reason to do it anyway.  I've been honest with Paul all through this, when I told him that I loved you like a Kit (best friend love) I meant it, because that is where we were at that moment in time.  He thinks I'm changing my story - but I'm not - I have been honest with him.  I've basically told him everything now (excluding the cyber sex - hey, when are we doing that again???  I'm getting horny here!!!) and he's dealing.  I used one of your lines (thanks, check is in the mail) about feelings - you can't  control how you feel, only how you react to it.  **Thank you for being honest with him. It's really hard to use something against someone when you throw it in their face and they just say "Yeah, I know, I'm the one that told YOU."   He is mad - but I think he sees the way out...  I told him if I was that focused on Dennis, why didn't I run off with Dennis, sign all of my shit over and get it done with?  (Neglected to mention just how close to doing exactly that we came...)  I just told him that I am really intent on doing the right thing - which means I have to put my obligations to both he and Chris first.  (Get this!!!  He said, "Well, how do I know that you won't run off and fuck him?  You've lied about other stuff!"  So I had to say, "I could stand naked in front of Dennis and work it for all I was worth and he'd still tell me no!"  Uh, so if he asks, no  matter what might actually happen, you'd say no, ok???)  Haha, I had to tell him (was NOT ready for this!!!) that you are worth waiting for!  OMG - that was hard to say - the look in his eyes - gawd.  But I did it :-D  I can do anything as long as I know you're there for me.  Thank you thank you thank you!  **:-) I'm glad that you two are talking and dealing with this, not fighting. I'm very proud of you. And thank you so much for the flattery! I'm glad that I make you strong :-)    I won't ever change my mind, Dennis.  You are worth it.  All of it.  In the grand scheme of things, when I weigh what I have to look forward to with what I have to do to get there - it seems way too easy, belive it or not.  As hard as each step seems, I know that it's bringing me one step closer...  DAMN!  (shut up, silly impatient girly parts!!)  **:-) I know you feel that way. Thank you for saying it! You are worth all of this too.   Dennis, I love you.  I hope and pray that everything is as right as it all seems - I have nothing but good feelings about this - this being US.  I guess the hardest part was taking the first step.  (and still, there is nagging, I didn't know I was this needy - please just put up with the neediness - I've been waiting so long, and you are so incredibly perfect - I still have trouble believing you're real - except when you're holding me in your arms, then I know)  I'm so afraid of messing up!  I am afraid that telling you this is going to scare you away - let you see just how insecure and needy I am, and turn you off?  Geez, I'm a wreck!  Meh, it's only been about 90 minutes since I told my husband I'm in love with another man, I guess I deserve a little bit of this, don't I?  **I'm glad that you shared your feelings with me. Yes, I have been completely honest with you, and always will be. Everything is exactly as it seems, as long as you are reading the same emails I am, lol. Your girly side is being kind of troublesome! She has been kept in the closet for so long that she is running around screaming at the top of her lungs now that she's free! I understand and can deal with that, just please do your best to not let your neediness lead us down the wrong road.  **I do sometimes have a hard time believing you are real too. Today I was feeling that hard-core while I did my "serious thinking".  Yeah, I'm getting better at thinking while I type.  I won't be able to think without a keyboard if this keeps up!  **LOL! You are funny!   So, I really want to know some kind of a plan?  I don't mean we have to nail everything down exactly - it's just so damn hard to be "open ended" totally.  I'm going to move to Litchfield for at least a while.  Get the house ready to sell - there are a few things to fix up, a few things to clean, etc.  Get stuff sold / moved / divided / given away whatever.  I don't know how damn long it will take to sell the house - the market is supposed to be good right now...  Sometimes that shit drags on forever.  Get back to school - I start August 26th.  I guess I'll commute from Litchfield - yipee, what fun!  (I'll have timing belt mileage on the car in no time that way, Dennis :p )  I'm going to have to work sometime - which won't leave me a whole hell of a lot of time to study - damn this is going to be like work!  But Paul will have Chris, so I'll have to send him some money every month.    **A plan eh? Well, I've told you what I thought a good plan would be, but you really don't seem to want to hear it right now, lol :-) I move out and get an apartment. You visit me and stay with me progressively more, as much as I can stand, but you DO NOT move in with me, at least until you are out of school. That way I can have a chance to adjust from nothing to everything...know what I'm saying? After that, when you are making better money, we can move up in the world from an $11/hr standard of living.  I'll have a better explaination of my reasons for going slow in the next email. I'm trying to be breif so I can get through all  of these ;-) Plus I'm still grinding on Paul's reply... don't want to make a stupid mistake with him and create a chink in our armor.   I want to see you - be with you, catch a movie or whatever whenever we have the time together.  Just cuddle and tell you about the mundane aspects of my life, ya know.  Just listen to your voice - I love your voice :-D  Hopefully sometime during all of that, the paperwork will get finished?  I've not gotten a good answer yet for how long it takes.  :x  Stupid details!    **I want to be with you, very badly. Cuddling with you and talking sounds absolutely great right now! I don't know how long the paperwork will take for your divorce, but until then it looks like we will not be seeing each other in person :-( I can do it. I will not gamble with Chris. We've done pretty well on just AIM and emails so far, and only recently have we been able to BE together in real life. I think we can make it :-) We have to! :-)   **You should tell Paul "thank you" for making us take some time apart in real life right now. Tell him that you are glad and that you beleive it will increase the odds of you and I being together. If anything will make him not care if you are with me, that will do it. Gotta love reverse psychology! lol  Then what?  Dang it, I just want to know everything right now :)  Hehe, I'm a silly one, aren't I?  What are you thinking?  Where do you see us?  What's going to happen?  I know what I'd like, but I don't know where your head is on it.  I feel like we're already kinda dating, ya know?  **When I asked you these same questions only days ago, you had no  answers for me other than "I can't see the future". What makes you think I can now? I really don't know. I want to be with you. I want to make this work with you in the best way I know how, but you have to understand my lack of experience and how much I'm growing right now to even meet you here. I do respect how far you've come for me!!! And I will go as far as you want me to(because I want to!), but I have to do it slowly. I've never even dated someone, let alone tried to live with them, or give all of myself to them.  **Yes, dating. I want to do a whole lot of that! Do you realize that if I'm dating you, you are the first person I've ever really dated? I mean I go and do stuff with Karla, be she and I have never "dated". We never referred to each other as boyfriend or girlfriend. And I went on 1 date with a crazy truck-driving chick, who was in love with me by the end of the date, despite me not really being so nice to her or even showing her any affection. I had to stop talking to her after that date! SHE WAS  CRAZY!!!  **Last night I stopped for coffee at the gas station on my way home. The guy at the register asked me what I was doing drinking coffee this time of night, was I going on a road trip, etc. I replied that my girlfriend was at work tonight and I wanted to stay up so I could talk to her, so I needed some caffeine. You know what? That is the first time I've ever been able to refer to someone as my girlfriend. Do you understand what I'm saying here? Do you get any idea of why I have to take this slow yet? I've never had anyone before that I could call mine. Never. I don't know how to do this. I'm doing good so far, but I need to learn 1 thing at a time.   I'm really really getting frustrated with not being able to "be yours."  There is so much restraint - such a big part of me that you just can't have yet.  I want to share, I trust you like I've never trusted another human being in my life, respect you, love you.  God's honest truth, I've never felt like this before either.  I never really believed that it was like they say in the movies :)  I've had glimpses - I do know that I have been in love.  But the trust, the respect, the urge to give myself over to you and let you take me where you will?  The equally strong  urge to show you everything I know, to teach you, find things out  together - it's all new.  **Reading that makes me feel SO happy and loved! Thank you so much for writing it! I know you are frustrated. You are much more experienced at dealing with having a person in your life that you care about than I am. Please just go slow with me. I KNOW I can't go fast now. I understand that you do want someone to be with, and that you are used to having someone in your life. I am not used to it, although I want you in my life very badly! In the past I have filled my life with so many hobbies to fill the time most people spend with their b/f or g/f or even the time spent with their friends. And now, I've grown used to these hobbies, and giving them up is hard to do. I realize that I will simply not have enough money to play like I do if I move out of my parent's house. I will do these things to be with you. I care about you that much. These things are fairly minor by themselves, but they all add up. I'm spoiled, please try to understand me.  **Back around my birthday Karla, Koby and I were talking and discussing old times. We realized that right now is the happiest we've ever been. None of us has ever been very happy before in our lives. Never felt free or comfortable with ourselves until just recently. I am so free and can do whatever I want, whenever I want. That is very hard to loose, but you are worth it! Just understand that I need to leave my freedom slowly, not overnight. Simply moving out will be a VERY big step for me that I've been putting off for so many years because I'm spoiled.      **I'm trying, but you aren't making it easy lately ;-) Your girly side is surprising me with her neediness too. I've been thinking hard all day today. I've been in a rather "outside of the situation" state of mind. Kind of sad. Sad because when I look at it that way, I can really see all of the ways that things could go bad. I can always see them, but when I can get up the nerve to step outside, I can REALLY SEE THEM. I'm picking the road for us that I see the least obstacles on. Please go down it with me.  Eventhough it's longer than the dangerous road, it is MUCH safer for both of us in the long run. 1 wreck on the short dangerous road will take us out of the race for MUCH longer(if not completely) than if we just keep a steady pace on this long safe road.   Well, dang, and I'm going to have you late at night too!   I'm one lucky woman :-D   You're amazing!   Love ya :)   **Yes, and I'm lucky too to have found you!! I love you!   Dennis
      


12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   Getting to 100% Date:   Fri 07/12/02 04:21 PM     **Don't worry that you're dragging me into pain by confiding in me during your divorce Shannon. I'm here to support you. I understand what I got myself into. I've known all along. And being with you, even just on the phone, makes it all worth it.  Let me know what you need, ok?  **Trust me, I will and so far I think I have :-)   I still mean it, I'm still in 100% - come what may, when it may, as it wishes - whatever.  **I know. It means so much to me that you say that. Thank you for  telling and showing me that :-)   I don't know what to say to you - so much of me wants to convince you, but that's wrong. So I'm a little stuck... I don't want to back down either, I won't change my mind about you. I'm just done being scared. I feel like I faught the good fight, did everything I could and I *still* love you more than I've ever loved anyone, anything ever. And I know you love me too.  **I appreciate you sharing that with me and I smile every time I read that :-) I do love you too! What is there to convince me of? I love you. I want to be with you. I'm not going to be 100% until we CAN be 100%. There are outisde circumstances that keep us where we're at. But I am 99.999% right now and giving you all I have to give of myself. I just need to hold that one little tiny piece back, because I've never done this before, we can't REALLY be together just yet because of your current situation. Eventhough I want to give that last little .0001%, I can't do it honestly, not right now. I know you can understand and be satisfied with that :-)   I wish I could give you my not-scared brain for a day :) When you're ready, let me know... I'm waiting, I'll wait as long as you need me too, until you're ok with everything. I'd never, ever, ever want to force anything on you. I don't mean I'm ready to do anything wrong. I'm just ready to be yours. I'm IN, Dennis, as of this moment, for good. You've got me. Call me, IM me, email me, whatever - when you're ready - before you're ready - as soon as possible - whatever. :) I'm yours. I love you.  **I don't know what to say to that really. I'm not scared, never really have been "scared" so much as cautious about going to a new place.   **Since you wrote this I HAVE called you, IMed you, emailed you, and even "whatevered" you ;-) I did it when I was ready and as soon and as often as possible. You know I'm yours, but I'll tell you I'm yours anyway. I love you! :-) :-D   Let me know what I need to do - to do this the right way - a way that we're all comfortabe with. That's what I want. Ok? You say things to me that indicate that you're ready, then you back off. I'm doing the same thing, I suppose. I'm ready now, not going to recant that. You can only dance so long before your legs get tired :)  **I know what you're saying. I'm VERY ready to be with you, to spend endless hours with you, and to love you. I am already doing these things. I just need some adjustment time as we take each step. I've grown a lot in just the last day, I'm sure you can see it :-)  **I'm not going backwards from here, only forwards. You know my plan, my road, my path. I won't go any slower unless I have to for both of our sake. I'm not dancing. I want to be with you.    Dang, hehe, I wish I was even close to being awake :) I'd be more  understandable that way. Sorry if I'm not being CLEAR. I feel clear, but damn words... You know. Hehe, I'm laughing at myself, I'm a dork, a silly tired in love dork. :-D  **I think you were pretty clear. If my replies make it seem like I didn't "get it", then type to me again. :-)   I can back off - give you time? Is that what you want? Or do you want me to work on convincing you? I'm not sure how I'm supposed to be - the only thing I'm going on here is feeling.   **Just do what we've been doing. Walk down this path with me, don't run. Be like we have been. And take the time to make sure that you're doing what you need to do for YOU right now during your divorce. I don't need convincing, I'm already convinced :-)  My brain is getting fried, now that I know what I want, I can't really fight anymore to try to get myself talked out of it.  **Don't fight yourself. Don't try to talk yourself out of this. I want to be with you, but I don't want to marry you overnight, that's all I'm saying :-)   I still want to do things RIGHT, Dennis, I never said I was willing to fuck it all up. Ok?  **I know.   I just feel very strongly that right may not mean waiting for ever?  **I'm pretty sure we're already past this issue, but if not, you know what to do :-) We're moving forward, as much as we can considering the circumstances, each day. Each time we talk. I just want to take small steps. I still want to get to the same destination :-)  It's also not pressuring you. YOU need to tell me what YOU need -  whatever you say is what I'll do. I want you to be as comfortable as I am, to not be scared anymore. I'll still wait, don't ever take it to mean that I won't. Hehe, talk to me after I've slept for a few hours ;)  **We did talk and I beleive we've resolved this:-)   Ugh, maybe between these last two emails I've managed to make a lick of sense? I hope so - I know what I mean anyway :)  **Yes. You made sense :-)   STILL in love with you :)   **I never doubt it for a second! And I'm in love with you too! :-D  BTW - call me if you want to talk today - or don't if you want time to think about stuff... whatever, I'm easy :) And don't feel like you have to stay up all night chatting with me - I can't help but feel like a loser with a shitty job sometimes. (Uh, cause I have a shitty job???)  **:-D There you go apologizing again! Remember that feather??? You're gonna get it!  Let me know if you still want to hang out Saturday - I'm thinking I'd love to catch a movie with you...  **Of course! We just gotta decide what movie to see and when. I'm  thinking something around 6ish so we can eek out a little "extra" time together ;-) Don't know what's playing right now, we'll just have to see. I'll have you home by 9, so don't worry :-) If that's too long or Paul doesn't go for it, I can do whatever we need to do. And let me know what's up with the Blaise PCM deal....  I just knocked out the 10 best radios of my life!  I totally rocked - I mean they were perfect!  Damn, and I didn't even think about saving the tapes...  Tapes?  Hehe, they're digital now anyway...  I though for sure that you'd have me all screwed up and my voice would waver / crack.  But no, not in the least!  I'm so fucking happy that it just shines through in my voice - the whole world is hearing me smiling :-D  You did this to me :-D  **Thank you! I love you! You do the same thing to me! I wonder if the people listening to your radios will know you're in love?  I thought they would suck big time this morning because I did them about 30 minutes after you went *poof*  I wasn't sure how I was feeling after that - I sorta 1/2 way freaked myself out for a little bit - about 10 minutes?  Sent you a little email right then, and yeah, I tried to call you :)  Hehe so sue me :p  **It's ok. I understand. It sucks getting cut off like that in the middle of a good conversation. It made me happy to know that you trusted me and knew I was coming back. You are finally starting to trust our love and it's very nice :-)  But then this lovely calm feeling came over me - the same feeling I have when I'm in your arms.  I know you're coming back, I'm not scared anymore.  (Hehe, watch my karma - now that I'm sure you're coming back, I've scared you off for good!!!  :-D  )  You finally got through my thick head the last little bit.  I guess I let go of whatever I had keeping you out?  I don't know - I haven't cried for joy in a good long while, thanks for that!  **Thank you for sharing that with me. You make me feel so good inside!!! I don't know what to do with myself sometimes! :-D:-D:-D:-D :-) :-) :-)!!!!!!!!!!  Thank you a million times - I mean it from the bottom of my heart, the deepest part of my soul - just thank you!  **You're welcome :-) I'm so glad I can make you feel like that. Just little old me.... :-)  

12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   Cancel on me :-P Date:   Fri 07/12/02 04:02 PM     

12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Re: Fwd: RE: Hey Dennis!! Date:   Fri 07/12/02 12:51 PM      

12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   Paul Yevcak   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   RE: Hey Dennis!! Date:   Fri 07/12/02 11:43 AM     --- Paul Yevcak   wrote:  **Thank you Paul. It means a lot that we can talk like this without fear of these delicate issues being used in anger.  **Like I said on the phone, you have my permission to use anything I've written for good, but not for a bad purpose. If it helps you to keep these emails, you can keep them or do whatever you want with them. My only concern is that they are used in a positive way only.  @@I hear ya man.  Only good.  I'm not out to burn anyone.  I'm going to do this whole process the proper way.  And even if that wasn't my intention, I recognize when someone's laid "their heart on the line"....and trust me, I'm not out for blood.  **I feel a lot better too now that we've talked. If you ever need to discuss something with me, feel free to email or call. It's much easier to deal with problems when they're small and new, rather than to wait until they've grown into something much larger and harder to deal with.  @@Glad to know that your door is open, so to speak.  And hell yes, I agree 100% with you about addressing problems while they're small.  It's easier to walk over a hill than it is to climb a mountain.  **Thank you for realizing that, and thank you for letting me be her friend right now while she needs support the most.    @@Like I said, I'm GOING to do the right thing here.  Throughout all of this.  And I KNOW that Shannon needs you to talk to right now, and to be there.  I'm NOT going to deny her that.  Not now..that's just not right, and would be completely inconsiderate of me.  Thanks again, Dennis!!  Paul
      


12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   Paul Yevcak   Subject:   Re: Hey Dennis!! Date:   Fri 07/12/02 10:43 AM    --- Paul Yevcak   wrote:  **Thank you Paul. It means a lot that we can talk like this without fear of these delicate issues being used in anger.  **Like I said on the phone, you have my permission to use anything I've written for good, but not for a bad purpose. If it helps you to keep these emails, you can keep them or do whatever you want with them. My only concern is that they are used in a positive way only.   

12,July,2004


    
       
      From:   Paul Yevcak   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Hey Dennis!! Date:   Fri 07/12/02 07:08 AM      Hey man,  I just wanted to thank you for taking the time to e-mail me yesterday.  I know that it was extremely difficult for you to do so; not knowing me so well and such.  But I want to reassure you that I have NO ill intentions WHATSOEVER with respect to your message, and your feelings.  I have NO plans of doing anything sneaky, anything nasty with what you sent me.  I printed that e-mail out yesterday, and let Shannon read it.  Immediately after she read it,  I tore it into a hundred or so pieces.  Shannon can vouch for that.  I also wanted to say that speaking with you, and hearing what you had to say was a GOOD thing.  I feel better now that I've heard from you. And finally, I can confidently say that I feel nothing is going to happen between you two that should not happen until this divorce is final.  That's about it.  Thanks again,  Paul
      


13,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Date:   Sat 07/13/02 11:02 AM        

14,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Your number! Date:   Sun 07/14/02 01:53 PM     First off, I have to tell you **again** that I had a TON of fun with you yesterday!  I love spending time with you - it's even better than getting an email from ya, if that's possible!  LOL, and I was bored at work, so I read horoscopes online - LOL - just to test the theory that you see whatever you project on to them...  I think that's true!  Um, except for the part that said, "July 10th will see a New Moon in Cancer signaling a time for new beginnings -- or, in your case, a higher level of emotional commitment to romance and love."  Whoa!  Yeah, I'm projecting, but uh, I worked midnights on the 10th :-D   *hmmmmm!*  And I was bored again, so I called you and left a message on your machine :-D  Why is your number so easy?  LOL - I *treid* not to memorize it!  Cause I knew I'd call all the time if I did...  But it's toooooo easy!  You need more numbers - too many 5's or something...  Hahaha, and if I could think of *any* reason whatsoever, I'd call you again RIGHT NOW.  The only thing I can think of is that I just want to hear your voice - meh, but I'll hear your machine's voice...  :-D  Hehe!  Ooooh great!  Blaise got a digicam!  Thank GAWD he's leaving tomorrow!!!  (That's so mean!  Bad me!)  Oooooh, found one!  "You and your Pisces are a pair who could outlast all others. You've finally found the perfect sympathetic ear to share all your tales of trouble and woe. Or maybe you could opt for a slow dance around the room with your Pisces companion instead. It all depends on what you're in the mood for. Nevertheless, you've finally found the right person to share all of your emotional experiences with.  Try not to overdo it with the emotional ups and downs. There is only so much even a caring Pisces partner can take. Once you get the ball rolling in the love department, you and your Pisces lover should be on the fast track to a very caring, highly romantic and certainly long-lasting affair."  :-) PROJECT!     I'm stuck in *happy*  - uh, shift me or something?  LOL - don't worry, the drive home will be enough to shift me all by itself :(  I'll be ok though :)  TTFN  ***pinch***  Shannon
      


16,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; No subject? wtf?  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Tue 07/16/02 05:14 PM   I'm feeling quite a bit like I'm trying to stand on a razor blade. I've  lost 5 pounds (not such a bad thing) in the past week (bad thing!)  since I've told Paul it's over. My tight pants are a little loose! I  don't want to buy new small clothes. The bummer is that I never seem to  loose any weight below the waist :x It all comes off up top :x Hehe,  do they make negative bra sizes? This is really hard. The good of that  is that I'm going through it!   **I know you are going through a lot. Don't be afraid to lean on me when  things get beyond your limit. I'm here for you and ALWAYS will be.   **Don't loose TOO MUCH weight! I like you just like you are! :-D Trust  me, although your appearance is a VERY NICE BONUS, I would love you just  the same if you weren't as attractive. I think you have a long way to  go before you need a negative cup size, lol. And have you heard me  complain about *anything*????!!!! NO!!! Did I mention that I thought you  had a nice ass? :-D :-)  kissing you

16,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Shift you? ok!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Tue 07/16/02 04:19 PM    First off, I have to tell you **again** that I had a TON of fun with you  yesterday! I love spending time with you - it's even better than  getting an email from ya, if that's possible!   **ME TOO! I'm getting spoiled tho. The more I see you, the less I can  just settle for sitting here and typing you an email.... the less fun  these are to type :-/   LOL, and I was bored at work, so I read horoscopes online - LOL - just  to test the theory that you see whatever you project on to them... I  think that's true! Um, except for the part that said, "July 10th will  see a New Moon in Cancer signaling a time for new beginnings -- or, in  your case, a higher level of emotional commitment to romance and love."  Whoa! Yeah, I'm projecting, but uh, I worked midnights on the 10th :-D    *hmmmmm!*   **I tell you, the more I think about this whole situation, the more I  wonder how much you and I really had to do with anything, lol! I feel  like I've been scooped up by a big hand and thrown into the mix with you.  And that's a GOOD feeling!   And I was bored again, so I called you and left a message on your  machine :-D Why is your number so easy? LOL - I *treid* not to  memorize it! Cause I knew I'd call all the time if I did... But it's  toooooo easy! You need more numbers - too many 5's or something...   **Yeah, and your frickin number is the same as a light bulb! 1056! Why  is that so easy to remember? 618-258-1056 I had it memorized the first  time I ever called you. Call all you want, as long as you can afford the  long distance! If I'm busy, just leave me a message :-)   Hahaha, and if I could think of *any* reason whatsoever, I'd call you  again RIGHT NOW. The only thing I can think of is that I just want to  hear your voice - meh, but I'll hear your machine's voice... :-D Hehe!   **I was thinking about recording my voice on there "Hello, this is  Dennis, leave a message, blah blah blah" but then you'd be calling even  more ;-)   Oooooh, found one!   "You and your Pisces are a pair who could outlast all others. You've  finally found the perfect sympathetic ear to share all your tales of  trouble and woe. Or maybe you could opt for a slow dance around the room  with your Pisces companion instead. It all depends on what you're in  the mood for. Nevertheless, you've finally found the right person to  share all of your emotional experiences with.   Try not to overdo it with the emotional ups and downs. There is only so  much even a caring Pisces partner can take. Once you get the ball  rolling in the love department, you and your Pisces lover should be on  the fast track to a very caring, highly romantic and certainly long-lasting  affair."   **That sounds so right on when I think about how all this feels that it  almost makes me wonder if I'm crazy! And in case you can't tell, I'm  VERY tollerant, but I'll let you know right away if things are getting  out of hand. :-D   :-) PROJECT!    **Ahh... you just want to BE balled! lol ;-)   I'm stuck in *happy* - uh, shift me or something?   **Show me where your shift knob is.... and I'll show you mine!   ***pinch***   **ouch!   **KISS**   Dennis   
      


17,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Twofor?? Threesome!!!:-D  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Wed 07/17/02 05:22 PM    I know! What am I going to do at work without Dennis emails? Ohhhh,  yeah, I guess I'll just daydream about Dennis :-D That'll work!   **Well, I don't think you'll have to do "without", maybe just ween back  a bit is all :-D And daydream all you want... I do! I haven't driven to  work without getting an erection in 2 weeks now....   

17,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp;Why IS this so funny?!?!?!?!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Wed 07/17/02 03:21 AM   Ok, it's 4:15 in the morning.  &nbsp;  You're asleep, I'm working with a bunch of **boring** ass people!&nbsp; I'm browsing OT, and dammit if this isn't the funniest fucking thing I've ever seen!!!  &nbsp;  http://forums.off-topic.net/showthread.php?s=&amp;threadid=348055&amp;perpage=25&amp;pagenumber=1" target="_blank"

17,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp;Your twofer!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Wed 07/17/02 12:04 AM    

18,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp;marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; depo surfing  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Thu 07/18/02 09:58 PM     urlLink http://www.suite101.com/article.cfm/14642/87114    Found that ^^^ while surfing. Lots of links, interesting stuff. You know  how you always hear a lot more from the people who got the bad stuff  than you do from the people who got the good stuff? Looks like it may  apply here..... Just wanted to share the link :-) Lots of other links  attached to that page and the pages attached to that page too ;-) I read  all 3 of the parts in that series:  #2:  urlLink http://www.suite101.com/article.cfm/14642/90527   and #3:  urlLink http://www.suite101.com/article.cfm/14642/91172    I'm going to read more. Gotta love the internet!   Dennis     
      


18,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Five knuckle shuffle?  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Thu 07/18/02 09:41 PM&nbsp;     

18,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com

19,July,2004


    
       
      From: "Shannon Yevcak"   To: spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject: Blah... headache... coughing...  Date: Fri 07/19/02 05:21 PM    

19,July,2004


    
       
      From: dennis   To: marfells@hotmail.com  Subject: Helping stall!:-D  Date: Fri 07/19/02 05:05 PM    *sigh* Oh well, I shouldn't hate like this - I'm going to have to deal  with her some anyway. I should be nice. I should be an adult. I  should be good! I'm trying, sorry I'm exposing you to my catty side.  Sounds like you understand why she brings it out of me though - you know  what kind of girl *I* am, and how girls like me respond to girls like *her*  --- right? So, does this look like a love match for Paul or what?!?!?!???  How can he possibly like someone so FAKE?!?!?!???!?!??? *grr* *sigh*   **You know about my quickness of "reading" people. I can definitely see  how you could dislike her, since I had no idea that this was *her* and  still found her rather unlikeable. NO bias required!   

19,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   It's more like dinner... or a snack! Date:   Fri 07/19/02 04:48 PM      

19,July,2004


    
       
      From: dennis   To: marfells@hotmail.com  Subject: Lunch!  Date: Fri 07/19/02 04:38 PM    Sounds promising... is she about 5' 5" or so (slightly shorter than me,  I believe) with (newly) blonde hair to the bottom of her jaw, very  skinny, and GOD YES she wears too fucking much makeup!!! She's got a  kinda weird face - not exactly ugly, but sorta, uh, maybe flatish? I  don't know - it's been a year and a half since I've seen her... Drunk  and stupid - that sounds promising too...   **Yes, would bet you a $100(yes, another one!) that that was her. Flat  face, not really attractive, pretty thin. According to Kevin "Looks like  a cheap whore." Came in, no uniform, went behind counter, etc, etc. It  all fits. We payed a lot of attention to her because we were having such  a good time making fun of her..."Hey, she doesn't belong back there!  She doesn't have a uniform! She must be a terrorist!" "She's hiding the  anthrax on her face!" She does not strike me as even SLIGHTLY  intelligent. First impression? BITCHY. Saw her interaction w/co workers,  not friendly.   

19,July,2004


    
       
      From: "Shannon Yevcak"   To: spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject: OMFG!!!!  Date: Fri 07/19/02 04:23 PM   

19,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis    To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Lauren! LOL!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Fri 07/19/02 04:10 PM    You've been spotted!!!   Lauren was at McDonald's - not working, just came in to switch days with  another person...   So, anyway, I hear she saw you...   Saw a JetCorp uniform, did a quick turn around, and...   LOL   **You won't beleive this, we noticed a woman come in that was not  wearing a McD's uniform and go behind the counter and do some paperwork  and such. She was wearing a black turtleneck sweatery thingy. Kevin(who  I go to lunch with regularly) has noticed her at lunch before and  mentions her when he sees her because "She wears enough makeup to make a  prostitute blush." and "She looks desperate to find a man" and he  always gets a good laugh out of her! DOH! This may or may not have been  Lauren, but if it was....!!!!!!!!! One night when I went to that mcd's/amaco  to get gas after work this same woman was out back of the place drunk  and acting stupid...lol.   Paul won't tell me what she said, so it can't be "good."   **PLEASE do not tell him about this! Do not "confirm" that she saw *ME*,  it could have been the *other* Dennis that works here at Jetcorp  ;-)...... BUT I can maybe tell you why he won't tell you. Kevin and I  were being absolutely obnoxious (as men sometimes tend to do). She may  or may not have heard us cracking about her makeup and being assholes in  general. Kevin is the guy I bragged to about you. The subject of your  husband came up.... "So what does her husband look like?" he asks. My  answer, since we were already in full obnoxious force was "He's pretty  scrawny." And of course Kevin, never being the kind of guy to miss a  beat has to fill in not at all quietly with "Well that's why she's not  satisfied with him, he's a scrawny little bitch!  Kevin laugh here

19,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp;spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; The cat's out of the bag!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Fri 07/19/02 02:58 PM    You've been spotted!!!  &nbsp;  Lauren was at McDonald's - not working, just came in to switch days with another person...  &nbsp;  So, anyway, I hear she saw you...  &nbsp;  Saw a JetCorp uniform, did a quick turn around, and...  &nbsp;  LOL  &nbsp;  Paul won't tell me what she said, so it can't be "good."  &nbsp;  Like I care...  &nbsp;  :)  &nbsp;  So anyway, that's my big news...  &nbsp;  That and I was checking out a cop's gun at Subway today, and he tried to talk to me....&nbsp; I was thinking, "I swear I've seen a few naughty movies that start just like this...."&nbsp; :o  &nbsp;  Um, AND I bought oil and an oil filter, still haven't actually changed the oil, but I'm running out of excuses not to...  &nbsp;  TTYL (I'll be here for a while, if you're around to email back and forth a few times....)&nbsp; Whateva...  &nbsp;  Shannon   
      


19,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Sixth gear!  Date:&nbsp;&nbsp; Fri 07/19/02 12:50 PM    

19,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com

21,July,2004


    
       
      schpoolboy2: Hey!  akatornado6: Hey :-)  schpoolboy2: How you doin?  schpoolboy2: :-)  akatornado6: Got tired, now untired again.  schpoolboy2: yeah, me too  schpoolboy2: gun show sucked ass  schpoolboy2: long drive sucked more ass  schpoolboy2: I've been to pawn shops w/more guns :-)  akatornado6: Just got a *worried* feeling a little bit ago, but I got OK about 10 minutes ago.  akatornado6: *yawn*  schpoolboy2: I was thinking about you :-)  akatornado6: What were you thinking?  akatornado6: I sent you an email.  schpoolboy2: Good things:-) Happy thoughts!  schpoolboy2:  akatornado6: Sneezy today!  schpoolboy2: yeah, probably from my frickin room...it was dusty  akatornado6: Nope, not started sneezing until I got to work.  schpoolboy2: so phil is going to wear a t-shirt eh? ;-)  schpoolboy2: :-D  akatornado6: Uh-huh!  akatornado6: *yawn*  schpoolboy2: Your email is so sweet.... Thank you! I love you! I feel the exact same way you do!!!!  akatornado6: :-)  schpoolboy2: *pinch*  akatornado6: Uhhh, can I come over ;-)  schpoolboy2: SURE!  akatornado6: Oh how I wish I could.  akatornado6: :-(  schpoolboy2: I know....  akatornado6: *sniff*  schpoolboy2: Sorry if I made it more difficult by saying that....  schpoolboy2: "sure"  akatornado6: No, I know.  akatornado6: It's ok.  akatornado6: OUCH!  schpoolboy2: ?  schpoolboy2: Cramps still?  akatornado6: ...for pinching!  akatornado6: ...  schpoolboy2: Oh, you said to pinch you....  akatornado6: Yeah.  akatornado6: :-)  akatornado6: *smack*  schpoolboy2: see, you're not dreaming!  schpoolboy2: owe!  akatornado6: I know :-)  akatornado6: I'm not!  akatornado6: It's real!  akatornado6: :-D  schpoolboy2: Yes!  akatornado6: BTW, my boss likes your shirt.  akatornado6: :-)  schpoolboy2: :-D  schpoolboy2: cool  schpoolboy2: Did you tell him it was mine?  akatornado6: Had to show it off :-)  akatornado6: I said "my friend"  schpoolboy2: ;-)  schpoolboy2: cool  akatornado6: Guess what?  akatornado6: *funny*  schpoolboy2: what?  akatornado6: Chris and Paul dropped by this afternoon...  akatornado6: Paul was like, "where are your clothes???"  schpoolboy2: .  akatornado6: And Chris gave me a big hug... he said, "Your shirt smells good!"  akatornado6: :-D  akatornado6: LOL!  schpoolboy2: :-)  akatornado6: I was like, I KNOW!!!  schpoolboy2: :-)  schpoolboy2: That is entertaining!  akatornado6: I know.  akatornado6: :-)  schpoolboy2: :-)  schpoolboy2: :-D  schpoolboy2: **HUG**  akatornado6: *hug*  akatornado6: I want you.  akatornado6: I want to be WITH you.  akatornado6: :-(  akatornado6: Blah.  schpoolboy2: Take me? Be with me?  akatornado6: I'm so sleepy.  akatornado6: I'd just curl up and take a long nap with ya.  akatornado6: *sigh*  schpoolboy2: Me too!  schpoolboy2:  akatornado6: Meh, I have to take Chris up to Litchfield :x  akatornado6: I don't get to nap.  akatornado6: :x  schpoolboy2: So Paul was not amused by your shirt?  akatornado6: He knows it's yours.  akatornado6: I don't fucking care.  schpoolboy2: What's up w/Litchfield?  akatornado6: I'm working tomorrow.  schpoolboy2: ic  akatornado6: Paul won't take the day off, even though he's known about it for a month.  akatornado6: So, someone has to watch Chris.  akatornado6: It's gonna be my Dad.  schpoolboy2: I'm still here, just don't have anything to say about that.  akatornado6: Ok.  akatornado6: :-)  akatornado6: I'm cutting something.  akatornado6: :-)  schpoolboy2: So what is your schedule this week?  schpoolboy2: Whatchu cuttin?  akatornado6: Oh, days Monday.  schpoolboy2: And midnights tues,weds, and sat sun?"  akatornado6: Then nights Thursday - Sunday (Wednesday through Sat. nights...)  schpoolboy2: Well, it looks like I'll be staying up late a lot this week:-)  akatornado6: I bragged again!!!  akatornado6: To Eric!!!  akatornado6: :-D  schpoolboy2: :-D  schpoolboy2: What did you say?  schpoolboy2: :-)  schpoolboy2: And what are you cutting?  akatornado6: I am cutting paper!  akatornado6: Why are you so worried about it??? :p  akatornado6: I said what happened, basically :-)  akatornado6: Hehe, that I was up all night, and why.  akatornado6: :-D  schpoolboy2: Just wondering, thought "I'm cutting something" was an invitation to ask....  akatornado6: LOL - no it's why I wasn't typing.  schpoolboy2: He's Morter, right?  akatornado6: :-)  akatornado6: Yeah.  akatornado6: Eric.  schpoolboy2: Just wondering if you mentioned anything about....:-)  akatornado6: Uh, yeah.  akatornado6: :-)  schpoolboy2: :-D  schpoolboy2: Makes me grin  schpoolboy2: You got to find out first hand;-)  akatornado6: Yeah.  schpoolboy2: DOH! didn't mean that pun!  akatornado6: He said, "RD 

21,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; "Shannon Yevcak"   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; spoolboy@autospeed.com

22,July,2004


    
       
      From:&nbsp;&nbsp; dennis   To:&nbsp;&nbsp; marfells@hotmail.com  Subject:&nbsp;&nbsp; Hey!  Date:&nbsp; Mon 07/22/02 03:56 PM&nbsp;   &nbsp;   Just seen your post on .org. You out there? If so, holla back. I can  talk on the phone if'n you want cause everyone GFO already.   Dennis    
      


23,July,2004


    
       
      From: dennis   To: spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject: Re: PM's from Neons.org  Date: Tue 07/23/02 06:57 PM    --- dennis  wrote:  

23,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Ketchup! Date:   Tue 07/23/02 03:00 PM        The Tomato family was running a bit late on their way to Church one fine Sunday morning.  The littlest tomato, Timmy, kept lagging behind.  Mother Tomato, sister Tomato, and even the little tomato dog tried to get him to pay attention to the walk instead of playing with the picket fences.  Finally, Father Tomato went back to have a talk with his son.  He stomped on Timmy and yelled, "Ketchup!"   

23,July,2004


    
       
      From: "Shannon Yevcak"   To: spoolboy@autospeed.com  Subject: Ketchup!  Date: Tue 07/23/02 03:00 PM    The Tomato family was running a bit late on their way to Church one fine Sunday morning. The littlest tomato, Timmy, kept lagging behind. Mother Tomato, sister Tomato, and even the little tomato dog tried to get him to pay attention to the walk instead of playing with the picket fences. Finally, Father Tomato went back to have a talk with his son. He stomped on Timmy and yelled, "Ketchup!"   

24,July,2004


    
       
      From: dennis   To: marfells@hotmail.com  Subject: ply mouth?  Date: Wed 07/24/02 10:36 PM    I'm running a bit late at work, bastards are making me place a stupid  order @ 11:35! Oh well... anyway I'll see you on AIM ASAP! :-D **HUG** *kiss*   If you get this message 1 or more times via PM, just ignore it. I was  having a hard time getting it to "send". It was hanging up or something.  Oh well, here it is again either way:    (apts)Yeah, I know - shit takes time. I've got time... And I need time  too - so this is going to be fine. I don't mind talking about it -  checking in every once in a while to see how we're both feeling is fine.  But I got wonkey last night - just got my brain to shut off from  thinking too much. All better   **Cool. Glad that your brain is working again   

25,July,2004


    
       
      From: dennis   To: marfells@hotmail.com  Subject: Good read!  Date: Thu 07/25/02 10:35 PM    http://www.rehermorrison.com/techTalk/08.htm   Thought you might like that.... was searching for some stuff and  stumbled onto it!   Here's the whole index to the articles:  http://www.rehermorrison.com/techTalk/indexStart.htm   That should keep you busy for a while if you get bored ;-)   Talk to you soon!   *kiss*   Dennis   PS-For Larry...   This is a copy/paste of a post I made on a list tonight about why big  cams don't work and how to use them right in turbo 2.2/2.5's....   "If you are reading this and have never sat down and tried to figure out   your compression ratio mathematically, you will be confused about what  I'm saying below. This is pretty advanced stuff. Read a book that tells  you how to figure your compression ratio if you are interested in  learning this.   If you have microsoft Excel, you can download a bunch of formulas  including a compression ratio calc I wrote into a spreadsheet by simply  clicking this link: http://www.fwdmopar.com/sites/dennis/math.xls   The first reason that most large camshafts do not work in our cars is  because the static compression ratio is too low, which kills the dynamic   compression ratio when the intake valve closes later.   Almost everyone is afraid to raise the static compression ratio for fear   of breaking something.   Lets say a stock 2.5T1 has 145psi cranking compression... now stick a  S60 in and the cranking compression drops to about 120psi.   Imagine if you raised the static compression ratio enough so that the  cranking compression w/the S60 cam was 145psi again...   This is what you'd need to do to make the big cams work, among other  things.   There is a formula for calculating how much to raise the compression  ratio in order to account for a longer duration camshaft. This formula  is complex, but what it basically does is use the *trapped volume* of  intake charge as your *volume at BDC* figure instead of BDC. Trapped  volume is basically anything that happens after the intake closes while  the piston is on the compression stroke. When it closes, call that point   BDC and use the volume in the cylinder at that moment as your figure  when figuring *dynamic* compression ratio.   So, in effect, we could figure the dynamic CR of a stock 7.8:1 2.5T1  w/an 89TBI roller (intake closes @56deg ABDC). Then figure out how much  to raise the compression ratio in order to use a longer duration  camshaft.   Ok, let the math begin! I have another REALLY HUGE Excel spreadsheet I'm   working on to answer this, but it might be easier and more accurate to  simply mock the engine up and measure the remainder of the stroke left  when the intakve valve rests on the seat.   Variables like rod ratio, piston pin offset, and actual valvetrain  geometry could throw this formula off quite a bit I think.   Oh, and another thing to think about before you get too excited....  bigger cams move the powerband higher.... not usually the best thing to  do if your cylinder head looks like it was designed by Briggs and  Stratton!" 
      


26,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   Chrysler? Date:   Fri 07/26/02 05:44 PM     

26,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   NO! Dodge! Date:   Fri 07/26/02 04:43 AM      

27,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Diamler Chrsyler, Dammit!!! Date:   Sat 07/27/02 03:21 AM      We drive German cars, duh!   Kraut!  Kraut!  Heil Herr Neon!  Bier ist gut!  Wo ist das badezimmer?  Uh, that's about all the German I know.  Beer is good LOL!  :)  At least I can find the bathroom!  I think I can ask that in about 5 languages...  I can always pee!  Hooray!    

30,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   marfells@hotmail.com Subject:   sneaky!!!  Date:   Tue 07/30/02 04:06 PM    I'm supposed to be *working* on some shit, but I can't resist when I  open up my email and your name is sitting there, just waiting for me to  *click* :)  **I have no idea what you are talking about... you mean you are tempted  to email me when you should be "working"? That's a very alien concept!   I love you, you're really cool and stuff ;)   Have a good day, that's all I wanted to say :-D  **All I can do is smile and say "ME TOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!" I LOVE YOU!!!!!  :-D ^99999   See ya tomorrow!   **Definitely! Quickies are good too ;-)  Dennis
      


30,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Sneak...  Date:   Tue 07/30/02 02:55 PM     I'm supposed to be *working* on some shit, but I can't resist when I open up my email and your name is sitting there, just waiting for me to *click* :)   I love you, you're really cool and stuff ;)   Have a good day, that's all I wanted to say :-D   *KISS* *HUG* *hug* *KISS* *nibble* *hug* *and stuff*   See ya tomorrow!   Shannon
      


31,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Re: Where's Spoolboy??? Date:   Wed 07/31/02 05:20 PM      I dunno, I'm still here...  LOL so, how are you doing?  Wanna PM, or just BS through email?
      


31,July,2004


    
       
      From:   dennis   To:   "Shannon Yevcak"   Subject:   Re: Where's Spoolboy???  Date:   Wed 07/31/02 05:19 PM       This fast enough?  Dennis
      


31,July,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Where's Spoolboy??? Date:   Wed 07/31/02 05:12 PM      Aw, man, musta gotten bored with .org already???  WTF???  I'm gonna be here until 6:50 - lessee how fast you are ;)
      


02,August,2004


    
       
      From:   Paul Yevcak   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Need some answers Date:   Fri 08/02/02 11:13 AM       Hey,  I had really hoped that you would e-mail me, and explain this whole  thing; without my having to e-mail you first and ask questions. Those few times that you and I e-mailed each other, you told me quite a  few things.  You told me that you were opening up your armor, for one thing. I can't quote directly because I no longer have any record of those e-mails, be it digital or a print-out.  You told me, time and again, awhile back, that you would NEVER do  anything with another man's wife that you shouldn't be doing.  You told me that  you respected Shannon enough not to do that until we're officially through.  You told me that you respected ME enough to not doing things such as you have been doing.  You told me that you knew it was in no one's best interest  to be intimate with Shannon until this was all through.  You AND Shannon  told me that if need be, you guys would just cool everything until this is  all over.  It took me over ONE FULL WEEK of CONSTANT dwelling on that fact, Dennis; but goddamnit, I honestly did end up believing that you were telling me the truth.  And now, especially given what you guys have done so far, I can't pull the huge knife out of my back.  Especially coming from you...I  BELIEVED YOU.  I liked hanging out with you, I thought you were a pretty damn  cool guy.  And now this.  For what??  Because it took me so long to actually believe what you were telling me, the "betrayal" I feel is absolutely ENORMOUS.  What changed Dennis??  What happened that made you decide to go against  what you (successfully) drilled into my head?   Do you even care about what's going on??  I know Shannon doesn't.  She has no plans on stopping what  is currently going on.    I honestly don't even want to begin thinking about the things you guys  have done, and are doing.  It literally turns my stomach.  True, I don't love Shannon any more, I'm not attracted to her anymore; and to be honest, I never really was 100% attracted to her.  That's not what upsets me.  It's the fact, again, that both of you spent days upon days telling me that nothing would happen.  You guys both told me that none of this would happen until this is all through; because it was the RIGHT thing to do.  Shannon said you're  worth waiting for; you've said that Shannon is worth waiting for.  So what changed??  I want to hear your side of this.  I've heard all I  care to hear from Shannon; now it's your turn.  Please don't just put this e-mail in your recycle bin.  I want to hear  your side of this.   If nothing else, I feel that I AM owed an explanation at least. And also, please don't be brief with me.  If I ever hope to get any sort of  closure here, I NEED to hear what you have to say.  It sucks, too, because I honestly did want to make it through this as  your friend; but never once did I think you guys would ever end up doing what you've been doing.  All I can guarantee now is that I'll be civil towards you.  A "hi" and a "bye" is probably all that I'll be able to manage.   And that really sucks, Dennis.  I wanted to continue being your friend, and  I DID look forward to many car discussions, and picking your brain about automotive things.  But honestly, right now I don't think that's ever  going to happen. I feel hatred right now, I feel like I've been slapped in the face by both of you, and I feel hurt right now.  To put it bluntly, and you probably already know this, most of that anger is directed towards you.  Most of  the hurt was caused by you.  I truly believed every word you told me when  you and I exchanged those few e-mails awhile back.  I never fully believed  that Shannon was ever telling me the truth when she said that nothing would happen between you guys.  That's why I brought it up so many frickin'  times with her.  But you, on the other hand, I finally found it inside to  believe what you were telling me.  I knew that Shannon would make suggestive comments, and probably "hit" on you; but I got consolation believing  that you would not return the same actions.  One more thing...I know that you'll show this e-mail to Shannon...but  can you at least reply to it before you do that??  I don't want her reading this, and tainting your response(s).  Shit, that's all I can manage to type right now.  I need to get my mind  on other things.....  Later
      


05,August,2004


    
       
      From:   "Shannon Yevcak"   To:   spoolboy@autospeed.com Subject:   Closing time... Date:   Mon 08/05/02 02:43 PM        I'm singing.  Listening to the music in my head.  "Every new beginning comes from some other beginning's end..."  I have no idea who sings that song - some one hit wonder, maybe?  I don't know!  I don't care in the least, I like that line - I'm feeling it today...   Huh.   We've only got so long before we don't need to email each other anymore!  That's almost sad.  Even though this was *fast* - it seems so long ago when you sent me that PM and I shot back my terse reply...  I feel as if I've known you forever.  Somehow.  But there is still so much I don't know.  I'm not worried that I'll ever find something I don't like, or can't learn to deal with - something that WE can't deal with together...  I can't wait!  I'm so excited about really getting to know you - in real life, in bed, in all of the weird situations I'm sure we'll find ourselves in the middle of... (You know how I am, I can never leave well enough alone!  What happened to the curious kitty again???)  You're fun, and I know that somehow no matter how much life throws at me from this point on, you'll still find a way to make me smile.  Probably just by existing.  Thanks for existing, Dennis!   I still have volumes of text in me.  Bits and bytes and gigs and all of that.  But I'm not going to be recording it for posterity anymore.  DAMN!  I'll be talking to you in person, in OUR apartment!  I guess we'll have those first few layers of our onion forever, won't we?  That's cool.  GO YOU for saving our emails - you're smart!  How'd you know?  Yep, the more I think about it, the more I think you **did** have a plan from the get-go.  Heeeeeh.  *sigh*  I am feeling (cause I know you'd ask me if you were with me!!!) comfortable and still a little twinge of sad.   Paul is getting much better as the day wears on.  He is buying Rob's motorcycle (CBR954RR, w/ some monor tweaks on it) later this week, or over the weekend.  He IMd me and asked, "Can I ask you one last thing before we go our separate ways forever?"  He wants to take me for a spin on the bike after he gets it.  Motorcycles scare me.  In a not nice, non-rollercoaster kind of way.  I don't like them so much.  I like going fast!  I like acceleration!  But I like having at least *some* metal surrounding my body - even if it isn't so much worse to be out in the open like that - it just scares me.  Dunno.  Anyway - that's a big thing for him to ask me.  We had a nice IM session - we both wound up crying.  He cried harder, I have trouble emoting in public ;)  He's got a cube, I'm, like, OUT here in the middle of the room, kinda.  Then I went to smoke and gave him a big hug.  I think he might just make it out of this...  That makes me so happy!  I do love him, I honestly do - he's my baby daddy, you know?  I just can't live with him.  I *thought* he had it in him to do this with me.  But for a while he really scared me!  I started to doubt him big time, thought about making a bid for Chris because I wasn't even sure if Paul was capable of taking care of him.  He'll make it!  I'm really happy about that - he *is* a good person, I swear he is.  Even though he's gone out of his way to show you otherwise...  Hopefully you two will come to be sociable with each other, even if you never quite make it to being "friends."   Haha, thank god for you, Dennis.  I don't know if I'm going to make it all of the time.  I could not do this without you.  You caught me at the last possible moment.  How on earth did this happen?  How did you know?  Who sent you?  I LOVE YOU!   Keep being easy.  Be gentle with me.  I've got a lot of things - old things, newer things, shit - there are issues that haven't even occured to me just yet - to deal with.  I want to deal with them.  I bet most of them have been held in for so long that they'll  be pretty quick and painless - like the deal with High School that I finally resolved by driving around Litchfield two nights in a row.  It was a lot easier to get through than I thought it would be.  I suprised myself - that was the night I remember just how strong I am.  Paul seemed to make it impossible for me to spend energy on myself.  I was so busy giving - to Chris and Paul and the relationship - and not getting a whole lot back.  I think I had almost exhausted myself.  That's why I was about to quit feeling.  I was running on fumes.  I think I must have given extra hard to Paul - trying to make him love me...  I never did it on purpose, but I think I must have been doing it all along.  He told me today that, "even though I knew it was doomed from the beginning, I still wound up falling in love with you."  I think he's confusing love and in love.  I don't think we were every totally 110% IN love with each other.  I'll readily accept the fact that he loves me.  That's quite ok...  It's better that way - we'll be good parents after we get it figured out!  I've loved lots of people without being in love with them.   Maybe, now that I've met you, I should think - reconsider - have I ever been in love before?  I wonder.  I'm too tired to give it the proper treatment right now, but remind me to think about it someday, will ya?   I *AM* in love with you, Dennis, 100%, no doubts, no worries, no catches, no hangups, no strings - I love you.   *whew*  Today feels like a big day somehow.  A day to rest and get myself psyched up for something BIG.  Like eating spaghetti before a marathon ;)  It feels somewhat like suspended animation too - Paul has let me go (or is letting me go finally) and you don't quite have me all the way just yet.  I don't feel bad - just I guess tired enough and clear-headed enough to take a second to reflect.  I don't want to forget this day - I feel like I need this deliniation.  It's MY day.   Well, I have work to finish...   And I'm calling you when I get home anyway...   *yawn*   Shannon
      



