
18,June,2004


	 
      I'm pretty sure this is a picture from a card.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Portgas D. Ace...he ate the Mera Mera Fruit and can extract and control fire at will.  Ace is also Luffy's big brother.  kakkoi ne??&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Hehee...wallpaper made my yours truly~~ ME!!  Nothing original since I'm not too good with photoshop....but not too shabby...right??~ =P&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Zoro Character sheet 4: Casual Zoro&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Zoro Character sheet 3:  Santouryo&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Zoro Character sheet 2:  demon roronoa zoro!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Zoro Character sheet 1&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Nami Character sheet 3:  Dorobou!!? iya...kaizoku yo!~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Nami Character sheet 4: elegant nami~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Nami Character sheet 2:  Usual clothes&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Nami Character sheet 1........"Yappari nami-swaaann!! looks good from every angle neee??" as Sanji would put it hahah&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Luffy Character sheet 4&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Luffy Character sheet 3&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Luffy Character sheet 2&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Luffy Character sheet 1&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


16,June,2004


	 
      jump cover #28&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Need I say more???  Zoro rocks!  Ussop and Luffy look like wimps compared to Zoro...hahah&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Sakura no Onsen = Sakura Hot Spring........Kimochi~~~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
       from right to left: meso; hikku; meso meso; MESO meso; egu egu!  In brown letters: "meso meso sunna yo"   Someone PLEASE tell me what this means....I think it's just a sound that they're making when they're sulking....&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Chopper is the animal king!  This is a movie poster.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Kaizoku Ou attire, and Demon Zoro in front!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Full crew.....for now?  I didn't read all of the manga yet...so I don't know why Robin joins Luffy.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Zoro and Luffy...hm....In the anime, Luffy seems as tall as Zoro...but I guess I was wrong!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Another group pic!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      I like this picture....it looks like someone took a picture of a photograph.  Now I know Sanji has six-packs too! muhahahah~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Chopper leaving Drum island to join Luffy's crew.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      minna in arabasta....hey...I thought sanji lost those glasses!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      i have no idea what Romance Dawn is...cute nonetheless&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      ~Taking a break~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      gya gya gya gya~~ &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Nami and Vivi in Arabasta ~ and of course wearing Sanji's favourite dance girl costume.  Sanji: "Dance girls are civilians too!!"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      don't mess with this crew!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Everyone is in action...heehee...except Luffy...he's just eating ~O~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      this must be the same sofa and same signs that Sanji and Ussop were holding a few posts back....the "Funk" picture!  I guess Luffy kicked everyone out hahaha....hey look at that mini "Going Merry"!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Nami's battle at Arlong Park!  I love the Hawaiian-style shirt that Zoro wears during this arc~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      lmao....this is so funny!!!  The bear is so cute!!....all the skull needs now is a mugiwara boshi!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      oh...I had more from the artbook that I forgot to post....Here is an earlier crew, without Sanji, Chopper or Robin.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      hm...the way Zoro is drawn here makes me think this is fanart....what do you think?&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Another "to die for" cute picture!!.....Tottemo tottemo kawaiiii!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      UWAAAA...KAWAIIIIII ~~~  Young Mugiwara nakama with Shanks!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Wanted!!  Bounty posters as background!  Luffy is first to get a bounty of 30,000,000 Belis....next one on the wanted list will be Zoro at 60,000,000 Belis while Luffy's bounty raises to 100,000,000 Belis!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Mugiwara Kaizoku symbol on barrels!  Cool glasses on Sanji!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Another casual attire pic...this time with Carue and Vivi-chan!  hey..zoro looks like he's carrying a golf bag haahah~&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Great wallpaper~ a collage of screencaps from the anime!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      The Journey!  Chopper is so cute!  I think this is from the artbook.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Casual clothes ^o^~  Zoro looks the best IMO!   Sanji....ehm...no wonder they have a gazillion Yaoi pages on him....look at his shirt! That's so Yaoi....=_="&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Arlong and his merman VS. Ussop, Zoro, Luffy and Sanji&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Cool Funky pic!  It's kind of blurry though.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      OMG...this is such a great picture!!!!!  The essence of Luffy and male Nakama....they're all pigging out like the boars beside them hahaha~   Zoro looks so funny!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Inner Peace~~~~For some reason Ussop looks young in this pic.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      A very lively picture...lots of colours....I guess they don't really need a musician after all hahaha...I love this picture...but then again...i like all of them ~teehee!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      And "No Slack" picture....heehehe...look at Ussop dancing like an idiot at the back!  Wou...Sanji looks so cool in this pic!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Here is the "Live a life of Ease" picture I was talking about earlier!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Cool wallpaper!  This is actually a combination of 2 separate pictures.  The one on top is the "No Slack" picture and the one on the bottom is "Ease".  Very nice wallpaper!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      "Grand Line" ...one of my favourite wallpapers!!  This used to be the background for my One Piece website, but unfortunately I'm not able to get it working again.. so this blog will have to do for now.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Unite Wallpaper! This is what I currently have on my desktop~  &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Nami under the moonlight picture.  Sugge sexy da yo~ ...This pic turned out bigger than it actually is...click on the pic to go to the actual size...Same goes for all the other wallpapers/pictures that I post...some may be bigger...while others may be smaller&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Luffy Screencap&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Zoro Screencap&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Nami Screencap&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Ussop & Sanji Ending Screencap&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    


15,June,2004


	 
      Here I will post my collection of One Piece pictures/wallpapers/gifs, one of my favourite anime!!
    



