
29,May,2004


    
       
                             Opening a gift with my Nanay    Big Smile with my Tatay    Leaving on a Jetplane
       
    
    



28,May,2004


     
        We look so 'maalaala mo kaya' like in here.  We're supposed to appear as sophisticated and sexy.    It's hard to project, though... i'm sorry girls but i think we appear rather funny.  We had tons of giggles looking at the outcome, though and that's better than our goal.   Au and Annie looked like mom and child here.  Dey and I were laughin at it still on our way home riding the MRT. Yeah, we're giggling like lil girls in the crowded train all because of au and annie's dove commercial pose.    Okay, if you take a look at each of us individually, we look ok.  It's chaotic when you put all of us in one shot, Ugh!  But i've pretty pretty friends.  I remember having disagreements with Ann and Annie and Dey took her side.  Except for the sweet au au, she was the one i had lunch with when the rest of the witches (he he) decided to ignore me like i am the kontrabida.  Maybe I was a bit insensitive then.  heck, maybe a bit bitchy!  Just remembering the times, it's over now.  Ann said i should update the people i'd tell my 'fights' with, like how i told john what them witches did to me.  I am so easy to talk to and i forgive easily but John's like, 'you're not friends with em anymore, right?"  I guess every good relationship would have 'downs' like what happened.  Heck, everything's forgotten and i love my girls to the bits. 
     
    


21,May,2004


     
       232 2323549;;8498ot1lsi"

21,May,2004


     
                                                
     
    


16,May,2004


     
           braces are contagious?! HA!!                               
     
    


12,May,2004


     
      It's really our first time to 'come out'...    Ann and Au looked real pretty here    Ann, Au and me after a sumptuous meal-at least for them, i think my chicken was bland, ugh!    Dey, Me, Annie and Ann don't look at all sober -- pier0ne, the fort    Japayuki's to go...note to self: make up doesn't make me pretty, it made me look a baduff,as john would say    A bit wasted...not really...it's not what it looks like    havin a fun time with the girls    Famous Dey look      It's the flash from the camera...they ain't drunk (yeah, right!)                 
     
    


12,May,2004


     
      missing them...we should go out again soon...   with sheila...she's going to china next week and i hope i'd get to meet her in HK...princess procrastination me!    Red...we would've been work mates...i miss that we don't hang out cuz he's got a serious boylet now...      heehee, funny ivee wrapped in my long arms...she's hating me right this very minute cuz i wasn't allowed to sleep over their place...she'll get over it.
     
    


12,May,2004


     
      December 2003, Christmas Party World Trade Center  Pictures with Ivee, my HS bestfriend...        Tita Corla's big tummy--missing her badly--        With the pretty etel peepz      
     
    


26,June,2004


     
      My father said we should've taken the picture of HK and China not of ourselves.   232;=92 2323565339748ot1lsi"


