
31,May,2004


	 
      The bullshit part about weed is that you always run out.  It's fun getting there but it's not a nice place to be.  I dedicate the 3 weeks to pure fitness.  Thats how long it will take to undo Friday, Saturday, and Sunday...
     
    


29,May,2004


	 
      I had a cold all weekend.  Also drank way too much, ruined my diet with some narly apple pie, and didn't have quite enough weed.  What else... Nothing else.  I'm already sick of this blog.  I could say a lot but most of it would be really worthless.  Don't waste your time reading this blog.  You will regret it.  Thats a promise.
     
    


29,May,2004


	 
      In his column over at nytimes.com:    "Now the airwaves are filled with sexually ambiguous young male designers, bubbly female colorists in tight T-shirts, and sensitive but studly carpenters, who descend upon bland suburban rec rooms, closets and garages while the owner is away or in a coma. In a flurry of exuberance and flirtation, they transform a once normal if unremarkable room into the interior design equivalent of the old Funkadelic concert costumes"  The rest is pretty much just as funny.  Also, props to the "Pimp My Ride" reference on the nytimes.com op ed page.  We all saw it coming, I'm just surprised it wasn't in an unreadable Maureen Dowd column.
     
    


26,May,2004


	 
      When you have a bad cold.  I'm trying some generic thera-flu right now.  I hear it works really well.  It certainly tastes bad enough to work.  I'm hoping i didnt waste my money, but alka-seltzer cold was pretty expensive anyway, and it looks like pretty much the same ingredients.  Must end this misery somehow.
     
    


26,May,2004


	 
      Okay this isn't intended to be offensive.  The criteria for this ranking is what religion would i want to be brought up in.  I'm doing this off the top of my head so sorry if i leave your faith out.  You are probably going straight to hell anyway, fucker.  1) Judaism - I just dont see how you can argue with this.  As far as I can tell Jews are just plain awesome. 2) Lutheran - This is what i grew up with.  the OG of protestant religions.  More bible, less bullshit. 3) Baptist - All music comes from god, and these guys can pump up the jam pretty well 4) Islam - Probably the only religion still capable of actually making their believers behave (for the most part).  Plus they are pretty much badasses 5) Eastern orhodox christian religions - They have some neat churches & outfits 6) All other protestant - gotta rank methodist etc somewhere.  most of these seem like watered down donut munching clubs who think being christian is equivalent to being republican 7) Catholic - Dominates europe for hundereds of years and accomplishes jack shit.  dont hate it, just dont like it. 8) Mormon - On one hand, they are pretty weird, which is good.  On the other hand, have you ever been to Utah?  It makes hell look like something to shoot for. 9) Elrond Hubbard's Scienetics - whatever man.  how much are you paying tom cruise to advertise your insane books? 10) Any cult, occult, or mystic shit - Give me a fucking break.  Just b/c you dont like waking up for church doesn't mean you can worship random things and pretend like its meaningful. 11) Wiccan - I invite every wiccan out there to cast all their spells on me please.  Dungeons & dragons is a more valid religion than being an unshowered girl dressing up in black.  and thats it folks.  pray for my soul please...
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
      Fuck the lakers.  Fuck Derek Fisher, Fuck Kobe, Fuck the Mailman, Fuck Shaq.  Fuck me having a cold.  Fuck my job. Fuck me being broke.  Fuck your mom.  Fuck not fucking.  If I'm leaving anyone out fuck you too...  Gotta love the old f-bomb.  IMO it's the most beautiful word that there is.  Huckin fuskers...  I'm going to drink a bottle of nyquil now (the whole thing) and maybe toss down a few shots to give it a little boost.  That usually gets rid of a cold overnight for me.
     
    


25,May,2004


	 
      Whoever can beat the lakers.  Actually, I really like Detroit.  Probably just because of Sheed, who was always one of my favorite jailblazers when they were totally awesome(along with sabonis and bonzi).
     
    


24,May,2004


	 
      In the year of our lord 2004.  I weighed myself this morning.  Down 26 pounds total so far... Work with that shit, hookers!
     
    


24,May,2004


	 
      I wasn't going to do this test b/c i thought the concept sounded about twice as stupid as fuck, but then i got bored...  Level Who are sent there? Score  Purgatory  Repenting Believers  Moderate  Level 1 - Limbo  Virtuous Non-Believers  Very High  Level 2  Lustful  Moderate  Level 3  Gluttonous  Low  Level 4  Prodigal and Avaricious  Very Low  Level 5  Wrathful and Gloomy  Low  Level 6 - The City of Dis  Heretics  Very Low  Level 7  Violent  Low  Level 8- the Malebolge  Fraudulent, Malicious, Panderers  Low  Level 9 - Cocytus  Treacherous  Very Low   First Level of Hell - Limbo  --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  Charon ushers you across the river Acheron, and you find yourself upon the brink of grief's abysmal valley. You are in Limbo, a place of sorrow without torment. You encounter a seven-walled castle, and within those walls you find rolling fresh meadows illuminated by the light of reason, whereabout many shades dwell. These are the virtuous pagans, the great philosophers and authors, unbaptised children, and others unfit to enter the kingdom of heaven. You share company with Caesar, Homer, Virgil, Socrates, and Aristotle. There is no punishment here, and the atmosphere is peaceful, yet sad.   Wow, sounds like my afterlife will be exactly like my life.  I guess that's fair enough.  Socrates is one of my favorite heros anyway.
     
    


23,May,2004


	 
      Everybody else is doing it...  Disorder  Rating Information  Paranoid:  Low  Schizoid:  Moderate  Schizotypal:  Moderate   Antisocial:  Low   Borderline:  Low   Histrionic:  Low  Narcissistic:  Moderate  Avoidant:  Very High  Dependent:  Moderate   Obsessive-Compulsive:  Low     No big surprises there.  I would have bumped up narcissistic one notch or so i guess.  Compared to my friends and their internet pimps im pretty together though.  You want a link?  Find it yourself fucker....
     
    


23,May,2004


	 
      On tonights Lakers-Twolves game 2 on TNT they showed Malkmus for like 5 seconds just now.  At least im 99% sure it was him...
     
    


22,May,2004


	 
      No dear reader, not  that  time of the month...  I'm talking about the part where i haven't been paid in forever & a day, and im poor as a whore.  This is the part of the month where the liquor is cheap and the weed is nonexistant, where the peanut better jelly sandwiches are made with neither bread nor jelly.  Also, it's rainy and Sunday.  In short, today is the winter of despair.  What am I to do?  A) Read a book B) Socialize C) Exercise D) Sleep E) Fag out and play computer F) Write in my blog  Congrats to those of you who correctly selected E)
     
    


22,May,2004


	 
      ... that stands for association not anything to do with ass.  But maybe it has everything to do with ass....    Finale:: Plays and the fags who like them  Martial arts:: Roundhouse  Flirt:: People talking about retarded shit (i guess everything reminds me of that)  Energy:: Nuclear  Flavor:: Grape popsicles (who knows)  Guess?:: Jeans worn by hot women... wasting money on jeans...  Accomplishment:: wasting your time trying  Prom:: the national science bowl (we went to washington dc to get our ass kicked by other nerds instead of prom... i dont regret it one bit either)  Diploma:: the fact that berkeley never sent me one.  i guess you are supposed to order it or something.  and its a good thing b/c i would be wiping my ass with it about now  Bloody:: dracula (and his son)    I found out about this game from the  urlLink excellent blog  by my good friend  urlLink busty wilde .
     
    


22,May,2004


	 
      hello world.
     
    


27,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Tall Boy&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hello Nasty&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    eh&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Palm trees ain't the only greenery in california&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    BOMB&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Bomb Tree&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


25,June,2004


	 
      I can't wait. I'm going tommorow @ 5:00.  The ultimate crazy adventure hell presidency becomes the ultimate movie.  Maybe this movie will incite a civil war between smart & stupid in america.  Unfortunately stupid is in charge of the army right now....
     
    


19,June,2004


	 
      in the country getting big and tall for me :)...  Yeah today i went out and checked the crop at my parents acreage.  OMFG.  I discovered huge patches of weed in places i thought i'd checked.  When i say huge patches i mean just that.  I mean probably 25-30 plants in each (there are 2) of the patches.  All 3 of the biggest patches are on the same hillside.  Im just hoping there is something left there and it has some buds in october.  God, I know you didnt come through on the billion $ or the lifetime supply of pussy, but please, please please let me have this bomb. and let it get me FUCKING HIGH AS SHIT baby...
     
    


18,June,2004


	 
      Inspired by the And1 mix tapes, a few friends and I have been thinking up streetball names for ourselves over the past couple of months.  Originally I dubbed myself  The Big Swig  based on my pop/beer drinking tendancies and a kwik shop employee having used the term to describe a pop i was buying.  Yesterday my friend came up with the name  Syxpho , which does look a lot like a homie or streetball name.  Why syxpho?  Because i'm 6'4" (actually 6'5") and I drink 64 (oz).  Hmmm... I could also choose  Afe  for my moniker, b/c i smoke an 8th.  Still leaning towards the big swig though...
     
    


17,June,2004


	 
       urlLink     urlLink Sorry but i felt the need to post this...& nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


16,June,2004


	 
      Bought a fridge pack of diet coke with lime today.   urlLink Here is your daily dose of f-bombs.   Boring day at work.  I'm thinking long and hard about law school now.  If I can find a way to afford it, I think it would be really good for me.  I could singlehandedly legalize it.  Maybe.  But it would be better than not trying, right...  Worked out today.  I'm trying to follow the HST style routine up on bb.com.  Full body work out 3 times a week.  So far so good, though i must say the back thing monday scared me...
     
    


14,June,2004


	 
      Hurt my back lifting tonight... Doesn't feel bad but it is in a place that has a history of acting up.  Hopefully i will still be able to ride tommorow and everything.    Went grocery shopping today.  Dont think i got everything interesting except an 8 pack of C2 which is a sweet size.  For those of you who dont know C2 is the half calorie coke...
     
    


13,June,2004


	 
      Long weekend.  Didn't do shit.  Baked some cookies on saturday which turned out well.  NBA finals are shaping up nicely.  Would be nice to see it end in a game 5 blow out of the LA flakers.  Work today was just pretty much unbearable.  pure boredom.  ugh.  I need a career...  why cant i figure out what i want to do (I'm pretty sure i can do what i want)  Not thinking about it for 2 hours... laundry & bongs...
     
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink     urlLink 'Young Merlin (was 'Mage Walk')'   SF&F Picture 33 out of 48 by Ken McCracken.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


12,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    blow up the moon&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    


12,June,2004


	 
      last night i dreamed that i was totally concerned b/c i was eating a triple cheeseburger & i rememeberd eating a double bacon cheese burger earlier in the day, and i thought "omg im out of control".  ha. 
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      Thinking of doing some baking tommorow.  Planning on it, actually.  I had the day off today, due to the passing on of Ronald McReagan.  Thanks for the good times Ronald.  A 3 day weekend never hurt anyone.  Pistons v Lakers - i'm enjoying this.  seeing phillip & the lakers lose in the finals would be incredible.  I heard pistons fan call his team the 'stones on jim rome the other day.  The detroit stoners & the florida marleys... what if...  managed to exercise today... i'm going for a long bike ride tommorow and maybe sunday too.  have to make up for all this beer im drinking today...   I wonder if i should go to law school before they put me in jail... seriously though i think i could be a good lawyer + my dad is a lawyer & it would be fun to argue with dumb people all day long...  but not as fun as smoking i guess...
     
    


10,June,2004


	 
      If you are looking for some good smelling hair products, I reccommend Redken For Men brand.  
     
    


09,June,2004


	 
       urlLink Dictionary.com/Word of the Day: braggadocio   Ok i don't really find the word braggadocio that interesting.  The reason this post exists is that i found out the google bar has a blogger button.  One click and you are posting a link to your blog.  Most of you probably know this already, but hot shit, i sure as hell didnt.  It looks like my dictionary bar installed correctly after all.  It just happens to NOT DEFAULT TO VISIBLE on the toolbar!  At least on my cpu.  So not only could i not tell whether it was installing, a less intelligent person than myself probably never would have realized that it actually installed.  Oh yeah I almost forgot.  The dictionary.com bar has a button that links to the word of the day: braggadocio...
     
    


08,June,2004


	 
      And im fucking happy.  B) thats me in some oakleys kicking it with a big ass grin.  thanks bw!  youre the best....
     
    


07,June,2004


	 
      But now there's proof....         urlLink What Famous Leader Are You?    urlLink personality tests by similarminds.com  


06,June,2004


	 
              Conscious self


04,June,2004


	 
                   INTP  - "Architect". Greatest precision in thought and language. Can readily discern contradictions and inconsistencies. The world exists primarily to be understood. 3.3% of total population.  


04,June,2004


	 
            urlLink What Classic Movie Are You?    urlLink personality tests by similarminds.com  


04,June,2004


	 
       urlLink if you didnt listen to rome today... 
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
      Cough cough... for some reason i keep coughing this morning ;)  Obviously can't work with a "cold" this bad...  Listening to Diamond Dogs by db.  How could anyone say this isn't one of his best albums?  holy shit...  Granted it's not hunky dory or ziggy but wtf is?  Diamond dogs is as good as low, alladin sane, and man who sold the world added together.  Ok its not.  But it's on par with any of those individually.  Let me address the songs:  1)  Future Legend  - Ok so he starts off on a pretty bad foot.  At the time this may have been the dorkiest thing ever put to tape... 2)  Diamond Dogs  - This ain't rock & roll!!!! This is GENOCIDE!!!!!!  Sorry can't fuck with that.  Not my favorite Bowie rocker (its no queen bitch).  Gets the job done easily since you are all pumped up from his intro. 3)  Sweet Thing  - I really really like this song.  Bowie's vocals are basically off the hook for the next 2 songs.   4)  Candidate  - Probably my favorite bowie song right now.  The lyrics on the last song were pretty good but they are out of this world for this song.  People probably weren't ready for this shit when it came out. 5)  Sweet Thing  (reprise) - 3 is not the magic number for this series of songs... Why?  Why does david rip off the only krautrock song anyone has ever heard?  I guess he is david bowie and he can do whatever the hell he wants.   6)  Rebel Rebel  - Bowie makes up for the knavery on the last song with a legendary song.  Too bad it makes me think of tommy hilfiger...  Dont you just love advertising? *puke* 7)  Rock N' Roll With Me  - I could see someone not liking this song.  I like it quite a bit.  "i would take a foxy kind of stand... while tens of thousands found me in demand" is a pretty good line at just the right part of the song... i actually always laugh when i hear that part... a damn fine song but it should rock a bit harder 8)  We are the Dead  - Great song.  I like it better than the songs afterwards.   9)  1984  - Has its fans.  I think it sounds like a theme song from a tv show.  Not a good one either. 10)  Big Brother  - I like this song.  The chorus seems oddly too familiar since i dont listen to this song much.   11)  Chang of the Ever-Circling Skeletal Family  - Embarassing song title.  This song rubs me the wrong way...  Wow i just listened to the whole cd.  Not much better to do when you're sick.
     
    


03,June,2004


	 
      Immediately after smoking a bowl, you can't get high as easily.  It has never stopped me from trying though.  Moderation & pacing is the key to becoming a successful stoner.  I sometimes speculate that computer games and online masturbation are pretty bad hobbies for developing these qualities.  Any kind of habitual computer use will probably do the same thing though.  So you're screwed too...  I have pretty much given up on the idea of ever quitting smoking.  No good reason to...  Alcohol, on the other hand, is slowly being phased out of my arsenal.    June is a strong contender for best month of the year.  You just can't fuck with the weather or the long sunny days...  Summer does, however, have the drawback of bringing out the worst in a lot of stupid people.  The hot weather & increased traction seems to give some people the idea that they need to be rowdy & dumb and under clothed.  That last one applies mainly to fat people, old people, and males who think they need to exercise their unfair, unequal & highly unnecessary right to walk around without a shirt.  Just suck it up and sweat it out in a shirt.  Please...
     
    


02,June,2004


	 
      How long has it been since i have been able to come home to a nice freshly packed bowl?  Alas!  Far too long.  Ahhh...  Weed is my ultradrug and my antidrug and my favorite hobby.  I honestly can't understand why someone capable of logic and reason would think weed shouldn't be legal.  For one thing its way worse than some of the stuff the government allows people to sell.  Alcohol, lottery tickets, diet coke, oil, video games, and about 2/3 of everything for sale at the supermarket right now are all more addictive and worse for you than weed.  Plus every religious nut job out there should be reasoning that God created a law that said people can use plants & animals as they see fit.  Hell, even vegetarians are ok with exploiting plants.  What the fuck man...  On the other hand, i personally have weed and access to any music i care to hear.  and a desk that needs cleaning but wont get it.  I strongly advise against voting for President Bush.  He is a fucker.  I won't be surprised if he legally changes his name to George W Freedom or George W America and declares the day before the election a federal holiday.  If he thought it would work, he would do it.  A scam.  That's all he amounts to.  It would be like me offering you $10 to let me write a bunch of bad checks off your checkbook.  I guess people would go for it.  I think I better go start Patriot Liberty Financial Services....
     
    


01,June,2004


	 
      If i drink heavily for 4 days in a row, why should i throw up in the middle of the night the morning after the day of the least heavy drinking?  In a way I'm glad.  I'll just consider it an opportunity at a fresh start to this month...
     
    


28,July,2004


	 
      3. !!! - Me and Giuliani Down by the School Yard (A True Story) (11:55) br 

23,July,2004


	 
      Yes, yes, y'all.  Friday after work and i have never been happier.  8 hours of work on 3 hours of sleep just never adds up to any kind of decent day.   Respectably productive today, but not sufficiently reproductive.       Still lacking any form of purpose.   I do have a goal though.  Problem is, i need to improve dramatically both financially and physically before i can accomplish it, and by then I might be too old.  I already am too fucking old.  oh well.  i guess i will keep on making the same old mistake.  not b/c i dont know any better, but because that seems to be how i work.  maybe someday i will be able to truly give up and start on a new goal.      Time to get high and sleep.  
     
    


05,July,2004


	 
      No, i'm not dead or incarcerated.  You can all go ahead and wipe the disapointed looks off of your faces.  Today i convinced my little brother to dump gasoline on and set ablaze a paper sack full of firecrackers.  It was pretty cool.  Interestingly, the firecrackers didn't all go off right away.  Some of them withstood a couple minutes in the blaze before they went off.  And some of them fizzed and flew off like bottle rockets.    I have attained a top 500 ranking on US East server of Warcraft 3.  I am losing a lot though, so i dont expect it to last.  I call my new strategy "Merlin's Incredible Dogs of War"  It doesn't work on Undead (or human or orc).    I haven't smoked any weed for over a week.  I wouldn't be surprised if I had already died from weed starvation, and I'm in some kind of bruce willis-esque sixth sense afterlife.  Not much else to report.  Magic Window, hit me in the back of the head!!!
     
    


08,August,2004


	 
      I'm just warning you right now to prep you up for tommorow 
     
    


05,August,2004


	 
      What a day. I guess work went okay. This hotel that we had a meeting at sent us some cookies, so I had something to eat other than carrots and chicken, which is all I've been bringing to work. I probably shouldn't have, but I never met a free cookie that i didnt like. They tasted good but didn't get me as high as the cookies I like.  Tommorow I get paid, so I will probably buy like a quarter or something.   I wish I could get a new bowl to smoke it in...   One troubling aspect of this world we live in is that you can't really trust anyone. If you let someone get to know you, and see what types of things you struggle with, you are just giving them something to use against you when they turn on you. They always turn on you. If you don't turn on them first, that is. I've had it happen to me and I hated it. I have done it to others, and I regret it. Take this fact to the bank: in all of your relationships with other people, either you or the other person is going to turn and try to say the most vile thing they can.  Usually, in my life, it has been me who turns on the other person. My roommate, let's call him Mumm-Ra, would be the perfect example. I can't even count on both hands the number of times in the past 10 years I have tried with all my will to break him with a cruel sentence. Usually he just tells me to stop being "assholian" and then we argue for a couple hours. It always concludes with us not being angry with each other though.  That's the sign of true friends I think. They always remain friends, even after one friend shanks the other friend right where they know its going to be most painful.   
     
    



