
28,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here's the queen of my world&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here is my friend Danika, she dresses up like characters from Willy Wonka in here spare time.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here's a view from the Schloss Mittersill in Mittersill, Austria&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here's my soon to be new ride&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here I Be&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
      So I'm talking to my beautiful girlfriend on the phone and she is a little skeptical about this whole blog thing.  I'm trying to assure her that I will only give out her full name and home address, not her social security number.  Honestly.  So tomorrow I get to clean several houses but then I'm off to kick it in Rochester.  My girlfriend (Kim) is house sitting and I'm going to go keep her company.  On Saturday we're going to her friend's wedding.  That should be sufficiently awkward...Hopefully we won't run into any undesirables.  I seem to run into old high school friends every day which is not a positive.  Anyways, I'll give you the wedding update when I get back.  Okay, I am off like a prom dress.  Peace. 
     

    


27,May,2004


	 
      Hey peeps, How exciting, I have a blog.  Apparently these are the new hip thing, or so Rich says.  So, I will put random stuff on here that nobody but myself will find amusing.  Enjoy!
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
      Heres the address for:  Lesley Brusven   www.lesleyb_26.blogspot.com Sally Hopper     www.sallysloveshack.blogspot.com
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    It's too bad you guys aren't as hot as the last group that was here :-(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
      I'm bored with blogs where people write paragraph upon paragraph of what they had for lunch, so I am going to post many pictures, with occasional thoughts.  Pictures are always more fun anyways, that's why magazines are so popular.  
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Ahh, We can't escape him ,even here.  Stupid Americans&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Is this jackass Matt Nowachek...or is it Jesus?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
      Rich, Stacy, April, Julie (3), Kim, Becky, Carrie, Bekah, Karen, Debbi, Kimmy, Bekah, Katie, Joelle, Danika, Sally, Mara, Anne, Trina, Jamie, Alyssa, Michelle, Lesley  Luckily you were here to see your name posted.  Be patient, I'm still working on pictures and home addressed.  
     

    


09,July,2004


	 
      Sorry guys, I am such a putz..I tottally forgot about this thing!  Ahh, I'm sure you're all dying to know whats going on in my life and I would love so very much to share...but I am running on 4 hours of sleep and I can no longer functions.  I WILL write soon!
     

    



