
30,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Koreans have an obsession with going to the bathroom, fart noises, and other such things. Their bathroom art reflects this. Pictured here is the bathroom specifically for (and ONLY for) really large bummed sexless robots who pee out of their bellybuttons.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    On Wednesday, I went hiking on a path near Bundang, and on Thursday, I went to Namhansansong Park with Jeanette and did more hiking. These are pictures of Wednesday, followed by Thursday later. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I was pleasantly surprised to find exercise equipment out in the middle of the path - a public service, I suppose!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This reminds me of a poem. I can't remember which one...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Oooh. The terrain becomes rocky!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Isn't it cool how the two leaves on either side are shaped differently because of the third leaf in the middle?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A colourful mushroom.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    When I got to the top of the mountain near Bundang, there was a single lily plant at the peak. It was pretty.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    More Buddhist prayer stones, seen on my Wednesday hike.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A view of only a small part of Seoul. The symmetry and identicalness of all the buildings is striking.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Check out the shag carpet on this caterpillar! Dude, the 70's are OVER!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A nifty mushroom on my solitary hike on Wednesday.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Don't ask... this hangs in Wa-Bar. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Dried chili peppers, by the BAGFULL! Despite the huge number, all the chilis are still dried traditionally in the sun - often in the parks and beside small rivers.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Here is a picture of Namhansansong Park - we started at the base (#1, left hand side) and walked up to the Great Wall, shown in blue. Then we continued around the wall for 2-3km and took a bus back down after seeing several temples.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The people in the park filled the rocky river, as it was a scorchingly hot day. A great day to go hiking up a huge mountain... crazy foreigners.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Buddhist prayer stones (so I'm told).&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Another temple at Namhansansong park.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This tree was completely covered in fungi.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    You can see part of the wall breaking the foliage in the distance. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    We went and saw what is called "The Great Wall of Korea". It's a 9km wall encircling the top of Namhansansong fortress in Namhansansong park, atop the mountain with the same name.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A passageway beneath the wall.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A Haiki: Golden Dragonfly, Perched on the steely barbed wire, Take my picture please.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A dragonfly that stayed on the barbedwire long enough for us to take its picture. Cool, huh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The forest covers the mountainside so perfectly, it looks like a carpet of greenery!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Isn't Korea beautiful?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A doorway in the wall.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    More Buddhist prayer stones.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Fungi, fungi, fungi!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A view of one of the various peaks of the wall. Jeanette, looking very intrepid.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Everything is so lush right now!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A group of Koreans taking a lunch break under the bridge. "Like a Bridge over Dining Koreans... I will lay me down!!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Korea - land of Nazism? Not at all. The Nazis took what is a traditional Buddhist symbol and flipped its design, making it the swastika. Those crazy nazis liked to do that - just think of the upside-down cross...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The Wolsan temples from afar. I would have liked to have taken pictures of the insides of the temple, but didn't out of respect for the holiness of the place!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Two temples, with the white stone monument in the background.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Check out the intricateness of the painting on the wood. It was beautiful.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The side of the roof. I love the architecture! Also notice the hanging bell - often, the bells have metal fish hanging from them. A very Buddhist symbol, I'm told.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A view looking down on the path that we climbed to get up to the temple. It was gruelling!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    One of the Wolsan (I think) temples in Namhansansong park&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Check out the dragon on the side of the temple! Cool stuff, man!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    In front of one of the Buddhist temples at Namhansansong park.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    At the temple site, there was this cool monolith. I'm not sure if there are them, but on the map, they were marked as "breast temples"...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This is probably the weirdest looking church I've ever seen...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Spices, veggies, meat, kitchen accessories, home funishings, clothes, you name it, you can find it at the Moran market we went to. It was amazing!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Bulbs of garlic (?) being sold in bulk at the Moran market.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


27,July,2004



       
      I am currently on a break from school. It's nice to have the time off, but the first of our only two real vacations in the year couldn't have come at a worse time. Having just got here, I have no money to spend to travel to somewhere nearby, like China, Japan, Thailand, or Australia. The other foreign teachers at our school who have been here for a while went to Australia. I'm jealous. Well, sorta. I have never really had a desire to see Australia all that badly. Seems like a&nbsp;fairly pretentious travel destination to me because it's where "all the parties are, man!".  Anyway, I'm hanging around in Bundang and the Seoul area. I spent last night playing Risk with Jeanette at a boardgame-bang - they have places where you can go pay to play boardgames - it's pretty cool. The night before, I went out with Charlie for Kalbi and then drinks. We had a good time socializing...  All in all, I've been spending a lot of time just hanging around, sleeping in, and resting. Tomorrow, I hope to go to the nearby mountains to do a little bit of hiking. Other things that have been suggested to me that I do: visit the DMZ, see the Salvador Dali exhibit at the Seoul Museum of Art, go see Dundaemun market (a huge open-air market in Seoul)... I think that I have a lot of stuff cut out for me to do, but I don't imagine I'll make it to many of those places. I am planning on going down to the south of Korea on Friday and Saturday with Jeanette and her friend.  To everyone back home: I miss you all and I wish you could come visit! Korea is great!  
     

    


24,July,2004



       
       urlLink    An interesting picture I took of an ant trying to take out a pretty beetle. Yay for my camera's super-macro mode!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Myself and Christina.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A profile shot of the spike. Oh, the looks I got! It was like we were superstars!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Ahh Korea, the land of the neon Jesus. Everywhere you look at night, you can find neon illuminated crucifixes in the skyline. Also seen here is the waxing moon. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    My neighbor has a bit of a sense of humour... this is taped to her apartment door.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    More duck. I guess it would be called Peking Duck, huh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A cool statue at the Olympic Park Museum&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    This is what a Korean duck looks like.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Yet another. :-)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Me and Heracles class at the Olympic Park.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The AFTER picture&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The BEFORE picture...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Mud, mud, and more mud!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I am Muku-Muku, the mud warrior!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Yikes! You could put out and eye with that thing! Kudos go out to Dawn Lahti for inspiring me on this... ask her about her green spike!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Christina showing off her mud mask and muscles!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Leslie looking somewhat like she just fell off the boat, no?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Observe the spectacular Mud golem in its natural habitat!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A photo of one of the bellydancers on the parade's float.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The parade had a marching band...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Crikey! Look at this shot of the rare and elusive Blue Boobie! A spectacular find, mate!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Christina with a whole convention of lifeguards...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    "Hey man, quit riding my ass!" or..."Wow, you have a small ass"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Pictured here is a frog we saw at our "hotel"... it was about the size of my pinky fingernail.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A restaurant we didn't go to. It was too expensive... but it sure was cool to look at!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The beach at Daechon... It was hot, packed, and more fun than an ocean full of asians! Riding the waves was so much fun.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Kids playing in the mud at the festival. This is the smaller version of a slide the adults got to use. It was a blast.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    The train ride back from the Mud festival. Trains sell sitting seats as well as standing. This train was hot and packed. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Christina REALLY had to go badly... quite the splash-back...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    I couldn't wait to find a bathroom, so I let loose here... check out the bottom right hand-corner of the screen to see what I'm talking about...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Fill Land! .... Have your fill of fun?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Everyone here drives a motorcycle. Even the statues... pictured here. Don't ask me why it's wearing two... I guess it's for extra protection for the wild lifestyle a statue leads...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A truckload of Korean infantry holding down the fort...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    A sign on a public washroom. Graphic, no?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    "Welcome to the Beonyeong Mud Festival - get down and get Dirty" (or something like that)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Pictures of our train ride to Daechon, the site of the mud festival. It was beautiful.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    On the train to Daechon, the site of the Mud festival. Most of Seoul and area is nothing but buildings, so all this was a refreshing sight.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    .&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    On our way to the mud festival. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Christina on the right and Kelly on the left.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


21,July,2004



       
       urlLink    Charlie, a foreign teacher, and his Korean girlfriend, Daemi. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    


13,August,2004



       
      I came to a sudden realization today while I was walking down the street, which rather startled me... there seems to be a LOT of asian people here... I wonder why... 
     

    



