
09,July,2004


     
       urlLink The Grim Ripper - an awesome bit-o-kit! 
     
    


08,July,2004


     
       urlLink Arse I am - wicked flash stuff 
     
    


08,July,2004


     
       urlLink LEGO.com Mindstorms Home - cos lego blocks... sorry - lego rocks! 
     
    


08,July,2004


     
       urlLink aussiefrogs.com - French Car enthusiasts site for Australia - Citroen Peugeot Renault - aussiefrogs.com & Froggy Forum! 
     
    


08,July,2004


     
      I know you're sitting there with that awful feeling right now of   "hmmm, something is wrong... I just dont feel right... I've forgotten something"  Its ok tho, you can be excused, its not your fault. Its mine. You're right...  There was no Haiku yesterday! You can be excused for feeling a little green around the gills after all, whats life without haiku (not really much diffferent when youre referring to my haikus i guess). Thats why today, im starting a call to action, im gonna get the people who opened my eyes to the wonderful world of haiku to start helping me out.  I bet they ignore me tho...
     
    


08,July,2004


     
      Its not fair at all, i think i must be cursed...  Why is it that every time I buy something, within 2 or 3 weeks I see the same thing for sale at a hugely discounted price??  Its just not fair!  The current object of frustration is a Lego set of all things! They have the most amazing set available at the moment, a fully functional backhoe which uses pneumatics to run everything (using 2 air pumps, 7 switches and 10 air rams no less!), which I got for my birthday a couple of weeks ago (thanks Manda!).  3 weeks later, the same kit is now at 80% of the price we got it for!  (get to k-mart asap all you australian lego fans out there!! its well worth it. The most involved and invoving kit ive built from Lego!)  ah well..  just have to go buy another one! 
     
    


07,July,2004


     
      no haiku today im not very good at it you slackers dont help 
     
    


06,July,2004


     
      oooooh...  day 3.  If only i didnt have to stand around for half an hour waiting to see someone this morning, im sure id still be ok.  im just a little bit restless.  hmmm.  coffee.  thatl get me by.  mmmmmmcofffeeeee... 
     
    


06,July,2004


     
      today i told you all that i have a new blog. now YOU write haiku! 
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      today is day 2.  of attempt 6.  for quitting smoking this year.  Yesterday was fine, didnt think about it. Today I fear I may be a little pre-occupied...  its 10 o'clock and all I can think of is smoking.  I just hope the poor car-crash victim who benefits from my body being disassembled for recycling appreciates this... 
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      dont you? 
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      dont know what i did i probably never will. leaves me cold inside 
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      its funny isnt it... when youre at work, all you can think of is going home, being on holidays, or just being elsewhere. I just took a holiday last week for my birthday (sometimes its nice to have some time to get over your birthday party weekend :) and by the end of the week, i was actually looking forward to coming back to work.  It's now monday, 11.30 am, im back at work. Geeze i wish i was somewhere else!  lucky i heard about blogger.com huh!?
     
    


05,July,2004


     
      Sometimes i really just dont understand.  Sometimes people do strange things, with no obvious rhyme nor reason.  To these people i ask...  y 4 u do this 1??  its a simple question really.  just wish i knew the answer.
     
    



