
27,July,2004



       
      [14:07] ~YuffieStr

26,July,2004



       
      [12:33] ~Richardandre

24,July,2004



       
      Our feelings.. such a complicated thing... is this a dream? is love some sort of enticing spell cast by a person? I don't know, and I don't think I will ever find out. But if such thing exists..let me live it. Let me live it till my heart dwells in happiness and comfort. Let me be until my soul can not take it any longer. Let me taste it until my lips get numb.. and let me feel it like if there is no tomorrow. Cause, my friends, such is the dream or a loner like myself. Because I don't want to be cold anymore. Because I don't want to live in the darkness again...  Yup, this has been my Poetry Fit. Heh
     

    


23,July,2004



       
       I'm an outcast. I am the scum of the earth. A threat to common religion. A threat to the world. But guess what. I rather be hated for who I am, than to be loved for someone I'm not. Indeed, such is the path I have to explore in my current life...or is it phase? 
     

    


23,July,2004



       
      Cannadian

22,July,2004



       
      My family is catholic, and my mom is a religious person. I used to be a catholic myself, until I decided to 'quit' due to what I saw in the Church... just a bunch of hypocrites, so... that's why I decided to quit, among other things...  Anyways, in the Catholic faith, most people have images of Jesus, or saints... and when I was a kid, my mom put this image of what is called "The Sacred Family" which is, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.  And so, since I don't believe in that anymore, I thought that if I left it there, i would be a hypocrite... and so, I removed it from the wall, and put it in a drawer in my room.  A few days later, my mom asked me where did the image was, and I replied it was in the drawer. And she got mad at me, and told me: "As long as you live in this house, you're gonna leave that image there." and I replied that it was my room and that I didn't believe in all that anymore, but she said she didn't care. But as soon as she put it on the wall again and she left, I removed it again.  The next day, she gave me a Jehova's Witnesses publication so I could read it!! I mean... holy f*ck...why the hell is she doing that?! Why can't she respect my damn decisions about my own ideas, my concepts, my beliefs?!  This is really f*cked up... 
     

    


21,July,2004



       
      So like yeah... Last Sunday, I bought a musical instrument. No, not a guitar, or drums. I don't have enough money to spare... but I bought a tin whistle. Yup, a tin whistle :P And so I'm trying to learn how to play it. Funny thing is, that the dogs bark really loud each time I practice with it, so... I don't really know if that's a good sign or a bad sign.   Bwahahahahaha.  Okay so, anyways, I found out a friend of mine is going to Canada with her sister. Damn, I so wish I was in her place... but oh well, her parents are gonna pay for it :P.   Anyways, 2 days ago I went to this job interview.  It terribly sucked ass.  Why? Because I thought that I was probably ready to take this kind of job, but.. I just realized that I'm not ready yet. Supposedly I'm a graphic designer, but now... I'm thinking that I'm not that good.  I just hope my destiny shines a little bit, and lets me accomplish what I have in mind...
     

    


07,July,2004



       
       Okay... so like the name of this posts suggests, my day today was a total piece of $h!t. I was talking to this person on MSN, and...he got mad at me for certain reasons, and his reply to my statements were: "that's just f*cking bullshit." Really, why some people just don't listen? Do they have like a big piece of cardboard in their mind? Or are they just a bunch of airheads? Or the 2 together? Damn, I don't know. All that I know is that my life is really screwed up, and at this very f*cking moment I wish I was dead. 
     

    


06,July,2004



       
      Today, after I came out of work, I came home. I went to the kitchen... and my mom didn't make food, so.. I decided to get japanese food. And then, I called Teriyaki San, which happens to be a local Japanese Restaurant...and they told me that the delivery service was not available.   Meh.  So, I had to get in the car, and drive to the damn restaurant. I arrived, and I had to wait for 30 minutes for the food to get done.  And then, when I came back home, I had a sushi orgy. O_o  I ate a lot of sushi rolls... fried salmon skin sushi rolls :P~ Of course because of this, I don't have any money left till saturday... but it was worth the time and the price I payed.  Sushi will take over the world, baby! Hellll yeah! XD
     

    


05,July,2004



       
       Right now as I write this, I'm chatting on IRC and really... how come some people can be so stupid, and ask something like: "Where are you from?" and when you say "I don't want to tell", they get all upset and crap... and they still act like if they loved you or worshipped you or something... damn, all this kind of thing makes me wish sometimes I was not a member of the human race. XD 
     

    


13,August,2004



       
       So like yeah... this time my nick was Rakka, and, looks like someone was looking for me.. haha   [23:04] * Joins: ddddddddd (~ddddddddd@219.95.219.194) [23:04] ~NIEL13


