
29,July,2004


	 
      I remember feeling so hopeful after I pushed the 'send' button on the fax machine yesterday .... faxing 7 pages to a Recruitment agency... I had an interview last Friday.  I called today to touch base and arranged for them to contact my referees. They have not. My heart sank....  I suppose, I will have to keep my options open....  On a brighter note, I've been talking to my significant other's little brother........ very smart and giggly lil' fella. Just like the brother.. ;-) 
     

    


27,July,2004


	 
      It has been quite a while since I have been seriously looking for a job. I already have a job and perhaps getting a bit too used to the fact (or fiction) that I have been getting mountains of rejection emails and letters because I am not yet a permanent resident. But fret not, the only delay to application --

04,August,2004


	 
       Where You Are - Jessica Simpson &amp; Nick Lachey     There are times I swear I know you're here When I forget about my fears Feeling you my dear Watchin over me And my hope seeks What the future will bring When you wrap me in your wings And take me:  [Chorus]  Where you are Where you and I will breathe together Once again We'll be dancing in the moonlight Just like we used to do And you'll be smilin back at me Only then will I be free When I can be Where you are  And I can see your face Your kiss I still can taste Not a memory erased Oh, I see your star Shining down on me And I'd do anything If I could just Be right there:  [CHORUS]  Then I will be free So take me where you are  Now baby there were times when selfishly I'm wishing that you are here with me So I can wipe the tears away from your eyes And make you see That every night while you are dreamin I'm here to guard you from a far And anytime I feel alone I close my eyes and just be there:  Where you are Where you and I can breathe together (and we will breathe together baby) Once again (oh, we'll be dancing in the moonlight) We'll be dancin in the moonlight Just like we used to be And you'll be smilin back at me (only then will I be free) Then I will be free Baby I still believe Oh I've got to believe I will touch you that sweet day That you take me there Where you are I still believe Oh I've got to believe I will touch you that sweet day That you take me there Where you are Oh where you are I 've got to believe I'll always be waiting here That sweet day yeah Only wanna be where you are  I still believe.....
     

    


02,August,2004


	 
      Called the consulate in Canberra this morning... Apparently my police clearance "has not yet been approved". Reason being she received it on the the 30/04/04 and she already submitted the whole sack of application on the 28/04/04 (I seriously remember mailing it to her on 19/04/04). Anyway, because of the 2 days delay, my application was sent out on 28/05/04 and to complete the extra 3 months waiting period.... surprise.. surprise, it'll be ready on 28/08/04. So, by the time I receive the A4 paper stating that I'm a good citizen, 4 months would have passed... Now, I feel like jumping off the cliff..... seriously, I dont even have a traffic offence under my name.... 
     

    



