
20,August,2004


     
       I really want visitors on my website, however I won't post the link. I will say that it is in my profile and ask that you please visit though. ;-)  
     
    


19,August,2004


     
        If you were here I'd never have a fear. So go on live your life. But I miss you more than I did yesterday.  You're beautiful  Well I'm a total wreck and almost every day. Like the firing squad or the mess you made. Well don't I look pretty walking down the street. In the best damn dress I own?  If you were here I'd never have a fear. So go on live your life. But I miss you more than I did yesterday. You're so far away. So c'mon show me how. 'Cause I mean this more than words can ever say.  Some might say we are made from the sharpest things you say We are young and we don't care. Your dreams and your hopeless hair. We never wanted it to be this way. For all our lives. Do you care at all?  If you were here I'd never have a fear. So go on live your life. But I miss you more than I did yesterday. You're so far away. So c'mon show me how. 'Cause I mean this more than words can ever say.  


18,August,2004


     
       I am sure there is some sick bastard out there able to track me down. If you ever see me walking out of my house I want you to shoot me dead, as many times as it takes.  
     
    


17,August,2004


     
       Maybe I just need to do anything and everything no matter how much it goes against my beliefs and values to survive. I'll go away and surround myself with a million friends, all guys of course. And forget about whomever was in my life before.       I'll never look back.  
     
    


16,August,2004


     
       I just wish there was some meaning to my life, some purpose for even being here.  
     
    


10,August,2004


     
       I would very much like to cut out my ovaries and sew my vagina shut.  
     
    


10,August,2004


     
        I want to see garden state and constantine.      Tony said good things about garden state. Plus I seem to have an obsession with jersey I only partially understand, and am curious about the guy from scrubs creating the whole thing and all..   
     
    


09,August,2004


     
       This is turning out to be  the month from HELL !  
     
    


07,August,2004


     
         NO MORE JUNK FOOD OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER AND ONLY DRINKING WATER.               the end    
     
    


03,August,2004


     
       I fucking  hate  men  
     
    


03,August,2004


     
       I don't know what the fuck I'm doing anymore. Just a warning. I won't post much, and I won't say much when I do. 
     
    



