
22,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      I used this picture of a White Bengal Tiger for reference. Isn't he beautiful? 


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      We start here with a blob of paint. I used acrylic paint for the stripes.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Dip brush in water.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Dip wet brush in paint.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Clear away excess paint if there's too much on the brush.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Make sure that the paint is just right. Not too thick or thin.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Draw in the outines for the stripes.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Color the stripes


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Simple stripe done.


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      There an example. More pictures  urlLink here .


20,August,2004


	 
        urlLink        Grrrr....    Finally onto the camouflage, adding in the tiger stripes. This will take longer than I expected as it took me one whole night of painting just to finish the head unit. I think it would take longer if I intend to mask and airbrush.      


18,August,2004


	 
      More updates and progress on my  urlLink model.  Some pictures are posted below. 
    


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      I have the power in the grasp of my hand!


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Eck! A "mouse"!


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Near Monitor.


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Where the hell is my leg!?


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      "A penny for the crippled?"


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink     One more leg to go.


13,August,2004


	 
        urlLink     Kampfer bust.  What i've managed to come up with so far. More pictures below and  urlLink here . 
    


11,August,2004


	 
        urlLink     Shoulder  Pre-shaded the left shoulder. Damage on shoulder is done using a routing tool. 
    


11,August,2004


	 
        urlLink     Kampfer Head 
    


11,August,2004


	 
        urlLink     Chest armor half done using pre-shading method. Pre-shading means painting on the shadows first, I used dark grey as a pre-shade coat. Lastly, off white is painted in gradually to achieve the effect desired. 


11,August,2004


	 
        urlLink      Kampfer Bust


11,August,2004


	 
        urlLink        MS-18E Kampfer     My current project at the moment, painting the above mobile suit known commonly as the "Kampfer" or translated "Champion" or "Fighter" in german. More information about the suit can be found  urlLink here  . 


11,August,2004


	 
      An exaggerated sms message i received one day:  "Oh!!! Luk at mi!!! Mi iz very guds at wrting shrthand. Mi tink iz so KuTe tat it wil impress the boyz wif tis kind of shrthand sms msg.  "OOoooOOOh Oh Oh!!! Lotsa luv and mi miz U 2....!!" ^_^  Can you understand such crap? Makes you wonder why we spend a quarter of our life in school. I used to think that spelling was such a waste of time, well it looks that way now does it? 
    


11,August,2004


	 
        I wonder how many people realize that once a person comes out from his or her mother's vagina, we inherently have our ass owned. Like bulls being tagged with a scorching iron label showing that it belongs to a cattle owner, likewise, we have this invisible "I own your ass" label tagged on us.  


11,August,2004


	 
      I guess i've got to start somewhere, there my very first post. 
    



