
11,August,2004


						
						    se路di路tion:  Conduct or language inciting rebellion against the authority of a state. __________________________________________   War Now - Right Now - Open Up Your Eyes!    MBR's Morning Sedition - 11 August 2004   It's a somber day in my heart, yall.   While the Southland around me lies in moral and cultural ruins, while my co-workers babble on (babyl-on) about Big Brother and the rest of the TV shows they killed brain cells consuming last night, and while the men we entrust to report the news stories that DIRECTLY EFFECT our lives sit around and jabberjaw about who knows what in their little editorial columns, I am distraught.  It is my firm belief that the American Empire has lead the world into a time of war like none we have ever known beofre.   I believe that the American Empire will continue to take our sons and daughters from our homes, our farms, our families, until there is no American man left to toss into the bone-grinding war machine of profit and empire.  I am not a conspiricist. Contrary to popular opinion, I am not a member of the "lunatic fringe" of doomsday prophets and the like. I am an optomist - a Chirstina Southern Husband and Father with a dream to restore his homeland to a peaceful and God-fearing land of prosperity. But all around me, I see the signs.  _________   urlLink  Draft Riots Feared!    "No Matter Who Wins in November, Draft Will Return"  By Mike Blair    http://www.americanfreepress.net/html/draft_riots_feared.html _______  Mike Blair isnt the only one looking at the draft being reinstated - there are Two Bills Now Pending Before Congress To Bring Back The Draft:   H. R. 163  : To provide for the common defense by requiring that all young persons in the United States, including women, perform a period of military service or a period of civilian service in furtherance of the national defense and homeland security, and for other purposes.    urlLink "

11,August,2004


						
						    se路di路tion:  Conduct or language inciting rebellion against the authority of a state. __________________________________________  Yall, I'm starting to see a trend developing.   I get to work in the morning, take care of my immediate responsibilities, and set into reading the news for the day. It's a sort of Daily Journal Staff Ritual, just short of a policy. They want us salesfolk to stay up on the news, I suppose, since we are a newspaper and all. So, while my co-workers are looking through today's paper, I'm running through the Dixienet.org news page, Dave Black Online, DixieInternetCo, the Drudge Report, WorldNet Daily, Freedom Watch, and a good dozen other like-minded news sites to see what's really goin' on in the world around us.   Most every morning, I see things that I want to share with my folks out here in email land, (aka: yall) and I've taken to sending it out as a blanket email with links to the more important news stories along with whatever little update on the Constitution Party of Mississippi, (CPoM) or the Upper Mississippi League of the South (UMLoS ) I have to share for that day. I enjoy doing this, and I hope yall enjoy gettin' em. I've even come up with a semi-pompous name for it - MBR's Morning Sedition, using my initials to make a pun on  urlLink  NPR's Morning Edition  - that early-morning, soft-voiced liberal noise pollution on Public Radio.   Just about everybody on my email list is getting this email right now. However, I know there are those on this list that dont feel like getting this email from me on a semi-daily basis is a good thing , and yall break down into basically 3 catagories: 1.)"I love ya Matt, but you can stick that UMLoS and CPoM stuff where the sun dont shine" folks, 2.) "I dont care about news and I'm sick of you trying to tell me about it" people, and 3.) I already go to the LoS Dixienet.org news page, Dave Black Online, DixieInternetCo, the Drudge Report, WorldNet Daily, Freedom Watch, etc. and it's redundant for you to be sending me this" folks. If you fall into one of the above catagories, reply to this email with "unsubscribeMBR" as the subject and I'll make sure to pull you from the email list - no hard feelings.   For the rest of you, welcome to the beginnings of the UMLoS / CPoM listserver. Now here's the news that ya aint gonna git nowherred else 'cept fer rat cheeyunh.  _________________________________   News Links:      Bush's Own Gettysburg Demise is Coming: The State of Pennsylvania on November 2nd   -  Pastor Mark Dankof   http://www.dixieinternet.com/page222.shtml      Home Schooling Grows, Federal Bureaucrats Worry  -  Al Benson Jr.  http://www.dixieinternet.com/page230.shtml  Now I want yall to listen: Ronnie Brandon has been saying it for a long time now - they aint gonna let us teach our own kids for much longer without some kinda fight. - MBR      Keyes: Obama holds 'slaveholder's' view  -  AP Wire  http://www.suntimes.com/output/news/keyes09.html God bless Alan Keyes as he attempts to knock " Osama" Obama and his his multicultural relitivism out of the national lovefest limelight! - MBR      Politically Incorrect and Proud  -  Offending with the Truth  http://michnews.com/artman/publish/article_4611.shtml "Have I now become your enemy by telling you the truth?"  Galatians 4:16  - MBR      Drunk Man Pulls Cop Over, Asks To Be Arrested  http://www.wftv.com/news/3636873/detail.html Now that boy had done got toe up from the flo' up.  Wait - is that Ted Kennedy? -MBR      Where have all the Southern men gone?  http://www.militarycity.com/valor/honor.html  They're dead.    As always, over 2/3 of  the Empire's troops are from the Deep South. I pray in the Name of Jesus that we never see our children on this site. - MBR    11 He said, " This will be the procedure of the king who will reign over you: he will take your sons and place them for himself in his chariots and among his horsemen and they will run before his chariots. 12 " He will appoint for himself commanders of thousands and of fifties, and some to do1 his plowing and to reap his harvest and to make his weapons of war and equipment for his chariots. 13 "He will also take your daughters..."   1 Samuel 8:11-13a      _____________________________   Southerners For Peroutka Update:   As we speak, somewhere deep in the Mississippi pine holler, hundreds of huge 2' x 4' Southerners for Peroutka signs are being made. These things are gonna be visible from a mile away, and when Good Ole Boys see the giant Confederate Battleflag ebossed on 'em as theyre driving down the road, folks are liable to jump a durn mailbox. Not since the Duke Boys roof has anyone in the mainstream so endorsed and revered the St. Andrews Cross, and we look forward to many a new voter gettin' behind Michael Anthony Peroutka when they realise the sheer yamsack it takes to run for President waving a "rebel" flag. Here's a Wallace-esque graphic I did last week for yall to link to, save, or do whatever you see fit to further the Peroutka Campaign.      Constitution Party of Mississippi Update:  http://www.constitutionpartyms.com Our Old-Fashioned Southern BBQ and Political Rally this past Sunday was an absolute success, and people are STILL fired up from it state-wide. Watch the CPoM site (http://www.ConstitutionPartyMS.com) for pictures, more info, and how YOU can get the next best thing to being there again:  the day's speeches on CD! Check it out tomorrow for the info.    I noticed when I got back to work on Monday and looked at my little desk calander from the Freedom Forum, Saturday the 7th's quote was purty dead on.   "It is but a short step from the banning of offending symbols such as burning crosses or burning flags to the banning of offending words." - Rodney M SMolla, constitutional scholar, 2002   Upper Mississippi League of the South:   I am in the process of having business cards and small, professional-looking info cards made for the purpose of giving to all the men I see wearing or displaying the Confederate flag on their teeshirts, cars, tattoos, etc. This is from a brainstormin' session me and Ronnie had one night about how to reach all the "Dixie Outfitters" crowd for the League, and I encourage each of you to do the same. (Let's get together on the actual copy and design of the cards so that we can avoid contradiction and maintain a certain stylistic approach.)  I think these will be an invaluable recruitment tool for us in a part of Dixie where Proud Southrons are ripe for the pickin', but bear in mind we will have to be prayerfully discerning when approaching folks. Keep in mind, the average Joe Six-Pack with a half-nekkid woman and the words "By Gawd I'm a Rebel" on his teeshirt and the "Let's get a rope" guy with a white sheet sticking out of his trunk are likely not going to fit the description of the morally strong, honourable Christian Southerner that we want to build the League with. Yall smell what I'm steppin' in?  Contact me about the card idea and let's get these thangs made. ___________________   See yall tammary -   -   Matthew B. Robinson   Lee County Chairman, Constitution Party of Mississippi    "It is impossible to mentally or socially enslave a Bible reading people."     the Constitution Party of Mississippi http://www.ConstitutionPartyMS.com  

						



