
23,August,2004


	 
      Just uploading some pictures now that I finally got my computer working right again. I've promised them to some people and I'm trying to make good on that. Right now it's focusing on where we live and our QRF (Quick Reactionary Force). I have some more pictures of conditions outside the wire and of the people and college but I have to get them cut down in size first. I'm also trying to get Professor Ali (mentioned in the article below) to be able to write up a small article about his experiences when he was back in the States. Hope you enjoy.     This is probably the highlight of people's time in Iraq. It means they are going home on leave for 15 days. Probably one of the only times we don't mind waiting around in the sound.     This is a collection of trucks that our QRF uses. As you can see they are all mostly cargo vehicles that have been heavily modified with 1/2 thick steel plating. Since the Army didn't seem it neccesary at the time we moved into Baghdad to think that all vehicles would need some armor protection our welders did it themselves. The LMTV (big truck =) ) has over 2 tons of steel added to it. While its not perfect its better than nothing.  The vehicle to the right is a M1114. Its the standard patrol vehicle for our Brigade in Baghdad. Once you put a .50 machine gun on top its not something you want to mess with. Too bad we only have one.     This is one of our QRF teams waiting to be called out. While not overly active on combat patrols they do provide a pretty damn important job of escorting our of our officers outside the wire and help a lot with getting the goodwill projects done around here. We couldn't do it without them. For reference there are 18 people on the team.     Finally is a small view of our lifestyle. I think there are close to 3000 of these trailers on Victory. This place is huge. We recently got blast protection in the form of these HESCO barriers. Its a nice touch about 6 months too late.  Thanks for looking today. Hope to get some more up soon when I'm not so busy. Good luck to everyone. 
    


19,August,2004


	 
      Sorry I haven't been around much recently but I have been really busy and working quite long hours. Everything here unfortently seems like things are heating up a bit. The frequency of attacks against US forces is increasing and I hope this isn't a sign of stuff that will be coming soon.  On a slightly different note I know I promised some more pictures to some people and I hope to be able to fulfill that request within the next day or so. The internet has been crawling over here and I have barely been able to even browse the web much less upload any pictures. So hopefully that will happen here soon.  Our commander is currently stuck in Jordan and on his way back from the States. Following is a somewhat long a

16,August,2004


	 
      Sorry I haven't been around much recently but I have been really busy and working quite long hours. Everything here unfortently seems like things are heating up a bit. The frequency of attacks against US forces is increasing and I hope this isn't a sign of stuff that will be coming soon.  On a slightly different note I know I promised some more pictures to some people and I hope to be able to fulfill that request within the next day or so. The internet has been crawling over here and I have barely been able to even browse the web much less upload any pictures. So hopefully that will happen here soon.  Our commander is currently stuck in Jordan and on his way back from the States. Following is a somewhat long article that was published in the Killeen Daily Herald. From what I've gathered they have done a pretty good job on it with very few mistakes. As always I welcome any comments or criticism. Thanks for your time.      By Debbie Stevenson   Killeen Daily Herald   FORT HOOD — Iraqi veterinarians from the University of Baghdad were given a warm Texas welcome by the family of a U.S. officer who has been helping to coordinate the restoration of the campus' veterinary college.  Penny McCarver and the couple's twin daughters, Christina and Anna, entertained Dr. Majid Injidi, the veterinary college's dean; Dr. Majid Nassir, the assistant dean; and Dr. Ali Abrahim, a veterinary surgeon.  The three were wrapping up a week's stay in Texas to visit the veterinary school at Texas A&M University, courtesy of McCarver's husband, Lt. Col. Bill McCarver, who is commanding the 15th Forward Support Battalion in Iraq.  "It's been several months in the making," McCarver said of the Iraqis' trip. "We've been trying to get it to happen since July."  McCarver said she and her daughters were excited to finally meet the Iraqis who have been working so closely with her husband since he left in January to spend a year in Iraq. Also present for Saturday's three-hour visit on Fort Hood were Bill's parents, Mildred and Ray McCarver from Alabama.   Smiles and warmth   For Abrahim, a veterinary surgeon and professor, the weeklong trip to College Station and Fort Hood was his first outside of Iraq."I'm impressed, very impressed," said Abrahim, in fluent English, as he relaxed on the sofa in the McCarvers' Fort Hood quarters.  Abrahim said the journey to Texas from the Iraqi war-torn capital was more than a lesson in the latest veterinary science. It was his first venture out of Baghdad and his first sampling of a different culture."The way of living here is totally different than the way in Iraq, different from all the Arab countries," said Abrahim. "The people here trust. They always have a smile, say 'hello' and are very kind."  Abrahim said he and his colleagues do not have passports, but were able to travel to the United States courtesy of visas obtained with the help of McCarver and the 1st Cavalry Division.With the backing of the 1st Cavalry, the application process was pushed quickly through channels, and the three eventually boarded a plane with Capt. Lawrence Camacho, commander for the battalion's Delta Company and their escort for the Texas tour.   Flying first to Jordan and Egypt before catching a flight to New York, Abrahim said the Iraqis' reception by their fellow Arabs was cold and difficult, especially as the three were traveling without passports."In Egypt, they kept us in the transit area because we don't have passports," Abrahim said. "Captain Camacho, he did a wonderful job of making sure everything was OK for us."  From the moment he set foot in New York's Kennedy Airport, Abrahim knew he was in for a very different experience."Our previous regime, when you entered an airport, you are always afraid of talking, even whispering. You always have to be searched," he said. "In New York, they smiled, said 'please' and apologized for a computer delay. The people in Washington's airport just waved us on."This is the difference between the Arabs and all the Western countries," Abrahim said.  Injidi said he had been stuck by their welcome once in Texas."Here the life really is a big difference from Iraq," he said. "The first thing I noticed was the people look very kind people. They say to you hello everywhere, in restaurants, hotels, you find smiles on their faces.Enjoying the ability to roam without fear, Injidi said he was struck by the cleanliness of the Texas cities he had visited and the stocked shelves of the stores."Everything is available in the market, in the shops," said Injidi, adding that he hopes Iraq will eventually find similar peace and prosperity."  The quiet life, that's all we are missing in Iraq right now," he said.   Elite campus   The 1st Cavalry's goal since it linked up with the professors has been to rebuild their veterinary clinic, which fell victim to the looting that followed the U.S.-led invasion of Baghdad in March 2003, Camacho said.The Texas trip, he said, was key to realizing that goal.  With 19 projects and another four big ones under way to repair and upgrade the college's facilities, Camacho said the soldiers knew their limitations. They could rebuild the facilities, find the equipment, get the supplies, but there would remain one key piece missing for the campus' success."The one thing we could not help them do is fix their curriculum that is 30 years behind because Saddam had stopped the flow of information," said Camacho, about the three-decade rule of ousted Iraqi dictator Saddam Hussein.   That was when McCarver approached Brig. Gen. Jeffrey Hammond, the division's assistant commander, about the possibility of linking the Iraqis with Texas A&amp;M, a college renown for its cutting-edge veterinary campus.   Hammond quickly agreed. Plans were quickly set in motion."It took the division five weeks to get the visas; it is usually a five-month process," Camacho said.With the hiccups and a few minor delays behind them, the A&M staffers officially welcomed their Iraqi counterparts to their campus last week, offering them more insight than Camacho dared hope for."Texas A&amp;M is all about helping them," he said. "I didn't expect that.  Finally able to see the university's famed large-animal clinic for themselves, Abrahim, Nassir and Injidi absorbed the scene."Dr. Majid, the dean, he had open heart surgery a few months ago," Abrahim said. "When we saw the large animal clinic at Texas A&amp;M, the machines there are more advanced than in Jordan where he had the open heart surgery."  For Injidi, the Texas tour was an important step toward realizing his goal of ensuring his Baghdad college is restored and advanced before he retires, Camacho said.  For Nassir, the information gleaned from the Texas equine staff will help keep healthy an important symbol for his country.  "The symbol of our culture is the horse," Nassir said. "I think they are the most beautiful animal in the world."  Alert and intense as he spoke of the Iraq's purebred Arabians, Nassir said the Iraq once led the Arab world with its bloodlines and fiercely protected their integrity by refusing to allow imported lines while willingly exporting their top stock. That was before Saddam, said Nassir, noting the country's equine industry quickly joined a growing list of Iraqi interests that suffered under the Baath Party rule."  The last years, the horses of Iraq have been held back because there was no way to bring them out to have a better evaluation," Nassir said.With Saddam gone, Nassir said he hopes the Iraqi Arabian will once again compete outside of Iraq. He was quick to quiz anyone who may possess even the slightest knowledge of the industry outside Iraq.  Once back in Baghdad, Abrahim said he hopes to be able to apply the information he has learned, teaching his students how to properly care for animals that pass through the college, including horses, sheep, cattle, dogs, cats and goats."They are very important," he said of the livestock. "They provide the meat."   Model program   The Baghdad university partnership with McCarver's battalion has become a model for the 1st Cavalry's rebuilding efforts in Baghdad, Camacho said.It also was one of the division's first endeavors, beginning shortly after the battalion's arrival in January.  Scouting their new sector, the Fort Hood soldiers quickly found the veterinary college, which still had not recovered from the postwar looting."The previous command never asked for input," Camacho said. "We were determined we were not going to make the same mistake."  Camacho said the soldiers had the Iraqis list the problems and repairs, which were then taken to the battalion and brigade commanders."We were asking them what they need instead of doing what we think they need," Camacho said.  Abrahim said the Iraqis dubiously complied, wondering if it would be another fruitless task.Before long, Camacho said the unit returned, this time armed with $2 million to begin a restoration project based on the Iraqis' suggestions and using Iraqi contractors and Iraqi labor.  Three months later after the 1st Cavalry completed its arrival in Baghdad, Camacho said Maj. Gen. Pete Chiarelli, the division's commander, was pleased with what he saw."  He said the college was his standard for all other projects," Camacho said. "That made us proud."Based on the success of the veterinary college, McCarver has since assigned another company to work with the university's agriculture campus.  Similar rebuilding is under way, Camacho said. A trip to Kansas State University's agriculture campus also was planned for this week.          
    


16,August,2004


	 
      Sometimes I wonder about how things are really going and if what we are doing here is even worth it. Most of the times I can push this away pretty quickly. A large factor in this is the failure of any major news network to be able to report accurately on what is going on over here. Everything you see is always negative. For example yesterday the headlines in Stars and Stripes was "Explosion Rocks Baghdad". I would love for once a syndicated news channel or paper to put something good on here. I know there are more than enough examples of what is happening in Baghdad alone to give a large variety of choices for them to choose from.  I think this shows one part of how our society thinks. It isn't news if it doesn't contain sex , drugs, or violence. Very rarely will a goodwill story get frontpage anymore. Another fact that saddens me is that the deaths of our soldiers over here are starting to get removed back to page 3 or 4 if they are even reported at all. While I know everyone doesn't agree or even support us being over here I think that every American should at least support the troops. Giving their lives to try and improve a country half the world away is the supreme sacrifice. I wish I could explain how it feels to talk to a person one day and the next day hear that they have been killed in an explosion with an IED. Even the soldiers that don't agree with being over here still do their duty.  It's not too much to ask for their country to do theirs too .  Just the other day MG Chiarelli had to come to our unit to authorize a 3   MILLION   reconstruction plan for one of the local colleges. This will improve the quality of life in that college in such a way its almost hard to comprehend. This obviously shows an investment in the future of Iraq itself and that we are trying to plan beyond the short term. While not nearly even close to the budgets that a college in the US would spend this is a pretty good amount once you consider the exchange rate.  On a slightly different note I found out today that my internet service here is shortly going to be cut off. We currently pay about $1150 a month for a 1mbit downlink on a satellite connection. Having to pay 3 months in advance and knowing we won't be here that long isn't going to work anymore. But I will continue to try and post as often as possible using the e-mail to blog feature.  As always I welcome your comments, suggestions or questions. Thanks for reading. 
    


15,August,2004


	 
      Since the failure of the peace talks in the city of Najaf by the Iraqi government and the presumed resumption of violence I figured this will be a hot topic. As in line with my earlier posts and what I am trying to do mine will have nothing to do with this. I don't feel I can report too well on Najaf considering I am no where near the area and don't have very much information on it. Consequently I would just be regurgitating information from CNN and other non-reliable news sources.  Our unit is closely integrated with University of Baghdad College of Veterinary Science and Preventive Medicine (long name jeesh). We have done such projects there as arrange for curriculum to be shipped from the US (they had no books), restocked the laboratories (everything was looted after the war) and instate a training program and train a guard force (it was a haven for AIF forces).  Lastly our company commander recently took 3 of the staff (including the Dean) to Texas A&amp;M in College Station, Texas to meet with the staff there and discuss ways to improve the both the learning progress and the overall situation and opportunities for the Veterinary College. While I don't agree with the amount of money that was spent ( I won't mention an amount but it was close to my yearly salary) for 4 people for 16 days I think overall it was a good idea. Hopefully it was expand the learning progress and allow the overall situation in Iraq improve.  As I have stated before keeping the younger generation on our side and away from such religious fanatics as Al-Sadr I believe are our only hope for democracy to flourish here.  On a less serious note I turned 24 today. I've managed for the past 5 years to be deployed or in the field every birthday. At least this should be the last one. As always I appreciate any comments or criticism. Thank you 
    


14,August,2004


	 
      Just posting a couple pictures of one of the palaces on South Victory. While it may not look like much the interior is almost all marble. And all for one person.     This entire lake is surronded by a few support buildings and a smaller lake off to the side that used to be used for fishing. It is really quite quaint until you realize that while this was being built his people starved.     Thanks 
    


13,August,2004


	 
      This one is a little different. Around two nights or so Iraq won it's first soccer game in the Olympics. I think this is great. After everything that Uday did to the Olympic competitors in this country its finally a great chance for them to have a bit of the spotlight. However there is one thing here that I don't understand.  It's somewhere between 12 am and 2 am in the morning. All of sudden it sounds like World War 3 just erupted outside of our fob. Looking up into the sky you see tracers flying everywhere. I'm not talking about just 30 seconds or so of gunfire. I'm talking about a good concentrated 15 minutes straight of gunfire. It encompassed about a 180 degree field of view. Of course its the Iraqi's way of celebrating. You know I would think that in a city of Baghdad's size they would find another way of celebrating. Shortly after this started we start getting reports in our CP of bullets starting to fall from the sky. Luckily no one was hurt that I know of. But it is quite un-nerving to be sitting or sleeping and hear a sharp pang. And find a bullet on your floor. While most of the energy is expended a lot of this can cause some serious damage.  To me this doesn't seem to intelligent. A lot of people here don't live in a house, they live outside. I know I wouldn't want to get rained on by stray AK-47 bullets in the middle of night. Not to mention that you have a hyper-sensitive army occupying your country. We here gunfire and things get tense. Unless bullets are impacting near you its hard to tell where they are shooting.  But on a good note, Congratulations Iraq. I only wish you the best of luck in these games.  On another note I'm going to have a few other people in my unit start posting here too. I figure the more news that gets out and the different points of view the better things will be. As always we welcome your comments. 
    


13,August,2004


	 
      I think a lot of people have a lot of misconceptions about the people here. When I look at CNN it seems as if everyone over here is trying to either kill us or make money off of us. From my perspective however that isn't the case. I don't have experience with any high ranking officials of either Shiite or Sunni class, everyone I see is just I would say your normal person.  I think the first group I want to talk about is the children over here. I have never seen such a diverse group of children before in my life. Having to grow up in the conditions they do is and they way they can smile amazes me every time I see them. However there are two distinct groups that I see.  The first group are the ones when I go out on mission that will surround the vehicle in a blink of an eye and start screaming "Mister, Mister give me food" or give me watch or give me water or give gun. I swear sometimes it just wants to make you run them over. I will try to get some pictures so you can have some idea of the sheer mass of these bodies pressing in on your vehicle. It doesn't help knowing that one of them can have a grenade clutched in their hand. Or one of them can be trying to distract you while their brother or sister attempts to rob you blind. Granted I know they are being kids but it gets to the point that it is dangerous sometimes.  Then there is the second group. I will use a specific example here. We employ some local nationals as workers in our motor pool to do some tasks. They get paid about 5$ a day or so which while it doesn't sound like much it is extremely good wages for this example when you are coming from a 5$ a month salary. There is one family in particular in which everyone is employed on post. I think it is a group of about 5 kids and their father. One of the youngest we have nicknamed Billy and he is the boss. He can't be more than 13 or so but he is in charge of probably 8 other people ranged from age 12 - 20 or so. Mostly since he speaks great english. But these group of 5 children mostly do the work that I would be suprised to see 7 adult men do back in the US. We asked them one day "What do you do with the money you make here?" The answer definetly shocked me. "We give the money to our father so we can get a car for our family". All of these people are gladly working to try and improve their family situation. I only can imagine what these young men could do if given the right chances.  Next up is the older adults. One example that never fails to bring a smile to my face is two specific workers. They are both brothers. One of the can't talk anymore. Why? His tongue was cut out during Saddam's regime. For speaking wrongly about something. He was lucky he wasn't killed. I wish I could bring their work ethic back to the US with me. I have never seen 2 people do the work with what they have. They usually come down and help me change the tires on my bucket loader. These tires probably weigh in at about close to 1000 lb or so. It usually takes us about 4 - 5 people to lift one upright. The first time I tried to help them they wouldn't let me. They told me to just sit down and wouldn't let me work.  We also have the local leader of the "village" outside of our gate. He used to be a republican guard soldier and fought against the US in the first war. Not by choice but by requirement from Saddam. Now he works glady at helping to rebuild his village. He didn't take his posistion and he didn't want it. But the people in his area elected him anyways. I really think that the way that we are winning over the Iraqi population is making a huge difference in our quality of life over here.  When I first got here we got attacked on a regular basis. Now after we have gone out and started to rebuild the attacks have tapered down to almost nothing. Maybe once a month or so. I really think this shows a lot that we are doing good here. Its not all that you hear on CNN on such. For example many times this local leader has contacted us and let us know that someone tried to get into the village last nite to fire mortars but the people ran him off. Or that they have seen suspicious people in the area and where to find them. Or where weapon caches were.   Winning over the young generation and at least getting the current generation on a neutral side will win this war in the long run. I don't believe that this war is more of a fight against terrorism as it is a fight to allow a people to be free. Hopefully we can construct the foundation and it can be built on. Too many people have lost their life for this. 
    


13,August,2004


	 
      Just a quick thank you to one of the best forums on the internet in my opinion. Keeps me busy a lot over here with stuff to read and is always good for a laugh or a serious discussion.   urlLink http://www.tfproject.org    
    


13,August,2004


	 
      Ok, this second I just want to say is based purely on my life here and is not in what so way anything near what the engineers, infantry, tankers or cav scouts go through. So take it for what its worth. And I do just back in a time a bit too.  I remember finally getting through Baghdad at about 10am and rolling up to the front gate of Baghdad International Airport and seeing a couple of Bradleys from 1st AD performing overwatch on a TCP (traffic control point) and the huge line of people trying to get in to find a new job working with the US gov't. We finally rolled through and came up to our new home.  Victory is built on what used to be Saddam's hunting grounds in the middle of Baghdad. (For size relation Camp Victory is the largest posting of soldiers outside of normal bases the US army has ever set up). It also houses a couple of palaces and lakes. The entire complex was walled and had guard towers on it in various places. It is surronded on 1 side by BIAP (the airport), on one side close by the Abu Gharaid district, one side by the Ameriya district and the last side by the Ghazaliya district of western Baghdad. Abutting one of the walls is the Baghdad Veterinary College and on another point is Baghdad College of Agriculture. There is also a small old Republican Guard base that is in between the two colleges that has been taken over by squatters and is now a small village of almost 4,000 people.   After going on a patrol one time and talking to people I was shocked to find out that the people were shot for even attempting to look into Saddam's hunting grounds. Definetly not a good neighbor policy.When I rolled into the complex the first thing I could see was endless lines of 40' x 10' long trailers. These were to be our homes for the time we were here. They are pretty nice and depending on your rank is how big the room is. My trailer has 4 people in and is split into 2 rooms. My roommate and I both get along great and it's air conditioned (Couldn't imagine it without). Definetly not what I was expecting. The power grid was pretty shaky for the first 6 months or so but its better now. We were actually living pretty well.  Well except for the mortar attacks that were still happening. You would hear a mortar whistling in, grab your gear and either duck on the floor or run outside into a bunker depending on where you were. There where a lot of sleepless nights the first couple of months.  One day my 1SG came up to me and asked me if I knew how to operate a front-end loader. I asked him if it was anything like a bobcat and he said sure. So I ended up the next day driving this huge Volvo loader outside the gate with a loaded M16 and full gear on outside the gate to start our reconstruction projects that we were assigned. Remember we are mechanics and such, this isn't something that we were trained for. At the time now my unit actually has a larger area of responsibility to patrol than one of the tank units there.  We started out with just clearing out from around the walls. It ended up being a project that still continues to this day. Every day except for friday we send at least one loader and most of the time 2 out there to clean roads, fill in pits, move trash, dig pits, knock down old buildings and try to help people. I have never seen such gratitude from people as when you do something as simple as spending a day building a landfill for them. (At the time due to the war there is no sanitation system and garbage just piles up in corners of alleys and such). Simple quality of life issues like this or taking an old field and leveling it out so some children can have part of their life back and play a game of soccer. I wish I still had pictures of everything that was out there but I lost them due to a hard drive crash.  We went over to the old Republican Guard airbase one day and started clearing the rubble out of the area. I kept seeing these large pits that were probably close to 100' across and about 70' deep or so I and kept wondering where they came from. Then it hit me. They were all bomb craters. Seeing first hand the devasation and precision that US employs both makes me proud and shocks me at the same time. The ability to drop a bomb in a crowded neighborhood and remove an aircraft hangar I think makes it a little easier to stomach. But then on the other hand sitting there on the ground and trying to help these people rebuild I was trying to think if it was even worth it. My question was answered soon.  I think I pissed off my platoon sergeant one day and me and my roommate got assigned to KBR (Kellog, Brown and Root) detail one night. No local nationals were allowed on post with a military escort and we got stuck being their escorts for a water truck that was filling up the shower water holds every night. I can still remember now 5 months later sitting in this truck with an older man about 45 or so and his assistant who was in his early 20's. They asked us to get some food for them since it was dinner for us. As it is all free for us it was no problem. So me and my roommate load up on 4 plates and bring it back out to the water truck to eat (no pork of course). When we got back they looked shocked at the pure amount of food that is normal for us to eat here. The older man started talking about how he used to serve in Saddam's army. They didn't get fed meals by person. Instead he was saying that they would get a certain amount of rice and tomatoes depending on the amount of people. A 5lb bag of rice and a bag of tomatoes for 40 people; I couldn't imagine those conditions. Working for around 1 dollar a day. I asked him if he was glad that the US had come in and the expression on his face was worth it. He told me that he was finally able to provide for his family, he was able to buy a car, he was able to buy new clothes for his daughter, he was able to buy dvds and get a satellite dish. He said none of this stuff would have been able to be done under Saddam.  I asked him about the attacks that kept happening to us and his reply was "Not iraqis, iraqis are happy." A little translation later and he was telling us that the majority of all the attacks were from other countries sending people there to attack us. I felt like I had walked up to a wall and seen a sign that said "Hunting Season Open - No Limit - American's Only"Well, work starts again.  Will do part 3 later today. It's quite relaxing to actually write a bunch of this stuff out. I really appreciate all the support everyone has been writing. I sorta worry about if this stuff will get me in trouble and I know freedom of speech won't save me. Sadly its a right I gave up when I raised my hand to enlist. Oh well, life goes and I'll do what I feel is right. 
    


13,August,2004


	 
      A little about this post. I tend to ramble on a bit when I start typing so I apologize in advance for any such actions. Secondly I'm not trying to express and political views on whether the war is right or wrong. I'm simply stating on how I see it being from actually being here and interacting with people on a daily basis. Lastly if anyone has any questions or comments or anything please let me know. The internet is my only real link to people outside my unit and I'm savoring it while I have it. I am trying to find a place to host some pictures and as soon as I do I will upload some of stuff that I think is nice over here. It is not all that you hear about in the news.  * All this information has been released and anything that I think may be detrimental I won't display specifics on. If I've found it on the net I will include it here *  A little background:I'm a SGT currently assigned to 15 FSB, 2 Brigade Combat Team, 1st Cavarly Division based out of Ft. Hood, TX. My assigned MOS (Military Occupational Specialty) is 63T which is a Bradley mechanic but I currently fill the role of company communications rep and basic computer guy. Our unit provides all of the direct support (high level maintenance stuff) to all vehicles, weapon systems, communication assets and such assigned to 2BCT and a couple other attached units. We got the word that we would probably deploy in August of 2003. It wasn't the best time of my life.  I've been in the Army for 4 years at the time and had 2 years left on my enlistment. My wife and I had just had our first child and I wasn't looking forward to spending at least a year away from him and she definetly wasnt' looking forward to raising him for that time period too. We deployed to Kuwait during the first week of January and spent 3 weeks in Kuwait receiving our equipment and learning new convoy procedures. At the time it almost just seemed like another rotation at NTC (National Training Center). It really hadn't sunk in yet.  We were issued 30 rounds of ammunition in case we got attacked in Kuwait. After all of our vehicles were ready and picked up from the port in Kuwait City we prepared to ocnvoy north to Baghdad to our new home. Being the only qualified gunner on a .50 cal MG I drew the lucky spot of being a gunner. I wasn't too happy since it meant that I had to stand up for the next 3 days with my head out of the gunner's hatch in a LMTV freezing my ass off (it gets cold in the desert!). The first day wasn't really too bad. We made it to the border between Iraq and Kuwait and thats where it really sunk in what we were going through.  The convoy ahead of us had gotten hit numerous times with SAF (Small Arms Fire) but thankfully no one was hurt. Since there was an entire brigade moving north at the same time the convoys were spaced apart at a certain interval. Anyone with half a brain knew exactly when we coming and which route we were going to take. I rolled across the border from Kuwait to Iraq at around 2am. I have never had such a profound sense of fear as such I did then. I remember frantically trying to see in all directions at once looking for something out of the ordinary. Thankfully nothing was there. It was a cold end to the second day.  The next day after we stopped at a waypoint camp that was set up where we had slept on the side of the road we really got a good luck at the countryside and the people. I was so amazed at the sheer poverty and destruction and almost run-down that Iraq was in. Everyone I saw was cheering that we were there. There was a stretch on the drive north when we were going past Nasiriyah (502nd Maint. Company fame) where the road would just be lined with kids all waving. Most of them were trying to get food but we weren't allowed to give them any. We were told that if anyone got in the way of the vehicles that we were to just run them over. They could be trying to stop the vehicles to launch an ambush. We didn't want kids coming onto the roads to try and pick up food. That had to be one of the hardest things was seeing starving children wave at me and ask food. Being a new father I could only imagine what it must be like not being able to provide the basic neccesities for my child.  When we started to roll into Baghdad it was near dawn and the city was coming alive. This was actually the most dangerous area to be in for the threat of an IED (improvised explosive device). They hid them in anything and everything. Having to be behind a locked and loaded .50 cal machine gun while trying to weave through traffic at 40 - 60 mph was definetly an unique experience. The .50 cal has no safety and I kept thinking 'Fuck what do i do if I accidentally shoot someone'. It was all that was going through my mind. Having to track peolpe with the barrel of a loaded weapon was not fun.  We ended up making it to our new home at Camp Victory in Baghdad. It is located near the old Saddam International Airport. Well now it is Baghdad International Airport. You can still see the signs where Saddam was spraypainted over. Eerie to see the whole airport deserted and to see large planes stripped of their engines and just sitting on the tarmac. Our battalion ended up being tasked to provide force protection for our camp. This is definetly not a job that we were ever trained to do. Think of a bunch of cooks, mechanics, and fuelers providing the protection for at the time close to 3,000 people. (Now we still do it and its over 15,000 people).  The first few nights we kept getting mortared and the sound of gunfire made me duck everywhere we went. Was not a sound I liked hearing at all. After about a week of being there we heard some reports on the net that there was a possibility of AIF (Anti Iraqi Forces) having obtained some cyanide and using it in attacks against us. That night we got hit by rockets. I wish I could explain the sound that a 127mm rocket makes when it is going overhead and when it explodes. I am so glad when I know that most people won't have to explain it. In the next minute after the strike came probably the worst moment of my life.  Battalion called down over the net "Gas, Gas, Gas". My stomach literally dropped so fast and everyone who was in the command post started frantically scrambling for his protective gear. We are trained to be able to put it on in 12 seconds. I think it was on in less than 5 that time. You could almost see the fear emanating off of people at that time.  About 10 minutes later it was discovered a false alarm. This soon turned to be one of the highlights of my life.  The second week we were there one of our guard towers got attacked by RPG (rocket propelled grenade) and SAF. One of our SGTs was pulling guard in the tower along with 2 members of an infantry unit from 82nd Airborne. All 3 were severely wounded and ended up going home for their injuries. This guy is walking with a cane now from his injuries. Not something you would expect from a radio repairman.  A couple weeks later we learned that what they thought was RPG fire and SAF was actually a Bradley who mistakenly targeted the tower at night with their 25mm cannon and 7.62 coax machine gun. Luckily their mistake didn't kill anyone.   I'm going to end it here for tonite since I'm exhausted so far after being on duty for the last 15 hours. I'll continue later today when I wake up. Again I welcome comments and questions or whatever you want to say. 
    



