
08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    He hates this one too.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Bradley hates this picture!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Brad working his '71 Mercury Comet&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is Jenn's birthday cake...I thought that "Shrek" was appropriate...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This was for Jenn's party...not the kids....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe pokes his eyes out.  &nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Silly Haeley bug&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Silly Jasmine&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    If I suck on the high chair after every bite I can swallow my cereal&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley, Jenn, and Jasmine&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Justin is asleep in his swing&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jasmine, Gabe, Haeley, and Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley and her sparkler&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jenn and Haeley do the Hula&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jenn got "Tommy Boy" for her birthday...the best movie EVER!  :-)&nbsp; urlLink   
    


08,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    June 1, 2004 &nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jasmine, Justin, Ezekiel, Haeley, Melanie and Summer...not the best picture of me....but OH WELL!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe and his tongue!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daddy and Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daniel and Ezekiel---Bradley and Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Uncle Daniel smashed the cupcake on me.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    "Uncle Daniel told me to eat it like this"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe was having "happy birthday" blown to him on a kazoo.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm eating a lemon&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Bradley and Jasmine are in orange, Melanie and Gabe are in blue&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Justin and Ezekiel sleep with all the noise around them.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hi there&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daniel and Haeley in the Go Karts&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    There are five months between us&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Zeke has pinned me down&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    "Nothing to worry about, I'm just chewing on Zeke's head."&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Lucca and Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    OH NO!!!! Not a diaper change!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Zeke is asleep on his daddy&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is the first time that I had green beans.  I loved them!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is my Mama Sue and me...we are at Uncle Daniel and Aunt Summer's house&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Introducing my little baby cousin Ezekiel.  He was born on May 1, 2004&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Mama took me picture upside down.  We are on our way to Uncle Daniel and Aunt Summer's house&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    This is my cousin's bouncy....but I'm having fun in it!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    MMMMMM.....toes are so yummy!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I have fallen asleep....yet again...maybe it is now time for the swing to be packed away&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yes, we are getting a bed frame!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe's Room&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe's Reaction....he said, "Mama, I wanted my woom to be blaack...an...and why doesn't i have squares on my walls?" &nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley and Jasmine's Room.  The girl's loved it!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley's reaction&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jasmine's Reaction to her room&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Katelyn is all dressed up.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


13,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm always so happy!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Justin loves sleeping with Junior.  He pulls him over....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I have a mixing bowl over my face&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    "Somehow I'm supposed to make this hit that and then it will make a noise...."&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I was helping mama feed me my squash.  YUMMY!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    My sisters were trying to make me go to sleep, but I didn't want to sleep.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    "I was crawling under the futon couch"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    I think the book was just a little bit bigger than Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here he is playing with the farm...it entertained him for a good 15 minutes...He LOVED all the different sounds.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,June,2004


	 
       urlLink    Climbing on the coffee table...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe lays on Jasmine, Justin sits on Gabe...what more can be said?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe explains how the train works to Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm holding my bottle&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Justin and Jasmine...they are precious&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe and Justin&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe is silly&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Look at mine go!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Wow!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe and Justin play with the trains&nbsp; urlLink   
    


02,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Why won't this box close?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
      Let's see...We are in trouble now.  Justin is pulling up on everything and he started crawling up the stairs.  He said his first word on Saturday--"Daa Daa Daa Daa Daa Daa"  The girls are doing good although they still haven't lost their teeth.  And that's not for lack of trying.  They sit at the table and eat carrots and then check the wiggle status of their teeth.  Gabe is doing good---rotten, but good.  I am having my wisdom teeth out on Thursday the 8th.  Whoo Hoo.  Brad is doing well, but work is getting very intense and stressful.  Pleas pray for him.  All in all things are good.  We love and miss you all.  Take Care!
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    John is sleeping in the coffee table.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm just going for a ride in the block wagon&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    UNCLE JOHN&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I love my trains!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Me and my trains&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hey Uncle John, pullme around the room some more&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    "LOOK AT WHAT I HAVE CREATED!!!!!"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jasmine Rae&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley bug--this outfit is too small on her&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Again&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Justin and Daddy sleeping on the couch&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm climbing into my chair&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The girls&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    GET ME OUT OF HERE!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley, Gabe, and Jerig &nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    look at him&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I fell asleep in time-out&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I am so stinking cute!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The original outfit choice&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Just hanging out in the bucket&nbsp; urlLink   
    


07,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The after product&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm knocking over the basket of folded laundry...oh, that's because I can't be trusted.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I have Thomas the train pj's&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    ...And in today's top headlines, we have "Godzilla Baby destroys middle class family's home"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    The Pool.  Isn't well water just grand?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    IT'S COLD!!!!!!!!!  &nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    We're just chillin.  &nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley "swims"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Having fun&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley helps Mommy and feeds Justin some plums and apples.  YUMMY!  &nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley earned a dollar for being the first one to go under&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daddy prepares to carry all of us to bed&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    And we're up&nbsp; urlLink   
    


10,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daddy drops all of us at the top of the stairs&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    look at how cute i am&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Just hangin on&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I climbed up on the box and I'm just standing her because I'm Justin and I can do these things now...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    "Mama take my picture with Jhereg."&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Daddy!!!!!  It's time to get up!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jhereg does not want to get out of the bed&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I will be a concert pianist when I grow up.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Look at me!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm a piano player&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I fall in love with this baby over and over and over again!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    I cannot get over how adorable he is!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


25,July,2004


	 
      I know that it has been quite some time since I last posted and I'm sorry...But here are a bunch of cutie pictures...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Isn't he precious?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Jasmine can kick!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Check her out!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Gabe is Forward Punching.  The instructor was trying to grab their hands when they punched and he barely touched her and then took off running...  :)&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    Haeley is "forward punching"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    KARATE!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    More Corn.....yummy.....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


28,July,2004


	 
       urlLink    MMMMMMM  Corn on the COB!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Getting on the bus....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Backing up....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    There she goes....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    One happy family&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    My first day of first grade&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm holding my baby brother&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Sisters&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    My carrot cake&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm bedtime bear&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    ....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    It took both the girls to hold him to do this.....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    PEAS!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Yes????&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Rubber Duckey you're the one....you make bath time lots of fun....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    See what I've done...&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    My first breadstick&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Look at us&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here we are again&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    We are in the pack-n-play&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    "you said what?"&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm going up....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hello&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm gonna get you....&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    It's a monster!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here I am again&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm on my bike....I'm a cool little man&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm coming....I'm coming&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm coming....i'm coming&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Here I am&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Before spaghetti&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    After spaghetti&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm oriental.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Aren't I cute?&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Look at me!&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    I'm eating Sloppy Joes&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    Hi.  My name is Justin and I'm chillin on the church floor.&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    VBS&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    VBS&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    VBS&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
       urlLink    VBS&nbsp; urlLink   
    


18,August,2004


	 
      ABS&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    



23,August,2004


    
       Well, I'm doing alright today. I'm moving all of the boxes from moving outside, since they're supposed to be picked up by the moving company soon. I'll be glad of the extra space that it opens up. I worked an extra long shift yesterday, 10am-9:30 pm, with an hour lunch around 5:30. I haven't done a shift like that in a long time..... (Note to self: don't volunteer for such a shift unless absolutely necessary.) Anyway, I didn't get to see John at all yesterday because of that. You know, he had the whole weekend off, plus he got off work Friday morning around 10am, so he had most of that day, too. Of course, he was asleep until I got home around 7pm, but that's beside the point. I don't think he did anything around the house at all. The least he could do is, I don't know, something. Dishes or something. I shouldn't have to be the one that does everything. I keep thinking about Mark. I can't stop thinking about our conversation from the other day. Am I really only merely content, or am I happy? I'm really not sure. I want kids, and I think I want them with John, but sometimes I wonder...... Is he REALLY who I want to be with? I know it's crazy. He is just so childish sometimes, and doesn't seem to have any self-control for most things. I'll admit he's getting better, but it's not enough..... You know, I'm not sure if I really respect him anymore. Part of it is my fault, but it's on him too. How many times has he told me that he's quitting smoking? Too many. And he has yet to quit. Oh, he says he's trying, but that it's hard. Problem is is that as soon as anything bothers him he doesn't try to deal with his emotions, he depends on the nicotene to deal with it. I want him to quit, I really do, but I guess I don't believe him anymore when he says he's trying. I know he's afraid that he can't, which is why he won't admit that he won't really try. I know that he can, I just don't know if he will. Why can't I get Mark out of my thoughts? He's a really deep thinker, and he wants me to be, also. Sometimes it makes me uncomfortable, because then I have to confront things that I'd just rather let be. You know, the old "if you ignore it, it might go away" thinking. Sometimes I wonder if I'm wasting my life with the wrong guy. Mark said that he thinks that I married John to get out of Alaska. What if it's true, but I just don't want to admit it? Why did I marry him? Do I really love him, or am I just imitating it in hopes that I'll convince myself one day that it's true and real? Such awful thoughts. He might be going to Kuwait in January. I don't know how I should feel. Upset? Relieved? Torn? Is it bad for me to not care if he goes? OK, OK, it's not that I don't care, because I really don't like having him gone, but I don't mind the being alone part as much as I used to.  
    
    


19,August,2004


    
       Living it up in Sunny Hawaii, life should be sweet, right?  Unfortunately, I don't know if I like it here, or maybe it's just that I miss some people back in Virginia.  I had people that I considered pretty close friends, and I left them all behind.  One person has told me that I didn't really have a choice, since I'm married, and nobody expected me to leave him just because he got orders, and I had to choose between friends, and him.  Well, obviously I chose him, but......  Another person told me that he can tell I'm not happy, I'm just content.  Too bad that he's right.  It would have been too scary to NOT come to Hawaii.  I'm married, we have an OK to good relationship, I think.  We don't fight.  Besides kids, my own home, and my family close by, what more could I want?  
    
    



