
13,June,2004


	 
      So.  My parents have decided that I'm going to buy a house.    When I say 'parents' I use the term very loosely.  My mother and father divorced when I was three.  Pops has been divorced twice since then and good ole mom remarried a recovering child beater.  Granted I wasn't the best behaved little fella but nothing... And I mean NOTHING warrants beating a kids ass with a board until the board breaks.  This will get it's own post eventually... in great detail.  I've payed back the physical part of this story... now it's time for public humiliation.  Paybacks are a bitch.  Pardon me for I digress.    As I was saying, my parents (being my real father) have decided that I am buying a hou

06,June,2004


	 
      I work for a national advertising agency which in turn is owned by one of the worlds largest and most successful private equity firms.  The fact that I remain on the payroll is quite simply astonishing.   Allow me to explain.  All my life I have been a rebel.  Even at 35 years of age I still question EVERYTHING.  Its an odd feeling to realize that being a rebel is in most cases completely incompatible with a corporate environment.  I would like to say that my rebellious nature is because I'm a man of principle.  I suspect however that it has less to do with standards and ethics and more to do with masochism.    Back to my paycheck.    I suppose I have Enron, Worldcom and "perp walks" to thank for still having a job.  I am very low on the food chain in the corporate world and it has always been my understanding that questioning your boss is not compatible with continued employment.  Hell, they shitcan people left and right at this place for far less than just asking questions.  Pardon me... did I say "questioning your boss"?  Let me rephrase that.  I flat out argue with her openly and in a somewhat less than subdued manner.  Sometimes I make her so mad that her skin gets all blotchy and her eyes bug out, but that's another story.    She isn't a bad person really, she's just a shitty boss.  I guess that's why they hired her.  Where I am a rebel she is the proverbial "yes man".  I can't help but think that her real job is kissing ass and she just manages the office when she can find the time.  Feh!  That's all for now.   
     
    


04,June,2004


	 
      Some people lack spontaneity.  I am not one of them.   In fact one could say that the only quality that overshadows my fondness for cynicism is my irrationally impulsive nature.  Welcome to my life.  
     
    



